Chapter 478: Disgusting

If one wants to defeat a Great Clan like the Calci Family, he would need to eliminate all of their leaders and elites. If those important personnel were to vanish, the family wouldn’t dare show themselves in the continent anymore. This was because Great Clans held great benefits, and the interests that they control are too great. Ordinarily, they would use this interest to gather good talents and then use it to grow their power.

When their leaders and elites vanish, all of these benefits and interests would instead become a curse to the Clan.

Because of this, this fort of the Calci Family cannot be defeated. At the same time, the Robert Family cannot lose as well. When they dealt with Zhao Hai before, they never thought that they would fail. Then sent out a great number of 8th ranks and they even used Antimagic Powder to defeat him to ensure its success. But unfortunately, they failed.

Not only did it fail, the Antimagic Powder was also made known to Zhao Hai. Now, it was not only Zhao Hai who knew, the Calci Family were now aware as well, and it wouldn’t take a long time for the entire continent to hear about it. Once Mages knew that the Robert Family held Antimagic Powder, they won’t be simply eliminated, no member of the family will be safe, and the execution would surely be ruthless.

This made the Robert Family decide to use all of their strength in dealing with the Calci Family. They must destroy the Calci Family in one clean swoop.

At this moment, the current situation within Dark Soldier Fort wasn’t good. The Calci Family was a Mage Clan, they held great importance to their Mages and not so much to their Warriors. Because of this, Mages populated the family. With Zhao Hai’s proposal, all the Mages were made to retreat from the walls. Now, there were only a few people left.

Zhao Hai was also aware of this situation. At this time, Smith came with a few people, all of them Mages. They were all members of the Calci Family, they couldn’t withdraw.

Third Grandfather and Juwan also walked together with them. Their complexions were difficult to describe. Although they have differences with Randolph, they weren’t fools. They knew that once the Calci Family is over, they won’t be able to survive. Only when the Calci Family survives will they have a good life.

The two also walked towards Randolph’s side, they weren’t in the mood to talk with Zhao Hai. Third Grandfather turned to Randolph and said, “Patriarch, why did you remove those Mages from the walls? If they are taken off, who will defend the fort?”

Randolph looked at him and shorted, “Think about it, why would I remove those Mages? Can’t you feel it? The other party has already spread a massive amount of Antimagic Powder. If I don’t remove the Mages, they would only be standing there waiting for death.”

Third Grandfather stared, then immediately went to feel the surroundings before his complexion became ugly. He felt that the Magic elements in the entire Dark Mountain were going extremely sluggish. With the situation of the elements like this, there was no way for a Mage to cast formidable magic spells. One could say that Mages became useless in such an environment.

Smith and the others also felt it, all of their expressions were quite ugly. Smith quickly said, “Father, how about we make the Mages escape through the secret passage, make them attack from outside the mountain?”

Randolph shook his head and said, “That’s useless. Even if they go out of the mountain, the opposite party still had Antimagic Powder in their hands, they can use it anytime.”

Right now, Peter and the others had no other ideas. The family paid too little attention towards Warriors. If they placed importance to the Warriors the same way as they did to their Mages, their family wouldn’t have reached this predicament.

Zhao Hai looked at the group and faintly smiled, “Grandfather, everybody, you don’t need to worry. The opponent only sent a bit more than 10 thousand people. Rest assured, we’re fine, I’ll take care of it.”

The eyes of the people couldn’t help but focus on Zhao Hai. They thought about what Zhao Hai said back at the lobby, he wasn’t affected by Antimagic Powder.

Randolph looked at Zhao Hai and said, “That’s right. Little Hai, since you aren’t affected, solve this quickly, blow those Antimagic Powder away.”

Zhao Hai knit his brows, “There’s too many. Even if I can, it wouldn’t take a short time. Also, the enemy wouldn’t give us that much time.” Just as Zhao Hai finished talking, a group of Warriors stepped out from the woods in into the front of Dark Soldier fort. They all wore armor and had weapons in their hands.

These were Heavy Armor Infantry, one of the most formidable types of unit in the continent. Their bodies were completely encased within a thick full body armor. They had a kite shield in one hand while a pear was held in the other. Now they have set up their shields and spear in a formation as they advanced slowly towards the fort’s walls.

Then they jammed their shields on the ground, with its front facing the fort. The shields were linked together, forming a firm wall. While they were connected, there was some holes present here and there, enough for their spears to be securely placed.

Behind the Heavy Infantry were large quantities of bowmen. Magic Cannons and Ballistas were powerful, however, they weren’t convenient to move. Moreover, they had already spread Antimagic Powder, Magic Cannons couldn’t be used well, it’s attacking power would be reduced significantly.

Bowmen aren’t people to be scoffed at either. They were  using longbows constructed in a way that it can at least be shot from 200 steps away. With Warriors wielding them, it was possible to shoot at 400 steps. Moreover, they could fire 40 times, their attacking strength was not small.

Behind the Bowmen and the Heavy Infantry were soldiers in leather armor. They were armed with swords and shields, some of them carried ladders and ropes.

Seeing this display, Randolph immediately issued his orders to have the people on the wall prepare. Zhao Hai looked at the attackers and couldn’t help but smile. This arrangement was very good, however, their numbers are too few, they wouldn’t be able to survive the assault of his undead.

Randolph stood at the walls and stared at the slowly approaching formation. He coldly snorted and said, “Robert Patriarch, you really went all out. I’ve always treated you as a friend. But you actually came to destroy my family, come out and see me.”

Zhao Hai stared for a moment and then smiled. If he was the Robert Family Patriarch, he wouldn’t come out and meet Randolph. Such an encounter might leave loose ends.

Unfortunately, Zhao Hai guessed incorrectly. When Randolph’s voice fell, a voice was heard shortly afterwards, “Randolph, you’re really naive. Do you think that with our current position, we would treat you as a genuine friend? Your Calci Family is a family of Mages, you’re finished. Hahaha. What do you think? Does the Antimagic Powder taste good?”

Randolph coldly snorted and said, “Robert Patriarch, what good would killing the Calci Family do to you? As long as people knows about your possession of Antimagic Powder, your Robert Family is finished.”

Robert Patriarch laughed and said, “Know? Who will inform them? Since all of you will die today, it would be impossible to pass this information. I’ll tell you, I’ve asked all of my family’s 9th ranks to deal with your family. Even if you use your secret passage, they would be able to find out about it.”

Randolph was startled, then his face changed. He gritted his teeth and said, “Good, Robert Patriarch, good. Worthy of the Savage Wolf emblem, you’re ruthless enough. But you can be sure that we, the Calci Family, aren’t going to go down easily. If you want to eliminate us, you will have to pay a great price.”

Robert Patriarch smiled and said, “Of course we’ll pay a great price, but that doesn’t matter. As long as we extinguish your Calci Family, we would be able to gain the resources to become the most powerful Clan in the Continent, hahaha. Compared to the price I paid, the benefits that I will obtain would certainly be more.”

Randolph’s expression was now pale. Zhao Hai looked at Randolph and smiled faintly, “Grandpa Randolph, consider this matter finished. No need to be angry with that crazy dog. Did he really think that they would win? Hehe, too laughable.”

Naturally, Robert Patriarch heard Zhao Hai, but he didn’t respond. At this time, a carriage slowly approached Dark Soldier Fort. This carriage didn’t have a roof, and it only had a chair and a table. Sitting in it was an old man clothed in Warrior clothes. On the table in front of him, there was a bottle of liquor and a wine glass. The person looked very tall, but he was also very thin. With the way he wore his clothes, he seemed to be very relaxed. His slender eyes seemed to flash with green light in this dark night.

The old person’s green eyes looked straight at Zhao Hai and coldly snorter, “Ignorant junior. Do you think that you’re already formidable just by by defeating some second rate warriors of the continent? I must let you know that compared to my Grandson Terry, you fall too short.”

Just as the old man’s voice fell, hoofbeats can be heard as a big white horse appeared and went to the side of the old man’s carriage. The horse was very big and tall, very much like a Demon Horse, four meters in height. Sitting on it was a fully armored Knight, the Knight wore silver body armor. He had a long spear in one hand and his helmet in the other. His sword was inserted in it sheath at the side of the saddle. The man looked very handsome.

Zhao Hai looked at the person and saw that it was Terry. He was dressed up as a genuine Knight, looking very eye-catching.

Seeing his appearance, Zhao Hai smiled and then whispered to Megan, “This guy really likes to pretend to be an honorable knight. But he actually has a vile heart.”

Megan snorted and said, “When we were children, I didn’t think too much about his appearance. But now, when I look at him, I really feel disgusted.”

Chapter 479: All Of My Enemies, Kill Them!

Terry didn’t think the same, he was feeling really good right now. His family had already surrounded the Dark Soldier Fort of the Calci Family. He had never felt this elated before.

Seeing Zhao Hai and Megan on the wall, Terry sneered and said, “Megan, have you ever thought that this day would come? I’ve shown my interest to you all these years, but what did you do? You chose Zhao Hai instead of me, today, I will make you regret that decision.”

Megan looked at Terry’s appearance and coldly snorted, “Of course I’d choose Big Brother Hai and not you. You don’t even compare to Big Brother Hai’s little finger.”

Zhao Hai said, “Megan, no need to exaggerate, how can you say that to Mister Terry? Why did you say that he can’t compare to my finger? He is well worthy to be on the same level as my little finger.”

When Megan and the others heard Zhao Hai, they couldn’t help but smile. They knew that Zhao Hai rarely cracked a joke. But even in this situation, he still managed to say one, this made them appreciate Zhao Hai’s temperament.

Megan smiled and said, “Right, just as what Brother Hai said, Terry, you’re comparable to his little finger. That’s why I didn’t choose you.”

Terry’s face turned pale when he heard Megan and Zhao Hai’s exchange. His dashing appearance completely disappeared from his face. He looked fiercely at Megan and said, “Why are you smiling, do you really think that you can deal with me?”

Zhao Hai looked at Terry’s face and smiled faintly, “I didn’t want to take care of you this soon, but since you came to the front door, why wouldn’t I grant your wish? Seeing you so rampant, I think it’s time for your life to end.”

When Terry heard what Zhao Hai just said, his face couldn’t help but turn black, then he said, “Enough wasting breath, today, I will make sure you die without a proper burial.”

Zhao Hai looked at Terry and smiled, “In the past, those who wished me death didn’t bade well. They didn’t succeed, so why should you?”

Then Zhao Hai waved his hand as he had Alien appear, Zhao Hai and the girls disappeared from the wall as well and entered Alien’s body. Alien opened its mouth as Zhao Hai’s voice boomed out, “One of the worst mistake that your Robert Family did was being enemies with me!”

As his voice fell, the Robert Family suddenly saw their lines being disrupted, undead creatures were appearing. As soon as the undead appeared, they immediately attacked the Warriors of the Robert Family. Now, the family’s formation was a mess.

And at this time, Alien jumped down from the wall. While it jumped down from the walls, it was also followed by some figures. Randolph and the others stared, those who jumped down with Zhao Hai were actually undead cavalry.

These undead cavalry were in the shape of Beastmen. Skeletal versions of a tall bullheaded Beastman was sitting on a horned bulls. When they fell to the ground, they produced a small indent on the surface. They seemed to be unaffected by their force of impact as they jumped over the fort’s moat and immediately attacked the Robert Family.

Randolph and the others were very startled when they saw Zhao Hai’s strength. These undead that Zhao Hai released were very different that what normal Dark Mages would summon. Their clan was a family of Dark Mages, they had researched summoning magic. However, they always managed to summon inferior undead. After each fight, those undead would need to be maintained well, otherwise, their strength would continually grow weak. Also, they weren’t a match against general Warriors, they can only use their numbers as an advantage.

But Zhao Hai’s undead didn’t fit any of these descriptions. Their fighting strength was extremely formidable. They aren’t any weaker than an 8th ranked expert. This strength made Randolph and the others extremely surprised.

What is most important was their numbers. These undead were numerous, from what they can count, Zhao Hai had already released about ten thousand. And the undead were still continuing to rush towards the Robert Family’s troops, their numbers constantly increasing.

One could say that it didn’t even take five minutes before Zhao Hai managed to destroy the Robert Family’s siege line-up. The undead already broke their formation, it was impossible for them to recover.

At this time, Alien was stood in front of the fort’s bridge, its big mouth opened as Zhao Hai’s voice sounded out, “Hahaha, Robert Family, do you really believe that you can deal with this Zhao Hai? Hahaha. Since, you’re already here, let me tell you. While I attended your banquet tonight, all of your businesses outside the capital have already been destroyed, your people all killed. Not only did we kill your people, we also looted everything and burned all of the infrastructure. Even if you didn’t act this night, your family would still be finished tomorrow. It’s very ridiculous that you still think that you can deal with me.”

Robert Patriarch and Terry recoved, ever since Zhao Hai’s attack began, the two of them were staring blankly. When Zhao Hai’s voice was heard, they came back to normal and changed their faced. They believed Zhao Hai’s words because there was no need for him to tell a lie at this moment.

From the present situation, Zhao Hai’s undead held the upper hand. It seems like the attack on the Calci Family was already going to fail. Zhao Hai had no reason to deceive them.

Robert Patriarch’s complexion was pale, he coldly snorted and said, “Ignorant junior. You’re quite proud of your undead, but can they contest against 9th rank experts? I request the elders to make a move, my Robert Family has reached a life and death moment!”

Zhao Hai’s voice came again, “Do you think that if you have a few 9th rank experts, you can change the outcome? It’s useless, since I’ve decided to deal with your Robert Family, nobody can save you!”

At this time, a cold voice was heard, “Can nobody really save them? I don’t believe you. My Robert Family has existed in the continent for more than 1000 years. With just your strength, exterminating my Robert Family is just a dream!”

Zhao Hai lifted his head and saw several human shapes floating in the air. All of them had a Warrior’s appearance. Zhao Hai looked at them and counted ten 9th rank experts.

Without waiting for Zhao Hai to speak, a voice suddenly sounded out from inside Dark Soldier Fort, “Savage Wolf’s Evil Sword, I didn’t think that you’re still alive, Hahaha. Good, I thought that I wouldn’t be able to settle our enmity in this life. Today, we can finally settle the account between us.” Along with the voice, seven figures appeared from the Calci Family. Six of them were dressed like Mages while one of them wore a Warrior’s clothing. Even if the mountain was filled with Antimagic Powder, its potency was too weak to affect these 9th ranks.

At this time, the 9th rank named Evil Sword laughed and said, “Dark Demon, I also didn’t think that you’re still alive. In the past, you’re not my match, now, you’re still not on my level. Although the Antimagic Powder isn’t very effective against 9th ranks, you’re still very restricted in your actions, feel it, your strength should be 80% compared to usual, right? Appearing this time is the same as courting death. In any case, without killing you, we won’t be able to ensure the Calci Family’s destruction.”

Without waiting for Dark Demon to speak, Alien suddenly vanished from the bridge, exposing Zhao Hai’s group underneath the 9th rank experts. When Randolph saw this, he was startled, he knew how terrifying 9th rank experts were. If Zhao Hai appeared, a 9th rank would only need to move a finger in order to erase him.

When Zhao Hai appeared on the bridge, he looked at Evil Sword and Dark Demon before opening his mouth, “Sorry for the disturbance. If you want to chat, go find a suitable place. I don’t want you standing on my head while you talk.”

Evil Sword looked down at Zhao Hai then coldly snorted,” Ignorant Junior, die !” His hand moved as Sword Qi, whistled forward and headed towards Zhao Hai’s direction.

Randolph felt his heart skip a beat. At this time, Zhao Hai moved and grabbed a whip. Seeing Zhao Hai wanting to meet his Sword Qi with a whip made Evil Sword sneer, in his mind, it was impossible for a whip to meet his Sword Qi.

However, he couldn’t believe his eyes with what he just saw next. The whip just blew the Sword Qi away, just like how a fan disperses smoke.

Zhao Hai received the whip and then looked at Evil Sword, “Daring to injure me meant that you and my Buda Family are now enemies. I ask my Buda Clan’s protectors to please come in!”

As Zhao Hai’s voice fell, ten large figures suddenly appeared from the forest. These figures didn’t belong to humans, but instead they were in the form of beasts. These were 9th rank experts from the Carrion Swamp.

Zhao Hai didn’t send a lot of 9th ranks, only ten. Moreover, these ten weren’t the strongest 9th ranks from the swamp, but instead, they were the weakest ten. However, these ten were enough to deal with Robert Family’s 9th rank experts.

After these ten beast appeared, they immediately flew towards Zhao Hai while shrinking their bodies at the same time. When they arrived in front of him, they gave a bow to Zhao Hai.

Zhao Hai nodded and said, “The enemies of my Buda Clan, kill them!” The beasts gave Zhao Hai a nod before flying into the air.

One of these ten was a 9th ranked eagle, he looked towards Evil Sword while using spiritual transmission to shout, “What audacity, to actually dare oppose our Buda Clan. Today, all of you will die!” Then all of the ten 9th ranks rushed towards Evil Sword’s group. There wasn’t any politeness at all, there wasn’t much that was said.

At this time, it doesn’t matter if they were from the Calci Family of the Robert Family, all of them were very shocked. They didn’t expect the Buda Clan that was previously exiled to have ten 9th rank experts, moreover, they were actually Magic Beasts!

Chapter 480: Rooting Out the Source of Trouble

Most importantly, they had noted how these 9th ranks treated Zhao Hai. One must know that 9th ranks belong to the top influences in the Continent. It was impossible for them to give someone a salute. Even if they gave respects, it would only be to another 9th rank. No matter what your status was, if you’re below their ranks they would never salute to you. This matter didn’t exempt even the Rosen Empire’s monarch.

However these ten 9th ranks of the Buda Clan actually gave Zhao Hai a bow. It was completely different from how other 9th ranks treat their patron families.

Randolph and the others weren’t the only ones who were startled by this scene, the other 9th rank experts stared as well. THey didn’t think that those 9th rank Beasts would act like this.

It was universally known that 9th rank Magic Beasts have an edge over 9th rank Humans. At the same time, they were also more arrogant than the Humans, it was very hard for a Human to come into contact with them, therefore making it impossible for a family to have them as a foreign elder. But this impossible thing was actually achieved by Zhao Hai.

However, the 9th ranks weren’t given enough time to think about this as the Buda Clan’s 9th ranks met with Evil Sword’s group. The scene of 20 9th ranks fighting was then witnessed.

Dark Demon looked at this development, he didn’t expect that people would interfere with his family’s matter. Moreover, they were 10 9th rank experts. This force was more formidable than the Calci Family.

Megan and the others just stood with Zhao Hai and didn’t make a move. They knew that the other party wouldn’t be able to escape. With only 10 9th ranks, Zhao Hai already held the upper hand, not to mention the 30 others still inside the Space.

Randolph blankly stared as Zhao Hai’s group chatted. Randolph’s heart was extremely terrified right now, he wasn’t terrified about the fact that Zhao Hai was strong, he was scared because of their earlier matter.

Initially, he wanted to ask a 9th rank expert to deal with Zhao Hai. If this went forward, the Calci Family would surely suffer bad luck.

The fight with the 9th ranks this time cannot be finished in a short time. Although the Buda Clan’s 9th ranks have the upper hand, it would be impossible for them to quickly deal with the 9th ranks of the Robert Family . The fight continued on.

At this time, Dark Demon’s group also made their move. Initially, Evil Sword’s group was able to hold on. But with Dark Demon’s group coming in, they can already feel a sense of danger.

While the fighting in the skies continued, the battle on the ground was coming to an end. At this time, Zhao Hai had all the undead surrounding Dark Mountain close in to prevent any stragglers from escaping.

At this time Robert Patriarch and Terry’s face were as bitter as chinese goldthread. They have never thought that the situation would turn into this.[1]

Terry looked at Zhao Hai with eyes that seem to be spouting fire. He felt that his whole life was left to ruin by Zhao Hai. Everything he had was snatched away from him. The only thing in his mind right now was to kill Zhao Hao.

While thinking about this, Terry inserted his hand into his chest. In his chest, there was an ancient Magic Scroll. Ancient Scrolls were passed down from ancient times, but most of them weren’t of good quality. There were only a few of them who were very useful, some of them even contained formidable magic spells.

The Magic Scroll that Terry has was special, as long as someone ripped it open, one can transfer to another person instantaneously within a radius of a hundred li(50km). This scroll was very rare, there were only a few of them present at this time.

Terry knew that Zhao Hai’s whip wasn’t simple, it should be one of those Ancient Artifacts with special magical attributes. However, the whip was currently used as Zhao Hai’s belt. Zhao Hai was a Mage so he shouldn’t have the quick reflexes of a warrior. As long as the used the scroll and teleported to Zhao Hai’s side, he should be able to kill him in one blow.

Terry wasn’t thinking of anything else other than killing Zhao Hai. Seeing that Zhao Hai was talking with Megan and wasn’t observing him at all, he immediately took the scroll out.

It was not only Zhao Hai, there was nobody who was paying attention to Terry. All of them were attracted to the fighting in the skies. Among the Robert Family’s 9th ranks, three of them were already killed while seven were heavily injured. They wouldn’t be able to last long.

Because their attention was focused on the sky, nobody looked at Terry since the battle on the ground was already finished. In their opinion, those on the ground were insignificant compared to those at the skies.

At this moment, Terry’s eyes flashed a cold light as he quickly tore the Magic Scroll into shreds. A white light them shot up into the sky, making people shift their gazes.

When the white light vanished, Terry disappeared from this present location and reappeared two meters right beside Zhao Hai. He immediately brandished his spear as he stabbed towards Zhao Hai.

The spear emitted a fiery radiance, indicating that Battle Qi was used to increase the effectivity of the strike. At this time, Randolph and the others pales, Megan and the others gasped.

When everyone thought that Zhao Hai would die, Zhao Hai immediately waved his Magic Staff towards Terry’s spear, *Ting* Then the strike was averted.

Terry looked at Zhao Hai with a surprised expression. Zhao Hai looked at Terry and said, “What? You think this can kill me? Are you this naive? I forgot to tell you, I actually cultivate both Magic and Battle Qi.” Then he waved his hand as his Magic Staff turned into a sword. Then he slashed towards the leg of Terry’s horse.

Terry immediately responded and pulled the reins. The Demon Horse not only evaded Zhao Hai’s strike by raising its legs, it also directed a kick towards Zhao Hai’s head.

Compared to Zhao Hai’s head, the horse’s hoof was much bigger. If this hoof gets in contact with Zhao Hai, his head would certainly turn into something like a smashed watermelon.

But Zhao Ha’s response was very quick. His body immediately moved and moved towards the belly of the horse. His staff lengthened and stabbed towards the belly of the beast, and also penetrating Terry’s body.

The staff immediately shortened as Zhao Hai moved away from Terry. Terry continued to sit on his horse as he stared at Zhao Hai with an unbelieving expression. Then his body shook before he fell down with a thud, followed along by his horse.

Zhao Hai’s fight made the crowd turn their attention towards them. Randolph and the others stared blankly at Zhao Hai. They didn’t think that Zhao Hai was a Magic and Battle Qi dual cultivator, moreover, he also had formidable Battle Qi.

Robert Patriarch looked at Terry with a grim face. Terry was the grandson that he valued the most. Now that he died in front of him, Robert Patriarch suddenly felt that he did something wrong.

Zhao Hai looked at Robert Patriarch and coldly snorted, “Robert Family’s Patriarch, I said that the worst thing that your family did was making me your enemy. Now, tell me, did I speak wrong?”

Robert Patriarch looked at Zhao Hai and then burst into laughter, he loudly said, “Good, Zhao Hai, Good, Buda Clan. Starting today, the Robert Family is now erased from the Continent, the Robert Family has lost. Zhao Hai, I only ask one thing, spare the roots of my Robert Family. Can you promise me this?”

Zhao Hai looked at Robert Patriarch and then shook his head, “No, if I don’t cut out the roots, it will sprout come spring. If our enemies completely eliminated the Buda Clan, there would be no Zhao Hai right now. If your family had any newborn children, since they don’t have any understanding, I will spare them. However, I will never let them inherit the Robert Family. I will let them keep their surname, but I will tell them that they have no relationship to you.”

Robert Patriarch looked at Zhao Hai and couldn’t help but show despair. At the same time he laughed again, “Good Zhao Hai, good. It’s a pity that we don’t have a child like that in our family, an innocent child. Hahaha. I’ve shamed the ancestors, I’ve shamed the ancestors!” He said as he drew his sword and killed himself.

At this time, the forces of the Robert Family had all been exterminated, the battle on the sky was finished as well. All of the 9th rank experts of the Robert Family were killed.

Zhao Hai was not polite, beside the Robert Patriarch and Terry, he turned all of the Robert Family’s forces into undead. Then he scanned the area using the monitor to see if they were still some survivors. Only when seeing that there were no enemies did he stop.

At this time, the 9th ranks of the Buda Clan gave Zhao Hai a bow before their bodies flashed and vanished. At this moment, a batch of 9th ranks appeared in the sky. The 9th ranks in this group were numerous, approximately 40 people. But if one would look carefully, one could see that these 9th ranks didn’t belong to a single clan, but different families instead. They came to see what was going on.

Dark Demon met with them and told the 9th ranks what was happening before all of them left. They didn’t care about this matter anymore, in their mind, this has nothing to do with their families. Other than the life and death of their clans, these 9th ranks wouldn’t bat an eyelid at anything else. Worldly matters were always handed over to their juniors.

After the 9th ranks left, Dark Demon turned his head towards Zhao Hai and nodded. Zhao Hai nodded back before his body as he returned to Dark Soldier Fort. The family’s other 9th ranks followed him as well.

Although Dark Demon nodding towards Zhao Hai looked like simple matter, it was a surprising event. Even if these 9th ranks see Randolph, they wouldn’t go out of their way to greet him. Seeing them take the initiative in greeting Zhao Hai showed how they see him in their hearts.

Zhao Hai didn’t think about this right now. He waved his hand as a Blood Hawk appeared. The Blood Hawk then carried the Magic Staff towards the Robert Family’s fort. He must root out the source of the problem. Thus, he sent the Blood Hawk over.[2]

* * *

Coptis, bitter tonic used to treat malaria

Maybe he can teleport anywhere but can’t send undead outside a certain range of the Magic Staff?

Chapter 481: Exterminating an Entire Family

Zhao Hai had read too much novels on Earth. The protagonists on those novels share the same feature, they were all hardworking but their hearts were to soft.

Having a soft heart had always been a feature of protagonists. Before they fight against their enemy, they would talk a lot of nonsense before showing their superiority.

Even if Zhao Hai said a lot of words, they were short compared to those main characters. Moreover, his heart was ruthless enough to completely pull out the roots.

Constant good fortune only happens in film and television. In reality, people cannot have too many miracles. When a family is destroyed, it was nearly impossible that one or two heirs that escape would be able to come back for revenge. But that won’t happen, Cai’er was already monitoring the entirety of the Robert Family’s fort, ensuring that there won’t be any survivors.[1]

With the Space’s surveillance, not only the people on the ground were seen, the 9th ranks in the sky as well as the underground passages can be seen. Under such circumstances, there was no way for the Robert Family to run away.

Zhao Hai didn’t like troubles, he also doesn’t like leaving behind something that would inconvenience him. If he handles something, he would make sure to remove all loose ends.

Robert Family might survive, as long as someone stayed behind, there would be a constant possibility of them resurging. Although he didn’t turn Robert Patriarch and Terry into advanced level undead, Zhao Hai knew that the Robert Family wasn’t simple.

Just by their clan’s strength, it was impossible for the Robert Family to acquire and produce Antimagic Powder, it was also impossible for them to have ten 9th rank experts. The Calci Family was considered as one of the top families in the Rosen Empire, and even they have only seven 9th rank experts. Therefore, the Robert Family having three more than them was very unreasonable. Because of this, Zhao Hai believed that Robert Family is part of a huge influence. Their 9th rank experts as well as the Antimagic powder was most likely supplied by this influence.

While Zhao Hai sent the Blood Hawk to deal with the Robert Family, he started to collect all of the Antimagic Powder that the Robert Family spread all around the mountain.

Because of Zhao Hai’s worries, he hasn’t taken the powder to the Space. But this time, he took the powder and placed it inside the Space.

When the powder entered the Space, a prompt was heard, “Radioactive isolation powder detected. Space doesn’t have the formula. Extrapolating formula from ingredients. Added formula to the Processing Machine’s list. Extracting Antimagic Powder’s characteristics, added the property to the Space’s insecticide.”

Zhao Hai didn’t expect to get the properties of the Antimagic Powder. It seems like the Space’s poison would be stronger in the future. Most importantly, Cai’er’s poison fog could now isolate magic, increasing the security of the Black Wasteland by another level.

Zhao Hai didn’t mean to receive the powder into the Space to obtain its benefits. He just wanted to store it so that he may use it in the future.

While Zhao Hai received all of the Antimagic Powder, he went to manage the matter with the Robert Family. At this moment, the Robert Family no longer had any experts. All that was left in their fort were old and weak. All of these people cannot contend with Zhao Hai’s undead. They didn’t even have the opportunity to fight back.

Zhao Hai didn’t exempt anybody, he even slaughtered the children. All of the members of the Robert Family were now dead. Not a living witness was left. Starting this day, the Robert Family was no more.

Beside this, Zhao Hai had also found the Robert Family’s treasure and storehouse. Without hesitation, he took all of them.

When treating his enemies, Zhao Hai would never be lenient. He knew very well that if he softened this time, he would be the one to suffer in the end. For Zhao Hai, the people who wouldn’t take revenge and won’t be a threat were only one type of people, dead people!

After living in the continent for this amount of time, Zhao Hai had already learned about how to act. If you are too soft, then you will get killed in the end. If you are not ruthless, people would constantly place you under their foot.

He had dealt with Boris’ 9th ranks before, he also slapped the Radiant Church’s face. But even if he managed to shake some people, its influence wasn’t very great. Rosen Empire was the continent’s most powerful nation, it doesn’t matter if they were commoners or nobles, every citizen of the empire held gread pride. Because of this they didn’t care about what Zhao Hai did before. At the very least, the Robert Family didn’t pay any attention to him.

But now, he believed that it would be different. Zhao Hai had taken care of the Robert Family in one swoop. Even if they think that it was the Calci Family who did it, they have to acknowledge that Zhao Hai had a hand in it. Zhao Hai can’t do anything if they place the credit on the Calci Family, but in the end, Zhao Hai was engaged to Megan. This would make people think that Zhao Hai had a powerful backer. These people wouldn’t be thinking so little about Zhao Hai any longer.

After collecting all of the powder, Zhao Hai returned to Dark Soldier Fort. At this moment, people from the fort were sending people to repair the damages in the surroundings. The pits that were caused by the undead were being pounded and levelled. The roadblock as well as the trees can only wait to be repaired tomorrow.

Upon arriving at the fort, people immediately invited Zhao Hai to the fort’s lobby. Randolph and the other high level members of the Calci Family were already waiting for him there.

Zhao Hai gave his greetings to the people in the lobby. This time, there were only a few of them who didn’t return his gesture, there were even some who stood up before giving a salute.

Looking at their behaviour, Zhao Hai couldn’t blame them. People in the continent tend to be realistic, they would only respect strength. If you are strong enough, then people would give you respect. If you aren’t strong, then they won’t be giving you face.

In the past, although Zhao Hai had some sort of strength, the Calci Family still looked down on him. With how he dealt with the Robert Family, the Calci Family’s people had no choice but to reevaluate how they see this young man.

The strength that Zhao Hai showed today was far from what they thought. Under such circumstances, those present knew that offending Zhao Hai wouldn’t’ be wise. Nobody would help them, even their own family members. If the Calci Family were to choose, they would rather pick Zhao Hai and wouldn’t care about the life and death of an ordinary family member. A big family like them was this practical.

After Zhao Hai sat down, Randolph looked at all the people in attendance and then nodded, “My Calci Family nearly suffered a tragedy today, it was one of our clan’s biggest crisis. We’re fortunate that we have Little Hai, otherwise the Calci Family would have been ended tonight.”

Nobody disagreed with Randolph’s words, they knew that what Randolph said was true. Because of the Antimagic Powder, all the Mages of the family were unable to use magic. Because of this, the fighting power of the family was greatly affected, even their 9th ranks wouldn’t be able to help them,. Regarding the Calci Family, tonight’s attack was extremely dangerous.

Randolph then said, “Compared to the attack on our family, the matter regarding Antimagic Powder is more important. Our Calci Family is a family of Mages, the appearance of Antimagic Powder was too great of a threat to us. This matter should be figured out and dealt with.”

Just as his voice fell, someone outside gave a notification. And then four servants came in carrying two bodies, both belonging to the Robert Patriarch and Terry.

Zhao Hai turned all the attackers into undead creatures. Only these two individuals were left untouched. Zhao Hai knew that these two still held great use.

Randolph looked at the two bodies on the ground and said, “Robert Patriarch and Terry are dead, now that there is no Antimagic Powder, we can now turn them into undead. Who is willing to do it?”

In the Calci Family, there was no shortage of Advanced Level Dark Mages, so Randolph asked such a question. Zhao Hai looked at the scene and quickly said, “Grandpa, slow down. I don’t think it would be a good idea to turn them into advanced level undead right now. Although it would be good to make them into undead, the Calci Family cannot deal with the matter of Antimagic Powder alone. This matter should be passed on to the Imperial Clan. The Rosen Imperial Clan is also a Mage family, they should care a lot about the Antimagic Powder. If we turn these two into undead right now, I’m afraid that the Imperial Clan would mistake us for forcing them to admit. Grandfather should bring them tomorrow to the Imperial Palace and then turn them into advanced undead in front of His Majesty. Interrogate them then, that way His Majesty wouldn’t have any suspicions.”

When Randolph heard Zhao Hai, he immediately understood what he meant. He thought for a moment and then nodded, “Little Hai’s words are true. I think we should delay this matter and bring them to the Imperial Palace tomorrow morning.”

The other people in the family didn’t oppose. Zhao Hai looked at them and said, “Grandfather, I just sent my undead to the Robert Family, completely eradicating their line. I’ve also looted all of their treasury and storehouse. However, I didn’t take any bodies away from their fort, Grandpa might like to take them. Also, I have no need for Terry and Robert Patriarch’s space equipment, I’ll give those to Grandfather.”

When Randolph heard Zhao Hai, he can’t help but stare, he looked at Zhao Hai with an face full of disbelief and said, “Little Hai, did you really kill all of the Robert Family? Are there any survivors?”

Zhao Hai shook his head, “No survivors. I’ve seen their Clan registry. After coordinating their bodies with the descriptions, there shouldn’t be any members left.”

* * *

I say BS

Chapter 482: Engraved Ark

Zhao Hai didn’t lie, he really was basing on the list. However, he didn’t use the list outside the family, but instead, he used the one he got from the Robert Family’s treasury. Every single person from the Robert Family was in that list.

From the list that he got, he inspected each member one by one. From the direct line to the side branches, every single one was taken care of, there were no survivors.

Also, since God’s Grace Day has passed, the Robert Family held the same custom as other clans. At this season, all of their members were in their fort. This made it easier for Zhao Hai to deal with them, it was like catching all of the fishes in one net.

A Great Clan like the Robert Family had a lot of matters to take care of as well, if it weren’t because of God’s Grace Day, it would be impossible to see all of the family members in one place. All of them would be spread out, managing their external operations.

However, when God’s Grace Day comes, it was imperative for them to return to the Clan. The family had too many members, if they didn’t return to Savage Wolf fort, the family would certainly place that member into suspicion. They would think that they might have failed in their own assigned operation.

Now, the faces of Randolph and the others were pale as they looked at Zhao Hai. Although they were Dark Mages, they were also Great nobles, they knew how tough it would be to exterminate another Great noble clan. But Zhao Hai actually told them about the elimination of the Robert Family in a nonchalant manner.

When one counted the direct line as well as the branches of the Robert family, they would number between 1 thousand to 2 thousand people. From Zhao Hai’s words, it seems like he had actually killed these 1 or 2 thousand people.

Killing a thousand or 2 thousand people isn’t something strange for someone like the Calci Family. But they knew that there were elderlies, women, and children among the thousand people from the Robert Family. Zhao Hai wasn’t polite, he actually killed them all. This startled the Calci Family.

Randolph stared deeply into Zhao Hai, this was the first time that he experienced Zhao Hai’s ruthlessness. Thinking of this, he couldn’t help but turn towards Smith. Now, Randolph was inwardly rejoicing, he felt very lucky when he recalled their planned attack on Zhao Hai. Otherwise, the Calci Family might have been completely exterminated.

Taking a deep breath to calm down, Randolph looked at the people in the room and said, “Alright, now everyone should go back and rest. You still have some matters to attend to.” The crowd nodded before they stood up and left.

Zhao Hai went towards Rustling Tree courtyard along with Smith. While walking with Zhao Hai, Smith said, “Little Hai, did you really extinguish the Robert Family?”

Zhao Hai nodded and said, “I did. I did so not only to eliminate the threat of the Robert Family, but most importantly to showcase my might!”

Smith understood Zhao Hai’s words, he nodded and said, “Alright, I won’t be butting into your matters. Also, Little Hai, are you planning to leave Carson City?”

From what Smith had seen, it would be impossible for Zhao Hai to stay here for too long. He had a lot of matters to take care of, it was certain that Zhao Hai would leave the Capital.

Zhao Hai nodded and said, “I’m ready to leave anytime, but I still need to wait for the results regarding the Robert Family’s matter. What happened would certainly shake the entire continent.”

Smith sighed and said, “The appearance of Antimagic Powder would really make the situation of the Continent quite turbulent.” He said as the two of them entered Rustling Tree courtyard. At this time, Zhao Hai returned to his own residence.

Laura and the others were waiting for Zhao Hai in the waiting room. When they saw that Zhao Hai has come back, Laura and the others immediately went and welcomed him. Laura looked at Zhao Hai and said, “Brother Hai, did we make a fortune this time?”

Laura and the others were natives of the Ark Continent. They had no qualms regarding Zhao Hai’s extermination of the Robert Family. This was because this matter was very common in the continent, families and clans would disappear from the map every year. To them this matter wasn’t strange.

Also, they understood the situation back at the Black Wasteland. They knew that the place needed a lot of things, and what it needed the most was money.

When spring comes, a hundred thousand Beastmen slaves would arrive in the Black Wasteland. In managing these 100 thousand slaves, money was extremely crucial. Zhao Hai was also preparing to go buy some slaves in the slave market in Carson City. This will require even more resources, therefore, the thing that the Buda Clan needed the most was money.

But now, in addition to the gold they have gotten from Grand Duke Lionheart, they also acquired the money of the Robert Family. At this point, they didn’t need to worry about managing these slaves.

The accumulated wealth of a millennium-old clan was difficult to imagine. A family as large as the Robert Family would have more than one treasury. The one at Savage Wolf Fort was just one of the biggest vaults that they have. Aside from this one, the Robert Family has secret treasuries in many places that they had built for over a thousand years.

One must know that these things are not cheap to build. Most importantly, this was also built in order for the family to wade through difficulties, allowing them capital to start anew.

But the addresses of these vaults weren’t in the treasury of the Robert Family, but instead it was stored in their secret vault. This vault was made even more covertly than the treasury. They built it in such a way that those who had found the treasury wouldn’t think that the vault exists. Placed in this secret vault were the most important artifacts of the Robert Family as well as their mostly hidden secret documents.

Zhao Hai didn’t have the time to look at all these things. After reading the addresses, he placed them on the side. For Zhao Hai, what they had gotten from the treasury and the secret vault was already enough for the Buda Clan to use.

When Zhao Hai heard Laura, he smiled faintly and said, “Not only a fortune, it was a mountain of fortune. What we got was enough for our Buda Clan to use.”

Laura and the others cheered, they knew clearly how important money was to the Buda Clan. Once could say that aside from population and background, the Buda Clan was now comparable with a millennium-old clan.

Zhao Hai looked at their expressions and smiled. He was very happy as well. What he obtained from Savage Wolf fort would strengthen the backbone of the Buda Clan. For Zhao Hai, this was very good news.

The group chatted for a while before the entered the Space. They had obtained so much from the Robert Family, they wanted to go and take a look.

Inside the Space, Zhao Hai immediately withdrew all of the things that he had looted from the Robert Family. Each person divided the loot and inspected them one by one.

Zhao Hai held the document about the location of the other vaults. Aside from Savage Wolf fort, the Robert Family also had 12 other secret vaults outside. The total value of these vaults was five times more than the contents of the vault from Savage Wolf fort. This was a huge fortune for Zhao Hai, he gave the document to Cai’er and made her mark the locations on the three-dimensional map. Now, they can easily see where those vaults are located,

Laura held another document, after reading for a while, her complexion changes as she turned to Zhao Hai and said, “Brother Hai, you should look at this right now.”

Zhao Hai placed the document in the hand down, and took the document that Laura was reading. The document that Laura held described an organization. From what Zhao Hai has read, the organization was named Engraved Ark. All of the people in this group held numbers, but they had a huge population. Moreover, Zhao Hai had seen the mission of the group, it was to subvert the entire Ark Continent.

Not only were they hostile to Mages, they also hostile to Warriors, Royal Clans, and nobles. One could say that the group held negative sentiment towards all of the people in Ark Continent.

The Antimagic Powder was produced by them. Moreover, they were also researching other things. Some of them were drugs, from what Zhao Hai had read, these drugs had the same effect as viruses on Earth.

This was too scary, Zhao Hai suddenly remembered a word from Earth, Anti-humanity. The vision of this organization had some anti-human elements to it. They wouldn’t stop before they make the entire human species vanish.

Zhao Hai’s face was very ugly while he was reading the document. Although this document had some introductions for the organization, important aspects of its operation was rarely written. All of its members used a code number, and they also couldn’t use this code to trace the origin of the member. The organization’s means of sending information was all through encrypted means. Once something goes wrong, the organization would immediately change the way they encrypt their messages. Because of this, Zhao Hai ruled that it would be impossible to find this organization.

Zhao Hai thought for a moment and said, “It looks like we need to hand this document over. This information isn’t simple. If this organization succeeds in its plans, the Ark Continent would certainly suffer a disaster.”

Laura nodded and said, “I’m thinking the same, Brother Hai, what do you think? Are they people of the Ark Continent? Why would they want the destruction of the continent?”

Zhao Hai smiled bitterly and said, “Nobody knows what these people are thinking about. But I can affirm that these people are lunatics.”

Megan sighed and said, “Big Brother Hai, are you going to give this to Grandpa? I think that it won’t be good if we participate deeply in this matter.”

Zhao Hai nodded and said, “Alright, I’ll hand this over to Grandfather. No matter what these people wanted to do, it wouldn’t affect our Buda Clan. After all, there was no way for these people to enter the Black Wasteland. Right, go and see if there are more documents about this organization.”

Megan and the others nodded. The group continued to read the document that they acquired from the Robert Family. Unfortunately, they were unable to find any other information about the group. There were some information about the other families in the continent, all of these would be very useful to Great Clans.

Chapter 483: Eternal Alliance

For Zhao Hai, these materials were very useful. His current understanding about the carious Great Clans of the continent was pitifully small. With the Buda Clan having no intelligence unit, acquiring information about these families was very hard.

The other documents were not very useful. Most of them were internal data about the Robert Family. But these information were no longer useful for Zhao Hai, the Robert Family was already exterminated by him. Those data were equivalent to waste paper at this point.

The group organized these documents, some were discarded, some were saved. After that, Zhao Hai and the others went to rest.

The next morning, Zhao Hai took the document about Engraved Ark out of the Space. After eating their breakfast, he immediately handed the document over to Randolph. After that, he went out of the fort to release some undead and made them clean the toppled trees of Dark Mountain.

When Randolph saw the document, he was startled. Then he immediately took Robert Patriarch’s and Terry’s bodies with him as he rushed towards the imperial palace.

The emperor naturally knew about the happenings last night. Of the 9th ranks who went to check the fighting yesterday, some of them belonged to the Royal Clan. Even if those 9th ranks didn’t say too much, they still passed the information about the conflict at the very least.

Randolph gave the document as well as the corpses over to the Emperor. The Emperor immediately had someone call the Royal Dark Mage over to turn Terry and Robert Patriarch into advanced level undead before interrogating them.

In the end, all the matters were made clear. From Robert Patriarch and Terry’s mouths, they admitted that they were members of Engraved Ark. Moreover, the Antimagic Powder was mostly manufactured by the organization.

Regarding these matters, the Rosen Empire immediately published the document out to the world. At the same time, they also communicated with the other nations of the continent, making them pay special attention to anything involving Engraved Ark.

Rosen Empire was the continent’s most influential nation, their rallying power was formidable. With how they were perceived by the entire continent, this time’s announcement from the Empire naturally turned the continent in an uproar.

Zhao Hai did not seem to care about these things at all. He spent one day in taking care of Dark Mountain and then stayed in his residence from then on.

Green and the others were still uninformed about last night’s battle. Zhao Hai wanted to tell them and ask about what they think.

Zhao Hai didn’t worry too much about Engraved Ark. All of the people under him were slaves, and slaves weren’t allowed to be members of the organization. For Engraved Ark, slaves held zero value, therefore, it was impossible for them to join.

Moreover, Zhao Hai had also read from the document that the population of Engraved Ark was relatively small. However, Zhao Hai believed that the status of those people mustn’t be low. Otherwise, how could those people pull the Robert Family over into joining them.[1]

On the other side, people were in an uproar. They had just been informed that the Robert Family had been eliminated. When they received this new, all of them were very surprised. They cannot believe that one of the most powerful families in the continent was now nonexistent. This was too unbelievable.

Afterwards, the Imperial Palace had released some news, which made them even more startled. Antimagic Powder, Engraved Ark, all of these things seemed to be from their imaginations. After their initial uproar, people couldn’t help but turn speechless.

And then, another information from the Calci Family came, which made everyone shocked silly. This information actually said that the Robert Family’s demise was accomplished under Zhao Hai’s hands.

But this information was something that majority of the people from Rosen Empire didn’t believe. Then, another piece of news was passed on. All of the Robert Family’s stores outside of the capital have been destroyed. All of their personnel were killed, their goods were looted, and lastly, their shops burned. It can be said that the Robert Family’s final chance of survival went up in smoke. From this day on, the Robert Family became just a word in the history of the Ark Continent.

These news went like bombs as it exploded inside the minds of all the residents of Rosen Empire. Millenium-old clans were much like the symbols of invincibility in the Continent. The number of Millenium-old clans that were exterminated in the entire history of the continent can be counted on one hand. Almost all of them were done from the inside, they all perished due to internal conflict. On the other hand, the Robert Family was actually destroyed completely by someone else.

In the past, when a millennium-old clan dissolved, there were generally some survivors left. But for the Robert Family, there wasn’t anyone left, all of their members were killed. This was too terrifying.

The Great Nobles of the continent were startled as well. They were even more startled when the Calci Family spread the fact that the extermination was Zhao Hai’s doing. Naturally, these people didn’t believe that it was Zhao Hai, one person cannot defeat the Robert Family. However, they were certain that Zhao Hai had a huge hand in the operation.

Now, all of them are changing the way they see Zhao Hai. The Calci Family’s strength was similar to the Robert Family. The Calci Family destroying the Robert Family was impossible. But now that Zhao Hai joined the Calci Family, they were actually able to eliminate the Robert Family. If they didn’t believe that this was because of Zhao Hai, then they might as well kill themselves for their stupidity.

Because of this, these Great Clans were now scared. Now that the Calci Family had united with the Buda Clan, their cooperation was much more formidable. Zhao Hai was far from what they previously thought; a playboy who liked playing around, eating and others.

Starting from today, all of the Great Nobles in Rosen Empire began to look seriously into Zhao Hai. His image of a playboy had now vanished.

The dissemination of information in the continent was very quick. In a day’s time, almost everyone in the continent knew of this matter. All the Mages in the continent became insecure. At the same time, all of the nation’s Mage’s guild decreed at once that all Mages must unite and look for this Engraved Ark, they must destroy this organization. Otherwise, if this group’s plans were to succeed, and they produce a lot of Antimagic Powder, all of the Mages in the continent would suffer a huge accident.

Right now, the thing that was in Zhao Hai’s mind was how this organization came to be. How this organization started, how they became a secret. From what Zhao Hai had heard, this information seem to have their own faith.

Faith was mysterious, people in the continent had different faiths. Warriors worship the Martial God, Light Mages worship the Radiant God, Dark Mages worship the God of Darkness, Wind Mages worship the Wind God, Water Mages worship the Water God, Fire mages worship the Fire God, Earth Mages worship the Earth God, Elves worship the God of Life, Beastmen worship the Beast God, and the Dwarves worship the Artisan God. But the Engraved Ark’s source of faith was actually out of the norm, what they worshipped seem to a Demon.

Why ‘seem’? This was because Zhao Hai had no concrete testimony that the organization worshipped a Demon. However, Zhao Hai had seen an image from the back of the document, it was a portrait of a devil. The devil had eight arms, three heads, six feet, and looked extremely terrifying. From this, Zhao Hai inferred that the Engraved Ark worshipped a Demon.

Zhao Hai knew that if a person didn’t have faith, he wouldn’t be such a lunatic. It was because of faith that people did overly extreme things.

While Zhao Hai was ruminating on these matter, a servant immediately came bearing a message that Jason had come to visit. Zhao Hai stared for a moment before he had the servant invite Jason to come in.

Jason was different from his usual wacky and joking face, now he had a serious expression on his face. Zhao Hai made him sit down and had the servant retreat. Then Jason turned to Zhao Hai and said, “Little Hai, are you really responsible for what happened last night? Is the Engraved Ark real? Did the Robert Family really use Antimagic Powder?”

Zhao Hai nodded and said, “I am, but my initial intention was to destroy all of the Robert Family’s businesses. I didn’t expect the Robert Family to assassinate me, moreover, they actually used Antimagic Powder. But since they were defeated, they became afraid that the Antimagic were to be made known to others, so they attacked Dark Soldier Fort. Later on, they were eliminated by the Calci Family. Then, I went to kill all of the remaining Robert Family members before looting their treasury. It was there that I managed to uncover the matter about Engraved Ark.”

Jason’s face had a heavy expression, he nodded and said, “I believe that this organization is real. You don’t know, but before I came here, I rummaged some data from my family and managed to see that there were a lot of strong Mages that suddenly died in the past. Moreover, their death actually didn’t involve them using any magic. These cases became one the mysteries of the continent. Now it seems like these incidents were caused by Engraved Ark, they were using Antimagic Powder.”

Zhao Hai stared, he truly didn’t know about this, he looked at Jason and said, “Really? There was such a thing?”

Jason nodded and said, “I just figured that out. As far as the information that my Crook Family has, there were at least 100 Mage deaths in the last ten years alone. 20 of them were 8th rank experts. But nobody thought more into these incidents, after all, these people came from different nations, their deaths were very far apart. But now that new information came about, people would certainly think that there was something wrong with the deaths of these Mages.”

Zhao Hai nodded and said, “It seems like this Engraved Ark has existed for quite a long time. No wonder they had such strength, but it’s a pity that there was no way to find out about their identity.”

Jason nodded, then his face turned serious as he looked at Zhao Hai, “Little Hai, today I came to look for you because of Grandfather’s proposal. He wanted my Crook Family and your Buda Clan to be in an eternal alliance starting this day. What do you think?”

Zhao Hai stared, he didn’t expect the Crook Family to initiate forming an Eternal Alliance with him. This Eternal Alliance wasn’t easy to enact. There were too many people involved in it and there were too many matters to consider.

The Eternal Alliance was also called the Ironclad Union by the people of the continent. When two families form an Eternal Alliance, if one of them falls, the other would have to help them recover and achieve their previous strength. This alliance had the same meaning as a Beastman’s Beheading Blood Oath.

Zhao Hai stared for a moment before he became happy. The Crook Family’s influence in the Rosen Empire wasn’t much smaller than millenium-old clans. If Zhao Hai forms an Eternal Alliance with such a family, then his Buda Clan would benefit a lot from it.

Zhao Hai immediately nodded happily and said, “I fully agree. But I still have a few reservations. Just by our relationship, forming this alliance seems to be wrong.”

When Jason heard Zhao Hai, he couldn’t help but laugh and said, “I’ll go back to grandfather and express your concern. If you have time, go to my family’s fort and play. You can also discuss this matter with the family.”

Zhao Hai nodded, “Alright, I’ll go there tomorrow.” Then as he said that, a knock was heard. Zhao Hai immediately responded and said, “What’s the problem?”

The servant’s voice was heard, “Young Master Zhao Hai, the Patriarch had sent a message. His Majesty, the Emperor, wishes to see you in the palace immediately. He said that he has an important matter to consult with.”

Zhao Hai stared, Jason stared as well. They looked at each other, confused. But Zhao Hai immediately recovered and said, “Alright, I’ll go tidy my clothes and then I’ll immediately leave.” The servant issued a sound of compliance as he walked.

Zhao Hai frowned towards Jason and said, “Why do you think his Majesty called for me?”

Jason also frowned as he replied, “I really cannot say, but it should have a something to do about what happened yesterday. You should go, right, why haven’t I seen sister-in-laws today?”

Zhao Hai smiled and said, “They’re currently rummaging through all of the documents from the Robert Family in another room. We didn’t expect that the Robert Family would have a lot of information about Great Clans in the continent, these things are very useful to my clan.” Actually, Laura and the others were sorting through all of the Robert Family’s documents inside the Space, not in another room.

Jason smiled faintly and said, “You lucky guy. This time, you looted the Robert Family. The wealth of a millennium-old family, you’re really making me envious.”

Zhao Hai laughed and said, “Lucky, right? As it turns out, there’s nothing much faster in gaining money other than robbing people. It seems like I need to do this a few more times.”

Jason laughed as well, “Are you really a guy who likes to rob? I really didn’t see it before, but you actually have the potential to be a thief. Hahaha. Right, we shouldn’t be talking too much, the Emperor is waiting for you, we can’t have him wait too long.” Zhao Hai nodded and stood up, then he tidied his clothes before leading Jason to the exit.

When they came out of the courtyard, a servant was already waiting for them with along with a carriage. The two rode the carriage as they left Dark Soldier Fort. Jason rode his carriage, but before leaving, he reminded Zhao Hai about his visit to the Crook Family. Zhao Hai nodded before boarding the carriage that the Calci Family already prepared for him.

Since Zhao Hai’s carriage was destroyed, Randolph personally assigned this carriage to Zhao Hai. The carriage was pulled by a Demon Horse, the carriage itself was very spacious, it had a room inside that could fit six people. It also had a bedroom inside. The carriage was made from Iron Driftwood as well as Saint Lightwood, it looked beautiful and elegant.

* * *

A lot for a secret organization, but small compared to the population of the continent. I think xD

Chapter 484: Third Eunuch

Zhao Hai’s previous carriage wasn’t that large, it was a vehicle that was used by common nobles. The one he was using right now was something that a Great Clan’s Patriarch would use, it was beautiful and elegant.

Randolph gave Zhao Hai this carriage because Zhao Hai’s status was now different. Zhao Hai was now qualified to sit in this kind of carriage, he was now treated the same as the Patriarchs of millenium-old clans.

When Zhao Hai boarded the carriage, he asked the driver about why the Emperor was looking for him, but naturally, the servant had no idea. This made Zhao Hai very confused.

When the carriage entered Carson City, all of the people who saw the vehicle immediately gave way. All residents of Carson City was well aware that someone who rode such a carriage didn’t have a simple status. These were people that they cannot offend, so they backed away immediately.

Before long, the carriage arrived outside the Imperial Palace. Rosen Empire’s Imperial Palace was extraordinary. Its outside fence was several feel high, in front of the gates were two rows of Warriors, numbering 40. All of them wore full-body armor, the material that it was made from looked very uncommon either.

Outside the palace was a moat, with a bridge connecting the two sides. Zhao Hai’s carriage stopped in front of the bridge, the servant went down from the carriage and informed Zhao Hai, “Young Master Zhao Hai, the carriage has reached its destination. You need to walk to the bridge and have your name registered, after that, people would lead you to see His Majesty.”

Zhao Hai nodded, then he went down the vehicle and walked towards the bridge and crossed it. When he reached the other side, he was blocked by two of the Warriors. Looking at Zhao Hai’s carriage, these Warriors naturally didn’t look down on Zhao Hai as one of them said, “Mister, please head inside and have your name registered.” Then he gave a gesture.

Zhao Hai followed the direction he was pointed to and arrived in a place with small rooms, it seems like these were used for registration. Zhao Hai nodded and walked into the room he was led to.

He opened the door and walked in. The room wasn’t very big, but it was warm. The inside of the room was quite simple, it has one table and four chairs. Sitting on one side of the table were two men, both of them looked approximately 30 years old, they were very white and flawless. They wore a patterned dress that looked beautiful.

Seeing Zhao Hai come inside, the two men immediately stood up and gave him a bow before saying, “We have seen mister, may we ask mister’s name?” Their voices were a bit thin. When he heard their voices, Zhao Hai immediately knew that these two men were eunuchs.

Although Zhao Hai didn’t have much liking towards eunuchs, he was still very polite. In the history of China, there were a lot of incidents were eunuchs were the principal cause. Who knows what these people could do, so Zhao Hai became polite and returned the bow before answering, “I am Buda Clan’s Patriarch, Zhao Hai Buda. I came here to answer His Majesty’s summons.”

As soon as the two eunuchs heard the name of Zhao Hai, they immediately became even more respectful, they quickly nodded and said, “We’ll take care of mister’s registration before Mister can go, another eunuch will be waiting for you inside.”

Zhao Hai nodded, after the two eunuchs registered his name, they gave him a golden token. One the eunuchs said, “Mister can take this and head inside. Someone will be leading you to His Majesty.”

Zhao Hai nodded and received the token, then he turned around to leave the room and walked towards the Imperial Palace. The guards inspected the token in Zhao Hai’s hand before allowing him passage.

When Zhao Hai entered the gate of the Imperial Palace, he saw that a eunuch was already waiting for him there. The eunuch wasn’t young, he looked over 50 years old. However, Zhao Hai didn’t dare underestimate the eunuch. The eunuch had an imposing manner, a kind of attitude that someone of a high position would have. Moreover, he also had a very heavy killing aura around him.

Upon seeing this eunuch, Zhao Hai immediately knew that he wasn’t simple. He reckoned that this man should be an assassin, an advanced level assassin.

When the eunuch saw Zhao Hai, he immediately went forwards and gave him a bow before asking, “Patriarch Zhao Hai?”

Zhao Hai didn’t dare neglect the gesture as he returned a bow and said, “Mister is too polite, this one is Zhao Hai.”

The eunuch immediately replied, “Mister Count, please come with me. His Majesty is already waiting for you.” Then he walked towards the interior of the palace, Zhao Hai followed him behind. While walking, the eunuch gave Zhao Hai instructions about how he should give courtesy to the Emperor.

Giving respects to a monarch in the Ark Continent was not quite the same as in Earth. On Earth, when you see an Emperor, you would need to perform a kneeling ritual, if you meet for the first time, a kowtow would be needed. However, in Ark Continent, as long as one held a Noble title, they won’t need to kneel in front of the Emperor, a bow would suffice.

Bowing naturally had its own rules, it was different between noble ranks. Lowest nobles would need to bow 90 degrees, the scale lessens as the rank increases. All of these were introduced to Zhao Hai.

It was Zhao Hai’s first meeting with this eunuch, it wasn’t good for him if he were to ask too much. He just quietly walked at his side and listened to the eunuch, but Zhao Hai wanted to try gaining his favor.

When they arrived in a hallway, Zhao Hai looked around to make sure that there were nobody else before he turned his hand and retrieved an item that he had looted from the Robert Family. This was a piece of magic crystal, an alchemy product. He didn’t know how the alchemists made this but he can see that there was a formation engraved in it. The formation was very beautiful, all of it was inlaid with gold along with some other materials. The formation seemed to sparkle, and along with how the formation itself, the crystal became even more beautiful.

The crystal wasn’t very big, only the size of one’s palm. It might look small, but its function was very nice, it can help in regulating a person’s temperature, eliminate fatigue, as well as remove any strange odors in one’s body. It was a rare plaything.

Zhao Hai gently handed the crystal over to the eunuch and said, “This is the first time that I had met eunuch, so I was not prepared. I would like sir eunuch to accept this small plaything as a gift from me.”

The eunuch looked at the crystal in Zhao Hai’s hand. He was a person who was keen on noticing an item’s worth and he saw how extraordinary Zhao Hai’s crystal was. He immediately said, “The Count is too kind. I’m just a eunuch, it wouldn’t be proper for me to accept such a gift.”

Zhao Hai smiled faintly and said, “Sir eunuch is too polite. For His Majesty to trust you meant that you are absolutely worthy of  this small gift. The current weather is very cold, this little thing can keep Sir eunuch’s body temperature at a comfortable level. Sir eunuch would also be by his Majesty’s side all the time, this thing can also relieve fatigue. Additionally, this one can eliminate any odors in one’s body, even if it didn’t have much use, it should still be able to take care of the small nuances in Sir eunuch’s day to day living.”

The eunuch looked at Zhao Hai, the first two points wasn’t much of a problem for him. Just as Zhao Hai has suspected, the man was indeed an assassin, an 8th rank assassin. With his strength, the cold and heat wasn’t a problem, he doesn’t get tired easily as well. However, the last point of eliminating odors attracted him.

Eunuchs have this problem, because of their function, they didn’t have the advantages that a normal man might have, there were things that they can’t do. Moreover, they are easily prone to odors. Because of this, they rarely eat in the morning, they rarely drink water as well. Their tasks were stressful. One should know that if the King notices a strange smell in them, there was a high possibility of them being executed. If not, they would fall out of favor, and for them, falling out of favor was much worse than death.

Therefore, this issue of body odors was a very important issue to these eunuchs. Besides eating and drinking a little, they would also constantly change clothes. They would also sprinkle powders along with other methods in order to mask the smell of their bodies.

With Zhao Hai’s crystal, all of these issues would be solved. The eunuch became elated when he heard Zhao Hai point out the uses of the crystal.

Seeing the eunuch’s expression, Zhao Hai immediately handed the crystal over and said, “I ask Sir eunuch to receive it and give me face. Right, I’ve been very disrespectful, I still don’t know Sir eunuch’s name.”

The eunuch didn’t decline this time, he received Zhao Hai’s crystal and placed it near his chest. He immediately felt the benefits of the crustal, in his usually cold body, the temperature began to rise. The eunuch smiled and then turned to smile at Zhao Hai, “The Count is too kind, we don’t have any names. But in my generation, I’m number three. Later on, people began to call me Third Eunuch.”

Zhao Hai quickly said, “This count has met Third Eunuch. If mister has any needs in the future, please don’t hesitate to inform me.”

Third Eunuch laughed and said, “Very well, I will do so.”

Zhao Hai didn’t believe that this gift would completely buy Third Eunuch. He just wanted to earn his good favor, it might make things more convenient in the future.

Actually, with his current strength, he didn’t have to earn Third Eunuch’s favor. But Zhao Hai still did it in order to establish relations. He knew that he still couldn’t offend a lot of people. After all, nobles still held control of the matters in the continent. People who didn’t have any good relationships in this world wouldn’t be able to survive.

At this time, they have arrived outside the Imperial Palace great hall. This was the place where the Emperor handles his day to day politics. The place didn’t have an elegant name, it was just called Hall of Administration. Like the rest of the continent, it’s naming was a practical one.

The Hall of Administration had a few dozen steps in it. Third Eunuch asked Zhao Hai to wait at the bottom of the steps while he goes in and reports his arrival. Before long, Zhao Hai heard a voice announcing his presence, “Mister Zhao Hai has arrived!”

Zhao Hai patted his clothes to make them proper before ascending the steps. He was going to see the Emperor of the continent’s most powerful nation. If he said that he wasn’t anxious, then he would be lying.

Chapter 485: Matters in the Great Hall

When Zhao Hai arrived in front of the Hall of Administrations’ door, the eunuch announced a second time, “Zhao Hai Buda has arrived!”

Zhao Hai looked into the eyes of the eunuch and then took a deep breath before he entered the hall. Upon entering, Zhao Hai scanned the hall to see that there were a lot of people inside. He also saw people he was familiar with, the Crown Prince, the Second Prince, Charlie, Randolph, Jason’s Grandfather, as well as Nobles he became acquainted with during the banquets that he had attended the days before. Now these people were divided into two sitting columns. Zhao Hai already expected other people to be present, but he didn’t expect that it would be this much.

There was an elevated stage with a throne in the middle of the hall, a man can be seen sitting down on it. The throne was made of gold and silver, it was also inlaid with a lot of gems, and covered in a layer of animal leather. The throne looked very soft and comfortable.

The man wasn’t very tall, he looked very refined, maybe even delicate. His hair was faintly gray, his complexion was still quite rosy. He had a gold crown on his head and a staff in his hand. The staff wasn’t very long, it was only about 40 centimeters. The staff was made entirely of gold, its head was decorated with gigantic gemstones. This wasn’t a Magic Staff, but a scepter, an item that was a symbol of influence.

This man wore very magnificent and expensive looking clothes. Although he looked very refined, he also gave off a very imposing aura, enough to make a weaker man submit. The man just sat there, calmly looking at Zhao Hai. However, Zhao Hai felt pressure, this pressure came purely from the man’s body. This pressure wasn’t deliberately made to shake Zhao Hai, it was just the natural aura coming from the man’s body.

“This should be the Rosen Empire’s Emperor”, Zhao Hai mused inwardly. He immediately made a move and slowly walked towards the man, when he was five meters away, he performed a 90 degree bow to the man. He straightened his body and then said, “Zhao Hai Buda has seen His Majesty!”

Rosen Empire’s Emperor looked at Zhao Hai and then nodded, “You are Zhao Hai? Good, young man, very good. Were you present when the Robert Family used Antimagic Powder?”

Zhao Hai quickly responded, “Yes, Your Majesty. The Robert Family did use Antimagic Powder to attack me.”

The Emperor nodded, then said, “Are you really a Mage? How did you survive the Robert Family’s attack?”

Zhao Hai stared, then he thought that Randolph might have not told the Emperor about him being a Martial and Magic Dual Cultivator. Randolph also didn’t tell the Emperor that Zhao Hai can cast magic under the influence of Antimagic Powder, leaving Zhao Hai with a card in hand.

Thinking about this, Zhao Hai immediately said, “Replying to His Majesty’s question, this one isn’t only a Mage, I’m an 8th rank Warrior as well. Because of that, Antimagic Powder cannot suppress me.” Zhao Hai also didn’t reveal the fact that he was unaffected by the Antimagic Powder, he wanted to make this into his hidden ace. Compared to his ability as a Warrior, this matter was a better choice to conceal.

After hearing Zhao Hai, the people in the hall became shocked. They couldn’t help but whisper to each other. They already knew that Zhao Hai was an 8th rank Mage, but they didn’t expect that Zhao Hai was an 8th rank Warrior as well!

In other words, Zhao Hai was a Dual Cultivator of Magic and Battle Qi? However, in the history of the continent, Martial and Magic Dual Cultivators didn’t have much of a success. There were only a handful of people of people who can reach 6th rank, reaching 7th rank was the highest recorded instance.

But now, Zhao Hai revealed that he wasn’t only an 8th rank Mage, he was also an 8th rank Warrior, this was unbelievable. If Zhao Hai wasn’t in front of the Emperor right now, they would surely think that Zhao Hai was lying.

The Emperor was also somewhat surprised at Zhao Hai, then he nodded and said, “Good, young man, you’re very good. This Emperor has called you today for a small request. If you handle this matter well, you will be rewarded.”

Zhao Hai bowed and said, “For the benefit of His Majesty, I wouldn’t even need a reward to take action. I ask His Majesty to show me.”

The Emperor gave a satisfied nod and said, “This is about Engraved Ark that you have uncovered. I will not hide it from you, we already turned Robert Patriarch and Terry into advanced level undead in order to interrogate them. However, the matters that they knew were not many. They also mentioned that there should also be another member of Engraved Ark in their family. But as to who this member was, they didn’t know. Now that the Robert Family has been eliminated by you, the amount of corpses present is too much for our Dark Mages to turn into advanced level undead. Randolph told me that you can achieve it. Is that true?”

Zhao Hai nodded, “I can, Your Majesty. Rest Assured.”

The Emperor nodded and said, “Then can you do it inside this hall? Our country wants to see how different your Dark Magic is.”

Zhao Hai stared for a while before saying, “Your Majesty, turning these corpses into undead needed them to be present. If we do it inside this hall, it might contaminate Your Majesty’s sights. Moreover, I’m afraid that His Majesty might not like the way I use Magic.”

The Emperor didn’t seem to care, he shook his head and said, “No need to worry, just do it in this hall. Let this Emperor see for himself.”

Zhai Hai didn’t say anything else, he nodded and said, “Just as you wish, Your Majesty.”

The Emperor nodded, then he waved his hand. Third Eunuch, who was standing right by the Emperor’s side, took two steps forward and said loudly, “Take them in!” Then a buzzing sound was heard outside the hall before stretchers carrying bodies covered in white cloth entered.

These corpses were naturally processed. They didn’t have any unusual smell, but the sight of this row of corpses looked very unattractive.

The nobles inside the hall already knew that it was Zhao Hai who exterminated the Robert Family. But when they saw the bodies being carried in, they couldn’t help but exclaim about Zhao Hai’s ruthlessness, they whispered between each other.

The Emperor didn’t care, he turned his head to Zhao Hai and said, “You can begin.” Zhao Hai gave a bow before he took his Magic Staff out and muttered several incantations. Then a black gas appeared and covered the corpses inside the hall. When the black gas disappeared, all of the bodies were already standing. These people looked no different than when they were alive. If it weren’t for their pale complexion and lifeless eyes, people might even mistake them for live people.

Zhao Hai could just change these people into skeletons, but since he wanted to display his abilities, he deliberately made them into zombies. In Ark Continent, one didn’t need to be afraid if they had the strength. As long as you are strong, people would give you great importance. Conversely, if you are useless, nobody would look at you in the eyes.

When the people in the Great Hall looked at the undead, they couldn’t help but feel somewhat restless. In their minds, undead were generally either skeletons or rotting zombies. However, Zhao Hai’s zombies were in a pristine condition, they looked exactly just like a normal person. This wasn’t something that they had seen before.

After reviving the undead, Zhao Hai turned to the Emperor and said, “Your majesty, you can now ask them questions. I can assure you that they wouldn’t lie.”

The Emperor was also shocked by Zhao Hai’s undead, he looked at Zhao Hai and then said, “Alright, you go ask them. Just find out who the other member of Engraved Ark was.”

Zhao Hai nodded, then he immediately went to ask the group of undead. But unfortunately, the member of Engraved Ark wasn’t present among them. Zhao Hai didn’t say anything as he received these undead into his Space and then had another batch of corpses be sent in.

Zhao Hai remained in the hall as he turned groups upon groups of corpses into undead until he found out the other member of Engraved Ark. When he found out, Zhao Hai was surprised, the member of Engraved Ark turned out to be one of Robert Patriarch’s wives!

From the mouth of this member of Engraved Ark, Zhao Hai managed to get a few more information. The source of faith of the organization was truly the Demon God. Destroying the continent was their duty. All of the members of Engraved Ark almost never meet, they just communicate with each other using encrypted codes. Most importantly, none of these members knew each other’s identity. They don’t have any marks on their bodies. If one wanted to find out about anything regarding their identity, then it should be that each of their homes should have an idol of the Demon God!

This kind of information was truly useless for Zhao Hai. How many people were in the continent? How many noble families? They don’t have any obvious characteristics, just the fact that they have an idol of the Demon God in their homes. But who actually knew what the Demon God looked like? There were too many factors to consider, there was no way to find it.

However, even if they didn’t have a single good harvest, this member knew much more than Robert Patriarch and Terry. This organization has existed for more than a thousand years. In the very beginning, all of them were just people at the bottom of society. These people were oppressed by the nobility and found that there was no way to resist them. In the end, these people joined up and create the Engraved Ark, it was also at this point that they started to worship the Demon God.

Along with the transformation on the continent and the constant change of dynasties, the organization slowly gained power and influence and eventually became Great Nobles. The Robert Family was one of those families.

Also, even if there wasn’t a definite indication that one was a member of Engraved Ark, they were devilish in their hearts. They believed that the Demon God was a good killer and a ruthless person, therefore, the attitudes and temperaments of their members would generally be ruthless and sinister. All of these would naturally reflect on the overall outlook of their families, just like Robert Family’s Savage Wolf emblem.

Obtaining this information was a great help for the Rosen Empire. At the very least, they now have a heading, they can now somewhat decrease their scope of surveillance.

At this point, the nobles in the hall were now dreading Engraved Ark. This was because this organization’s threat to the continent was much higher than the Radiant Church. The Radiant Church only wanted to establish control, but Engraved Ark actually wanted their life!

Chapter 486: Reward

The Emperor was very satisfied with Zhao Hai’s performance. He had seen how other Dark Mages use Dark Magic. Seeing how Zhao Hai was so relaxed showed that Zhao Hai was strong.

Moreover, Zhao Hai or the Buda Clan’s Patriarch, was Calci Family’s son-in-law. He also heard that Zhao Hai had a good relationship with the Crook Family, he was also someone from Charlie’s side.

Because of these, the Emperor became very fond of Zhao Hai. Although he was an Aksu Empire noble, it didn’t matter. The Emperor wouldn’t care about his background as long as he is strong. It was also impossible for the Emperor to not know about the Buda Clan’s resentment towards the Aksu Empire. In his opinion, it was impossible for Zhao Hai to not hold a grudge. If he was able to pull Zhao Hai into the Rosen Empire, it would be good for the empire overall.

The Emperor was clear, Zhao Hai had offended the Radiant Church, he had also offended Aksu Empire’s Royal Clan. In this case, if Zhao Hai wanted to find a place to place his foundation, the Rosen Empire was the only choice, it was impossible to do so in other places.

Thinking about this, the Emperor felt assured that he can pull Zhao Hai over to the Empire. This was Rosen Empire’s standard of recruiting people. Regardless of their origin, as long as someone has talent, they would bring them to the Empire’s fold. This was the method that the Rosen Empire used to become the continent’s most powerful nation.

After Zhao Hai found the Engraved Ark member, the Emperor still had the bodies sent over to be turned into advanced undead. The Emperor was afraid of any fish that might slip through the net. Fortunately, there were no other members of Engraved Ark in the Robert Family.

After waiting for Zhao Hai to be done, the Emperor nodded, then he turned his head towards Third Eunuch. Third Eunuch immediately took two steps forward and declared, “Zhao Hai Buda, go forward and receive the decree.”

Zhao Hai stared, he immediately complied as he went forward and knelt on one knee. This was also a custom in Ark Continent. When a monarch rewards you, you shall kneel down on one knee upon accepting. This makes it seem like you really valued the reward.

When Zhao Hai knelt down, Third Eunuch immediately said loudly, “Zhao Hai Buda, you are a Noble with outstanding ability and excellent strength. Receive this title of First Class Marquis. The Crown has also bestowed Golden Island to Zhao Hai Buda as his perpetual fief. “

Zhao Hai immediately said, “I thank His Majesty for this reward. Zhao Hai Buda shall fully serve the Rosen Empire!”

Ark Continent’s rewarding process was very simple, Zhao Hai liked it very much. But what he didn’t expect was how comfortable the Emperor was in giving him the title of Marquis, moreover, he also gave him an island as a fief.

The Ark Continent’s ranking goes: Duke, Marquis, Count, Viscount, Baron, and then Knight. Knights can only be regarded as a false noble, with the lowest nobility rank being the Baron. The Duke, Marquis, Count, Viscount and Baron, these five ranks are the official ranks of nobility. Each titles are divided into three Classes with third class being the lowest and first class being the highest. Above a First Class Duke was the position of Grand Duke. A Grand Duke can establish his own Duchy. Above a Grand Duke were the Princes. Princes generally came from the Imperial Clan. A Prince’s power can only be dictated by the Emperor. If the Emperor doesn’t give a Prince any power, then they can only be a normal noble, he cannot do anything serious. Although, he technically held a higher status, his influence wasn’t as good as a Grand Duke.

Not only did Rosen Empire give Zhao Hai the title of First Class Marquis, he was also bestowed by a perpetual fief. This was a very good thing. Some Noble’s fiefs weren’t hereditary. If they want to keep their territory, they need to work hard. Only through this way would their lands stay in their hands. However, Zhao Hai’s was different, it was equivalent to the Buda Clan owning the territory.

However, Zhao Hai felt strange when he heard that his fief was Golden Island. This was because he hadn’t heard of this Golden Island before.

For a place to be called Golden Island, it would surely be a special one. Moreover, since it’s an island, it should certainly be at sea. But Zhao Hai had already stayed for quite some time in the seas of Rosen Empire, he had never heard about a Golden Island there, it was quite strange.

But since it was the Emperor’s reward, he had no other choice but to accept it and ask Randolph later.

Since Zhao Hai had accepted the reward, naturally he was now a noble of the Rosen Empire. Later on, when meets the Emperor, he wouldn’t need to bow so low.

After Zhao Hai received his reward, the Emperor looked at him and said, “Zhao Hai, you’re now a person of the Rosen Empire. I won’t interfere with your matter with Aksu Empire, but you must remember, no matter what you do, you cannot lose the face of Rosen Empire in Aksu Empire.”

When Zhao Hai heard this, he couldn’t help but stare. This was because the Emperor basically just told him that he was supporting him. This was something that was out of his expectations.

Zhao hai immediately bowed and said, “I thank His Majesty. This one will certainly not lose the face of Rosen Empire. His Majesty can feel relieved.”

The Emperor was satisfied, then he nodded and said, “Good, it’s good that you understand. Alright, today’s affairs are finished, everybody can go back.” The others immediately stood up and gave a salute to the Emperor before they asked to be excused.

Outside the hall, Randolph and Charlie approached Zhao Hai. After seeing the two of them, Zhao Hai gave a salute. Charlie smiled at him and said, “Good, you’ve now become a Marquis. Hahaha. If you have free time, go visit my mansion.” Zhao Hai nodded, then Charlie gave a nod before leaving.

Randolph looked at Charlie before he turned his head to Zhao Hai and said, “It looks like Charlie highly thinks of you. Also, it’s good that your title has now risen.”

Zhao Hai nodded, and then he looked around before he whispered, “Grandfather, this Golden Island, where is it? How come I never heard of it?”

Randolph looked around as well and then whispered, “Let’s talk about this back at the fort.” Looking at Randolph’s conduct, Zhao Hai understood that there may have been some secrets that he wasn’t allowed to ask publicly. He nodded and then headed back to the fort with Randolph.

When they arrived outside the Imperial Palace, Randolph and Zhao Hai rode their carriage and drove towards Dark Soldier Fort without saying a word. Before long, the two of them arrived at the fort.

Upon reaching their destination, Randolph immediately brought Zhao Hai to the lobby. Then he sent someone to call Smith and the others over. Zhao Hai looked at Randolph, he didn’t ask anything and just waited in the room for Smith and the others.

Before long, Smith and the others arrived, Zhao Hai sood up and gave them a salute. After the group sat down, Randolph opened his mouth and said, “Earlier, His Majesty just asked Little Hai to turn all of the Robert Family members into undead, then he asked them about Engraved Ark. Although we didn’t manage to get a lot of information, what we got wasn’t few either. His Majesty was happy with Zhao Hai’s performance that he gave him the title of First Class Marquis. He also bestowed Zhao Hai with Golden Island as his perpetual territory.”

Upon hearing Randolph’s words, everybody stared. Then they started whispering to each other in discussion. Zhao Hai was confused, being a First Class Marquis wasn’t something to be surprised about, was it because of Golden Island?

Seeing Zhao Hai’s confused expression, he seriously said, “Little Hai doesn’t know about Golden Island. Second, go tell Little Hai.”

Smith nodded and said, “Alright, Golden Island was once rich in gold. But even before the Rosen Empire has been established, all of its gold was mined up. Right now, the island doesn’t have any special products left, only the mining tunnels remained. Such an island isn’t very noteworthy. However, its position was extremely coveted. The island was placed in between Rosen Empire and Aksu Empire’s marine border. Because of this island, the two Empires often had frictions between them. Now, there was nobody who owned it. But since the island still had some freshwater, it became a Haven for pirates. Although it was like this currently, its importance to both empires didn’t decrease. If Rosen Empire obtains that island, they can construct a naval base there and threaten the Aksu Empire’s marine region. The opposite case was the same. Also, because this place previously produced gold, it had very good piers, it wouldn’t be a problem if a thousand huge boats were to dock there. The strategic value of this island is very big.”

Zhao Hai answered, “Is this the case? Does this mean that even if I got the fief from the Rosen Empire, the Aksu Empire can still declare it as theirs?”

Smith nodded and said, “Yes, like that. I think His Majesty gave you this land possibly because he wanted you to thoroughly break off your relations with the Aksu Empire.”

Randolph nodded and said, “Right, I also think that this is His Majesty’s intention. Still, I think that this would be a good opportunity for you. Golden Island’s location is extremely important. As long as you eliminate the pirate’s nest, you can slowly allow passing ships entry. You can also establish a market there, carrying out trades. I believe that it will be a goose that lays golden eggs.”

Zhao Hai excitedly nodded. Golden Island’s position was indeed good. For Zhao Hiai, this was fantastic. As long as he held this place, he was sure that he would profit a lot off of it. He can also take the things in the Space to there and sell them.

Then Smith looked at Zhao Hai and sighed, “Little Hai, don’t be celebrate prematurely. Occupying Golden Island wouldn’t be simple. There were pirate groups controlled by Great Nobles stationed there. The Imperial Clan’s looting fleet has a stronghold there as well. If you really want to take control of Golden Island, I’m afraid it wouldn’t be very easy.”

Zhao Hai smiled faintly and said, “It’s fine. I wouldn’t be offending them much. There are a lot of islands in the surroundings, they can just move. If they really want to go head on head with me, then let’s see if they have the capability.”

Randolph nodded and said, “Little Hai’s words are justified. Little Hai can even deal with millenium-old clans. Those who wanted to move against Little Hai need to have good courage. What I’m currently worried about was the Radiant Church.”

Smith and the others turned silent, they understood what Randolph was thinking. Zhao Hai has a grudge with the Radiant Church. With Golden Island being in the edge of Rosen Empire’s territory, an in addition to it being overseas, it would be difficult for the Rosen Empire to give him help.

Moreover, with this domain, Zhao Hai would build upon it, making it one of his foundations. The Radiant Church cannot cope with Zhao Hai in the past because they couldn’t find his location. This time, the Radiant Church naturally wouldn’t let him off.

Zhao Hai sneered and said, “I don’t worry about the Radiant Church. They couldn’t deal with me before, they couldn’t deal with me this time either. What I’m worried about is Engraved Ark. Me eliminating the Robert Family this time meant that their organization just lost a Great Family. Not only did I destroy their Great Clan, I’ve also exposed them to the continent. I’m quite worried about them since we have close to no understanding of their operations.”

Randolph nodded and said, “That’s true, we now have a good amount of understanding with regards to the Radiant Church. But this Engraved Ark, we had almost to know information about them.”

Zhao Hai nodded, then he turned to Randolph and said, “Grandfather, I think that the Calci Family would also need to be more careful. The Engraved Ark would surely take the clan into account this time. People from Engraved Ark are different from the Radiant Church. When the Radiant Church copes with us, they would need to find an excuse to act in the open. But the Engraved Ark can do almost about anything. This time, they used Antimagic Powder, who know what cards they will use the next time. Moreover, since they can research Antimagic Powder, they surely have other types of concoctions in their hands. We should all be careful from now on.”

Randolph agreed, “This matter is surely thorny. Our Clan is a Mage Clan, just by using Antimagic Powder, they managed to place us in a difficult position.” At this time, Smith and the others were frowning.

Zhao Hai opened his mouth, “Grandfather, I think we should take extreme care for the important figures in the family. It is also better for the family to invest more into Warriors. In the meantime, I’ll head back and see whether my side can develop an antidote against the Antimagic Powder. If we can produce one, our days would become easier. If it’s impossible to make it, then the family can only increase their security even more.”

Randolph stared when he heard Zhao Hai. With an elated face he said, “Little Hai, is that true? Do you have a Potion Master?”

Zhao Hai nodded and said, “Two Potion Masters, they’re very good, but we really lack medicinal plants at this moment. I’ll need to ask Grandpa for help, I need a lot plants, the more advanced, the better. I can accept seeds as well, I can slowly grow them.”

Chapter 487: Appearing Aggressive

Smith smiled when he heard Zhao Hai, he turned to Randolph and said, “Father, Little Hai used to tell me this, but since it was winter, there weren’t really good plants available. However, it seems like we need to go all out in helping Little Hai to acquire various plants. If Little Hai develops the antidote, then it would really be very good for us.”

Randolph nodded and said, “Alright, go send the orders. Have the entire clan seek for strange plants, the more the better. Right Little Hai, do you need Magic Beasts as well?”

Zhao Hai nodded and said, “I do. Magic Beasts can also be used for making medicine. The more the better.”

Randolph gave a nod, then he looked at the people in the room and said, “Did you listen carefully? Fully coordinate with Little Hai.” Those present didn’t dare to oppose it, they immediately agreed. All of them knew that this matter shouldn’t be neglected, it was very important for the family.

Zhao Hai looked at the others and sighed in relief. Then he turned his hand and retrieved a large bottle from the Space. This bottle had enough volume to contain ten jins of water. It was made of glass and was gotten from one of the Robert Family’s stores.

Naturally this bottle wasn’t special, its contents were. Randolph and the others looked at Zhao Hai, they don’t know why Zhao Hai retrieved such a big bottle.

Zhao Hai carefully placed the bottle beside Randolph and said, “Grandfather, the family should distribute this water to everyone. If they encounter any accidents or get poisoned, drinking this water will be very useful.”

Randolph looked confused at Zhao Hai, “What is inside this bottle? Is it potion?”

Zhao Hai shook his head and said, “The liquid in this bottle isn’t a potion. It is much more effective compared to a potion, this is Life Liquid!”[1]

Life Liquid! When they heard Zhao Hai say this, all of the people present breathed a cold air. Life Liquid was something very useful, no matter how rich you are, you might not be able to get it.

Randolph stared at the bottle for quite some time, then he turned his head to Zhao Hai and said, “Little Hai, this, is this really Life Liquid?”

Zhao Hai nodded and said, “Yes, I’ve obtained this from a 9th rank expert of the Radiant Church. At the time, the 9th rank was cooperating with the Fighting Bulls to deal with the Herculean Bulls. When he was killed by me, I obtained this Life Liquid. I asked the person where he got it, he said that it was given to him.”

Randolph nodded, he also got something from Zhao Hai’s words. He frowned and said, “The Radiant Church are meddling with the Beastmen?”

Zhao Hai nodded, then he told Randolph about what happened the last time he was in the Prairie. He also introduced his status as a Prince of the Cow-headed race.

Randolph was surprised at Zhao Hai. He didn’t think that Zhao Hai would have such a status. Beastmen don’t trust humans, it was surprising to know that Zhao Hai was actually a Beastman Prince.

But then he immediately thought about the Radiant Church, he hesitated for a moment before he turned to Zhao Hai and said, “Little Hai, since you now have some sort of status in the Beastman Prairie, you should play attention to the the movements of the Radiant Church in the Prairie. Know what they are planning to do. And if you can make the Beastmen turn on them, then that would be fantastic.”

ZHao Hai smiled faintly and said, “Grandfather can feel relieved, I’ve already figured out the temperament of the Beastmen. It would be easy for the Beastmen to deal with the Radiant Church. There aren’t any radiant Church believers in the Prairie, as long as they are members of the Radiant Church, the Beastmen wouldn’t be able to trust them.”

Randolph nodded and said, “I’ll accept your Life Liquid, it’s very useful for the current situation. Right, since you’ve given this to the family, the family wouldn’t be ungrateful. Now that you have the Golden Island as a territory, the family can provide you with a fleet to help manage it.”

Zhao Hai declined and said “Grandfather, doesn’t need to trouble himself. I really don’t need to deal with the pirates in Golden Island. Making the family move would be very troublesome. This Life Liquid isn’t very important to me, I also have some left on me.”

Randolph nodded, then he looked at Zhao Hai in appreciation. At this moment, he felt that Zhao Hai looked more pleasing to the eyes. He was a decent human being, a good leader, willing to help the Calci Family, even giving them Life Liquid. At this point, Zhao Hai was much better than the other members of the Calci Family.

Randolph looked at the other members of the family and said, “Alright, we have a lot of things to do. All of you know your assignments, go back and deal with the. Remember to not make any mistakes.”

The others nodded, then Randolph made them disperse. Smith went with Zhao Hai to Rustling Tree Courtyard. The two sat on the living room, then Smith turned to Zhao Hai and said, “Little Hai, how do you plan to handle Golden Island’s situation? I think you should be careful about this. Otherwise, it wouldn’t be only the Aksu Empire that would come after you, all of the noble controlled pirates would be going after you as well. You may even aggravate the situation even more.”

Zhao Hai nodded, he understood what Smith meant. But now that he knew the location of Golden Island as well as knowing about how lawless the place was. It would be a pity if he doesn’t make use of the pirates.

Of these pirates, it would be impossible for all of them to be affiliated to a Great Clan. Those who had connections could just sell their loot over to those Great Clans. However, for those who didn’t have any connections, they can only find a middleman and sell their loot at a much lower price.

There was a huge business opportunity here. Zhao Hai’s idea was to turn Golden Island into a free port. Pirates can trade on the island, but they have to pay a certain amount of tax. Merchants can trade here as well, and naturally, they would also be taxed.

Zhao Hai wanted Golden Island to be a place for Merchants, Pirates, and other influences to trade, like some sort of black market. He will place the tax here at a very low level. Pirates can also take refuge in the island. If he manages to achieve this goal, the island wouldn’t only be a goose that laid golden eggs, it would in itself turn into a golden goose.

When Smith asked him this question, Zhao Hai didn’t immediately tell him of his plans to make the island a free port, he just said, “It’s not difficult to subdue the island. Although its location was very special, it wasn’t irreplaceable for the pirates. In addition to the reputation that I have gained, those who would dare to attack me shouldn’t be true pirates. In the end, if anyone really wishes to challenge me, then I won’t be polite to them.”

Smith knit his brows, he really didn’t want Zhao Hai to have any conflicts with Great Nobles. If the situation goes to south, things wouldn’t be good for Zhao Hai.

Looking at Smith’s expression, Zhao Hai smiled faintly and said, “Uncle, rest assured, the solution for Golden Island is nothing more than a two-step process. First step is to not attack them, make it known to them that we mean well while at the same time making them respect us. Second step is to then offer them benefits. This point is actually something that I needed uncle’s help with. I’m preparing to turn the island into a free trading harbor. No matter pirate or merchant, all of them can come to the island and trade. What does uncle think?”

Smith stared for a moment before his eyes lit up. He was a Merchant and he naturally understood what Zhao Hai was planning to do. If Zhao Hai really managed to accomplish this, then the yearly income of Golden Island would be comparable to Sky Water City, if not more.

However, he soon recovered from his thoughts as he frowned, “This is a really good idea. But if we really do as you said, then would Merchants really dare to go to Golden Island? Wouldn’t they be afraid to get robbed?”

Zhao Hao smiled faintly and said, “This is simple, I can just issue a rule disallowing violence inside Golden Island. I shall also make sure that the rule would get applied at a thousand li radius around the island’s waters. Those who dared violate this rule would get eliminated. With this, nobody should act unreasonably. What does uncle think about this?”

When Smith heard Zhao Hai, he couldn’t help but look into Zhao Hai’s eyes. Zhao Hai was appearing very aggressive these past few days. Hearing him say that he would eliminate those who would dare violate his rule in a thousand li radius of the island seemed like he was also expressing his aggression at this time.

In the past, only Great Clans dared to speak such words, but now, Zhao Hai was also speaking it. This was undoubtedly due to the change in Zhao Hai’s status.

Moreover, Smith was certain that if Zhao Hai completes this matter, his Golden Island would surely become another Sky Water City, another huge trading harbor.

At this point, Smith was admiring Zhao Hai. He knew about the Buda Clan vanishing, but in just one year, they were able to reach this height. They can now appear on the continent, this was all because of their current strength, it was also because of Zhao Hai.

For a clan to survive, strength was an indispensable resource. However, strength alone was not enough, the clan also needed a smart leader and good direction. Zhao Hai’s leadership was already well proven. Having such a head, the Buda Clan would be able to overturn their past situation and became one of the powerful Clans of the Continent, the only thing that they require was time.

When Smith knew about Zhao Hai’s plan for Golden Island, he understood that the island would have a lot of work needed to be done. There were things that needed help, and Smith wanted to provide it.

* * *

I keep forgetting what this is called

Chapter 488: Walking in Circles is Hereditary

Smith knew that although the Calci Family has a lot of relationships with other clans, they had nobody who could shared the hardships of their family. This was one of the Calci Family’s disadvantages.

Now, the Buda Clan appeared, a Clan that has a potential to become a Great Clan. If at this time, the Calci Family gives the Buda Clan a helping hand, the Buda Clan would surely become the Calci Family’s true friend in the future. With the two clans helping each other, both of them can become the strongest clans in the continent.

After thinking all of these through, Smith nodded and said, “Alright, Little Hai, I won’t bother you with Golden Island. However, I’ll go inform father about this. If you need any help, immediately tell us, we will certainly support you. I believe father wouldn’t oppose to it.”

Zhao Hai nodded and then with a serious voice he said, “Uncle, I have a matter to ask for your opinion. Today, Jason looked for me and sent a message telling me that their Crook family would want to have an Eternal Alliance with my Buda Clan.”

Smith became surprised when he heard Zhao Hai, he knew what being in an Eternal Alliance meant. He didn’t expect the Crook Family to suddenly propose being an Eternal Ally to the Buda Clan.

When he recovered, Smith’s mind suddenly sprang into action. He knows that the Crook Family wasn’t simple. A few years ago, they were just an ordinary Great Clan, but now, they already had reached the levels of millenium-old clans. What does this mean? This indicated that the Crook Family’s head had the ability, and was very insightful as well.

In this case, for the Crook Family to make an Eternal Alliance with the Buda Clan only meant one thing, they were very optimistic about the future of the Buda Clan. Because of this, they wanted to reach out to the Buda Clan before they reach their full potential. Later on, when the Buda Clan completely grows into being a Great Clan, they would gain a very strong ally!

Good plan! Smith had to recognize the Crook Family’s plan. It was pure benefit without disadvantages. At the least, when the Buda Clan doesn’t reach the Crook Family’s level, Zhao Hai would still be allied with them, bringing good benefits to the Buda Clan.

Smith walked several steps on the ground, he had thought through all the parts of it. Then he turned to Zhao Hai and said, “This is a very good thing for the Buda Clan. You should accept, how about going to the Crook Family tomorrow?”

Zhao Hai smiled and said, “I won’t only go to the Crook Family, I’ll need to go see Charlie tomorrow as well. Haha, I’m quite busy tomorrow.”

Smith looked at Zhao Hai and laughed, “Right, it’s also time to visit Charlie. Alright, you get busy, I have something to discuss with father.” Zhao Hai nodded and then turned towards his own residence before going to the Space. He wanted to see what Smith would tell Randolph.

Zhao Hai didn’t believe that Smith and Randolph would harm him. He had given Randolph the Life Liquid, giving Randolph a good impression of him. Zhao Hai believed that Randolph wouldn’t move him, he believed that Randolph would even attach great importance to him.

When Zhao Hai arrived at the Space, he immediately entered the villa. At this time, Laura and the others were reorganizing the documents. They were sorting through documents that might be helpful to the Buda Clan.

Seeing that Laura and the others were very enthusiastic in working, Zhao Hai became happy. Then he went to the living room and turned the monitor on, showing the scene inside Randolph’s study.

Randolph’s study was very big, this was where he handles his things, and also where he meets the managers of the Calci Family. Because of this, his interior decoration was very good. Although it couldn’t compare to Evan’s study, it wasn’t that much worse. After all, Dark Soldier Fort wasn’t as big as a Grand Duke’s mansion.

When Smith arrived at Randolph’s study, they sat down and drank some tea. Apparently, they still weren’t talking about Zhao Hai’s matter.

When Randolph saw that Smith came to see him, he knew that it surely has something to do with Zhao Hai. Therefore, he didn’t worry too much, so he first sent someone to get them some tea as he and Smith sat and chatted.

At this point, Smith held Randolph’s favor. If Smith didn’t insist, it would be impossible for Zhao Hai to be married into the Calci Family. If their family actually became Zhao Hai’s enemy, he wouldn’t be able to imagine the consequences.

Zhao Hai getting married to the Calci Family brought great benefits to them, and this was Smith’s doing. Because of this, Randolph placed great importance to Smith.

Randolph drank some tea and sighed, “This time’s incident was really breathtaking. Who would’ve thought that an ordinary attack can lead to so many things. If it weren’t for Little Hai, our Calci Family would have surely  ended.”

Smith nodded and said, “Right, nobody thought that there would actually be a hidden snake in the continent. This Engraved Ark organization is too dangerous. Right, Father, what can you say about Little Hai’s Antimagic Powder antidote? Do you think he’ll succeed?”

Randolph sighed and said, “I hope that he can succeed, but it seems like it wouldn’t be very easy. From the time when Antimagic Powder first appeared, people had only found ways to suppress it, not make an antidote. The powder’s original recipe was destroyed as well, with no concrete source being present. This will bring a lot of trouble to Little Hai. You need to figure out the ingredients of a certain drug first before looking for ways to make its antidote. However, I still think that Little Hai’s approach is correct. Even though the continent was now aware of Engraved Ark, the only source we got about them came solely from the Robert Family. Now that the method to make Antimagic Powder has disappeared, making its cure much more difficult to achieve, what do you think will the Mages of the continent think when Little Hai manages to make an antidote?”

It would lead to great benefits! Randolph meant that when Zhao Hai manages to make the antidote for Antimagic Powder, his reputation among the Mages would surely skyrocket. As long as he succeeds in making one, the respect that he would gain from the Mage community would surely be colossal. And at this time, the Calci Family would be profiting from it as well.

Both Smith and Zhao Hai hadn’t thought about this before. Now that he was reminded by Randolph’s words, Smith found it hard to sit still. However, he was currently in front of Randolph, so he was embarrassed to walk around in a circle. Therefore, he can only take his teacup and kept turning it around.

After some time while looking at the ground, Smith looked at Randolph and said, “Father, if Little Hai succeeds, the rise of the Buda Clan would take zero effort.”

Randolph nodded and said, “So now, we should give Little Hai our full support. If Little Hai succeeds, the Buda Clan would gain great benefits, but our Calci Family would profit off of it as well. Little Hai doesn’t need our help in dealing with Golden Island, but as long as Little Hai needs our help for something else, we must fully support him. Make sure to remember this.”

Smith couldn’t help but smile when he heard Randolph, then he turned to Randolph and said, “Father, I also came her today for something else. This has a connection to the thing you said about fully supporting Little Hai. This is an important one.”

Randolph looked at him and said, “What is it?”

Smith smiled and said, “Just earlier, Little Hai told me that Jason came to look for him and delivered a message from his family. The Crook Family sent a message telling Zhao Hai that they wanted to form an Eternal Alliance with the Buda Clan, making their families eternal allies.”

When he heard about this, Randolph couldn’t help but stand up and walked around in circles. Smith looked at Randolph,thinking about the matter made him smile. He didn’t think that walking in circles was actually hereditary.

After who knows how many circles, Randolph stopped. He turned his head to Smith and said, “Did Little Hai personally tell you this? This isn’t a mistake?”

Smith nodded and said, “It’s absolutely real. Father should know that Little Hai doesn’t say these kinds of things easily. And since he told me, it should be true.”

Randolph nodded and said, “The Crook Family is good. Their vision is really good. We really need to completely support Little Hai. If Little Hai became eternal allies of the Crook Family, it would also be good for us.”

Smith nodded and then said, “Father, there’s another thing. Little Hai told me that he wants to turn Golden Island into a free trading harbor. Pirates and Merchants would be able to trade freely in the island, he only needs to collect some taxes. Moreover, he shall also make a rule forbidding violence in a 1000 li radius outside the island. If this succeeds, then the Buda Clan would surely have great gains.”

Randolph nodded and said, “It’s a good idea, if it becomes successful, Little Hai wouldn’t be worrying about money anymore. However, its early stages would be difficult, he would need enough naval might to shake those people. We shall fully support Little Hai in this matter. But it looks like Little Hai didn’t need our support in this. However, you should still go and find some little matters where we can insert ourselves. Also, there’s another point, don’t mix in sand.”

‘Mixing sand’ was a type of slang. Randolph used it here to tell Smith that they shouldn’t send in some spies towards Zhao Hai’s camp. For a Great Clan like the Calci Family, this was something that was rarely seen.

Smith knitted his brows, then after some time he said, “Father, if we do that, wouldn’t some people in the clan object? Seeing Third Uncle’s stance, it seems like they want to control Little Hai.”

Chapter 489: Family Greeting

“Stupid!” Randolph said after he heard Smith. “Don’t listen to them. They’re short-sighted, who knows how many people outside the Calci Family died with their tricks.”

When Randolph talked about this, he stopped for a moment and then took a deep breath before continuing, “Second, remember this. When you become a Patriarch of a Great Clan, there are some moments where you want to insist your own thoughts, no matter how unordinary they may be. As long as it brings benefits the clan, then we must do it. Even if it fails, we, that Calci Family can still afford to lose some. If we become afraid and don’t dare to do anything, then our position of Patriarch might as well be a decoration.”

When Smith heard Randolph, he nodded understandingly. At the same time, his eyes turned bright. Why did Randolph tell him this? Smith’s mind couldn’t help but think of all the implications.

Randolph looked at Smith, he smiled then said, “What is Little Hai’s status right now? He’s the head of the Buda Clan, he has formidable strength and can command ten 9th rank experts. Do you think that kind people can control him? I would think they’re crazy if they actually believed that they can take control of Little Hai. And even if we control Little Hai, what would it give the Calci Family? Little Hai is so strong that his addition is enough to cause instability in the Clan. What the Calci Family needs right now aren’t 9th rank experts. What we need is a strong ally. If the Buda Clan becomes the strongest Clan in the continent, then it would be very good for us. With that in mind, we might as well support Little Hai, we can remove some roadblocks from the Buda Clan’s road to greatness. This will not only allow us to gain a strong ally, it would also leave a good impression on Little Hai. When the time comes, he will certainly help the Calci Family become greater.”

Smith nodded, “Yes father. I understand, you don’t need to worry. Right, father, if Little Hai’s plan on Golden Island succeeds, will it affect our Sky Water City?”

Randolph smiled faintly and said, “It shouldn’t affect it. Even if it brings affects to Sky Water City, it would be good things. If he does well, then the products flowing through there would be pirated goods, so it would surely be cheap. Merchants would go there, buy the goods, and then resell them in Sky Water City. Pirates wouldn’t dare come to Sky Water City, but Merchants would. Golden Island will be the hub where pirates discharge their inventories. In the end, it would be a very good thing for Sky Water City.”

Smith nodded, “After Little Hai goes to the Crook Family, he would head to Charlie’s mansion. What do you say about Prince’s Charlie’s intentions?”

Randolph smiled faintly and said, “What can Prince Charlie do, Zhao Hai is his man, and His Majesty the Emperor know it. His Majesty rewarding Zhao Hai was equal to making Charlie’s influence increase. Naturally, Charlie would be glad. It seems like Charlie has a greater chance of mounting the imperial throne right now. But we still need to hold ourselves back and refrain from interfering, we should maintain our Clan’s passive stance.”

Smith nodded, “Rest assured, I know what to do. I will not participate in Little Hai’s matters.” Randolph nodded as well.

After seeing this scene, Zhao Hai decided to stop spying at them anymore. He knew that he now had the full support of the Calci Family . For the Buda Clan, this point was very important.

Zhao Hai let out a long sigh and sat still in the living room. The recent developments were extremely good. Not only did he obtain the title of Marquis, he also obtained the full support of the Calci Family as well as gaining the Crook Family as an Eternal Ally. at this point, he has now unfolded his own web of relationships in Rosen Empire. This web might still be immature, but when the Buda Clan slowly gains strength, this web would get more and more dense and sturdy.

After having rested for a while, Zhao Hai called the Robert Family undead. He wanted to ask them about other matters, for example, their Battle Qi Techniques and so on.

Although the Buda Clan had the Wild Dragon Battle Qi manual, this Battle Qi doesn’t suit everyone. So Zhao Hai wanted to look at the Battle Qi techniques of other clans. Even if he couldn’t use them, he can have these techniques provided to the schools to have the children study. This was one of the most fundamental things that millenium-old families do.

This time, the most precious thing that he acquired from the Robert Family wasn’t money. But instead, it was the Robert Family’s internal library.

There were a lot of books circulating in Ark Continent, but the genuinely useful books were all kept within the internal libraries of Great Clans, commoners were unable to see them.

With the Robert Family’s standing in Rosen Empire, it was certain that they had their own internal library. This library contained not only the materials of the Robert Family, it also had a lot of manuals for Battle Qi and Magic. These things were very important for Zhao Hai.

Another thing that made Zhao Hai ecstatic was the fact that there were some notes paired with these manuals. These notes were carefully kept in wooden crates and looked more expensive than those books.

 After Zhao Hai saw these notes, Zhao Hai knew why the Robert Family placed these things in a secure location. This was because these writings were actually cultivation notes of their 9th rank experts!

Cultivation notes of 9th rank experts were very precious things. For Zhao Hai, these might not be important, but for Green and the others, this was an absolute treasure.

Green, Merine, and Kun were all at the peak of 8th rank, they only need a single nudge to reach 9th. For them, these  notes would give them crucial insights that they might be able to use in advancing.

Zhao Hai had now understood why these Great Clans could get 9th ranks easily while general noble clans would still have difficulties. Those common Nobles surely lacked or had little amounts of cultivation notes.

As for those cultivation techniques, Zhao Hai naturally wouldn’t remember them. He had the Robert Family undead write those down. After all, they were advanced undead, writing wasn’t a problem for them.

While Zhao Hai was thinking about all of these, Zhao Hai summoned all the other undeads that he had and made them write their cultivation methods down. They had nothing else to do anyway, they weren’t very needed in fights, so they might as well go and write down their techniques. In the future, these manuals would surely be important for the Buda Clan’s development.

While Zhao Hai’s day went smoothly, the entire Ark Continent was in a storm. The appearance of Engraved Ark, the Antimagic Powder, the extermination of the Robert Family, Zhao Hai’s title of Marquis and his bestowment of Golden Island made the population go into unrest.

Engraved Ark and Antimagic Powder did not have a huge effect on the common folk and was only an enormous matter for the Mages and major influences in the continent.

However, the ownership of Golden Island made the every person go alert. Golden Island was well known among Nobles and commoners.[1]

Golden Island was a sensitive matter between the Rosen and Aksu Empires because there weren’t any owners of the island in the past.

And now, a claimant of the island appeared. Moreover, the identity of the new owner was a very interesting matter. The Buda Clan was a family that came from Aksu Empire, however, Golden Island was bestowed onto them by the Rosen Empire. This made the continent look at the situation in interest.

Rosen Empire’s bestowment was very thought provoking. The relationship between the Buda Clan and the Aksu Empire was well known among the people of the continent. The Buda Clan was supposed to be finished, but they surprisingly reappeared and was on their way to becoming one of most powerful clan in the continent.

When the Rosen Empire gave Golden Island to Zhao Hai as his fief, the people immediately thought of its ramifications.

The Aksu Empire took a stand immediately, declaring their disapproval of the Rosen Empire’s decision. Moreover, they also insisted on their ownership of Golden Island. If Rosen Empire really asserts their influence on the island, the Aksu Empire wouldn’t be able to guarantee peace.

This was without a doubt a threat. They were certainly saying that if Rosen Empire doesn’t take their bestowment back, then the two empires might get into war.

However, Aksu Empire didn’t say anything about Zhao Hai. His title and territory in their empire was made under the authentication of the nations of the continent as well as the Radiant Church, it was irrevocable. Because of this, the Aksu Empire cannot do anything about Zhao Hai at this time.

But all of these commotions were nothing in Zhao Hai’s view. In his mind, Golden Island was already his. Before, he doesn’t dare occupy any location because he was still not part of Rosen Empire, it would be equal to offending two empires. Now, if he wanted to fight for Golden Island, he can only offend one of them, this made him unafraid to go forward.

Zhao Hai didn’t have a favorable impression of Aksu Empire. What they did to the Buda Clan was so terrible that Zhao Hai didn’t regard himself as a person of the Aksu Empire anymore. He was now a person of the Black Wasteland, he already considered the place to be his kingdom. Because of this, offending Aksu Empire was not a psychological burden to him.

In the evening, Zhao Hai went to the Space in order to meet Green and the others and tell them todays matters, his new title and new fief.

Green and others didn’t oppose to Zhao Hai’s decision since they didn’t have a favorable impression of the Aksu Empire either. Now that Zhao Hai’s title in Aksu Empire was lower than Rosen Empire, Green and the others can now claim that they are people of the Rosen Empire. In the end, they were all natives of the Ark Continent, the only thing that matters to all of them were the titles that they held. But this wasn’t the case in Zhao Hai’s mind, for him, strength was the most important thing, nobility was less important.

Green and the others agreed to Zhao Hai’s procedures. For them, it didn’t matter that Golden Island was a goose that lays golden eggs, what mattered was the fact that the Buda Clan has achieved another domain.

After the group discussed this matter, Zhao Hai gave the notes to Green and the others. When the group saw these notes, they immediately acted as though they just had received a treasure. They didn’t leave the Space, the just went to their own rooms and proceeded to read.

The environment of the Space was good, it was really suited for cultivation. Because of this, they didn’t want to leave. And since there aren’t a lot matters left to take care back at Iron Mountain Fort, they chose to close up for several days inside.

After resting the entire evening inside the Space as well as having his morning breakfast, Zhao Hai boarded his carriage and headed towards the Crook Family.

Zhao Hai’s arrival at the Crook Family wasn’t the same as last time where it was only Jason who came to receive him. This time, along with Jason’s grandfather, the senior members of the Crook Family was waiting for him in the entrance. For Zhao Hai, this was a very good respect for his face.

Zhao Hai didn’t bring too many people today, only Shue and Shun. Laura and the others were still organizing the documents inside the Space. With the quantity of books that they acquired, a day or two wasn’t enough to organize it.

Zhao Hai was still inside the carriage when he saw the Crook Family’s arrangement. He didn’t think that the Crook family would mobilize these people to meet him. When the carriage stopped, he immediately got down and went to Jason’s grandfather and said, “Grandfather, why did so many people come out to meet me? This is too much.”

When Jason’s Grandfather heard what Zhao Hai said, he couldn’t help but show a smile on his face. Then he gave Zhao Hai a salute and said, “Crook Family Patriarch, Jesse Crook, has seen Patriarch Zhao Hai Buda.”

Zhao Hai couldn’t help but stare at Jesse, then he immediately understood what he was doing. Zhao Hai quickly returned a salute and said, “Zhao Hai Buda has seen Patriarch Jesse!”

After the two parties offered their greetings, Jesse introduced Zhao Hai to the people from his family. Jason’s father was named Ron. While Zhao Hai personally remembered Jesse and Ron’s names, he didn’t do so for the other members of the family, he just had Cai’er record their names and have him be reminded later.

When he finished introducing the people present, Jesse then turned to Zhao Hai and laughed, “Little Hai, welcome to our home. Also, it has already been several days since God’s Grace Day, I’m offended that it took you this long to visit.”

Hearing Jesse this time, Zhao Hai knew that when he was introducing the family members, he was acting officially as the Crook Family’s Patriarch. This time, he was acting as Zhao Hai’s friend, thus, explaining his current change of tone.

Zhao Hai naturally preferred this tone of speech, he immediately smiled and said, “I really have too many things to take care of. I attended your banquet a few days ago, but grandfather has a lot to manage and wasn’t able to participate, so we didn’t have the opportunity to meet.”

Jesse laughed and said, “Alright, I’ll accept that. However, you have to accompany me to drink today. Right, let’s go in and take a seat.”

Then, Jesse led Zhao Hai to enter the fort and sat down inside the lobby. While they were walking, Zhao Hai noticed how powerful Jesse was as a Patriarch. The other Crook Family members were walking behind him and didn’t even have a lot of chances to speak. Jesse seemed to have full control of the family. However, Zhao Hai can also see that Jesse was open to the opinions of his family members. When it came to decisions, he was too influential that all of his choices went unopposed and final.

* * *

Zhao Hai you noob.

Chapter 490: Two Identities

The Crook Family’s lobby was relatively similar to the Calci Family’s. Although Jesse’s influence in the family was unprecedentedly high, the other members of the family still held their own power. If they united, Jesse wouldn’t have any choice but to surrender. But in addition to Jesse’s influence, his skill and wit was also good, drawing support from his family members. Because of all of these support, Jesse’s word carried heavy power, however, he was still polite to those who supported him.

After having sat down on the lobby, Jesse didn’t become polite as he looked at Zhao Hai and said, “Little Hai, I have a few things to say first. In my mind, you now have two identities. The first one is the Patriarch of the Buda Clan, and the other one is Jason’s friend. With your first identity, you’ll be my equal, in the other, I’m your elder. Which identity would you use today?”

Zhao Hai smiled faintly and said, “Grandfather, of course I’ll talk to you as Jason’s friend. I can only be the Patriarch of the Buda Clan in public. Privately, I’m Jason’s friend. You’re Jason’s Grandfather so you are naturally my elder. I will be speaking to you as a junior.”

Jesse looked at Zhao Hai, he was waiting for this response. When Zhao Hai said it, he was certain about how this man carried great importance for sentiment. Such a man was worthy of the Crook Family’s full support, of being their ally.

Upon hearing Zhao Hai, Jesse couldn’t’ help but laugh and said, “Alright, Little Hai, since you’ll treat me as an elder, I won’t be polite. I hope that the Buda Clan and the Crook Family can have an Eternal Alliance, becoming allies forever. I don’t know if Little Hai can agree?”

Zhao Hai smiled and said, “Naturally I agree. But from the current matter, I think that the Crook Family would suffer a loss.”

Jesse laughed and said, “Even if the Crook Family suffers some losses, it wouldn’t be for long. Alright, since this matter has been decided, we’ll go announce it in two days. Right, Little Hai, how about your new fief? Will you claim it? Or you’ll just leave it alone?”

Zhao Hai smiled faintly and said, “Naturally, I’ll claim it. If I don’t, then wouldn’t that be a waste?”

Jesse frowned, “Little Hai, the situation with Golden Island isn’t simple. If you really want to claim it, it would be very difficult. Moreover, it might even lead to a war between two nations.”

Zhao Hao coldly snorted and said, “War? I don’t think so. If the Aksu Empire really wants to contend for Golden Island with me, we’ll have to see if they have the ability. Rest assured, the Calci Family will fully support me, and if the Crook Family support me as well, the Aksu Empire wouldn’t have any choice other than recognize my claim over Golden Island. Grandfather, don’t forget, I’m still a noble from the Aksu Empire. If necessary, I can use this status as a leverage against them.”

Jesse stared, then he immediately understood Zhao Hai. Even if Zhao Hai did have a stiff relationship with the Aksu Empire, he still had his title, he just cannot be attacked. In the end, his identity in Aksu Empire was still very useful.

Jesse nodded and said, “What would you plan to to do after securing Golden Island? You cannot mine gold from there anymore.”

Zhao Hai smiled, “I haven’t thought about this yet. I’m still thinking about how to claim it.”

But Jesse was an old fox, he knew that Zhao Hai wasn’t telling the truth from what he saw. He knew that Zhao Hai already had a clear idea but just didn’t want to reveal it at this time.

Jesse didn’t question him and just smiled and said, “Alright, today’s matter ends here. Everyone can disperse. Little Hai, accompany us to drink a few cups!”

Zhao Hai bitterly smiled and said, “Grandfather, I’m preparing to visit the Third Prince this afternoon. Can we not drink today?”

Jesse doesn’t care, he stared at Zhao Hai with one eye and said, “No need to waste your breath, you’re drinking with us today. What’s there to be afraid of? When you visit the Third Prince later, the least he could do is reprimand you for being incompetent.” When he heard Jesse, Zhao Hai couldn’t help but smile bitterly.

At noon, Jesse’s group and Zhao Hai drunk so much liquor that Zhao Hai’s mind began to turn dizzy. Jesse wouldn’t be satisfied if they he don’t drink until he collapses, Zhao Hai had no other choice but to keep up.

But Zhao Hai still went to Charlie, he didn’t want to leave Charlie disappointed. When Zhao Hai left the fort, his appearance almost couldn’t be recognized. However, he immediately drank Life Liquid and recovered.

Megan felt very amused by this. The Calci Family treated Life Liquid as though it was a treasure while Zhao Hai just uses it to sober up. If the family knew about this, then it was certain that Randolph would kill Zhao Hai on the spot.

In Charlie’s mansion, the Third Prince was waiting for Zhao Hai in his front door. The two gave their respects to each other before going to the rear courtyard. Zhao Hai didn’t ask for tea from the servant, instead he asked for water since he was supposed to be drunk.

Charlie looked at Zhao Hai’s appearance and smiled, “What’s wrong? The Crook Family made you drink too much?”

Zhao Hai smiled bitterly and said, “I didn’t know that they can drink so much. Have you tried having dozens of people offering you a toast? I was scared that I almost ran away from the table.”

Charlie laughed and said, “The Crook Family is always like this. People from the Imperial Capital actually has a nickname for them, the Rascal Nobles. People from their family were well known to be troublemakers. There were few people who can receive their actions peacefully.”

Zhao Hai forced a smile and said, “Who would’ve thought that such a very old man can be so shameless, really.”

Charlie laughed, then after a while he said, “Right, what matter did you go to the Crook Family for? Did you only go to drink with them?”

Zhao Hai smiled faintly and said, “It’s a good thing, the Crook Family and my Buda Clan have formed an Eternal Alliance. In two days, their family will announce it to the outside world.”

Charlie stared, then his face became happy as he said, “Really? That’s fantastic!”

Zhao Hai was on Charlie’s side. The strength of the Buda Clan was shown to be not weak, and they also had a good relationship with the Calci Family. This made Zhao Hai’s reputation change greatly. If you add the Calci Family’s full support for Zhao Hai, then even if Charlie fails the succession, keeping his title as a Prince wouldn’t be difficult. It might even be possible for him to be a Prince who held real power.

Of course, Charlie understood that he currently had the best chance of acquiring the throne. The Crown Prince used the strongest among the Princes, with Charlie coming close second. But since Charlie was acting low-key, nobody noticed it.

Afterwards, because of Terry, the Great Clans came to know that the Crown Prince had the Robert Family’s support. This was an extraordinary matter, the Crown Prince’s strength increased immediately, making him look like he would definitely get the throne.

But the sudden demise of the Robert Family, the appearance of Engraved Ark. and the Antimagic powder, placed the Crown Prince in an awkward position. These made the Crown Prince’s plans go into disarray. Because of his relationship with the Robert Family, he had displeased the current Emperor. He had also disappointed the Mages of the continent because of the Antimagic Powder. And because of Engraved Ark, the other nobles kept a safe distance away from him. At this point, he now became the most unlikely candidate to get the throne.

The Second Prince was too crude, he just couldn’t be compared to Charlie. Rising Water City and Jade Water City had always been in a competitive relationship. However, Rising Water City had no way no contend with the current Jade Water City. Therefore, it was impossible for the Second Prince to get the throne.

But Charlie was different, he had the very competent Zhao Hai by his side, who had just been rewarded by the Emperor with a title of Marquis as well as Golden Island as his fief. All of these affirmed Zhao Hai’s strength and status. This made Charlie’s influence increase. And adding the indirect support from the Calci and Crook Family to the mix, Charlie’s strength had now surpassed the Crown Prince by a few levels.

Zhao Hai smiled and said, “Your Highness can feel relieved, this matter has already been settled, there will be no mistakes.”

Charlie’s face was currently red. It took some time before he managed to calm down, he looked at Zhao Hai and said, “Little Hai, you really are my lucky star.”

Zhao Hai smiled faintly, “It’s too early to say that I’m a lucky star. Right, your highness, I’m afraid that I’m going to be very busy for a while. I’m preparing to claim Golden Island.”

Charlie stared and then he nodded, “Claiming Golden Island is also good. But this matter was not easy to do, have you thought about what to do after that?”

Zhao Hai nodded, then he told Charlie about his plan to turn the island into a free harbor. While he was talking to Charlie, the other party listened closely as well. Charlie was surprised, he didn’t think that Zhao Hai’s plan for the island would be this big.

However, he still supported what Zhao Hai wanted to do. If this plan succeeds, it wouldn’t only benefit Zhao Hai and the Buda Clan, but him as well.

Thinking about this, Charlie then said to Zhao Hai, “Little Hai, I fully support your plan. If you want help, then I will provide help. But you have to give me one thing, if you succeed in making the place into a free harbor, then you have reserve a place for me to establish a shop. What do you think?”

Zhao Hai smiled and said, “Your Highness is too polite, with our relationship, this is a natural thing to do. Rest assured, I will certainly have a piece of land for you in Golden Island. When that time comes, I’ll have to ask you for help and carry some goods over from Jade Water City.”

Charlie became happy with Zhao Hai’s response. He was afraid that Zhao Hai might change his attitude towards him now that his status has increased. If Zhao Hai did, then it would be a great blow towards him.

If Zhao Hai leaves Charlie at this time, not only would he lose his strength, the blow on his reputation would be very heavy as well. He simply cannot forcefully keep a strong person like Zhao Hai. When that happens, how can he become the Emperor? People who were following him would lose confidence, and the current Emperor would feel disappointed in him.

Chapter 491: Announcements

After coming back from Charlie’s place, Zhao Hai immediately returned to the Space. Laura and the others had been very busy these days. Now, the documents that they have acquired were already organized. Even though they didn’t read them, putting them into categories wasn’t very difficult. It has been two days since Zhao Hai asked the undead to write, Laura and the others were now in the final step in their task.

The reading materials were then divided into two classifications, those which were to be placed in Iron Mountain Fort to use for education, and those which were important to the Buda Clan and were placed inside a room in the Space’s Villa.

When Zhao Hai entered the Space, Laura and theo others were relaxing in the living room while drinking some tea. When they saw Zhao Hai enter, Laura immediately went to serve Zhao Hai a cup.

Looking at Zhao Hai somewhat red and smelt of alcohol, Laura knit her brows and said, “Brother Hai, you should drink less liquor. You smell like wine.”

Zhao Hai couldn’t help but smile bitterly and said, “I really don’t want to, but I have no choice. The Crook Family wanted to celebrate our Eternal Alliance while Charlie wanted to give me his regards.”

Laura nodded, she also understood Zhao Hai’s position. Zhao Hai had a lot of matters to consider, returning another person’s courtesy wasn’t something that he can avoid. But she still felt grieved. [1]

Meg felt grieved as well, then she quickly said, “Young Master, you should bathe in the hot spring. That should make you comfortable.”

Zhao Hai thought for a moment before nodding. Him smelling of wine made him very uncomfortable. Bathing in the hot spring would be great, the warmth would do him good.

While Zhao Hai went to soak in the hot spring, Laura and the others sat outside and continued chatting. Laura turned to Megan and said, “Megan, with Brother Hai’s title, how about we build a fort outside Carson City?”

Megan nodded and said, “That’s a good idea, but I’m afraid that Big Brother Hai wouldn’t agree. It costs a lot of money to build a fort, and all of the nice hills around the capital are already taken. The ones that are unoccupied aren’t very good.”

Laura thought for a moment and said, “Or Brother Hai can just ask His Majesty to take over Robert Family’s place. In any case, nobody would want to take their fort.”

Meg knitted her brows and said, “I don’t like it. The Robert Family has been eliminated by us. Occupying their fort would seem very strange.”

Megan nodded and said, “I don’t like it as well. And His Majesty likely won’t agree to it. I think we should just built one for ourselves, we can’t skim on the money. Building a fort around Carson City is also a status symbol. This would show how dedicated one was towards the crown.”

Laura knit her brows and said, “There’s that as well. If we can build a fort around Carson City, then it would be good for the Buda Clan’s face. I think we should discuss this matter with Grandpa Green.”

Megan nodded, “We should ask Grandpa Green and the others’ opinion. This isn’t a minor matter, this would affect the Buda Clan’s future.”

Laura nodded, then the group talked about other topics. Before long, Zhao Hai came out of the hot spring looking very neat. Laura told Zhao Hai about what they had discussed, he didn’t oppose to it, in fact, he was very interested.

However, constructing a castle cannot be done in one or two days. Zhao Hai told them that it would be better to solve the matter with Golden Island before thinking about a fort. Laura and the others naturally agreed.

The night went by uneventfully, then the next morning Smith informed Zhao Hai that the Calci Family would be having a banquet in Dark Soldier Fort. This was to celebrate Zhao Hai becoming a Marquis.

Zhao Hai didn’t decline, he knew that this was part of the process of being a noble. This banquet can also make him better known to these Great Nobles. It would let these nobles be aware of his existence.

The banquet went very successfully. Zhao Hai’s name was very resounding in the Rosen Empire recently. These nobles wouldn’t dare to not give Zhao Hai face.

Additionally, these nobles aren’t fools. From the strength that Zhao Hai has shown, as well as having the support of both the Calci Family and the Third Prince Charlie, these nobles knew that the Buda Clan was on its way to greatness. At this time, these nobles wouldn’t miss the opportunity to make an early impression.

The day after Zhao Hai’s banquet, the Crook Family formally announced their Eternal Alliance with the Buda Clan. This was without a doubt a huge bomb, making the people look into the Buda Clan yet again.

There were no nobles that didn’t know what an Eternal Alliance meant. No noble would dare violate an Eternal Alliance, if they went back on their word, they would get ostracized by the other nobles. When that happens, they wouldn’t have any other place to survive in the continent.

After hearing this announcement, the old nobles immediately knew that the Buda Clan was no longer worse than they are.

While the waves of this announcement was still echoing on the continent, another news came that made the continent shocked even more. The Shelley Family released word of their alliance with the Buda Clan.

An Alliance and an Eternal Alliance were different. Although an Alliance can also make two parties allies, both of them weren’t bound by being an eternal ally. An ally was just what it states, when one of them gets into trouble, the other would give some help. The two’s relationship can just be considered to lighter than an Eternal Alliance.

The Shelley family’s fame was very huge in the continent. They held the most profitable hotel business in the continent. All of the Great Nobles respect them as a Merchant Family. For them to form an alliance with the Buda Clan came as a surprise, this made the people anticipate for the future.

This matter was already known to Zhao Hai. When he arrived at Carson City, this matter was discussed to him by the Shelley Family, of which he agreed. His alliance with the Shelley Family was settled much earlier than the Crook Family, Zhao Hai just chose not to announce it.

The Buda Clan was quite busy recently, so they hadn’t had much chance to announce the alliance. Now that the Shelly Family made the announcement, Zhao Hai’s clan would get very great benefits.

The Shelley Family also understood that in the end, they were just a Merchant Clan. If they made an alliance with the up and coming Buda Clan, they could only benefit without losing anything.

Although having an alliance with the Buda Clan would have an effect on their businesses outside the Rosen Empire, the Shelley Family believed that they would be able to take this loss, they have enough reserves from their many years of operation. On the other hand, if they let this opportunity for an alliance with the Buda Clan slip by, they would find it difficult to find another one.

When Shelley Family announced their alliance with the Buda Clan, the people of the continent went into an uproar. Now, there was nobody who underestimated the Buda Clan.

However, there were also people who took this opportunity to humiliate the Buda Clan. These people were no other than the Aksu Empire. The Aksu Empire used this time to come out and announce in a high profile manner that they absolutely couldn’t agree with the Rosen Empire’s reward for the Buda Clan. If the Buda Clan dared to lay claim on Golden Island, they wouldn’t hesitate to use force in occupying the place.

This wasn’t a warning, but a threat. WIth the Aksu Empire’s announcement, the people turned their attention to the Rosen Empire and the Buda Clan.

The Rosen Empire didn’t respond. They just declared that Golden Island would be the perpetual fief of the Buda Clan. The only people who will own the island would be the Buda Clan. If the Buda Clan asked the empire for help, they would without a doubt provide it, this was because Zhao Hai was a noble of the Rosen Empire.

The nobles of the continent weren’t fools. They all knew that the Rosen Empire was just doing this to aggravate the situation between Aksu Empire and the Buda Clan.

When Zhao Hai saw how tyrannical the Aksu Empire had become, he also released his own statement. He gave a strong word that Golden Island completely belonged to his Buda Clan. This was the territory that was bestowed to him by the Rosen Empire, those would dare to oppose this decision would be challenging the Buda Clan. He wouldn’t hold back in using force.

This statement of Zhao Hai was also a warning for the pirates that were occupying the island.

Regarding Zhao Hai’s announcement, the Aksu Empire immediately fired back, laying claim to the island, announcing that it is the Aksu Empire’s territory. Those who dared to occupy the island would meet the fiercest attack of the empire.

Zhao Hai released another statement, giving all those who were currently occupying the island ten days to leave. Ten days later, if people were still occupying the island, the Buda Clan would dispatch their own troops and deal with those people with no mercy.

This situation made the continent riled up. Everyone was anticipating about whether the Buda Clan would actually send troops to the island ten days later. Zhao Hai actually declared that he would deal with Golden Island’s matter in ten days.

At this time, a Blood Hawk was carrying the Ghost Staff as it kept flying around Golden Island; not only to monitor the place, but to also see the Aksu Empire’s action.

After Zhao Hai’s declaration, the pirates immediately left the island. Whether it be the Buda Clan or the Aksu Empire’s threats, Golden Island was no longer a good place to stay in. Therefore, all of them went and left the island.

Just like what Zhao Hai said, even if Golden Island was a crucial location, it wasn’t that important for the pirates. The pirates only occupied the island because nobody owned it. But now that the Buda Clan made their claim, the pirates would naturally avoid offending them.

Zhao Hai’s ruthlessness was well known in the continent. He was able to eliminate the Robert Family, in front of such a person, these pirates were naturally afraid.

* * *

The only thing that can kill Zhao Hai right now is a bullet shot  in his head, what are you worrying for?

Chapter 492: Switching Owners in One Night

Zhao Hai was very glad about the pirate’s response, but he also felt a bit of regret. He really didn’t want all of these pirates to run away. If all of them left, nobody would remain on the island, and he wouldn’t have any excuse to attack those pirates. These pirates have looted for many years, they should have a lot of good things in their hand. If all of these ends up in Zhao Hai’s hands, he can surely make a great profit.

Zhao Hai was now a little obsessed with robbing people. Taking things by force made more profit than any other business, and its earning was gained all at once.

But Zhao Hai knew that it was impossible, the reason he made his announcement was to make these pirates leave. He knew from Smith that these pirates certainly had a major power as their backing. If he said nothing and just attacked the pirates, he would be offending a lot of people. Then, the Buda Clan would be placed in a disadvantageous position.

He issued his statement with a heavy tone so that the pirates would leave. If there were still some groups who remained, then nobody can blame Zhao Hai for killing them.

However, Zhao Hai underestimated his image in the hearts of the major influences of the continent. These people weren’t fools, they knew that Zhao Hai was strong, they were also aware of how formidable his web of relationships was. Because of this, nobody dared to go head to head with Zhao Hao at this time since they still want to live. Therefore, they immediately had their pirates leave and find another place to settle in.

In fact, Golden Island wasn’t the original lair of these pirates. They all have their own hideouts and were just using Golden Island as a trading hub. Pirates would trade with each other here with goods that had dirt cheap prices. They would trade living commodities here as well, allowing them to survive for a long time at sea.

Also, even if these pirates stay in Golden Island all year round, they still kept their base on other islands. Therefore, they immediately left the moment their backers told them to retreat.

These pirates also understood what when the Buda Clan goes to the island, the Aksu Empire would make a move. At that time, Gold Island would become a battlefield, and these pirates didn’t want to get caught in the crossfire. They knew that they weren’t qualified to join in.

After the pirates left, Zhao Hai switched his focus on the Aksu Empire and the Rosen Empire. The nearest territory to Golden Island belonged to Southern King Boris. With Zhao Hai’s enmity with him, it would be impossible for Boris to let this opportunity go.

The Rosen Empire might also carry bad intentions. They bestowed Golden Island to Zhao Hai not only because they want Zhao Hai to aggravate his conflict with the Aksu Empire, but also because they wanted to terrorize the Aksu Empire’s waters. Zhao Hai was afraid that the Rosen Emperor was just using him and would then have him removed when the matter gets finished. Because of this, he was also keeping a keen eye on the Rosen Empire.

However, he placed more importance with regards to the Aksu Empire’s actions. In Rosen Empire, he has Charlie, the Calci family, and the Crook Family. If the Rosen Empire wishes to make a move, he had people who will come and inform him. Therefore, Zhao Hai didn’t worry much about Rosen Empire. But with regards to Aksu Empire, Zhao Hai had no choice but to stay vigilant.

Sure enough, as Zhao Hai thought, the Aksu Empire has assembled more than 500 large and small ships and were preparing to occupy Golden Island.

Seeing this scene, Zhao Hai didn’t make a move. He just calmly stayed inside Dark Soldier fort everyday. Some days, he would attend some noble banquets while having a carefree expression, as if he has forgotten about Golden Island.

Such actions made the people of both the Aksu and Rosen Empire confused. They didn’t know what he was doing, it seems like his prior statement was a lie.

Only Laura and the others understood what Zhao Hai was planning, he was waiting for the Aksu Empire’s fleet to arrive at Golden Island. As soon as the fleet reached the island, Zhao Hai would immediately appear and release his undead to wipe them out. Then, he would turn the fleet into his own undead navy.

Zhao Hai’s actions made the people of the continent confused, they began to despise him as well. But nobody said anything to his face. After all, even if they think that Zhao Hai’s strength was weak, he wasn’t someone that common folk can offend.

Boris’ fleet didn’t care about Zhao Hai’s inaction. No matter what happened, they still started their operations. More than 500 ships started to sail from the Aksu Empire’s southern port of Sula and were headed towards Golden Island.

Smith and the others were puzzled about Zhao Hai’s actions as well. They asked Zhao Hai what he was doing, but Zhao Hai just gave them a smile and didn’t answer.

Two days before the arrival of the Aksu Empire fleet, the Rosen Emperor suddenly summoned Zhao Hai. Zhao Hai knew why the Emperor called for him, he didn’t say anything and just immediately boarded his carriage as it went towards the Imperial Palace.

This time, the only people present in their meeting was the Emperor and Zhao Hai. They were in a place at the rear part of the palace, inside the Emperor’s study. Zhao Hai gave his greetings to the Emperor before he was invited to sit down.

After Zhao Hai sat down, the Emperor looked at him and said, “Marquis Zhao Hai, do you know the movement of the Aksu Empire’s fleet?”

Zhao Hai didn’t expect that the Emperor would be this direct, he immediately answered, “Answering his Majesty, this official knows.”

The Emperor nodded, then he looked at Zhao Hai and seriously said, “I wonder if Marquis Zhao Hai has any plans for it. You should know that Golden Island was bestowed to you by the Rosen Empire. You shouldn’t let those Aksu Empire savages snatch it. Do you understand?”

Zhao Hai quickly responded, “This official understands. Your Highness can rest assured, Golden Island will forever belong to the Rosen Empire under the rule of the Buda Clan. This official wouldn’t hand it over to anyone, His Majesty doesn’t need to worry.”

When the Emperor heard Zhao Hai’s answer, his expression turned slightly mellower, he nodded and said, “It’s good that you understand. Marquis Zhao Hai, you are now a Marquis of the Rosen Empire, a subject under the crown. If there are matters that are out of your control, then Rosen Empire can provide you with help.”

Zhao Hai understood what the Emperor meant. The Emperor was afraid that Zhao Hai didn’t have the strength to handle this matter, so he told Zhao Hai that if he couldn’t solve this situation, the Rosen Empire will act for him.

Zhao Hai smiled and said, “His Majesty can feel relieved, this official can certainly deal with a small thief. What this official wants to do is to invite the thief inside the house and then close the door behind him. This way, he wouldn’t be able to escape.”

Upon hearing Zhao Hai, the Emperor stared, then he immediately laughed and said, “Alright, Marquis Zhao Hai. Remember those words that you said, do not disappoint me.”

Zhao Hai stood up and gave a salute, “His Majesty can be assured, this official surely won’t betray your expectations.”

The Emperor nodded, “Alright, you can go back. This Emperor shall be watching your performance.” Zhao Hai nodded, then after he gave another salute, he asked to be excused.

It was already the eighth day in Zhao Hai’s ten-day announcement. In two days, Zhao Hai’s deadline would be done, at the same time, Aksu Empire’s fleet would arrive at the island.

Now, every person in the continent had focused their sights on Zhao Hai. They wanted to know what Zhao Hai would do. But in the end, they were left disappointed, it seems like Zhao Hai wasn’t planning to do anything. He still stayed inside Dark Soldier Fort and occasionally attended noble banquets with a smile on his face.

At this time, a lot of people believed that Zhao Hai had already accepted his fate. In their minds, they couldn’t blame Zhao Hai, the other party has dispatched more than 500 ships. The fleet had about 200 ironclad ships, and more than 300 three masted battleships. The sailors numbered several hundred thousand people. Moreover, the number of 8th ranks that the Aksu Empire had sent numbered about a thousand people. They had also heard that a 9th rank expert was in charge of the operation. In this case, Zhao Hai would have no choice but to give up.

But there were still nobles who went to ridicule Zhao Hai. The Buda Clan’s reputation had been rising too quickly, this made people feel uncomfortable with their rise.

Two days passed by in a flash as people kept watching the Aksu Empire fleet. The fleet had already entered Golden Island’s waters and were preparing to land. It seems like they were preparing to station their troops there.

Sure enough, as soon as the Aksu Empire’s fleet came to land, the Empire immediately declared that Golden Island was an inseparable territory of the Aksu Empire. They even want to build a naval base on the island.

Aksu Empire’s statement made the people on the continent speechless. Then, all of them simultaneously turned their heads towards Rosen Empire. In their minds, Zhao Hai was already not in the equation. What they paid attention to right now was the Rosen Empire, they wanted to know how the Rosen Empire reacts towards Aksu Empire’s obvious provocation. They waited to see where the situation boils down to.

However, what made them surprised was the nonresponsive stance of the Rosen Empire. It seems like the Rosen Empire chose to swallow this time’s humiliation, it seemed very strange.

Under the looking eyes of the continent’s people, the Aksu Empire spent ten days doing construction. In this ten days, Zhao Hai didn’t have any response while the Aksu Empire went all out, freighters kept coming and going to the island carrying building materials on board. They didn’t stop for even a minute, hundreds of thousands of man-hours were used. In the end, with the help of Mages, the naval base took roughly ten days before completion.

The establishment of the naval base symbolized Aksu Empire’s victory. In the minds of the people, with Aksu Empire’s naval base on Golden Island, the Rosen Empire would find it very hard if they wanted to take it away. Also, at this point, it seems like the Buda Clan was already forgotten.

Ten days after the Aksu Empire’s fleet landed on the island, their naval base was already up and running, all of the people involved were celebrating in the evening. While the celebration was taking place, countless undead suddenly appeared on the island. The assault spread all throughout the island, including inside the Aksu Empire battleships. The slaughter continued on until daytime arrived.

Nobody knew about what happened on Golden Island that evening. The people just noticed that on the next day, the flags of the Aksu Empire were nowhere to be seen, in their place, Buda Clan’s Wild Dragon Banners were waving with vigour. Aksu Empire’s naval base was turned into the Buda Clan’s base as well. At the same time, Aksu Empire ships were being blocked when they tried approaching the island.

The overnight transformation made everyone shocked. They didn’t know what just happened. Did Aksu Empire’s fleet do a collective revolt?

While the people on the continent were baffled, Zhao Hai had already left Carson City. He rode his carriage and travelled using his ship to head towards Golden Island.

Everyone turned their gazes towards Zhao Hai again. At his side were the same people, the two servants, his three fiances, and one maid, nobody else. The carriage and the ship only had them as passengers.

However, when these people saw Zhao Hai’s carriage and his ship, all of them gave way. They wanted to see what would happen when Zhao Hai arrives at Golden Island. They wanted to see whether he would be warmly welcomed or turned back.

Before long, they got their answer. When Zhao Hai entered the island’s marine region, the Aksu Empire fleet immediately escorted him towards the docks. When Zhao Hai arrived at the island, he immediately made a declaration, “The Aksu Empire’s fleet have all been turned into my undead. If the Aksu Empire didn’t immediately construct their naval base, their fleet would’ve been exterminated the day they stepped foot on the island. Let this be a lesson to the Aksu Empire! Let this also be a warning to those in the continent who wishes to invade Golden Island. Take the Aksu Empire’s fleet as an example!”

Such remark immediately made the entire continent speechless. However, they didn’t suspect ZHao Hai’s words. This was because when Zhao Hai made his announcement, the Aksu Empire sent another fleet to attack Golden Island. In the end, they were repelled by the original fleet. In the process of their battle, the people on Aksu Empire’s second fleet noticed that the people they were fighting with were all undead!

Their testimony confirmed Zhao Hai’s statement. This made the backs of everyone in the continent turn cold. They felt shocked by Zhao Hai’s method, and then they felt fear. In their minds, Zhao Hai was no longer a person, but a living devil instead!”

Chapter 493: Golden Island Finally Belongs To Someone

The scale of the Aksu Empire fleet was well known to all the people because all of them were looking into this event. What the Aksu Empire sent this time weren’t only ship crews and some combatants, they also sent in artisans to help make the naval base.

The people on the more than 500 battleships, along with some artisans and coolies, all add up to hundreds of thousands of people, how many people was that? Moreover, those hundreds of thousands were turned into undead by Zhao Hai. If he wasn’t a devil, then what was he?

Although there were other people who killed more than a hundred thousand people before, most of them were still relatively lenient. On the other hand, Zhao Hai didn’t even bat an eye when killing those more than a hundred thousand people and then turning them into undead.

This announcement by Zhao Hai made every single person in the continent shocked, they were even more shocked by Zhao Hai’s strength. What kind of person can make more than a hundred thousand undead? How strong was Zhao Hai really? All of these questions placed Zhao Hai behind a mysterious veil.

The major influences in the continent wanted to lift this veil not only because of curiosity, but also for their interests. Zhao Hai’s strength and methods were really scary.

When people went to investigate Zhao Hai, they suddenly discovered that he quite had a terrible youth. For the first eighteen years of his life, he was a standard playboy; overbearing, prideful, and didn’t learn any talent nor skill. He was a low class playboy.

When he drank the Water of Nothingness and banished to the Black Wastelands, he suddenly made his transformation. Several months later, a person named Zhao Hai appeared on the continent.

As soon as he came out, he immediately took care of an group of undead mercenaries before he established his own business. Then, he became an enemy of both the Radiant Church as well as the Markey Family. After killing their people, Zhao Hai then ran away to the Prairie.

After coming out of the prairie, he turned into another appearance as he arrived at Rosen Empire. There, he managed to bring down Grand Duke Lionheart, having Lionheart’s entire clan slaughtered. Then, he was acted upon by the Calci Family, where in the end, the family admitted defeat. Zhao Hai also rescued the Purcell Duchy from their demise, obtaining about 100 thousand undead in the process. He also revealed that he had at least 10 thousand undead Beastman cavalry. When he extinguished the Robert Family, people found out about his method, he killed every single person of the Robert Family, not even a living witness remained. Moreover, he also turned all of the Robert Family into undead. Then, their investigations arrived to the Aksu Empire’s fleet.

Now, from the people’s calculation, Zhao Hai should already have about 1 million undead in his hand! About 1 million Advanced level undead? What did this represent? Not to say any ordinary noble clan, even millenium-old clans and the giant Rosen Empire might not even dare to offend him easily.

One could say that people cannot connect the previous Zhao Hai to his present form. In the past, the Buda Clan doesn’t even have a 9th rank expert, and was also dumped into the Black Wasteland. However, this was not the case this time, people have heard that Zhao Hai has 9th rank experts among his people. And adding on his status as the son-in-law of the Calci Family as well as the Eternal Ally of the Crook Family, those who would dare offend him would probably might as well have their heads bashed in by a closing gate.

The moment Zhao Hai stepped foot on Golden Island, the whole continent turned silent, even the Aksu Empire didn’t make a sound.

Then, Zhao Hai immediately stated that Golden Island would be turned into the continent’s first free harbor. Anyone can come here for business, regardless of status and background. As long as they pay taxes and don’t stir up any trouble, they can do business on the island. At the same time, Zhao Hai also stated that on a 1000 li radius around the island, his policy of non-violence must also be followed. Those who dared violate his rules would be killed immediately!

If it was the past Zhao Hai who issued this killing order, people wouldn’t have believed it. But now, Zhao Hai’s voice wasn’t something that the major influences wouldn’t dare to not listen to.

Strength decides everything, and Zhao Hai did have the strength. Therefore, this killing order was immediately followed. This was because people were very aware of the current strength of the Buda Clan.

The more than 500 undead-filled battleships of the Buda Clan can certainly enforce the rule on a 1000 li radius.

After Zhao Hai released his statement, the Aksu Empire released another announcement that was very thought provoking: Count Zhao Hai Buda of the Aksu Empire has been awarded the title of Third-Class Marquis. The Buda Clan is also awarded the fief of Golden Island as their perpetual domain.

This statement was really interesting. The relationship between Zhao Hai and the Aksu Empire was very well known. It can be said that this statement was the Aksu Empire’s way of admitting defeat.

This made the people on the continent very puzzled. They couldn’t understand why the Aksu Empire suddenly admitted defeat. They should at least send 9th rank experts to deal with Zhao Hai.

Then, a piece of information immediately circulated. The Aksu Empire did indeed send out 9th rank experts to deal with Zhao Hai. But the five 9th ranks that they sent out to Golden Island wasn’t able to return. This made the Aksu Empire accept their defeat.

Although not confirmed, the people of the continent believed that this information was real. This was because they knew that if the Aksu Empire didn’t send 9th ranks to the island, they wouldn’t admit their defeat this easily.

No matter what reason, the Aksu Empire’s statement settled the matter of Golden Island’s ownership once and for all. From now on, the Buda Clan would own the entirety of the island.

When this matter was settled, the people turned their attention to what Zhao Hai said before, turning the island into a free harbor.

‘Free Harbor’, this was the first time that such a word appeared on the Continent. But even with this, the nobles immediately knew what this free harbor would do.

This free harbor would give the pirates a place to publicly sell their loot. This was very attractive, however, nobody still went to Golden Island because they were scared. After all, this was a place where hundreds of thousands of people have died, it was not a mystery that they would be afraid.

With the people’s response, Zhao Hai didn’t worry. At this moment, he was inspecting Golden Island.

Although Zhao Hai had already seen the island on the monitor, being here today felt very different. Zhao Hai now knew why pirates occupied the place, it was because the destruction brought by gold mining was extremely serious.

The entire island looked like a worm eaten apple, full of holes. The way the people mined this place was much different from how Dwarves mined Iron Mountain.

Dwarf mining didn’t leave behind a lot of tunnels, if there wasn’t a lake in the middle, Zhao Hai would have been certain that the Dwarves made a city inside Iron Mountain. On the other hand, Golden Island was very different. There were a lot of tunnels here, so many that Zhao Hai wasn’t able to count all of them. So he let Cai’er do the counting and in the end, the large and small tunnels numbered up to more than 20 thousand.

These twenty thousand tunnels made the originally small Golden Island look like face full of sores, horrifying to look at. Also, even if the vegetation slowly came back to the island after a thousand years, with the prior destruction of the island, there were no tall trees that grew here, only weeds were present.

There were two mountains in Golden Island, making a T-shaped structure in the island. But these two mountains were riddled with tunnels as well, they had suffered very serious destruction.

But fortunately, the original miners on the island still had a bit of brain left. Although the tunnels weren’t connected, there were roads made on the mountainside since transporting ores was  difficult. Although many years has passed since then, the roads can still be used.

Zhao Hai looked at the tunnels in the island and can see traces of people living on some of them. What Zhao Hai was puzzled about was the fact that there were no Magic Beasts that can be seen on the island.

Although it was strange, Zhao Hai didn’t think too much about it. Aksu Empire’s naval base was constructed on the tunnels of the island. From what Zhao Hai saw, the naval based used nearly a thousand tunnels and caves for places of rest. It also had one of the largest piers of the island, which was also constructed in between stone walls. Looking at the naval base, it wouldn’t be a problem for it to be home to tens of thousands of people.

The base was built underneath a part of the T-shaped mountain formation. Because of the joint effort from Mages, workers, and warriors, the base was built to a very high standard.  This base was completely ready for Zhao Hai to use. The undead who weren’t on board the ships were made to stay in the naval base.

For the Golden Island to successfully become a free harbor, it needed ironclad rules that should be enforced. These undead would be the on the island to keep the place in order.

Besides the undead, Zhao Hai had also released large quantities of marine Magic Beasts to protect the waters around the island as well as to monitor the surrounding activities.

In reality, Zhao Hai wasn’t really very invested in Golden Island. For him, this was only a place to make money. When speaking about environment, he much prefers Ape Island, where the atmosphere was better than Golden Island.

Zhao Hai decided to stay at the base after arriving at the island. Then, he transferred some managers from Iron Mountain fort to manage the administrative matters of the island. The other matters were handed over to the undead.

What Zhao Hai needed to do right now was to repair the island’s roads, only then can he be comfortable opening the island for business.

Zhao Hai already thought about the situation. Nobody came to the island because nobody took the first step. But he wasn’t afraid of this not happening, he had the Calci Family, the Crook Family, the Shelley Family, and Charlie. All of them wanted to do business in the island and open their own stores. Also, Zhao Hai didn’t believe that these people would be so clean to not have one or two privateer groups under their control. As long as those pirates enter the island and take the first step, others would follow.

Chapter 494: Plate Silk Grass

Although there was nothing in the island right now, as soon as its function as a free port goes full throttle, everything will fall into place. Do you want to do business in the island? Then you will only be provided a piece of land, the other matters are for you to deal with. If you want to use a tunnel for yourself, then go and make your own structures, the island would give you preferential treatment.

If you don’t want to make your own structure, then that wouldn’t be a problem. The island would help you construct it, however, you need to remember to pay the fees.

Zhao Hai already thought about how Iron Mountain fort had nothing right now. So what did he do about the artisans that the Aksu Empire brought here? If he didn’t use them, then it would be a pity. Because of this, Zhao Hai has thought about making a construction team and having them build some structures for him. After all, even if they are undead, their capabilities aren’t much less than those who were alive.

A group of 8th rank undead builders constructing a house, what scene would that be? Thinking about this made Zhao Hai smile. He believed that if this construction force were to be brought back to earth, their bosses would certainly make sure that they get their wages on time.

Zhao Hai used this construction group to build a small building outside the naval base first. This building would be used by the managers that he had brought from Iron Mountain Fort.

These staff that were from Iron Mountain fort was naturally Laura’s subordinates. All of Laura’s people were capable of handling an important task by themselves. Placing them in Iron Mountain to teach as well as to command undead was too much of a waste.

Zhao Hai didn’t really want to kill those coolies and artisans. However, he didn’t have any choice since the artisans themselves took up their own weapons and fought against him. Because of this, Zhao Hai had no choice but to end them.

A thing that made Zhao Hai happy was the number of Mages present this time. Majority of these Mages were Earth Mages and Water Mages. This was because they had the most use in constructing a naval base.

Aksu Empire got together and sent forth about a thousand Mages. Moreover, the levels of these Mages aren’t low since they needed to create a naval base at the shortest time possible. This was to ensure that the Aksu Empire held the advantage in the future sea battles around the island.

However, it was a pity that this naval base was handed to Zhao Hai. Originally, Zhao Hai wanted to wait until the fleet stepped foot on the island before he made his move and extinguish them. Who would’ve known that as soon as the fleet arrived, they would immediately construct a naval base. This gave Zhao Hai an idea, they want to construct a base? Fantastic! Then he would just have to wait until they are done before he stepped in and clean them up.

It would be impossible for all of these builders to participate in making the small building. Zhao Hai was planning to make a five story building, the first floor would be used for working, while the remaining ones are going to be used for living quarters. The remaining coolies and artisans were sent out to repair the roads of the island.

Zhao Hai remembers a very famous slogan in China. If you want to be rich, then build proper roads first. If Zhao Hai wants to attract merchants to Golden Island, then he would naturally have to provide them with a good environment. So Zhao Hai was also preparing to improve the overall facade of the island.

What was something that was abundant in the island? The answer was tunnels. There were a lot of tunnels and caves in the island. Some of them were interconnected with each other, while some were just dead ends.

Inside those tunnels and caves were weeds that needed to be dealt with. But when Zhao Hai saw these weeds, he found out that they were weeds that he hadn’t seen before. He became curious about them so he placed some of them into the Space, “Thousand-year old grass detected. Has strong medicinal functions. They might look like individual blades of grass, but all of them are interconnected with each other, making the grass have a strong vitality. It is recommended that the host transfers all of the grass into the Space. The Space would use its property to improve its grass as well as the growth of the plants inside.”

The Space didn’t hint that the grass can make it level up, nor did it provide the rank of the grass. However, the function of the grass made Zhao Hai glad. With these properties, he didn’t wait for a moment before he started to collect them.

As long as he can upgrade the Space, Zhao Hai wouldn’t hesitate even if he needed to uproot all of the weeds inside Golden Island.

Presently, the way that Zhao Hai can receive items have become much easier. In the past, he would open a spatial rift before he can store the items. Now, after the Space has gone through its upgrades, as long as the item was within a kilometer from Zhao Hai, he can immediately get them. Even if it was underground, it didn’t matter, it can still be absorbed into the Space.

Zhao Hai immediately moved, it took him five days before he swept the island clean of weeds. Every weed and shrub was received into the Space.

Zhao Hai was very surprised when he was taking the weeds. When he gets them, he also made sure to get the soil a meter around them as well. He was afraid that he might damage the roots of those weeds.

However, Zhao Hai didn’t expect that the roots of these weeds could actually reach more than 2 meters into the ground, some of them were even rooted into the bedrock.

After Zhao Hai took every plant in Golden Island, the Space gave a prompt, “Massive amounts of wood energy received. Space’s level has reached 49. Plants can be improved, making them interdependent. The Wood energy has been added to the Metal energy, upgrading the host’s body. Host has now acquired Plant Manipulation.”

When Zhao Hai  heard this announcement, his mind went blank. At its current state, it was really very hard for the Space to level up. With the amount that he took in, he only managed to upgrade the Space by one level.

But Zhao Hai having Plant Manipulation was a very extraordinary matter. He can already control metal, now he can control plants as well.

He also knew that with all of his efforts, he can only control 100 jin of metal at most. With this, he also knew that he would need to practice Plant manipulation in order to be good in it.

But all in all, Zhao Hai was very happy. At this point, the only thing that bothered Zhao Hai was the fact that there was no longer any vegetation present on the island, it was now a barren island.

Zhao Hai clearly knew that it would be troublesome if there weren’t any vegetation on the island. When a storm comes, landslides and mudslides could become common. When that happens, the island wouldn’t be suitable for humans anymore.

While Zhao Hai was bothered, he suddenly heard fluttering of wings. Zhao Hai was surprised, did the Space release a flying Magic Beast on its own? At this time, the sound of the wings vanished, then while Zhao Hai was confused, a voice came, “Young Master, I levelled up!”

Zhao Hai stared, then when he followed the sound, he saw Cai’er. Cai’er wasn’t finger sized any more, she was now almost as tall as his arm, but her outfit wasn’t changed. However, it wasn’t undeniable that Cai’er had indeed leveled up.

Cai’er flew towards Zhao Hai’s side before she said, “Young Master, this is fantastic! With my level up, even a dozen 9th ranks wouldn’t be able to damage me. I can also make more branches. I can control the plants in the Space as well as improving them. I can even fuse two seeds together in order to make a new seed.

Zhao Hai was surprised, he s looked at Cai’er and said, “Cai’er, are saying the truth? Did you really level up?” Cai’er nodded and said, “Young Master, I really leveled up.”

Zhao Hai couldn’t help but laugh happily and said, “Fantastic! Cai’er, that’s fantastic. Right, I have a problem, you can see that all of Golden Island’s vegetation has been uprooted by me. I want to plant new ones here, what do you think I should plant?”

Cai’er looked at Golden Island and made some calculations before she turned to Zhao Hai and said,” Young Master, there is a plant that is very suitable for Golden Island. It’s a plant in the Space’s shop called Plate Silk Grass. According to the Space, it is a recreational plant. If it is planted in an incompatible land, then it would take a few years before it fully grows. Since it’s very compatible to Golden Island, it would grow on its own when planted. It also has some medicinal effects according to the Space. After improving its seeds, it would become more suitable for the island. Young Master can plant some seeds and spread them all over the island. If you sprinkle them with the Space’s water, they would be able to grow quickly. And when they reach their full growth, Young Master can then leave them alone. Every year, young master can also harvest some plate silk grass three times. Plate Silk Grass can be made into medicine. It can also be woven, items made from woven Plate Silk Grass can bring benefits to both Mage and Warrior cultivation. The effect can continue for two years.”

Zhao Hai stared, then he looked at the shop. Not only did this plant exist, it actually appeared in the Journey to the west. This thing was truly a recreational plant. In the past, Zhao Hai didn’t see this plant in the store, it seems like after the Space leveled up, it suddenly appeared.

Zhao Hai looked at its price, 1000 gold coins for single bag  that can cover a hundred mu of land. But Golden Island’s area seemed to be about a hundred thousand mu. If Zhao Hai wishes to plant Plate Silk Grass all over the island, he would need to fork out 1 million gold coins.

Without hesitation, Zhao Hai immediately bought more than 1 million gold’s worth of Plate Silk Grass seeds before he spread it around the island and watered it with Spatial Water. There wasn’t a limit on Spatial Water now, so Zhao Hai can feel relieved in using it this way.

After being watered with Spatial Water, the Plate Silk Grass immediately started to grow. Zhao Hai didn’t think that it would only take ten hours before the whole island would be covered by Plate Silk Grass.

Chapter 495: Nuances of Golden Island

After ten hours, these grasses can even be harvested. However Zhao Hai didn’t want to touch them right now, he decided to just let them grow. Even if the grass can be harvested, they were still very short. If he harvests them now, Golden Island would only return to its previous state. Because of this, Zhao Hai decided to let them grow more before harvesting.

By the time Zhao Hai, Laura, and the others appeared back on Golden Island, the grasses were already a meter long. The entire Golden Island was green and full of vitality.

Looking at the situation of Golden Island, Laura smiled and said, “Brother Hai, I’m afraid we need to enforce a rule forbidding people from moving these Plate Silk Grass on their own. Otherwise, our losses would be very big.”

Zhao Hai smiled faintly and said, “Construction would certainly destroy a part of them, but we can control it. These grasses can provide us with profit.”

Megan looked at Zhao Hai and said, “Big Brother Hai, you still care about money? These grasses can only be worth so much.”

Zhao Hai showed a faint smile and said, “I certainly don’t care about money, but these grasses are necessary to guarantee Gold Island’s appearance. Alright, no need to think too much about it. Now that everything has been completely prepared, the only thing we need to wait for are the people.”

Megan smiled and said, “Big Brother Hai, do you think it would be that easy? It’s almost been a month and nobody has come to visit the island.”

Zhao Hai smiled faintly and said, “They didn’t come because I still haven’t made them come. Now that we have taken care of Golden Island, we can have them come. Right, I have to send Grandfather a letter when I go back.”

Megan was confused, Zhao Hai hadn’t told them what he was planning to do in the island. So it was no wonder that Megan and the others were puzzled.

After returning to the naval base, Zhao Hai immediately sent a letter to the Calci Family, Prince Charlie, Crook Family and the Shelley Family. He relayed his plan carefully and asked them to cooperate.

In fact, Randolph and the others wanted to send people to Golden Island, but Zhao Hai still hasn’t agreed. He asked them to wait for his letter before they can come.

Soon, Randolph and the others received Zhao Hai’s letter. They couldn’t help but comment him, they thought that Zhao Hai’s plan was fantastic. If the pirates don’t come to Golden Island in order to trade, the major forces of the continent would suffer as well.

However, the pirates were still uncertain about the situation on Golden Island. Therefore, they chose to wait until there is exact confirmation coming from those who went in first.

Randolph and the others knew about this. So when they received Zhao Hai’s letter, the Calci Family immediately sent a party to enter Golden Island. Because Sky Water city was closest to Golden Island, they can immediately send a party as soon as possible.

The second group to enter the island was from the Shelley Family. Recently, Shelley Family’s businesses on the continent have been severely suppressed by the Radiant Church. Although they had taken care of it, the businesses weren’t as good as before. For the family, this loss was huge. The elders of the Shelley Family were now very dissatisfied with the Patriarch for his support for Zhao Hai. Their arrival at Golden Island this time was a good opportunity to cover their losses.

The third group who entered Golden Island was from Prince Charlie. His base was Jade Water City, although it was farther than Sky Water City, its distance to the island wasn’t that far. It was because of this that they were quite slower than the Calci Family.

The Crook Family were the last people to enter the island because their family doesn’t have a port city. If they want to move to Gold Island, they needed to make more preparations compared to the others, which made them a lot slower.

These four groups entering Golden Island wasn’t a mystery for the people of the continent. All of them knew about their relationship with Zhao Hai, because of this, people weren’t very surprised by it.

However, two pirate groups suddenly entered Golden Island to do business. Naturally, they weren’t there to make a shop, they wanted to sell off their snatched goods. They went to the island to have their loot sold and were given gold or other goods in exchange, the trade went very smoothly.

Not only did they manage to buy what they needed, they had also bought it at a much lower price than what they usually paid for. The things they sold were also bought at a much higher price than what they were usually bought at. This time, they earned three times the profit compared to what they had before.

The two pirate groups who entered the island were quite courageous, they directly entered the island. In the end, their courage was well rewarded, they gains that they made was more than satisfactory.

Their success stimulated the other pirate groups. The pirates really lacked a place where they could trade. Now that Golden Island appeared, all of them were very happy.

The coming of these pirates brought great fortune to the Calci Family and the other three. Naturally, these profits weren’t hidden from the other forces in the continent, they immediately went and started to move.

Their first action was to set up shops on Golden Island. At this time, Laura’s men also arrived at the island and beacon to work as its administrators.

Before long, Golden Island became very bustling. Golden Island wasn’t only cheap, its taxes weren’t very high as well. All of their businesses weren’t very restricted, as long as they don’t violate the basic rules of Golden Island, the administration wouldn’t disturb them.

The pirates were extremely pleased. They haven’t been this rich before, they couldn’t help but be very happy. In the past they can’t even walk on the streets because of their fear of being arrested.

Now it was very different, as long as one arrives at Golden Island and follows its rules, the undead who acted as guards wouldn’t even spare you a glance.

In the beginning, they weren’t very used to seeing the undead patrols, however, in time they gradually accepted it as a normal thing. These undead were very good, as long as you don’t violate Golden Island’s rule, they wouldn’t pay any attention to you. Only when someone commits a crime would they become impolite.

The pirates have seen it with their own eyes. A pirate went to sell their items but didn’t receive any money. The owner even fought with him before the owner was taken away by the undead and whipped a few times.

If this was just the case, then there’s nothing strange about is. But interestingly, the person was from the Calci Family. When he was taken away, he was still very arrogant, he kept shouting to the undead that he was from the Calci Family. He said that if these undead dared to touch him, then he wouldn’t make Zhao Hai look good.

But the undead didn’t care about his words, they still proceeded to whip him. And at the same time, they heard that the person was heavily fined by the Calci Family.

There were some small merchants who were planning to no longer move their goods to other places. Instead, they decided to directly go to Golden Island. As long as they are inside the waters of Golden Island, they can be safe.

Naturally, some of the pirates didn’t follow the rules. After the Buda Clan announced this rule, they still robbed along Golden Island’s sea region.

However, even if they robbed at daytime, nighttime, or even if they didn’t use magic cannons, the Buda Clan would still be the first ones to know. After that, the pirates were guaranteed to be destroyed.

After three pirate groups were exterminated in a row, the pirates finally behaved themselves. The pirates knew that there should’ve been some kind of secret signal, otherwise it wouldn’t be possible to know everything.

Regarding the profits that the Buda Clan has lost in dealing with these pirates, it wasn’t that large. On the other hand, the action was very good for their income.

Some of the goods that merchants brought to the island and were sold off would fall into pirate hands. The cycle would then continue, therefore the Buda Clan doesn’t need to worry.

Because of the amount of goods being shipped to Golden Island, the prices of these items were naturally lowered. In the end, the ones who managed to save their profits would be the pirates. Therefore, the pirates were naturally very popular among the merchants.

But to say that the pirates would stop robbing would be impossible. The pirates would still rob, however, when they enter and sell their loot in Golden Island, nobody would tell on them. Even those who are eager to trace the pirates would find it hard to do so. Because of this, Zhao Hai wasn’t worried that the island’s income would be affected.

Zhao Hai’s taxation on Golden Island being very low was because he wasn’t taxing the goods that were shipped in, instead he applied taxes on each transaction.

Zhao Hai gave a clear announcement that this tax rate wouldn’t change, it would always be at this rate. Zhao Hai knew that as long as he made the tax of Golden Island very low, as well as provide good services, Golden Island would sooner or later have a reputation. As long as Golden Island has its brand, more merchants would come in. They may not want to deal with pirated goods and would only want to do normal business, but Zhao Hai reckoned that the tax rate would still be enough.

Just a month after the Calci Family arrived at the island, the place welcomed its peak season. Whether they be pirates or merchants, all of them wanted to trade on Golden Island because the taxes here was really cheap.

Even if the taxes on other places aren’t very high, they weren’t that low. Take Sky Water City for example, the city’s base tax for ordinary cargo was 5% – 8%, other goods would reach 10% to 15%

However, in Golden Island, the taxes for ordinary cargo was only 1%, other goods can be taxed about 2% or 3%.

The division between ordinary cargo and others was whether they are strategic resources. If they are strategic goods, then the tax would be higher, if not, then they would be lower.

Also, Golden Island taxed based on transactions, not the amount of cargo. If you sell something, they you would get taxes. If you don’t sell, then you don’t need to pay tax.

Also, damaged items might still be taxed on other places, but on Golden Island, damaged goods wouldn’t.

For other people, it might look like merchants can abuse this fact to evade taxes. However, such a thing doesn’t happen on Golden Island.

When goods arrive at Golden Island, they would be inspected. Moreover, each month, someone would come to the storehouses and record its contents before charging the merchants for tax.

Moreover, the people who would come and inspect the goods were undead. Undead couldn’t be bribed, and they were also very careful in their inspection. Because of this, evading taxes would be very difficult.

In order for Zhao Hai to prevent falsely declared damage goods, he borrowed the ticket system from Earth. If you make a transaction, you need to issue a ticket. Then the island would collect the taxes based on those tickets.

At the same time, Zhao Hai also carried appraisals for all damaged goods, assigning prices on them.  If 5 out of 100 of your goods gets damaged, then they would be classified as fragile goods. If their mean value is 6% of the value of the 100, then those 5 wouldn’t be taxed. If you claim to have 10% worth of damaged goods, but the appraisal for those are just 5%, they you would be punished. At that time, 100% of your goods will be taxed.

Naturally, this might sound unfair. For example, if someone encounters a typhoon which caused massive damages to their goods. In that case, then they can report the incident to the island. When the time where you pay taxes comes, those goods wouldn’t be taxed.

This way, most cases of tax evasion would be eliminated. However, there would still be some people who can find a way to escape being taxed. Because of this, Zhao Hai thought of a reward system. If someone goes and reports someone of tax evasion, as long as that report is true, then that person would be rewarded. As a result, tax evasion was almost non existent in Golden Island.

Golden Island became a place of enthusiasm and prosperity. The businesses on the island became very popular. This made everyone on the continent jealous. However, they aren’t able to sabotage the island.

Zhao Hai had already set his reputation on stone, he even offended two Great Clans but he still didn’t care. If he didn’t have his reputation, he wouldn’t have opened Golden Island.

At this time, Zhao Hai was smiling on his gains. Also, since there were a lot of merchants who came to the island for business, his construction team was very busy. Due to these constructions, Zhao Hai had also made a lot of money.

The merchants on the island weren’t fools. They calculated everything before they proceeded with construction. If they saw that the construction group was very expensive, then they’d rather buy materials elsewhere and hire some people to build the shops on their own. But after doing their calculations, they saw that the construction team wasn’t more expensive than the other construction groups of the continent, on the other hand, they were actually cheaper. Therefore, people on the island decided to just hire Zhao Hai’s construction group to do the job.

Chapter 496: Slave Market

Although merchants have only entered Golden Island for a month, the state of the place can only be described as hot. Pirates, Merchants, as well as major influences have come here to mingle.

This month’s development was only the first explosion of Golden Island. It would continue to grow, and over time, the popularity of this place would become stronger and stronger.

At this time, Zhao Hai wasn’t already on the island. He has now returned to Carson City. This was because he needed to take care of an important matter for the Buda Clan.

In the past, Laura and the others have discussed the possibility of them constructing a castle on the area around Carson City. This  would solidify the Buda Clan’s status on the capital. However, because of Golden Island, this matter has been placed at the back of their minds.

But they can’t put this matter aside for too long. So they went and asked Charlie, Jason, and the others for help to see which hills around the city was up for grabs. When they find a place, then they would make their move immediately.

Charlie and the others were naturally willing to help. However, after the passing of years, all of the hills around Carson City was already occupied. Even when there was a suitable place, they either had a bad environment, or they were too low. Not to say Zhao Hai, even Charlie and the others wouldn’t like it. They surely wouldn’t let Zhao Hai claim those hills.

Originally, Laura suggested that they occupy Robert Family’s fort. But Zhao Hai didn’t agree since they were the ones who eliminated the Robert Family. If they occupy their fort, then that would really look very strange.

Charlie and the others didn’t agree to it as well. But after a long time, they still weren’t able to find a place. This made Charlie and Jason feel apologetic to Zhao Hai, he asked for their help but they were unable to deliver.

Then, Charlie finally thought that since they couldn’t find a suitable hill, they they might as well find someone who were willing to sell.

But after checking for several days, Charlie still wasn’t able to find people who were willing. This made Charlie feel bad, Jason as well, he even felt more sorry than Charlie. But there was no other way, all people who lived on the vicinity were all Great Clans. All of these clans have their own businesses, so all of them are doing very well. Charlie and Jason cannot just make them leave in account for Zhao Hai. It wasn’t worth offending these people just for such a paltry reason.

Zhao Hai didn’t think too much of it, almost two months had passed since God’s Grace Day. Golden Island has been doing very well, spring had also arrived at Aksu Empire, which means that spring would be arriving at the Prairie. As long as spring arrives, he would be heading to the Prairie, then he wouldn’t worry about constructing a fort anymore.

When Charlie and the others were about to give up, information suddenly came. The current owner of Lionheart’s fort was willing to sell.

Lionheart was Zhao Hai’s first enemy on Rosen Empire. He also colluded with the Radiant Church before being killed by Zhao Hai. His family’s fort was then occupied by a noble of the Rosen Empire.

Saying occupy wasn’t excessive. This was because at that time, nobles were scrapping Lionheart’s possessions. At that time, the fort was being sold for a cheap price so the noble decided to buy it. At the same time, since he bought it, he might as well occupy the place.

However, because of the Robert Family and the Engraved Ark, Carson City’s atmosphere became tense. The eyes of Great Clans were very active regarding people with good relationships with the Robert Family. At this time, people went to investigate the noble who bought Lionheart’s castle. This person was a Second Class Duke and he didn’t have the power to have his own duchy. However, this person’s fief wasn’t small, moreover, he had a very good relationship with the Robert Family. His clan’s emblem was a mad cow. This cow lacked one horn while its eyes were red with rage.

At this point, the Rosen Empire was very critical in looking for clans’ emblems. In addition to finding friends of the Robert Clan, the empire was also looking for suspicious clan emblems.

When the investigation found that this noble and the Robert Family were very intimate, they immediately prepared to do a thorough investigation. However, when they came to do so, the nobleman’s family suddenly vanished.

Overnight, all of the family members have left, they didn’t even take their precious things along with them. Even the servants stayed behind as well as their businesses. Only the family itself vanished, nobody remained.

This caused the entire Rosen Empire to be in a stir. For an entire clan to run like this, it clearly confirmed their status. The Imperial Clan immediately went and thoroughly searched their home. As a result, all of the family’s documents were taken away. Since the family didn’t take their valuables with them, the Rosen Empire became skeptical. The empire immediately issued an order to seize the family. However, all of them were already gone, no news was found about them.

As a result, their fort became empty. The Rosen Empire grabbed all of the servants and the people associated with the family and interrogated them. They wanted to ask them about the family, but the servants literally knew nothing at all.

Because of this, nothing was known, and the castle was left empty, which was a pity. Charlie and Jason were very happy when they knew about this, they knew that Grand Duke Lionheart’s fort was very well constructed. Now that the place was ownerless, it would be great if Zhao Hai bought it.

Also, because the family ran away in a hurry, all of the precious things in the castle weren’t taken away. Although the gold and silver items were taken away by the Imperial Clan, the fort was still left well equipped. Therefore, Charlie immediately told Zhao Hai to buy it.

Zhao Hai also knew that even if he already has Iron Mountain Fort, he still needed a fort on Carson City for the benefit of the Buda Clan’s face. At the same time, it would also indicate that the Buda Clan has considered themselves as people of the Rosen Empire.

The matter was quickly completed under Charlie’s operation. In the end, Zhao Hai bought the hill as well as the castle for a price of 10 million gold coins.

After acquiring the fort, Zhao Hai immediately sent a construction team over to modify the fort. At the very least, he needed to have the emblem changed, there were also some little things inside that Zhao Hai wished to change.

Zhao Hai returned to Carson City for this matter. But when the fort’s construction was underway, he assigned the undead under Cai’er’s supervision. Then Zhao Hai took Laura and the others to Carson City’s slave market.

Carson City’s slave market wasn’t inside the city, but in a valley not too far. The entire mountain valley was a large slave market.

It was the first time that Zhao Hai had come here. Now that Kun was in Golden Island along with Laura’s people, Zhao Hai didn’t worry about anything. He lead Laura and the others to come to the slave market. When he goes to the Prairie, he would get 100 thousand slaves. However, 100 thousand slaves who were all Beastmen wasn’t good. Because of this, Zhao Hai decided to buy some human slaves as well.

The valley’s entrance wasn’t very wide, giving people a hard time because only two carriages can pass side by side. There weren’t any people that can be seen on the entrance, there weren’t any structures as well. Just by looking at it, one might even mistake it as an ordinary mountain valley.

However, the moment Zhao Hai’s carriage entered the valley, he immediately became surprised. In the one year that he has been in Ark Continent, this was the first time that he saw this kind of slave market. He thought that this slave market would be very dirty and very chaotic. Only when he entered did he understand that he was wrong and that he was thinking ridiculously.

This slave was neither dirty nor chaotic. In contrast, this slave market looks even more cleaner than any ordinary market. It wasn’t as crowded as ordinary markets as well. The shops here were well constructed and also had a very pleasant facade.

Looking at the 21 three-story buildings, Zhao Hai cannot really connect this place with a slave market. After staring for some time, Zhao Hai turned to Megan and said, “Megan, are you sure that you’re not mistaken? Is this really the slave market?”

Megan smiled and said, “Of course I’m not wrong, this is indeed the slave market. I came here before because I’m curious.”

Zhao Hai nodded, then he looked around before he murmured, “This is a beautiful place, who would’ve thought that it would deal with filthy transactions.”

Laura and the others didn’t say anything, all of them were natives of Ark Empire so they didn’t have as much of a dislike for slaves as Zhao Hai. But seeing the happy expressions of the slaves who had become commoners back at Iron Mountain Fort, they couldn’t help but also develop a dislike for the slave trade.

Their horse carriage stopped in front of a shop’s door. When Zhao Hai and the others walked down from their carriage, someone from the shop immediately came to welcome them. The man looked very decent, he was tall and wore a merchant’s suit without anything else on his body. But Zhao Hai didn’t underestimate this person because Megan had told him that almost all of the people who dealt with the slave business were nobles. The bigger the slave merchant, the more powerful the noble above them. Even small slave merchants would still have formidable powers behind them. Because of this, nobody dared to look down upon these people.

When this merchant saw Zhao Hai’s carriage, his eyes turned bright. He immediately wore a welcoming face as he bowed to Zhao Hai, “Merchant Ren has seen Mariquis Zhao Hai.”

Zhao Hai stared, he looked at the Merchant and said, “You know me?”

The merchant smiled and said, “How can I not know of Marquis Zhao Hai. This small merchant has always heard of Marquis Zhao Hai’s name. If I don’t recognize the Marquis even after seeing the Buda Clan emblem, then I might as well have by eyes gouged out.”

Chapter 497: Artisan Slaves

Zhao Hai looked at Ren, then he showed a faint smile and said, “You really have good eyes. You should do your best to keep it.” Then he was led into the shop by Ren, the others also followed.

After having entered the shop, Zhao Hai stared. The inside didn’t look like what a shop should be, one could even call this a living room. The ornaments and decorations inside was commonly seen on living rooms, it wouldn’t be bad if it was one.

Ren immediately asked Zhao Hai and the others to sit down. Zhao Hai didn’t hesitate and just sat down just as Ren presented him with tea. Ren just stood respectful as the asked Zhao Hai, “Sir Marquis, what can this little one do for you?”

Zhao Hai looked Ren and smiled faintly, “What else? I’m here to buy some slaves, both men and women. I have just recently bought a castle and want to place some slaves to maintain it.”

Ren immediately nodded and said, “Alright, how many slaves does sir Marquis need? How many males and females?”

Zhao Hai waved his hand and said, “Why are you asking these things? Lead me to see them first, I want to look at their quality. If they’re good, then I would buy a large number. If they aren’t up to par, then I wouldn’t want to buy even one.”

Ren smiled and said, “Then Marquis, please, follow me. I believe there won’t be any shop in this valley who would sell low quality goods. Because of the valley’s vicinity to Carson City, the guests here are all great nobles, we wouldn’t want to risk our business, so we certainly wouldn’t sell substandard goods.”

Zhao Hai waved his hand and said, “Talking is useless, go, go guide me.” Ren complied and then led Zhao Hai to walk towards the back of the shop.

Right behind the shop was a very big cavern. There were large and small caves inside as well. These caves held people inside, the people only wore the simplest clothing on their bodies, just enough to cover important parts. The rest of their bodies were exposed.

Each cave had about 10 to 100 people in them, men and women were separated. It was only here that the face of the slave market was seen, they didn’t seem like people at all, they were more like beasts waiting to be sold.

Zhao Hai looked at these slaves, he has to admit, these slaves were really very good. They were all young people, and from their skin, one could see that they are all very healthy.

From their eyes, Zhao Hai can see that all of them were strictly trained. Their eyes were expressionless much like their faces, they looked just like Zhao Hai’s undead. If it weren’t for the fact that they were living, Zhao Hai might have thought that all of them were undead.

Zhao Hai looked at these slaves calmly. He was currently a noble, he couldn’t just lose heart in front of these slaves, otherwise he would be looked down by the other nobles.

With the state of the continent, nobles wouldn’t lose their hearts when dealing with slaves. Because of this, Zhao Hai also acted as though he was calm.

Looking at the slaves, Zhao Hai nodded and then turned to Ren, “Good, Mister Ren, these are very good. Alright, I’ll go take 200 men and 200 women. These people should be enough for my castle.”

Ren nodded immediately and said, “This is not a problem, Sir Marquis. You can take them any time you want. If Sir Marquis wants us to deliver them on your doorstep, as long as we have your address, then we can send these slaves as soon as possible.”

Zhao Hai nodded, then turned to Ren and said, “Ren, does your shop some specially skilled slaves? Like Artisan slaves, or some battle salves? As long as you have those slaves, then I also want a lot of them.”

When Ren heard Zhao Hai, his eyes couldn’t help but turn bright, he quickly replied, “I invite the Marquis to the living room, this is not the place to talk.” Zhao Hai nodded and then returned to the living room. Ren went to give a person some commands before he served Zhao Hai a new cup of tea.

To be honest, Ren was initially quite disappointed, 200 male and 200 female slaves can only be considered to be a small scale transaction in a shop like this. Altogether, it only costs 300-400 gold coins, their shop can only make a little amount of money. Average nobles would buy slaves in transactions that involved thousands to tens of thousands of gold coins. Some transactions even make it to to a hundred thousand gold coins. Compared to Zhao Hai’s small transaction, it’s certainly not worth mentioning.

But when he heard that Zhao Hai wanted some artisan slaves and battle slaves, Ren became happy. Artisan slaves and battle slaves are several times more expensive than average slaves, some were even several hundred times more expensive.

If Zhao Hai wanted dozens of artisan slaves and battle slaves, it certainly wouldn’t be called a small-scale transaction. But he didn’t believe that Zhao Hai would buy so much, all of the artisans and battle slaves on their shop was worth millions of gold coins; such number wasn’t small. Average nobles wouldn’t spend that much money on slaves.

After Zhao Hai and the others arrived at the living room and sat down, Ren immediately went to Zhao Hai’s side and said, “Sir Marquis, we also have some artisan and battle slaves at the shop. But sir must know that the price of these artisan and battle slaves are very high. And these include the most ordinary ones among them.”

Zhao Hai nodded and then looked at Ren and said, “Ren, I don’t care about the price as long as they are worth it. I believe you know about the fact that I own Golden Island, what I need there the most were artisan slaves, we can discuss their prices. Also, if you have slaves that are whole families, I want them as well. Very young slaves are also good, but I want a discount on them.”

Ren understood Zhao Hai as he nodded, “The Marquis’ words certainly made this one feel relieved. This shop has a lot of good quality battle slaves as well as artisan slaves. Artisan slaves are have many types according to which production branch they are skilled in. And their prices depend on how skillful they are. We also have a lot of battle slaves with varying strengths, the stronger the slave, the more expensive it is.”

Zhao Hai nodded and said, “Let’s go look at the artisan slaves first.”

Ren nodded, then went to one side of the living room and took a big book from a bookshelf. Then he placed the book in front of Zhao Hai as he said, “Sir Marquis, this has all the names of our shop’s artisan slaves. Their situations are present as well, Sir Marquis can take a look.”

Zhao Hai nodded and then carefully took the book and read its contents. The artisan slaves in Ren’s shop were very good, all of them numbered more than 200 people. A lot of them were carpenters and masons, their speciality was also written. Quite a few of these slaves were blacksmiths and the like. What made Zhao Hai the most surprised was that there were actually two artisans that can brew alcohol, there was also one Potion master present.

Zhao Hai placed the book down and looked at Ren and said, “You really have a potion master slave? How can a potion master become a slave?”

Ren smiled and said, “Sir’s eyes are really as bright as torches, immediately noticing the problem at a glance. This potion master isn’t an ordinary person. He used to be a fairly famous potion master, but later in his life, he developed a highly toxic potion that had exploded, spreading its effects outside of his laboratory and had killed a lot of people. Because of this, he was demoted into becoming a slave, we had spent quite a lot of money in order to buy him.”

ZHao Hai nodded, he wasn’t very excited about this potion master. This was because he already has the Processing machine to make potions for him. If he wants a potion, he can just have the machine make a potion that was even better than ones that a potion master can make.

What Zhao Hai was interested about were the other slaves. Except 30 of them, the others had their own families with them, one of them was even a family of three generations.

Zhao Hai handed the book over to Laura and the others. Laura wasn’t polite and took the book and scanned through it. Meanwhile, Zhao Hai’s action made Ren surprised, but when she remembered who Laura was, he became calm again.

In Carson City, it wasn’t only Zhao Hai who had become famous, Laura and the others acquired some fame as well. Laura and Megan held the most fame. There was no need to mention Megan, she was one of the twin flowers of the Imperial Capital, it was impossible for any nobles who didn’t know of her. Because of Laura’s relationship with Zhao Hai, people went and had her background investigated. When they received their reports, they found out how formidable Laura was in the past.

She was a flower of Purcell Duchy. She started from scratch and managed to establish her own business presence in the duchy. She even managed to become the most powerful merchant of the duchy at one time.

Even the not too famous Meg has become famous right now. Meg was in herself a talented mage. This young and was already a 6th rank Water Mage. This basically meant that her future achievements would be limitless. Because of this, her reputation wasn’t any lower than Zhao Hai’s other fiance’s.

Laura carefully read the register and then nodded before handing it over to Megan. Megan took a look and then handed it over to Meg who also scanned through its contents. Zhao Hai looked at the three, then all of them made a nod.

Zhao Hai turned to Ren and said, “Ren, I want all of these slaves in this book. I also want those 400 slaves I mentioned before. Moreover, do you have some young slave? I want to buy some to train myself.”

Ren stared, then he became overjoyed, he didn’t expect Zhao Hai to take all of these slaves. This was surely a huge transaction, the overall price of these 200 slaves was around 200 thousand. The potion master alone was worth 20,000 gold coins.

A transaction worth 200 thousand was a huge business for even a shop like them. Ren quickly said, “We don’t have child slaves here because this was just a place to sell them. Slaves would only be sent here after being trained. Only artisan slaves who have their families with them have children included.”

Chapter 498: Wedding

Zhao Hai nodded and said, “I want some child slaves, go help me find some. The price is open for discussion.”

Ren nodded, “No matter how many slaves Sir Marquis wants, we can certainly provide.”

Zhao Hai nodded, then he thought for a  moment before saying, “Golden Island needs a lot of slaves right now. Those 400 slaves are only for my fort in Carson City. I still haven’t bought any for Golden Island. You go see whether you can provide me some young slaves. I also need some old and experienced ones, I have some facilities that needed managing.”

Ren couldn’t help but hold Zhao Hai in high esteem. General clients would only buy some young and strong slaves. Those who would buy old ones were very rare. This was because those slaves have been so overworked that their bodies aren’t very good anymore. Such slaves would only survive for only two years before dying. Because of that, nobody wanted to buy them.

From all of his years of selling slaves, Ren had come to know that these old slaves have its own uses. Although these old slaves cannot read, they had a lifetime of experience behind them. They understood situations that only an experienced person knows, like what disease a certain plant was suffering, the best time to plant, and there are even old slaves that can predict the weather. Those abilities are absolutely priceless.

But a lot of Nobles didn’t know about this. It was even possible for those Nobles to have never been on their territory in their entire life, they simply cannot understand farming. There was a substantial difference in income between Nobles who have old slaves compared to those without.

It was unfortunate that this difference wasn’t something that Nobles took note of. What they cared about was the strength of their slaves. It was because of this that they overexhaust their slaves and have them die an early death.

These old slaves were actually treasures. In Ren’s eyes, these slaves should be more expensive than the younger ones. But it was a pity that nobles do not share his views. What they always see was a slave that wouldn’t be able to live long. A lot of these old slaves just die miserable deaths.

Ren also understood why Zhao Hai wanted to buy some child slaves. These child slaves are very malleable. If they were allowed to learn some crafting skills, then their price value would increase by dozens of times. A lot of slave merchants do this method now. They would buy some child slaves and then find some artisan slaves to train them. When those child slaves grow , they would have learned a lot and would be sold at the price of artisan slaves. This would bring them a huge profit.

Zhao Hai buying slaves along with their families are also good as well. Ren had seen a lot of slaves who went crazy because they became separated from their families, so their handlers had no choice but to kill them. Slaves are people as well, Ren knew this, so he saw Zhao Hai’s approach to be very agreeable.

Zhao Hai looked at Ren and then asked, “Ren? What’s wrong?”

Ren recovered, then he shook his head hastily and said, “There’s no problem. How many slaves does Sir Marquis want?”

Zhao Hai thought for a moment before saying, “A hundred thousand, having more isn’t a problem, but make sure that there aren’t less.”

Ren became ecstatic, he immediately said, “Sir Marquis can be rest assured, as long as you give me a month to prepare, those hundred thousand slaves wouldn’t be a problem. Do you want us to deliver those slaves to Golden Island for you?”

Zhao Hai shook his head and said, “When they are prepared, you send me a message at my fort. Then wait for my instruction before sending them there. Right, how much money do I need to give you?”

Ren nodded, then he went to the side and did some calculations before saying, “Sir Marquis, everything is 213 thousand gold coins. It would be fine if Sir Marquis paid 210 thousand gold coins, we can waive the three thousand.”

Zhao Hai smiled faintly and then waved his hand as two crystal cards appeared. There were some markings on the cards, one showed 200 thousand while the other has 10 thousand. These cards were issued by banks and were commonly used by nobles.

These banks made this crystal cards with different denominations. All of them had special markings made by their banks and can be revealed as long as energy was provided. By doing this, one could see the authenticity of these cards.

Ren had been dealing with these cards all year round, he can distinguish between fake and real in one look. But authentication wasn’t needed, Zhao Hai was famous, it would be impossible for him to use a fake crystal card.

Ren accepted the cards and said, “Marquis can be rest assured, we shall certainly provide good slaves. Do you want to see the artisan slaves?”

Zhao Hai shook his head and said, “No need, I believe that you won’t deceive me. There aren’t a lot of people in the continent that would dare to do so.”

Ren felt his heart stop, he was sure that Zhao Hai wasn’t joking. What he said was true, there won’t be many people in this world who would dare deceive him. Those who dared to deceive him would have to face death. Even his backers wouldn’t dare to offend Zhao Hai.

Ren immediately said, “Sir Marquis is cracking a joke. Our little store wouldn’t be able to withstand your fury. Mister can be rest assured, I can assure you that our shop would certainly ensure the safety and security of your goods.”

Zhao Hai nodded and said, “That’s good. I’ll go back first, I’ll go look at your battle slaves in another time.” Then he stood up and headed out.

They boarded their carriage outside and then headed out of the slave market. Laura looked at Zhao Hai and said, “Brother Hai, we bought a lot of slaves this time. I think we should inform Grandpa Green about it ”

Zhao Hai nodded and said, “Rest assured, not only this matter, I will also talk to him about another important thing.”

Laura looked at Zhao Hai, she was puzzled as she said, “What’s that? Is there anything important matter left? We already bought the castle. As long as the renovations are finished, we can immediately move in. When that time comes, we can then hold a banquet. I think there’s no other matter left.”

Zhao Hai smiled faintly and said, “This matter must be taken care of, otherwise Grandpa Green would throw me into a pit of fire.” Laura still didn’t understand what Zhao Hai meant. But seeing that Zhao Hai didn’t want to say it, she didn’t ask anymore.

Soon, they arrived at the fort. Zhao Hai already had the name Wild Dragon Castle prepared for the place. The flag that was raised also had the Buda Clan’s Wild Dragon Insignia. This along with the name of the fort, people would certainly know that this place belonged to the Buda Clan.

At this time , there were a lot of undead in the castle being busy. They were carrying the final renovations of the castle. This was Carson City, the capital of Rosen Empire, the place with the largest distribution center in the continent. Because of this, it was very convenient to buy anything, so Zhao Hai was able to confidently do renovations on the fort. He was also preparing to have Cai’er place one of her branches on Wild Dragon Castle.

When noon came, Ren sent people to deliver more than 600 slaves to Wild Dragon Castle. Zhao Hai had some of these slaves go to Iron Mountain Fort under the leadership of Rockhead and Blockhead. He had the two of them handle the newcomers to do specific jobs at Wild Dragon Castle.

When it came to managing slaves, Blockhead and Rockhead already had a few tricks. They had already been assigned by Zhao Hai to do some management tasks before. And after having them study at the school, the two should be able to handle the slaves without a problem.

Most importantly, both of them spent a long time with Zhao Hai. They understood his habits as well as what he liked. The 400 slaves that were left in the castle needed to be managed well, otherwise Zhao Hai wouldn’t feel comfortable in living there.

The artisan slaves were easier to manage. Zhao Hai directly transferred them to Iron Mountain Fort since the fort badly needed people like them right now. However, the Potion Master was referred by Zhao Hai to Shun’s mother. Shun’s mother studies potion and that potion master just happens to be an expert in it. Zhao Hai wanted to the slave to teach Shun’s Mother.

After having arranged these people, Zhao Hai went to the Space where Green and the others were waiting for him. Green and the others knew that Zhao Hai was busy with the slaves, therefore they didn’t go and disturb him. After all, they fully supported Zhao Hai’s methods.

After the group arrived at the villa’s living room, Zhao Hai turned to Green and said, “Grandpa Green, I went to see you today for two matters. The first one was to tell you that I had bought 100 thousand Human slaves. They aren’t artisan slaves, just regular ones. After they arrive, I want to have them farm on the Black Wasteland. I have a lot to do in the future, so I won’t have enough time to do farming. We should make a village for them outside the fort.”

Green nodded and said, “Alright, that’s good. But although we already have 200 thousand people coming, I still think that they aren’t enough to farm the Black Wasteland. I suggest the young master to have them forage on the land as well as raise some livestock. With this, we may have more income from having a ranch. If we don’t do this, the big area of the Black Wasteland would be wasted.”

Zhao Hai nodded and said, “That’s a good idea. Before utilizing the whole area for farming, we might as well use the unused parts for rearing animals.”

Green nodded as well then said, “The second matter?”

Zhao Hai took a deep breath, then he looked deeply at Laura and the others who were listening at the side before turning his head to Green and said, “Now that our Buda Clan’s reputation has been established, as well as having our own castle and fief, I want to officially marry Laura and the others. Having them be my fiancees for too long will make people gossip.”

Green stared, and also Kun as well as Laura and the others. They hadn’t thought of this, the matters that they had been handling were too big recently, they have absolutely forgotten the marriage. Now that Zhao Hai opened the topic, they were suddenly left staring blankly.

After some time, Green recovered as he laughed and said, “Right, right, I also think it’s time for young master’s wedding to be pushed through. We have been very busy these days that I’ve completely forgotten about it. Good, good, I’ll immediately go arrange it.”

Kun was happy as well, Laura being somewhat of Zhao Hai’s follower has hurt her reputation. However, Zhao Hai insisted that they should wait until the Buda Clan establishes themselves before carrying on to their marriage. Finally, the opportunity to do so has arrived.

Laura and the others were also happy , when Zhao Hai goes out, he can only introduce them as his fiancees, this made them feel a little bit uncomfortable. Now, it’s time for them to be married.

Merine was also in the living room, she was naturally the happiest one in the room, she smiled and said, “Young Master, fantastic! We’ll go and give respects to the ancestors and tell them the good news.”

Zhao Hai smiled and said, “Alright, then it’s all settled. Grandpa Green, Grandpa Kun, I need to ask you to help me prepare the invitations. I’ll go to Grandpa Randolph tomorrow and ask him for help as well.”

Green replied with a smile, “Alright. But Young Master, how long are you planning to prepare for this wedding?”

Zhao Hai understood what Green was saying, the latter wanted the date to be farther off. With this, they would be able to prepare the invitations properly as well as having the event more grand. However, Zhao Hai doesn’t have much time right now, he turned to Green and said, “Grandpa Green, I want the ceremony to happen as soon as possible because I need to go the the Prairie. I also need to take care of the business with the merfolk.”

Green thought for a moment and nodded, “Alright, spring is coming to the Prairie, it wouldn’t be good if you head there late. Very well, we’ll see to it that it happens as soon as possible. I think we should also discuss this matter with Randolph, in any case, we need to respect his opinion on this matter. Old Kun, what do you think?”

Kun nodded and smiled, “That’s fine. I’ll go tell Karen about this matter. Right, there should also be an invitation for the Markey Family. I’d like to see their reaction, if they dare act up, then they can’t blame us for being impolite.”

Green snorted and said, “If they dare, do they really think that the Buda Clan is the same as before? Let’s see if they act unreasonably this time, hmph. We must make this wedding ceremony as grand as possible, let’s make sure that all of the people in the continent gets to hear it.”

Zhao Hai nodded and said, “I’d like that, I can’t let my fiancees feel wronged. If not because of this fear, the wedding might have been already done. This time, we must make it grand. I think we should do it in Wild Dragon Castle, what does Grandpa Green think?”

Green thought and then shook his head, “Young Master, I think it would be better if we do it at Golden Island. That’s our domain, if people would want to act impolitely, then we can deal with them immediately!”

Chapter 499: Wedding Date Has Been Decided

Zhao Hai stared, he didn’t even think about doing his wedding at Golden Island. This was because there was nothing there. He preferred to do his wedding at the castle, that would be more befitting for a noble.

Seeing that Zhao Hai was silent and frowning, Green got confused and said, “Young Master? Is Golden Island not good?”

Zhao Hai forced a smile and said, “Grandpa Green, there aren’t any good structures in Golden Island yet. There are only tunnels and caves there, I don’t think it would be a good idea to have our wedding at that place.”

Green thought about it and nodded, “This is really an issue, there aren’t any good enough structures at Golden Island. If we do the wedding there, then it would really seem simple.”

Laura opened her mouth and said, “Brother Hai, Grandpa Green, I really don’t think it’s bad. Golden Island is our territory, we can handle matters there anyway we like, completely different to Carson City. Some people might want to cause trouble during the ceremony, so there will be fighting. Although Brother Hai is very strong, we very much prefer to hide it. The Emperor wouldn’t’ really care what we do on the island, but in Carson City? If we show our strength, it might even frighten him. This would be troublesome. This is why I think it would be best if we do the wedding ceremony on Golden Island.”

When Laura heard that Zhao Hai was going to marry her, she naturally became shy. But doing so was good, they already wanted to marry Zhao Hai for so long. Now that their desires had been met, they were more happy than shy. Also, they aren’t ordinary women, so they don’t act like them.

Hearing Laura made Zhao Hai’s mind unexpectedly calm. He had already offended the Aksu Empire, the other nations were also under the heavy influence of the Radiant Church. If they go there, then they won’t be able to have any good days. At this point, they can only rely on the Rosen Empire to accommodate them. He was afraid that he can only defend Golden Island in his lifetime, Zhao Hai didn’t want this, so he had no choice but to consider the empire in his decisions.

After thinking for a moment, Zhao Hai nodded, “It’s a pity, although Golden Island’s environment is good, there aren’t just any good structures there. If we do our wedding there, then I would only be doing you women injustice.”

Laura smiled and said, “We really don’t mind it Brother Hai, there’s no such thing as injustice. With the Buda Clan’s reputation, there aren’t anyone who dared to underestimate us. Don’t worry about doing our wedding in such an ordinary place, nobody would dare comment on it.”

Zhao Hai looked at Laura and then smiled, “Alright, then I’ll go talk to Grandpa Randolph tomorrow about the wedding date. After having it settled, we’ll begin to make the invitations. I already had the processing machine make the templates for the invitation, the only thing missing are the names as well as the date.”

After that, Green and the others went and continued to talk to Zhao Hai about the details about the wedding, the reception, the food, the drinks, as well as who to invite. They must prepare the event properly, Zhao Hai’s status wasn’t ordinary. Because of this, his visitors would be similarly not ordinary, if the visitors are unsatisfied, their Clan might offend them.

Fortunately, Green and the others were quite used to being stewards, so these kinds of things aren’t enough to burden them. Since Zhao Hai raised this matter, Green and the others needed to fulfil his requirements, these matters would be left for them to arrange.

Presently, the Space wasn’t lacking any kinds of commodities, therefore Green was able to manage everything easily. Additionally, they have more than 1 million undead to command, handling this matter was too easy.

After reaching an agreement, Zhao Hai and the others rested. Zhao Hai returned to his room and laid down on the bed, he also went to see the situation back on Golden Island.

After one month of construction, the shops on the island had already been built up. But these shops were mostly made with stone which the undead mined from the island, since they aren’t exploited, they are the best product left on the island. Even with the Shelley Family’s five-story hotel, there wasn’t any decent building on the island. Holding a wedding in such a place was such a injustice to Laura and the others. Zhao Hai really didn’t want this event to be a lifelong regret for them.

Although his eyes were already closed while he lied down, Zhao Hai’s head still stayed constantly moving. This was also one of his rituals. Before sleeping, he would think about all the things that he hadn’t managed to handle during the day. This was because he believed that the time where the mind is most active was just before sleeping. If he thought over the matters of the day, he might get some great inspirations to deal with them.

Sure enough, Zhao Hai wasn’t left disappointed this time. When he was just having a headache about dealing with the structures on Golden Island, he suddenly thought of a certain image.

This image wasn’t anything else other than a sea of flowers. It was a flower garden, everything in it was made of flowers, even the walls were made of plants.

Zhao Hai was originally starting to fall asleep, but when this image appeared, his eyes immediately turned bright. This scene was extremely familiar, this looked exactly like the Carrion Swamp’s Flower City!

After he thought of this, Zhao Hai immediately summoned Cai’er over using his thought. Cai’er immediately appeared on the room as she looked at Zhao Hai and said, “Young Master, what matters did you call me for?”

Zhao Hai looked at Cai’er and said, “Cai’er, can you send a branch over to Golden Island and have it formed into a castle? I like to use it to hold my wedding.”

Cai’er nodded and said, “I can, Young Master. Since I leveled up, I can even make a flower garden as large as a big city.”

Zhao Hai’s face showed his excitement as he said, “There’s no need to make it so big, just make it as large as Wild Dragon Castle. Remember, make its color and atmosphere similar to Flower City.”

Cai’er nodded and said, “Alright, Young Master, I’ll go do it immediately.” Then she flashed as she vanished. Zhao Hai breathed a sigh of relief. He doesn’t plan to tell the girls about this, he wanted to give them a pleasant surprise when the time came.

The next morning, Zhao Hai came out of the Space and sat on his carriage as he headed to Dark Soldier Fort. Naturally, Laura and the others were with him as well. Actually, for someone like Megan, if she still wasn’t married, then she would need to stay in Dark Soldier Fort. However, Megan strongly disagreed. Additionally, Randolph also saw that Zhao Hai already had two fiancees on his side, if Megan was at home all the time while Laura and Meg were with Zhao Hai, it would probably make Zhao Hao favor Laura and Meg more. Because of this, Randolph chose to have Megan also stay by Zhao Hai’s side.

Upon arriving at Dark Soldier Fort, Zhao Hai was immediately welcomed to Randolph’s study. Zhao Hai saw only Randolph inside the study since Smith was already back at Sky Water City. The city cannot survive for long without Smith at the helm.

Seeing Zhao Hai come, Randolph smiled and said, “What brings you here today? You have a lot of matters to attend to, you don’t have much time to come and visit me here.”

Zhao Hai smiled faintly and said, “Grandpa Randolph, I’m here to discuss with you about a matter of deep importance.”

Randolph looked at him and said, “What matter?”

Zhao Hai smiled, “I want to wed Megan soon, I chose Golden Island for the venue.”

Randolph stared blankly for a moment before looking at Zhao Hai and sighed, “Right, Megan already follows you everyday. If you don’t hold a wedding, her reputation would be affected. Also, you’re still young, men your age are very thirsty. If anything goes wrong before the wedding, things wouldn’t be too good. Alright, I agree, when do you plan to hold it?”

Zhao Hai’s mind went black with Randolph’s dark words. He really didn’t think that Randolph would have such thoughts. But when he thought about it, he was at Ark Continent and not Earth. Here, it was quite common to be scoffed at when people live together before marriage. Randolph was just afraid that Zhao Hai wouldn’t be able to endure.

Zhao Hai immediately recovered and said, “The sooner the better. I still need to head to the Prairie after the ceremony. There are a lot of things I need to handle there, and there isn’t enough time to do it.”

Randolph nodded and then thought for a moment before he said, “How about ten days later. We should immediately go and prepare the invitations. Then hand them over along with the notification that the wedding would be ten days later at Golden Island.”

Zhao Hai nodded and said, “I already have the invitations made. The only thing missing from them are the dates, I’ll have them prepared immediately.”

Randolph nodded, “Go and prepare them. We have a lot of things to take care of, I’ll do my part here at the fort.” Zhao Hai nodded, then he gave Randolph a greeting before heading out. After returning to the castle, he immediately had the processing machine print the dates on to the cards before having them sent.

There are a lot of invitations that Zhao Hai needed to send this time, the farthest one was to Evan, while some were sent to the other Nobles of the Rosen Empire. Although it can be said that Zhao Hai doesn’t have too deep of a relationship with these nobles, he had already met them at various banquets. It would be disrespectful in his part to not send them an invitation.

Fortunately, Cai’er had already taken down the names of these nobles, making the manufacturing of the invitations much easier. After printing the names of these people, the invitations were then sent over.

Zhao Hai didn’t have a lot of people by his side, therefore most of these invitations were sent either by undead or Blood Hawk. This was a new and odd way of sending invitations.

While Zhao Hai became very busy in preparing for the wedding, the people outside were very excited. The Buda Clan’s reputation has been quite loud recently. These people knew that the Buda Clan wasn’t only powerful, they also had the literal golden egg which was Golden Island. This matter made people very jealous, but they weren’t able to do anything about it.

Now that Zhao Hai was holding his wedding, this made the small and medium sized noble clans feel an opportunity. As long as you can participate in the wedding and form a connection with the Buda Clan, one’s rise in the future would be more reachable.

At this moment, another information came out which made these nobles more inclined to throw their lot with the Buda Clan. Even if they cannot be under the clan’s umbrella, at the very least they needed to make a good impression.

Chapter 500: Marriage Bestowment

The Rosen Empire’s Emperor bestows a marriage to Zhao Hai with his daughter, the 9th Princess Lizzy, and she was to be a normal wife!

People on the continent weren’t estranged to this kind of thing, they knew that Grand Dukes would generally be bestowed marriages, and such person was a very lucky man.

When this news arrived to the Buda Clan, Zhao Hai and the others were shocked. Zhao Hai wasn’t actually glad, he was startled to receive such a decree.

After this information passed on, the entire continent seethed with excitement. The 9th Princess of Rosen Empire, the most powerful nation on the continent, one of Carson City’s Twin Flowers, the most dotted daughter of the emperor, she was attractive, intelligent, a pureblood noble, she was the continent’s number 1 candidate for marriage.

But such a person was actually bestowed to Zhao Hai, and as a formal wife! In other words, after Lizzy marries into the Buda Clan, her status would be the same as Laura and the others. Her position as a princess would be placed on the side.

This was surely a dropped bomb to the minds of the nobles of the continent. However, for Zhao Hai, this wasn’t a good thing. If he marries the princess, people who had unrequited love for her would surely be his mortal enemy. This would certainly bring a lot of hidden enemies to the Buda Clan.

When Zhao Hai heard this decree, he was absolutely terrified. He didn’t want to accept this decree, but Green and the others forced him to accept it.

After the person that served the decree left, Zhao Hai was left in the living room staring at Green. Green didn’t budge, as though nothing just happened, he stayed very calm. What Zhao Hai was surprised about was the fact that Laura and the others were calm as well.

Zhao Hai looked at Laura and said, “Laura, why would you make me accept this? This would be unfair to you, I only met Princess Lizzy once at Charlie’s residence. With this marriage bestowment, not only would it be unfair to you, it would also be unfair to Princess Lizzy.”

Laura looked at Zhao Hai and then faintly smiled, “Brother Hai, you don’t need to be so anxious. It’s alright. I think that it was Princess Lizzy who wanted to marry you, otherwise this decree wouldn’t have passed. Princess Lizzy is extremely favored by the Emperor, moreover, with the Rosen Empire’s strength, it wouldn’t be a problem for them to find a better candidate. In this case, it can only be because of Princess Lizzy that this decree was accepted.”

Zhao Hai stared, “Is that really the case? But how come I couldn’t see that Princess Lizzy wanted to marry me? Moreover, for her to make this decree happen, wouldn’t it be too much for a princess to do?”

Megan smiled and said, “Big Brother Hai, you don’t know but yourself has that kind of thing that women gets attracted to. In the beginning, it was also because of this that I got to like you. We hadn’t even met a lot of times before, nor did we exchange a lot of words.”

Laura smiled, “Additionally, Brother Hai shouldn’t forget, you have rescued the Princess’ life. I’m quite sure that it was because of this that Princess Lizzy came to like you.”

At this time, a voice was suddenly heard from the door, “Right, it’s because of that.”

Zhao Hai and the others turned their heads towards the door and saw Charlie. The Third Prince was led by the servant to was guarding the door. The servant didn’t announce Charlie’s arrival therefore Zhao Hai and the others were unable to notice him.

Zhao Hai and the others immediately gave Charlie a salute, Charlie waved his hand and said, “I didn’t make the servant announce my arrival. Little Hai, I came here today to talk to you about this decree.”

Zhao Hai nodded and invited Charlie to sit down. After having a seat, Charlie looked at Zhao Hai and said, “Little Hai, I know that you have been hiding from Lizzy these past few days. However, Lizzy hasn’t forgotten about you, she actually placed you in her heart. The imperial decree came about when Lizzy heard that you are getting married. She kneeled in front of father, the Emperor, saying that she wanted to marry you, and that she wouldn’t marry anyone else.”

Zhao Hai stared, then he smiled bitterly. He really didn’t have anything to say. He only met Lizzy once, and when he sees her in a banquet, he would do his best to hide from her. With this, how could Lizzy actually have deep feelings for him?

Zhao Hai still didn’t understand that since Lizzy was a nation’s Princess, the plan succeeding would certainly make her lose her own dignity. Zhao Hai appearing and saving her made Lizzy’s heart regard Zhao Hai very deeply. It had left her with a lasting impression of him.

Women are sometimes emotional beings. They believe in love at first sight more than men did. They liked romance and fantasy more, and they were also more likely to love blindly. There were previous occasions that women would fall in love with a man over a very small thing.

When Megan had thought that her life would end, Zhao Hai stepped in to save her. For Megan, this was very memorable. Because of this, Megan came to find herself having fallen in love with Zhao Hai. With the passing of time, this sentiment didn’t decrease, conversely, it was getting stronger and stronger.

Therefore, when Lizzy heard that Zhao Hai was going to be married, her emotions defeated her reason. She immediately ran to the Emperor and kneeled. She asked the Emperor to bestow her to Zhao Hai, moreover she stated that she won’t marry any other man.

Knowing about the beginning and the conclusion of this matter, the only thing that Zhao Hai can do was sigh. He didn’t say anything, he understood that if he refused this decree, Lizzy might do something stupid. When that happens, his relationship with the Rosen Empire would go down the drain.

Regardless of whether or not Lizzy was indeed in love with him, refusing this bestowment would make Lizzy a laughingstock of the continent. When that happens, Lizzy would certainly be left with nothing to do. Also, since the Emperor heavily favored Lizzy, the Buda Clan would suffer an unfortunate fate. Not only the Buda Clan, the Calci Family, and the Crook Family would share the same fate.

Zhao Hai sighed and then forced a smile, “I initially thought that I wouldn’t marry any other women after Laura and the others. Not only would I be fair to Laura and the others, I would also be fair to the other women, but I didn’t expect Princess Lizzy to actually find favor towards me. God really won’t leave me at peace. Your Highness, rest assured, this Zhao Hai would surely take the Princess as a wife and will treat her like Laura and the others. Right, Your Highness, we shall be married at Golden Island, and can you see to it that Princess Lizzy gets to Wild Dragon Castle? We still need to discuss about the marriage matters.”

Charlie looked at Zhao Hai and smiled, “Alright, I shall tell this to father. But kid, you really are quite lucky. You’re also going to be my brother-in-law in the future. Hahahaha.”

Zhao Hai was speechless at Charlie’s remark, he didn’t think that Charlie would be thinking about such things. At this time, Green and the others were actually very happy. Zhao Hai had become the Rosen Emperor’s son-in-law. For the Buda Clan, this was a very huge thing.

Green didn’t even consider that Zhao Hai marrying the princess would heavily offend the other nobles. In Green’s eyes, Zhao Hai already had enough status to deserve it. Even if the other nobles gets angry, they wouldn’t be able to do anything. Among those who wanted to marry the princess, people who love her not for her status was very scarce.

So long as Lizzy gets married to Zhao Hai, the Buda Clan’s strength, along with the help of the Calci Family, would certainly rise at a very short time. Even those who wanted to put down the Buda Clan would need to consider the consequences.

It must be said that Green was a native of Ark Continent. He knew that nobles wouldn’t offend a strong power just because of a woman. They would certainly weigh the pros and cons of their actions.

When information about the Rosen Empire’s wedding bestowment to Zhao Hai spread out, all the Nobles in the continent understood that the Buda Clan had just acquired a formidable backer. There were now a lesser amount of people who would dare to offend them.

At the same time, the Nobles also felt strange, especially those who knew Zhao Hai. They knew that Zhao Hai’s appearance was very ordinary, so why would such beautiful women be throwing themselves at him? They didn’t understand what about him that attracts women.

But no matter what, everybody knew that establishing a connection with the Buda Clan would certainly bring huge benefits.

In the past, Zhao Hai didn’t make any invitations towards people who he didn’t have any previous interactions with. But now, it seemed that he had to do so since he would have the princess as his bride.

Marriage was really troublesome, especially for people like Zhao Hai where a lot of things needed to be considered. One of these was the clothes that they need to wear. Zhao Hai really disliked what they wore in Ark Continent, because of this, he made the processing machine make the clothes worn back on earth. Even if they looked excessive, they were also much more elegant.

Laura and the others didn’t say anything about their wedding dresses, naturally they also didn’t expose it. Ark Continent still wasn’t open to such a degree, but wonderful weddings were surely well regarded by the people of the continent.

As for the food and drinks, Zhao Hai prepared to do the same thing as banquets did back on earth. People who would come were certainly many, therefore, the food and drinks must be prepared well. Because of this, he had assigned ten Processing Machines to make the food and drinks.

The liquor that Zhao Hai had the Processing Machine made were red wine, white wine, and beer. Among these three liquors, only red wine was very common on the continent. The only white liquor on the continent was Zhao Hai’s milk wine, and finally the beer was only something that a select few were able to drink.

In order to prepare for this wedding, Zhao Hai placed a huge capital on it. He not only made Cai’er make a Seven-colored castle, he also allocated the Processing Machines to the preparations. Almost everything that was going to be used for the wedding was made using the Processing Machine. Zhao Hai knew that with the current manpower of the Buda Clan, they wouldn’t be able to finish everything in time. He also didn’t want for Randolph to intervene. Therefore, he had no choice but use the Processing Machine.

Chapter 501: Marriage

Ten days was too short for the people on the continent. In a blink of time, tend days passed by. In those ten days, Golden Island was constantly in a buzz. Nobles kept arriving at the island to the point where there aren’t any rooms left to stay in. There’s nothing left for these people but to stay in tents.

Seeing that he cannot do anything about the room problem, Zhao Hai chose to just put out some Beastman tents for them to use. The tents were very big, enough for a Beastman family to use, so it was certain that Humans can accommodate them.

These great Nobles haven’t seen such a tent before. In the end, a lot of them requested to have a tent and chose to stay in them instead of the finding a room.

Sitting in the tents and gazing at the green grasses of the mountains made these people feel as though they were in the Prairie. However, those Nobles who had merchant eyes could clearly see the specialness on the grass.

These grasses growing were actually Plate Silk Grass. These grasses were very tough, simply impossible for beasts to eat. But theses grasses can actually be used for medicine as well as be weaved into useful garments. Those few nobles who recognized this grass couldn’t help but have their eyes turn bright.

On the day of Zhao Hai’s marriage, the entire Golden Island was fully occupied. Not being able to stay of any other place, even the pier had ran out of places for the ships to dock.

Zhao Hai’s group arrived at the island three days prior, Lizzy was with them as well. When Zhao Hai saw Lizzy, he became somewhat surprised.

In God’s Grace Day, when Zhao Hai saw Lizzy, she was still  colorful and held a full posture. But now when Zhao Hai saw Lizzy, she was completely different from before. Her face was yellow, her body became very thin. She looked at least 20 pounds lighter and was thinner than before. She had become a skinny woman.

Seeing Lizzy’s appearance, Laura and the others felt sad. They understood what women were like if they weren’t able to see their lovers. Lizzy was certainly like this for the whole time.

When Zhao Hai looked at Lizzy’s appearance, she also felt sad. Even if he doesn’t have any feelings for Lizzy right now, he certainly felt Lizzy’s feelings for him. This made him touched.

After ten days of recuperation, Lizzy was no longer much different than her original figure. She felt much better than she did before.

ZHao Hai looked at Lizzy’s figure and went happy. When Lizzy looked at his eyes, he can even somewhat feel that he was melting.

After the group arrived at Golden Island, Zhao Hai made the women stay at the naval base while he made the final preparations on the venue. Everybody thought that Zhao Hai would perform the ceremony at the naval base, but they didn’t know that Zhao Hai was just using it as a disguise.

Seven Colored Castle was the place where Zhao Hai actually wanted to do the ceremony. It was built on the summit of the intersection of the two mountains. Zhao Hai already ordered a strict rule in the past that stated the prohibition of walking to this area. Because of this, it was impossible for people to see the situation inside.

It was finally the day of the marriage. According to the customs of the Ark Continent, Zhao Hai needed to pick the bride up from her home before they go to his house and get married there.

However, Zhao Hai’s situation was special, so he can only do all of this at Golden Island. Laura and the others would wait at the naval base as Zhao Hai picks them up.

All the people who came for the ceremony were invited by Zhao Hai to the T-shaped mountain and just outside Flower Castle. However, Flower Castle was covered with a dark fog so that nobody can see inside.

The nobles didn’t know what was going on. When they came, they expected that the ceremony would be carried out on the naval base. Now that they had been gathered in this place, they felt their hearts turn strange. They had heard that everytime Zhao Hai turned people into undead, he would use a dark fog along with it. At this time, the Nobles were thinking, “Will Zhao Hai turn us into undead as part of the celebration?”

Before long, they came to know the answer. They saw Zhao Hai’s carriage come out of the base and then circled around the place before taking his brides outside.

His horse carriage wasn’t a full car, but was something without a roof. Zhao Hai and the others were inside the carriage and can be fully seen by the people outside.

The nobles stood on the mountainside and were looking as Zhao Hai brought his brides out of the naval base. They also saw what the brides wore and even though they haven’t seen them before, they liked it and saw that they were beautiful.

These nobles thought that Zhao Hai arranged them here so that everyone can see the entire process of the wedding. They were very satisfied with this arrangement.

But they heard that the military base wasn’t preparing for food and drinks. So how does Zhao Hai plan to make them eat? Will they just go home after the ceremony? Isn’t this ceremony just too quick?

While the people were confused, they saw that Zhao Hai’s carriage was heading towards them. This startled them, they thought that after Zhao Hai receives his brides, they would go back to the naval base and continue the ceremony there. They didn’t expect that their carriage would actually go to them.

Before long, Zhao Hai’s carriage arrived in front of the crowd. The people looked dumbfounded at what they were seeing. In his formal dress, Zhao Hai had a red silk thread on his hand. The other end of the thread was divided into five, the threads were connected to the hands of Laura, Megan, Lizzy, Meg, and Ni’er, and in the middle of the thread was weaved into a flower-like appearance. The brides were wearing wedding dresses while holding a bouquet of beautiful flowers. The women’s smiles were more delicate than the flowers on their hands, people were staring at this view with a blank face.

Letting Ni’er marry was Laura’s idea. Laura knew that Ni’er wouldn’t want to leave her side forever. She reckoned that Ni’er would sooner or later become Zhao Hai’s woman, so they might as well have wed her at this time.

Zhao Hai agreed, he understood Laura’s thoughts so he didn’t oppose to it. Their current arrangement was one Zhao Hai came up with. There was no red silk thread tradition in the Ark Continent. Zhao Hai made his wedding according to the ancient ceremonies of China.

When Zhao Hai’s carriage passed by the Nobles, the nobles gave their applause. Regardless of what they thought, they need to send Zhao Hai their blessings.

The brides were also looking at the dark fog and were confused. They didn’t know what was going on since Zhao Hai withheld the ceremony procedures from them.

Zhao Hai arrived at the front of the undead and waved his hand, making them give way. Then he also waved his hand and had the dark fog go away.

When the dark fog spread out, everyone froze, the nobles were the same. This was because in front of them was a castle made of flowers. Whether it be the castle walls or the gate and even the castle itself, all of them were made up of flowers, seven-colored flowers large and small formed the entire castle.

At this time, the gate made out of flowers slowly opened. Green, who wore neat clothes along with Blockhead and Rockhead came out. The two guided the carriage towards the castle as Green incited the other nobles inside.

The nobles looked at the castle in surprise. They didn’t think that Zhao Hai could quietly come up with such a castle.

Among those who came, Randolph was the one most happy. Knowing that Zhao Hai wanted to hold the wedding at Golden Island made them unhappy. But seeing the Flower Castle right now, their discomfort disappeared. They didn’t expect Zhao Hai to be this good, very good.

Soon, the nobles were following Green as they entered the castle. Upon arriving inside, they noticed that even the floor was made of flowers. What they were stepping on was soft and felt like walking on a carpet.

Zhao Hai and his brides were waiting for their visitors on the main square. Among them, only Lizzy didn’t understand how this castle came to be. Since Zhao Hai hadn’t brought Lizzy to the Space, she was unaware about the existence of Cai’er. However, when she saw the castle, her heart couldn’t help but be moved, tears cannot stop flowing out of her eyes.

While inside the castle, the nobles were very curious about everything. The castle was made of flowers, everywhere was flowers, countless flowers.

When everyone arrived at the square, Green walked up to Zhao Hai’s side and coughed twice before saying, “I thank everyone for taking time out of your busy schedules to attend the wedding of Zhao Hai Buda, Laura Markey, Megan Calci, Lizzy Rosen, Meg Buda, and Ni’er Markey. I welcome you in behalf of the Buda Clan.

The people applauded, after they stopped, Green continued, “Zhao Hai Buda is the Buda Clan’s Patriarch. The Buda Clan is a family with a long history, and although it suffered a tribulation, it had stood up once again. Now, Zhao Hai Buda has chosen to marry his brides, showing everyone the love that they shared. Does anybody agree?”

This was the first time that the people present were able to experience this type of wedding. In the weddings that they had attended before, the ceremony only included the fetching of the brides and bringing them into the groom’s house. After then, the elders of the groom’s family would reside over the ceremony and offer their blessings and then have everyone toast a glass of wine before having the banquet. They didn’t understand why Green needed to introduce the background of the Buda Clan. However, since they were already here, all of them clamored in applause, some of them shouted and said, “Agree!”

Then Green looked at Zhao Hai’s and the brides’ eyes and saw that all of their faces were red. Even though this arrangement was Zhao Hai’s, when the event came, he couldn’t help but be embarrassed himself.

Green chuckled and then said, “Then I would start with my Granddaughter, Meg. She was the first one to know Zhao Hai Buda. At that time, Zhao Hai was called Adam Buda. He was a famous playboy back at Aksu Empire’s capital. But even so, my granddaughter still liked him and stayed by his side all the time. Even when Zhao Hai had drunk the Water of Nothingness, she was still at his side.”

The people issued a warm applause. Especially the females, they were moved by Meg’s passion.

Then Green said, “The second is Miss Laura. She was Purcell Duchy’s loved girl. Not only is she beautiful, she also has the talent to stand on her own and established a large merchant group. So why would such a woman be with Zhao Hai Buda? Then answer was because Zhao Hai had saved her life….” Green continued on and introduced Zhao Hai’s and Laura’s initial interactions. When the crowd listened to it, they also gave an applause to Laura.

Green waved his hand and then said, “Third is Miss Megan. Miss Megan is the little princess of the Calci Family. She’s a lovable girl, gentle, and is also very beautiful. Why would she be with Zhao Hai? The answer was because Zhao Hai….” then Green introduced how Zhao Hai saved Megan. Naturally he didn’t include the Space in his anecdotes. He only said that, at that time, Zhao Hai had given Laura a very small undead creature that can detect and defend against any assassins. Because of that Zhao Hai had managed to save Megan’s life. This was said in order for people to understand why Megan wanted to marry Zhao Hai. It turned out that Zhao Hai had actually saved her life. This made people who had done good things to Megan before feel comfortable, thus they applauded.

Then Green’s gaze turned to Lizzy and said, “Finally, I shall introduce you all to Her Highness Princess LIzzy. She is an honored noble, and her beauty is like the bright moon in the sky. So why would such a woman marry a man who already had many fiance’s? This was because Zhao Hai….” Then Green once again explained the circumstances between Zhao Hai and Lizzy. This time, he wasn’t polite. Even if he didn’t clearly state the persons involved, those who were present understood who it was. This made people know why Lizzy was suddenly bestowed to Zhao Hai. This also made the nobles present understand the big picture, their evaluation for the Crown Prince had now dropped by a few levels. How could they think of following a person who would even plot against their younger sister?

After waiting for the crowd’s applause to die out, Green nodded and then said, “Alright, now that we have been introduced to the to be wedded, i shall alsk Randolph Calci to come and officiate the ceremony.”

Randolph stared, he didn’t expect that he would have a part in the ceremony. But he immediately responded and stood up as he smiled while walking to Zhao Hai and the others. Green had already prepared the materials and handed Randolph the marriage certificates.

Randolph couldn’t help but stare at the certificate for a while. Then he recovered and said, “Zhao Hai, are you willing to be a responsible husband to these women? Do you vow to stay with them forever, in sickness and in health, for richer and for poorer?”

Chapter 502: Swatting Some Bugs Down

Randolph read the other words on the certificate. But when he said these, the other nobles felt their hearts tighten.

In Ark Continent, there aren’t any wedding pledges. This was because men were dominant in this society, and polygamy was allowed. Because of this, nobody would say vows during marriage.

When the nobles heard Randolph, they thought that Randolph was angry with Zhao Hai for having multiple wives. He asked this question in order to create some obstacles in Zhao Hai’s path. Now, everybody present wanted to see Zhao Hai’s reply.

Zhao Hai looked at the eyes of his to-be wives and smiled faintly before saying, “I do!”

Those under the stage burst into thunderous applause. Randolph kept his calm and turned his head towards the brides and said, “Laura, Megan, Lizzy, Meg, Ni’er, are you willing to be responsible wives to this man? Do you vow to stay with him forever, in sickness and in health, for richer and for poorer?”

When Randolph asked this, the crowd finally realized that this was a type of marriage testimony. This was the first time that they had seen this kind of thing, so they were very curious.

Without a single moment of pause, all of the brides said, “I do!” And was followed by another round of applause.[1]

Randolph nodded, and then he looked at Zhao Hai and the others and smiled, “Remember your pledges. In behalf of all the guests present, I shall offer our blessings to you. I declare that you are now officially, husband and wives. Your marriage has been legally bound and protected by Buda Clan’s territory, Golden Island.” He said as he gave Zhao Hai the certificate.

Zhao Hai took the certificate and held it up high, then an applause followed. One could feel that the applause this time was very sincere. The crowd knew that the wedding was entirely prepared by the Buda Clan, so the ceremony should have been made by the Buda Clan as well. The nobles could say that this was certainly the most unique wedding that they had attended. Especially the final part with the marriage lines and the pledge which added color to the wedding.

And in the end when Randolph said that their marriage was protected by the laws of Golden Island, the nobles were surprised. But they also understood that this was another guarantee for the authenticity of their marriage, making it even more solemn.

After doing all of these, Randolph stepped down from the stage. Then Green returned to Zhao Hai’s side as he addressed the audience, “I want to thank you all for coming, the wedding ceremony is over. I invite everyone to please follow the servant’s instructions as we go prepare the banquet.”

The nobles stared, they thought that the Buda Clan didn’t prepare anything to eat. When they were asked to eat here, they were too guilty that they couldn’t help but laugh.

At this time, people appeared. They stood in line and wore servant clothing. But when the nobles looked carefully, they noticed that these people weren’t ordinary servants, they were actually undead.

But these nobles didn’t panic, they knew that Zhao Hai was a Dark Mage, everybody knew about it. Therefore, it wouldn’t be strange for Zhao Hai to use undead as servants.

The undead who appeared were quite many, about a thousand. This number was enough to accommodate the about ten thousand nobles present.

The nobles thought that they would be invited to another place to dine, they never expected that the undead would just ask them to the side of the square and didn’t leave the area. When they were confused, the ground suddenly moved. The topmost layer suddenly receded, revealing another layer of flowers inside. The nobles were looking at this scene in surprise, they didn’t know what Zhao Hai was planning to do.

After the second layer of flowers appeared, they didn’t stop from moving upwards. Large flowers went up slowly and stopped when it was about the same height as a table. Also, along with the large flowers, then smaller flowers appeared and assumed the appearance of an ordinary stool. This arrangement was naturally to make the area as the place for a banquet.

The nobles understood why the flowers on the first layer receded. It was because those flowers were stepped on and were dirty so they cannot be used as tables and chairs. Therefore they retreated and had the second layer be the furniture since they were clean.

The undead quickly led the Nobles towards the tables and had them sit on the chairs. Upon sitting down, the nobles noticed the differences between the two flowers. The chair felt very soft, much softer than the ones they were used to. On the other hand, the table was very hard, they can even hear a ‘duo’ ‘duo’ sound when they tapped on it.

What intrigued these nobles was the material with which these flowers were made of, and also the flowers making up the castle as well.

After the nobles had sat down, rows upon rows of undead suddenly came out as they placed dishes on the table. These undead were all wearing uniform; black vests, white shirts, black pants, black leather shoes, black bow ties, and while gloves. Seeing them made people feel very comfortable.

It was at this point that the nobles got a new understanding with regards to the strength of the Buda Clan. It would’ve taken a lot of time before all of these uniforms were prepared. For Zhao Hai to do it in such a short time wasn’t a very easy task.

More importantly, except for Zhao Hai and the others, very few members of the Buda Clan had appeared. This placed a shadow over the true numbers of the Buda Clan. This made these people hold a small fear for Zhao Hai deep inside.

There were various dishes on their tables. The meal that Zhao Hai had prepared this time was done according to the Ark Continent’s customs. In front of the guests were a set of knives and forks, and the dishes were something that people from the continent were familiar with.

These dishes were also made using the Processing Machine, so there was nothing else to say about their taste. Although they might not reach the level of top chefs, it was much better than those that people ordinarily ate. Moreover, there were a lot of dishes present.

The nobles didn’t become polite. They immediately took their knives and forks and placed some dishes on their plates. But soon they discovered something special about the table. The petals of the tables were separated into two layers, with the larger layer placed below the smaller one. While the utensils were placed on the large layer, the dishes were placed on the small one. They noticed that the small layer was spinning slowly, enabling the guests to eat all the dishes without having to stand up.

These nobles were once again curious about Zhao Hai’s designs, but in the end they had to agree that this was a very good idea. If you go to the nobles’ banquets, even if you have your own spot to yourself, you still need to stand up and get your food. Some may see the gesture of standing up to be disrespectful and would much rather not eat and just stay sitting. With the Buda Clan’s design, one wouldn’t need to stand up just to eat some dishes.

Then, the undead brought over the liquor. All of them were placed inside transparent bottles, one bottle had a clear liquid, the other had red, and the last one was yellow.

Red wine was commonly consumed in the continent, but their process of manufacturing wasn’t very perfect. Because of this, the brewing of their wines weren’t done very well.

White wine and beer was very rare, most of the guests weren’t even able to understand what those two others drinks were. When the liquors were sent, each one of them had their own set of glasses. The characteristics of each liquor were also written on the bottle, making the nobles taste them with scrutiny.

There were some of them who liked the intensity of white wine, some of them loved the red wine, and some of them liked the aftertaste of beer. This reception to the liquor made the atmosphere of the room warmer.

At this time, a large cart was suddenly pulled towards the square. The cart was very big and was very long. On top of the cart was a whole Blade-Scale whale, completely roasted.

With regards to roasting Blade-Scale whale, Zhao Hai’s group was already quite experienced. They had successfully roasted one back at God’s Grace Day, so the one served today should be much better than the one before.

With how large a Blade-Scale whale was, the nobles were all staring blankly as it was carted in. While they were dumbfoundedly looking at the big fish, an undead servant suddenly wielded a blade as it sliced some meat on the whale and had them served to the tables.

The nobles were very curious about the taste of the Blade-Scale whale meat, not to mention how fragrant it was. With how a food’s appearance and smell affected one’s judgement, there was no wonder that the guests found the whale’s meat to be quite delicious.

The atmosphere became even more warmer, the guests were eating very happily. They didn’t expect the Buda Clan to deliver such a spectacular banquet.

The one that was happiest with the situation was Randolph. When Zhao Hai didn’t let him help, he thought that Zhao Hai was just doing it to save face. Because of that, he was afraid that Zhao Hai wouldn’t be able to deliver. But he didn’t think that Zhao Hai would actually make the guests satisfied. This thought gave Randolph a huge smile on his face.

At this time, a sound was suddenly heard from the skies, “Is Zhao Hai here? Have Laura and Karen come out! These two are traitors to the Markey Family! They need to come with us back to the Markey Family. This is an order!”

The nobles who were eating suddenly stopped and stared at the figure on the sky. There was no need to ask, it was certainly a 9th rank expert. However, these nobles weren’t very scared at this 9th rank right now. What all of them had in their minds were, “The Buda Clan’s Patriarch would have to swat an insect down!”

In the eyes of the nobles present, this man was just an insect waiting to be dealt with. How many nobles were currently present here? Almost all of the Great Clans of the Rosen Empire was present. And also, what was Zhao Hai’s status now? He was Calci Family’s son-in-law, the Rosen Emperor’s son-in-law, as well as the Buda Clan’s Patriarch. For such an expert to come here and demand for his father and wife to be handed over, what does this look like? If this expert isn’t swatted down, everybody would certainly feel strange.

Zhao Hai, who was currently talking to a noble, couldn’t help but smile faintly and said his apologies to the noble. Then he looked up at the 9th rank expert.

* * *

I don’t know if this was an error on the author’s part or just lnmtl, but this wasn’t in the original raw. I decided to add it myself.

Chapter 503: Triple Collaboration

The person on the sky was a warrior. He wore black warrior’s clothes and had a longsword at his back. The sword was very long, even much taller than him, it may even be more appropriate to call it a spear.

The man had a dark skin, he looked like a black man, but he was more golden in his color, one really couldn’t describe it. This person had a long scar, spanning from his right eye to the left corner of his mouth. His right eye was already non-functional, so he placed a black eyepatch over it.

An ominous person! The word ominous was the first thing that came into mind when looking at him. Zhao Hai took up a wine glass and smiled as he said, “Does mister want to attend my wedding? How about having a glass of wine?”

The 9th rank expert didn’t expect Zhao Hai to be very calm in this situation. He stared for a moment before he coldly snorted and said, “Who do you think you are? Talking to me like this. Go hand me Karen and Laura, or else even your undead wouldn’t be able to stop me!”

Zhao Hai looked at the man and smiled, “This one is Zhao Hai Buda, Laura is my wife and Karen is my father-in-law. Sir, not only did you trespass on my property, you even demanded for my wife and father-in-law and dare threaten my life. Do you think that this attitude is acceptable?”

The 9th rank expert became angry and he snorted, “You don’t have the qualifications to lecture me, boy. I don’t have the patience to talk with you, go hand over Laura and Karen, otherwise, you’ll die!”

Zhao Hai stil calmly looked at the 9th rank expert and said, “Mister doesn’t need to lose his temper. You’re just a piece. Go call out your remaining eight partners, there’s no need to play around here.”

When Zhao Hai said his words, the 9th rank as well as the nobles were surprised. The 9th rank didn’t expect Zhao Hai to know that he didn’t come alone this time. At the same time, the nobles didn’t expect that Zhao Hai would know that there are other 9th ranks in the vicinity.

The 9th rank expert looked at Zhao Hai and laughed, “Good, good, young man, you’re interesting. I didn’t think that those old fogies wouldn’t know how to count properly. You actually found out about them. Young man, you’re really talented, it’s a pity that you shall die today!”

Zhao Hai smiled faintly and said, “The one who dies is still uncertain.” Then he waved his hand as ten figures suddenly appeared from Golden Island. The ones at the castle cannot see the figures clearly but the 9th rank can. And from what he saw, it seemed like those ten were all 9th ranks, 9th rank Magic Beasts.

The one-eyed 9th ranks stared before his complexion changed. He looked at Zhao Hai and then suddenly swung his blade, sending a strand of Sword Qi heading towards Zhao Hai.

Zhao Hai didn’t move at all, then a sharp sound suddenly came as a golden light clashed with the Sword Qi. The attack immediately dissipated and the one-eyed man’s face immediately changed. As soon as his expression changed, he immediately turned around to run away. At the same time, the other eight 9th ranks also appeared and started to fly away from the island.

Zhao Hai looked at them flying away before he turned his head towards his guests and smiled, “Everybody, no need to be startled, come, come, let’s drink!” Then he started to offer drinks to the guests along with Laura and the others. However, the nobles weren’t quick to shift their thoughts away from what just happened. They knew that those 9th ranks wouldn’t have retreated for no reason, it was possible that they were frightened with that golden light. For that golden light to negate an attack of a 9th rank expert meant that the golden light belonged to another 9th rank. Moreover, this 9th rank should be under Zhao Hai’s influence. This made the nobles reevaluate their view of the Buda Clan once again.

The nobles continued to eat the dishes on their tables as Zhao Hai was offering them a toast. It was like nothing just happened at the square.

Soon after Zhao Hai offered a toast to everyone present, he stood on the stage and looked at the guests and said, “To everyone, I want to let you know that there’s no need to worry about what happened earlier. My Buda Clan had already solved the problem.” Then he waved his had as an undead creature appeared at the side. The undead was the one-eyed 9th rank expert from before. He even had his longsword at his back.

When the nobles looked at the undead, they were very sure that this man was the 9th rank expert from earlier. This was because his appearance rarely changed even if he had become an undead.

However, there were some nobles who didn’t believe Zhao Hai. While he looked at the guests, Zhao Hai smiled and said, “Gyuki, tell everyone what’s going on.”

The undead immediately gave Zhao Hai a bow before saying, “Yes, Young Master. I am Markey Family’s foreign elder. This time I was presented an order from the family to lure the Buda Clan’s 9th ranks far away. As soon as the Buda Clan’s 9th ranks become distracted, the other 9th ranks would come here and kill everyone. When that time comes, the Rosen Empire wouldn’t have many high ranking officials left. After which the opportunity to seize the Rosen Empire would arrive.”

Zhao Hai frowned and asked, “Does the Markey Family have the power to seize the Rosen Empire? Are all these 9th ranks from the Markey Family?”

Gyuki shook his head and said, “They’re not, Young Master. They aren’t all from the Markey Family. Only three of them are from the family, the other six are equally divided by both the Aksu Empire and the Radiant Church, three each. The three had reached an agreement that as soon as the nobles here are killed off, they can then attack and occupy the Rosen Empire.”

Upon hearing Gyuki’s words, every noble present went into an uproar. They didn’t believe Gyuki’s words in the beginning. It was just like Zhao Hai said, with the strength of the Markey Family, it would be impossible for them to occupy the Rosen Empire.

But when they heard that both the Aksu Empire and the Radiant Church were involved, they immediately believed it. They all knew that the Aksu Empire did indeed have sinister thoughts towards the Rosen Empire and the Radiant Church was also the same, starting from the time when the Rosen Empire started to suppress their religion. WIth this, it was very likely for the three of them to collaborate.

Moreover, these nobles also knew that those that attended today comprises about 80% of the Rosen Empire’s nobles. All of them were high ranking nobles, small families were simply no qualified to attend.So if these people suffers an accident, the Rosen Empire would surely fall into ruin. If the Aksu Empire and the Radiant Church used this opportunity, taking over the Rosen Empire wouldn’t be very difficult.

Zhao Hai looked at the nobles and said, “Now all of you are aware of the situation. However, there is no need to worry. The other 9th ranks aren’t able to escape. As long as everybody arrives at their homes safely, the plans of the Aksu Empire and the Radiant Church wouldn’t come into fruition. Everybody can be rest assured, you can all just enjoy the banquet in the meantime.”

The nobles had already seen a magnificent scene, so they became calm as soon as they heard Zhao Hai. They understood that Zhao Hai’s strength was enough to deal with 9th rank expert to the point that they can’t even leave the island.

The people became energized once again, there were even some who shouted loudly, “This wine would be wasted if the groom doesn’t come and offer us a toast!”

Zhao Hai laughed and said, “Alright, good, Hahaha. Then I shall give you another toast!” Then he held his wine and once again gave a toast to the guests. It was at this time that the nobles noticed something extraordinary. Zhao Hai had actually remembered each and every one of their names!

This was very noteworthy, there were several thousand nobles present. But Zhao Hai can unexpectedly remember all of them. This was really too astonishing.

The people drank liquor until the skies turned dark, after which the place started to thin out, a lot of nobles were very drunk. Zhao Hai led these people out and made sure that they reached their tents safely.

In the end, Zhao Hai had expelled every single person from Flower Castle. The only people that remained was himself and his five brides.

Zhao Hai went to Meg’s room first, Laura and the others accepted this as well. This was because Meg had been the woman who was beside Zhao Hai the longest. The other women gave her the opportunity to be the first this time.

Zhao Hai had drunk a lot of liquor, but he had also drank Life Liquid so he was completely sober. At this time, Meg was sitting in the room on her nuptial garments. Her heart was jumping crazily, she had waited for this day for a long time and it had finally arrived.

Zhao Hai gently opened the door and walked in. Meg looked at Zhao Hai and then immediately lowered her head in embarrassment. Zhao Hai looked at Meg’s appearance and smiled as he walked slowly towards her. As Zhao Hai came closer and closer, Meg’s face became redder and redder.

When Zhao Hai gently held Meg’s hand, her body couldn’t help but shudder. Zhao Hai looked at Meg and then whispered, “Meg, you finally became my wife. Are you happy?”

Meg gently nodded. Then Zhao Hai smiled faintly as he hugged Meg whose face was still getting redder. She didn’t struggle and just leaned her body towards Zhao Hai.

Zhao Hai looked at Meg’s face as he slowly lowered his head to kiss Meg’s forehead, then her nose, then her ear, then her cheeks, then her mouth……

While doing so, Zhao Hai gently untied Meg’s nuptial garments and slowly removed her clothes. The temperature of the room rose a few degrees as a romantic atmosphere permeated.

Before long, Meg’s lamp had gone out. The sound of man and woman was heard inside. And soon a woman’s voice sounded out as everything turned silent. Then conversation was heard.

“Young Master, you should go to Laura’s room.”

“No, I’ll accompany you tonight.”

“Young Master, you still haven’t…. You should go to Laura and the others. This evening is also their wedding night. If you don’t go, then wouldn’t they be sad?”

“But if I go, then what about you? I’m sure they will understand.”

“Young Master, if you don’t go, I will get angry.”

………………….

Before long, the same dialog was heard on the second room.

Chapter 504: Markey Family Changes Leadership

Zhao Hai’s wedding had ended, but the buzz surrounding it was still continuing. There were a lot of new things in Zhao Hai’s marriage, a lot of new experiences. It would take some time before people can digest them.

Also after Zhao Hai’s wedding, the Rosen Empire immediately declared the Radiant Church as an illegal organization, everyone who can report their movements inside the Empire would be rewarded greatly. And since the Aksu Empire wanted to derail the higher levels of the Rosen Empire, all of the diplomatic relations between the two empires had been cut off. And because of the Markey Family’s involvement, they were now wanted criminals in the empire.

Rosen Empire’s response gave Zhao Hai a surprise. However, since he was still in the period of marriage bliss, he didn’t care much about the happenings in the continent.

A week after living inside the castle, Zhao Hai wanted to let Cai’er retrieve it. However, Laura and the others disagreed, so in the end the castle stayed.

At this time, Zhao Hai and the others were sitting in the living room. Laura and the others were now acting very much like young married women as they sat beside Zhao Hai. Green, Merine, Kun, and Karen were also present.

Zhao Hai looked at Laura and Karen and said, “Laura, Father-in-law, the Markey Family disturbing my wedding made the Buda Clan lose face, I want to deal with them.”

Green and Merine weren’t speaking, the decision on this matter lies on the hands of Laura and Karen. After all, they were people from the Markey Family. If they agreed to deal with the Markey Family, then Zhao Hai wouldn’t be polite. If they wanted Zhao Hai to let the Markey Family off, then Zhao Hao wouldn’t touch them. Everything hinges on Laura and Karen.

Karen coldly snorted and said, “Why are you hesitating, deal with them, do you still think that we are from the Markey Family? From the moment we entered the Purcell Duchy, we already stopped treating ourselves as one of them. Since they disrupted Laura’s wedding, then I shall not spare their lives.”

Laura’s face was also cold as she said, “Brother Hai, no need to be polite, don’t worry about us and just go deal with them. If we don’t do something, people of the continent would think that our Buda Clan is fine to be bullied.”

Zhao Hai looked at Laura and Karen, then he faintly smiled, “Laura, father-in-law. If you say so, then I shall be impolite.”

Karen coldly said, “Do it. If I just have the strength then I had already taken care of my mother’s enmity that year. Now I’ll leave this matter into your hands.”

Zhao Hai smiled faintly and said, “Then I have a plan. Father-in-law, how about we take everything from the Markey Family and have Laura be the Matriarch?”

Karen gawked, then he suddenly smiled and said, “Good! That method is fantastic. The reason the Markey Family had become what it is today is because of my mother. If the family gets handed over to Laura, then it’ll be good for my mother’s memory. Alright, let’s do that.”

Zhao Hai laughed, then he turned to Laura and said, “Laura, my wife, I’ll have to leave the Markey Family to you later. The Markey Family’s business spans across half of the continent, how to manage it depends on you.”

Laura smiled faintly and said, “What? You don’t trust my management? With the Buda Clan as a backing, I don’t think anyone in the continent would want to annoy me.”

Zhao Hai cannot help but laugh when he heard Laura. Then the group entered the Space as Zhao Hai had Karen and Laura mark the Markey Family’s location on the map.

However, the Space’s map was still incomplete. So Zhao Hai released a hawk and had it bring the Ghost Staff to map the continent.

At this point, Lizzy was now aware of the Space. On the evening of the wedding, Zhao Hai brought Lizzy to the Space and talked about it with her before the two ‘celebrated’ their marriage. This explains why Lizzy wasn’t startled by the Space’s abilities.

The hawk used five days to map the continent. Naturally, by continent, it only meant the parts where humans had inhabited. The places where the Dwarves, Elves, and the Beastmen live were still left undiscovered. They just didn’t have the time.

After mapping the human areas of the continent, Zhao Hai immediately had Laura and Karen list the Markey Family’s shops. When they finish marking the shops, their operation shall then begin.

At this time, Zhao Hai was also introduced to another ability of the Space. As long as Laura and Karen told Cai’er about the emblem of the Markey Family as well as the affiliated nobles to the family, their stores would immediately be marked in the map. This was an ability that Cai’er had acquired when she broke through. Zhao Hai was very happy about this ability, this can surely save them a lot of time in the future.

Karen also told Zhao Hai that since the Markey Family had made a lot of enemies throughout the years, the headquarters of their family was changed. There were also fake headquarters placed all throughout the continent, only one of them was the real one. There were only a small number of people who knew about it, and unfortunately for the Markey Family, Karen was one of them.

The reason why Karen knew about the place was by coincidence. He had once heard his father tell his stepmother that the real headquarters of the Markey Family was somewhere none other than the original headquarters of the clan of Karen’s mother. After the Markey Family absorbed Karen’s mother’s clan, the Markey Family had carried out a secret plan to have their headquarters transferred to Karen’s mother’s clan.

The headquarters was constructed in secret, and there were fewer people who knew that this was the Markey Family’s headquarters. People wouldn’t think that the headquarters of a small noble family would actually be Markey Family’s real headquarters.

When Karen revealed this information, Cai’er immediately marked the place on the map and had it displayed on the monitor. The Markey Family’s headquarters wasn’t just a simple structure, it was actually made of gold!

A house made of gold, where everything from the tiles to the walls were made of the precious metal, and was covered in mud bricks in order to hide it from outside. This was to ensure that if one day the family gets taken down, the descendants can use the gold in the building to start from the very beginning. But unfortunately for them, this didn’t manage to evade the eyes of the monitor.

Zhao Hai quickly drew out his plan of action. Just like what he did with the Robert Family, he would stage an attack to all the shops of the Markey Family. But this time, Zhao Hai wouldn’t kill the personnel, he wanted to control and restrain them until Laura takes control of the entire Markey Family. If those managers surrendered, they would be spared, but if they won’t, then they would be killed!

The third day after Zhao Hai finished his plan, they made their move. This time, Zhao Hai wasn’t polite. The Markey Family didn’t hesitate to deal with him, additionally, Karen and Laura no longer held feelings for the family. With this in mind, how could Zhao Hai be polite?

In one night, all the immediate members of the Markey Family vanished from the continent. The only heir to the family that remained was Karen.

The Buda Clan’s thunderlike attack made the Great Clans of the continent startled. While Zhao Hai extinguished the Markey Family, Karen made his move and assumed the position of the family’s patriarch. Then he announced his claim to all of the Markey Family’s businesses.

And just as what Zhao Hai had thought before, there were some managers who immediately surrendered while there were others who had other plans. Zhao Hai didn’t become polite and quickly eliminated those who refused to surrender.

This went on for quite some time and when all the opposition was dealt with, Karen immediately announced his resignation as Patriarch and handed the position over to his daughter Laura.

The people of the continent had long thought that such a day would come, but they didn’t expect it to come this soon. They didn’t think that the Markey Family would fall into the hands of the Buda Clan this quickly.

But nobody in the continent said anything. First, because Laura and Karen were legitimate successors of the Markey Family. And the second, because they had recognized the Buda Clan’s strength.

Now there aren’t any people who dared to underestimate the Buda Clan. This was because the strength that they had displayed was very formidable.

After Laura took over the Markey Family, she immediately announced that the family would let go of 20% of their shops. And these shops were all positioned in the Aksu Empire. This had a huge effect on the Aksu Empire’s economy.

At the same time, Laura also gave up another 10% of their shops which were placed on several other nations besides the Rosen Empire. This had also affected the economies on those nations.

Although the Markey Family had given up on 30% of their shops, the other 70% was growing fast. Laura also used this opportunity to bring the managers of those shops over to her side, making her have full control over the family.

After Zhao Hai had dealt with the Markey Family, the Rosen Empire immediately took back their sanctions on their shops. However, they didn’t do the same for the Aksu Empire.

The Rosen Empire has now placed a firm foot on the ground and had all of its channels to Aksu Empire sealed. Whether it be by land or water, whether they be legal or illegal, all of them were blockaded.

The nobles of the Rosen Empire were unprecedented united, this was because all of them knew that the Markey Family and the Aksu Empire had conspired against 80% of them. Because of this, those nobles cannot just let Aksu Empire go off unscathed.

In Lifeline Canyon, the Aksu and Rosen Empire soldiers were already having minor conflicts with each other. Zhao Hai’s navy from Golden Island also made its move, disallowing ships from entering the waters of the Aksu Empire. This made the Aksu Empire experience a crisis.

This time, the Rosen Empire, the continent’s most powerful nation, wasn’t playing around. When they get serious and consolidate their power on one target, the strength that they displayed was explosive. Although this matter had caused some losses to the Rosen Empire, they were willing to accept it. They want the Aksu Empire to learn a lesson that they will not forget.

In comparison, the business in Golden Island was doing extremely good. There were a lot of pirates who used this opportunity to ravage the waters of the Aksu Empire. Then they would sell their loot in Golden Island, bringing huge profits to Zhao Hai’s fief.

Actually, Zhao Hai understood that it would be impossible for the Aksu Empire to be unable to trade for anything. There were pirates who looted the Aksu Empire that cooperated with some merchants from the empire to trade their goods on Golden Island.

But Zhao Hai only placed one eye on this situation. As long as they don’t abuse this system, Zhao Hai would just let it go. However, if someone were to actually do a huge transaction with the Aksu Empire, Zhao Hai would send his navy after them and sink their ships while looting their goods. After this happened for a few times, the merchants finally behaved themselves.

At this point, there weren’t a lot of things in Aksu Empire’s waters that can evade Zhao Hai’s ears. He had released a lot of marine creatures out at sea and had them monitor the ships. Zhao Hai was able to deal with those who abused the system because of this.

The Aksu Empire was regretting. They regretted their treatment of the Buda Clan in the past, they regretted that they had been part of the Radiant Church, and they had regretted that they had participated in dealing with the Buda Clan.

Since Southern King Boris was a huge part on these operations, a lot of people at his side decided to leave him. In their eyes, Boris was hopeless. He had offended a powerful family that was the Buda Clan. It was only a matter of time before he was dealt with, and these people didn’t want to follow him on his grave.

The Buda Clan’s strength was now well known, so there aren’t a lot of people who were willing to offend them. The Buda Clan was so strong that they can single handedly deal with nine 9th rank experts simultaneously. At this point, those who underestimated the Buda Clan would be courting death.

There were now more and more people who came to Golden Island, making the business of the place better and better. Nobody dared wreak havoc on the island. All of them were here to make money, they didn’t want to lose their heads just because they had offended the Buda Clan.

It took nearly a month before both the Markey Family and Golden Island got back on track. It was also time for Zhao Hai to take care of his matters back at the Beastman Prairie.

Chapter 506: Welcomed by the Tribe

It didn’t take a long time before the news about the Buda Clan giving the Rosen Empire some flying beasts spread out to the continent. The people became curious about how the Buda Clan had managed to train those flying beasts.

The most enthused people regarding this matter were from the Rosen Empire. Almost all of the Rosen Empire nobles had turned their heads towards Golden Island. These people had one goal and that was to see Zhao Hai and ask whether they could get their hands on some of those flying beasts.

But unfortunately for them, the answer that they all got was the same. Zhao Hai was currently in the Prairie, he wasn’t in Golden Island.

Naturally, the nobles became disappointed. However, it didn’t take them long before they shifted their sights. All of them turned to Randolph, since the Calci Family was Megan’s home. They wanted to see whether they can get a flying beast there.

But it was a pity that Randolph also didn’t have any Blood Hawks. But this didn’t disappoint Randolph at all, on the contrary, he was very satisfied with Zhao Hai’s methods.

The Rosen Emperor was very satisfied with how Zhao Hai handled this matter as well. It may seem like he doesn’t involve himself in any matters, but it was impossible for him to not know about what happens inside the empire. If Zhao Hai gives some Blood Hawks to Randolph, even in secret, it wouldn’t take a long time before the Emperor hears about it. This made the Emperor appreciate Zhao Hai more.

The Emperor knew that it was impossible for Zhao Hai to not give Randolph any Blood Hawks. But the Emperor was very clear that Zhao Hai would only give Randolph the Blood Hawks later in the future. Because of this, the Emperor can use this time to train a more skilled Air Force, this was equivalent to having a big step ahead of the others. This step might be small, but it can definitely play a crucial role in future battles.

Zhao Hai naturally knew about this, but he wasn’t thinking about it right now. At this time, he was riding the Blood Hawk and was heading towards the main camp of the Herculean Bulls. However, he also wasn’t thinking about the Prairie, he was currently focused on handling the Markey Family.

The Markey family is very big. Moreover, there were a lot of matters to attend to when managing them. Also, with how they do their businesses in the past, they had managed to offend a lot of people.

After Laura took over the leadership of the Markey Family, some small clans began to bring trouble. Because of this, they needed to deal with a lot of things.

Most importantly, the Markey Family’s headquarters was placed on a small island, it was not a safe location. In the end, Zhao Hai decided to move their headquarters over to Golden Island then have the Rosen Empire as their main business joint. As much as possible, they wouldn’t do business with the Aksu Empire.

This matter made them very busy. It was good that Zhao Hai had eliminated the other competitors for power, this made the transition much smoother.

Three days after the Air Force matter, the Blood Hawks were finally flying in the skies of the Prairie. They can arrive at an earlier time, but Zhao Hai deliberately chose to slow down so that people wouldn’t have a lot of suspicions.

After coming out of the Space, Zhao Hai immediately released Alien and then had it walk towards the Herculean Bull camp. They were currently inside the Herculean Bull’s domain so their travel went by smoothly.

Moreover, when the Herculean Bulls were dealing with the Fighting Bulls, they had already seen Alien. Because of this, Zhao Hai didn’t bother to set up any flags in fear that people wouldn’t recognize Alien.

Sure enough, a group of Herculean Bull cavalry came. When the group saw Alien, they immediately became happy. They had their bulls charge towards the undead making the newcomers, Megan and Lizzy, very worried. Looking at the two of them, Laura immediately comforted, “It’s fine, don’t worry. These people are here to greet Brother Hai. They treat Brother Hai as their benefactor.”

Just as Laura’s voice fell, the cavalry arrived by the side of Alien. Then the group dismounted and gave a bow. A person took a step forward and said, “Is His Highness the Prince inside?”

Zhao Hai smiled and walked out of Alien’s mouth. He looked at the beastmen and gave a big laugh, “I didn’t expect you to still remember my mount. How is the tribe doing? Is Big Brother Busy? Did he miss me?”

When the Herculean Bull saw Zhao Hai, his expression turned into delight as he answered, “This one has seen the Prince. The Patriarch is in the main camp, he always talked about the Prince daily.”

Zhao Hai laughed and said, “Alright, good. I haven’t drunk with Big Brother for a long time. Go lead me to him immediately. I want to have a good drink with Big Brother.” The Herculean Bulls smiled and then issued a loud cry before having their bulls head towards the main camp.

Laura and the others, who were still sitting inside alien, chuckled. Only Lizzy and Megan looked dumbfounded. They hadn’t seen Beastmen before, but from the descriptions that they had read, Beastmen were vicious beings and were barbaric in nature. But what they saw just now was completely different, the Beastmen who greeted Zhao Hai were actually very respectful.

When Zhao Hai returned to inside Alien’s body, they looked at each other’s eyes and smiled, “I’m thinking about serving Brother Wales with a roasted Blade-Scale, what do you think?”

Laura smiled and said, “That’s good. I think Big Brother Wales would take a liking to it. Come, let’s go.” Zhao Hai smiled and then had Alien go towards the main camp’s direction.

Before long, Zhao Hai had arrived at the camp. The camp was in quite a stir when they received the information of his arrival, almost every single person of the Herculean Bull Tribe came out to welcome him.

When Zhao Hai saw this situation, he knew that it wouldn’t be proper if he continued forward. He immediately went out of Alien along with the others. He also received Alien.

When the Beastmen saw Zhao Hai, they quickly gave him a kneeling respect. This seen made Megan and Lizzy feel strange. They didn’t think that Zhao Hai would have this much reputation among the Herculean Bulls.

It was not only them, Zhao Hai was mildly startled as well. But he understood the Beastmen, he immediately said to everyone, “Alright, everyone, get up quickly. Go find me Big Brother so we can have a drink.”

Upon hearing Zhao Hai, the Beastmen cannot help but laugh and then stood up. An elderly member of the tribe then said, “Everyone, it’s very rare for His Highness to come drink with us. You all go home and get something for themselves. Make the Prince feel our hospitality.” Then the people became rowdy as they walked into all directions.

When these people dispersed, Megan discovered that the people who gathered here reached about 100 thousand people. This made her even more startled.

At this time, hoofbeats can be heard as a team of cavalry was approaching. Zhao Hai focused his eyes and saw that it was Wales.

Wales came down from his bull about five meters away from Zhao Hai. Then he hurried towards Zhao Hai before laughing and giving him a big hug, “Hahaha, my brother! You finally came, I was dying to see you.”

Zhao Hai laughed as well and said, “Big Brother, I also wanted to see you. Let’s go and drink some liquor.”

Then Wales let go of Zhao Hai and laughed, “Right, right, let’s go drink! Brother, did you bring any nice wines for your Big Brother?”

Zhao Hai laughed, “Naturally, how can I forget about you. Moreover, I had also brought some good news for Big Brother. I have been married, these are my wives. You’ve already met Laura, Meg, and Ni’er. This is Megan and this is Lizzy. Megan, Lizzy, this is Big Brother Wales.”

Seeing Zhao Hai and Wales’ happy expressions, Megan and Lizzy didn’t dare to hesitate as they gave their respects, “Megan(Lizzy) has seen Big Brother Wales.”

Wales laughed and said, “Good, good. Sisters-in-law doesn’t need to be overly polite with me. You’ve chosen well, my brother isn’t an average person. Marrying him can give you great benefits.”

Megan and Lizzy gawked. They weren’t used to having someone talk to them like that. Laura and the others were already used to the way the Beastmen talk, they always say what they think. Since he thinks that Megan and Lizzy had gained greatly, then he would definitely not hesitate to say it.

Laura chuckled and said, “Big Brother. Brother Hai is always very good in your eyes. Right, let’s hurry along, we’re quite hungry.”

Wales immediately smiled and said, “Alright, let’s go. Having you be hungry for long is not very good.” Then he called over some mounts and had Zhao Hai and the others sit on them before they headed towards the camp.

Currently, the camp was very busy in preparation for a feast. Since Zhao Hai, their benefactor, came, they decided to give him the best welcome that they can provide.

When Zhao Hai entered the golden tent, he saw that Yale and Mendez were already waiting for him inside. There were also some high-level members of the tribe present. Zhao Hai gave them his respects as he turned to Wales and said, “Big Brother, I have something delicious to give you. Have the tribe eat it.” Then he released ten Blade-Scale Whales. These ten whales aren’t small, each one having almost 20 thousand jin(10k kg) of meat. These whales were the biggest ones among the batch that the Space Produced. Zhao Hai took them out this time to have the people of the Herculean Bull Tribe eat it.

The population of the Herculean Bull tribe wasn’t that large, about less than a million. But almost 200 thousand jin of Blade-Scale whale meat was still insufficient. However, it would still enough for them to savor the flavor of the meat. Zhao Hai had also released a number of Magic Beasts to be cooked in order to fully feed the entire Herculean Bull population.

Wales didn’t become polite, when he saw these things he laughed and said, “You really bring a lot of good things everytime. But there’s nobody here who can cook these properly. I’ll have to depend on brother for this matter.”

Zhao Hai laughed and said, “This isn’t a problem. Brother can be rest assured.” Then he released some undead to help cook the meat. Having them cook ensured that there wouldn’t be a problem with the food.

Chapter 507: Joyful Reunion

After the introductions, Wales looked at Laura and the others and smiled, “Good, brother has finally married. I also think that it’s time for you to marry. I didn’t expect that you would be this quick.”

Zhao Hai laughed and said, “I won’t dare to be slow. Otherwise, they’ll be taken by someone else. Hahaha.”

Wales also laughed and said, “If someone dared rob my brother, then I’d form an army to deal with that person. Hahaha. Right, brother, why did you come this time? Did something happen?”

Zhao Hai smiled and said, “Everything’s fine. I just spent God’s Grace Day with everyone. Then after that your brother has managed to get promoted and had himself a new fief in the Human lands. It’s quite a good place. Also, Lizzy is a Princess of the Rosen Empire while Megan is a treasured lady of the Calci Family. After having them, I went to tie the knot by wedding. Then Laura’s family came to take her back, resulting in me eliminating their clan and having Laura take the place as the head.”

Wales gawked, and then he laughed and said, “So the status of my Sisters-in-law aren’t simple. Fantastic! With brother’s promotion and wealth as well as your marriage with sisters-in-law, you now have everything accounted for. Hahaha.”

Zhao Hai laughs and said, “Right, Hahaha.”

This way of talking was what Beastmen prefer, say what you think, don’t be a hypocrite. Because of this, they didn’t dislike Zhao Hai’s way of talking.

After chatting jokingly for a while, Zhao Hai turned to Wales and said, “Brother, how is the tribe doing now? You can tell me if you need anything, your brother will help you.”

Wales nodded and said, “I hope brother can get me some ironware, preferably weapons. You should know that the event where we had dealt with the Fighting Bulls was only known to few people because of the winter. But from now on, people would look for trouble with our Herculean Bull tribe. If we have enough iron weapons, then we can manage to deal with them.”

Zhao Hai smiled and said, “This is not a problem. How about this, I’ll send you two hundred thousand great axes, I’ll have them delivered later. Right, those slaves that you’ll send me, let them stay here in the meantime, have them help. When your fighting ends, you can send them backto me. Also, go help me get some corpses to turn into undead.”

Wales laughed, “Then I’ll be impolite. I’ll wait until everything gets settled down before bringing you those slaves. Right, we also need grains. I really don’t know what is going on, but there seems to be a shortage of food in the Prairie. Our Cow-headed race is rapidly running out of food right now.”

Zhao Hai smiled and said, “Alright, that’s not an issue. I have a lot of bamboo rice, and also some Bread Fruits. You can have as many as you want”

Wales smiled and said, “I know that I’ve been asking a lot from brother. But brother can be rest assured that I will not let you suffer. In the past few days we have gathered a lot of Magic Beasts. I promise to trade them to you at a suitable price.”

Zhao Hai smiled, “It really doesn’t matter. I can afford this, you don’t need to worry. You can also ask the other beastmen to see if they also lack food. If the entire Beastman race gets a shortage of food, then it might lead to a massive war.”

Wales stared, he hadn’t thought of this possibility. He immediately nodded and said, “Right, right, it seems like I really have to check on this matter. Our current Herculean Bull Tribe is still weak, we need a few years before we can recover, we aren’t ready for war. But brother, if the entire Prairie did have a food shortage, what do we do?”

Zhao Hai thought for a moment and then said, “Don’t worry. If the entire Prairie did lack grain, then I will find a way to provide it. I might not have enough of other things, but when it comes to Bamboo rice, I’m confident.”

Wales was now very trusting of Zhao Hai, when he heard Zhao Hai’s words, he immediately nodded and said, “Alright, then brother don’t need to worry about the other matters, I’ll take care of it. If you have the grain, then they would definitely buy it at a high price.”

Zhao Hai nodded, “I really don’t care about the price, so long as war doesn’t happen. But Brother, if you have a war with the Aksu Empire, then I won’t oppose. I’ll let you know that the Aksu Empire has been giving me trouble these days. They made me feel very uncomfortable.”

When Zhao Hai told Wales about the situation with the Aksu Empire, Wales became angry. Then he immediately declared loudly, “Good, Aksu Empire, they actually dare act against you? I definitely won’t let this matter go. Brother can be rest assured, if I find an opportunity then I will definitely avenge your grievance.”

Zhao Hao smiled, “But I also think that this isn’t a good idea. I can also avenge myself, but I don’t want to do so right now. I have a good relationship with the Purcell Family, if you attack the Aksu Empire, the Purcell Family would surely be the first to suffer bad luck. And I don’t want to see that.”

Wales nodded, “Brother, feel relieved, I won’t act unreasonably. Right, let’s not talk about these things anymore. The things outside have already been roasted, let’s go eat and drink!”

Zhao Hai nodded, then he followed Wales. Outside, Argali and Bulls have already been roasted. There were also some delicacies of the Prairie that were prepared. The seafood that Zhao Hai had brought were also prepared, all of it can now be eaten immediately.

Faced with the scene of the Herculean Bulls passing around the food made Megan and Lizzy feel like they didn’t have enough eyes to look at everything.

While looking at the hustle and bustle of the people, Wales’ raised his hand. Upon doing so, the Beastmen immediately became quite. This scene made Lizzy very surprised, even the Emperor of the Rosen Empire didn’t have this much control.

Seeing that the crowd had gone peaceful, Wales said loudly, “Today, our Herculean Bull’s brother Zhao Hai has returned to the Prairie. Let today be a special day for our tribe, we must celebrate well. But don’t cause too much ruckus. We’ve already prepared delicious dishes for you. Come join me in welcoming our good brother Zhao Hai.” The crowd cheered loudly.

Looking at this scene, Zhao Hai couldn’t help but smile faintly and didn’t say anything. He knew that these Beastmen didn’t need his speech. If one needed to say empty words, then he might as well not say anything at all.

Before long, a small table was placed in front of them. Placed on top were the delicacies as well as some milk products. Making these things were a Beastman’s forte, humans just can’t simply compete with them.

After Zhao Hai and the others sat down, all of the Beastmen went to sit down as well. They also had their own tables in front of them, and on top of those were the seafood that Zhao Hai had brought. These things were something that these Beastmen wouldn’t have been able to eat in their entire lifetime.

Wales didn’t become polite, he raised his wine glass and said, “Today, we shall welcome Brother Zhao Hai. Brother, come, have this cup. Cheers!” Then the crowd shouted as well, “Cheers!”

Zhao Hao also lifted his glass, then he drank the liquor. The rice wine that Zhao Hai brought was very delicious but strong. Wales liked it very much.

After downing this glass, the atmosphere immediately turned warm. As various delicacies were brought to their table by young Herculean Bull women, Zhao Hai and the others continued to enjoy themselves in eating and drinking.

Megan and Lizzy didn’t know how to let loose. Since childhood, the two of them had always been taught about how to act appropriately. They must follow set movements in whatever they do, so they found it hard to eat this freely.

The Beastman way of eating was something that they couldn’t’ easily adapt. But when they looked over at Zhao Hai and the others, they seemed to be doing it comfortably. The two couldn’t help but feel curious.

Looking at the two, Laura knew that they needed an explanation, she looked at the two and said, “Here in the Prairie, it’s really not very good to act very politely. If you become too polite, then they would feel angry. Because of this, one should just throw their etiquette out the window when eating and drinking here. The more you eat the more happy people get.”

Megan and Lizzy then looked at Ni’er who had stuffed her mouth full of meat. The two of them couldn’t help but want to try it. They opened their mouths and took a huge bite out of the meat. The two of them couldn’t deny that eating a huge chunk of the meat really does reveal a unique taste.

A banquet as warm as this was something that Megan and Lizzy hadn’t attended much before. The warmest event that they had recently attended was their own wedding, and that was considering all of the other banquets that they had attended before. But they had to admit, the atmosphere then wasn’t as warm as this one.

Before long, young Beastmen women started to dance. Some Herculean Bulls soldiers were also wrestling. The atmosphere immediately turned bustling.

Zhao Hai was already quite used to this atmosphere. This atmosphere made one drink more wine than they usually did. Sure enough, Zhao Hai drank more wine than usual, all of them were now drunk.

At midnight, Zhao Hai woke up. He felt much better right now. After all, rice wine wasn’t the strongest wine that he had drank. Also, Laura had Cai’er fetch him some water from the Space. So his state was now back to normal.

Zhao Hai sat up from the bed and felt that he had a good night’s sleep. He felt that his body become light and cool. He stood up and then went to the living room. This night, it was Shun’s duty to look at the monitor. Reflected on it was the tent that Wales had prepared for Zhao Hai.

Seeing Zhao Hai arrive, Shun immediately said, “Young Master, you’ve come. The madames have already rested.”

Zhao Hai nodded and said, “I’ve drank so much this time, now I can’t fall back to sleep. I’ll just sit here with you.”

Shun smiled and said, “Go sit down Young Master, I’ll go get you a cup of tea.” Zhao Hai nodded and then sat down.

Before long, Zhao Hai smiled to Shun and said, “I’ve always had a relaxed feeling everytime I’m in the Prairie. It may be because it didn’t need too much thinking when getting along with the Beastmen.”

Shun smiled and said, “Beastmen are truly adorable. I can see from their appearances that they really don’t want to attack the Humans. But they were only compelled to do so because of the suppression done to them.”

Zhao Hai forced a smile and said, “In this war between races, nobody is right or wrong. From the viewpoint of humans, what they did was correct. They control the prices towards the Beastmen because they don’t want the Beastmen to be strong. The Beastmen think that the Humans are bullying them. They think that as long as they are able to survive, they won’t be attacking the Humans. After all, they also don’t want to have deaths among them. But if the humans would go too far, then the Beastmen wouldn’t be polite anymore.”

Shun nodded, “So Young Master, what are you going to do? Will you help the Beastmen? If we do supply the whole race, then we can certainly guarantee the supply. We can just let Cai’er cultivate some Bread Trees, with those, we can get a lot of Bread Fruits that can supply the Beastmen.”

Zhao Hai nodded and said, “I also know about this, but I want to see how the situation goes. If the whole Prairie is really lacking in food, just as Brother Wales said, then there is a problem. Somebody must have been in control behind this. I don’t want to act before those people make their move.”

Shun nodded, he also agreed to Zhao Hai’s method. Zhao Hai wasn’t a saint, and he doesn’t need to wipe the ass of the Beastmen. What was currently happening to the Prairie needed to be checked. If they don’t, then it would be the Buda Clan’s miscalculation, and Zhao Hai didn’t want that.

After chatting with Shun for a while, Zhao Hai returned to his room and rested. The next morning, after the group washed themselves, they went out of the Space and out of the tent. At this time, the Beastmen were already going busy outside. Seeing the busy Beastmen, Megan and Lizzy couldn’t help but take a liking to them.

Yesterday, other than meeting the higher ranking people of the tribe, they also met with the commoners. In their opinion, whether they be high ranking beastmen or commoners, both were very adorable. All of them were diligent, much more than the most diligent nobles. Now the two of them can understand why Zhao Hai and the others were able to get along with these people. If you don’t get along with these kinds of people, then there’s something wrong with your nature.

When the Beastmen saw them, they all gave their enthusiastic greetings. Megan and Lizzy now saw how different the Beastmen and the Humans were.

At this time, Wales sent for Zhao Hai to invite them for breakfast. Zhao Hai didn’t decline as he led Laura and the others to have breakfast with Wales. After the meal, Wales kept Zhao Hai inside his tent as they were offered milk tea. Wales took a sip of the tea and looked at Zhao Hai, “Little Hai, I think we should go to the Mastiff Race and have a look there first. If the Dog race lacked grain, then we should ask them for help. After all, they have helped us a lot in the past.”

Zhao Hai nodded and said, “We should, we should. When our Herculan Bull Tribe were having difficulties in the past, the Mastiff Race gave us a helping hand. Because of that we managed to wade through the difficulty and managed to stand up again. Right, brother, if you have any other friends that needs help, then we should also help them.”

Chapter 508: God Exists

Wales thought for a moment and then sighed, “These years, the only people that we have a good relationship with is the Mastiff Tribe. We also have a casual relationship with the Horse Race as well as the Pig Race, however that relationship isn’t that deep. We really don’t have a lot of connections.”

Zhao Hai frowned, then he said, “This is somewhat troublesome. Brother, we might as well go to the Matiffs and ask them if they have any other tribes that they have good relationships with. After all, a friend of a friend can still be a friend. We are allies with the Mastiffs and they also have other allies, this way we can have several allies.”

Wales stared, then nodded, “You’re right, what you said would be the best thing to do. Also, you have a lot of grain in your hands. I’m sure the Beastmen would have some of those. If you keep providing food, then having no allies will be taken care of soon.”

Zhao Hai smiled and said, “That’s also good. But let’s see how the situation goes first. Brother, the Prairie always lacked grain, but if the deficit is too much this time, then I’m afraid that someone might have been pulling the string in the shadows. We must take this matter into consideration. If people were indeed causing mischief, then we have to investigate it through, eliminate the problem at its roots.”

Wales knit his brows and said, “That is indeed a possibility. Although the Prairie always lacked grain, the supply would still be enough to go by. But this time seems to be very different, the amount of grain circulating is pitifully low.”

Zhao Hai nodded, “Then it seems like people are really causing this deliberately. I think we must consider the Radiant Church in this manner. Even if they got defeated last time, it doesn’t mean that they have already given up. It’s highly probable that they are the cause of this time’s crisis. If they really are, then I’m afraid that war is the only solution.”

Wales frowned, “But the issue with this is that the Cow-headed race’s losses would not be small if we really would go to war. For our Cow-headed race, wouldn’t that scenario be harmful?”

Zhao Hai smiled faintly and said, “Big Brother, you should look at it another way. The Herculean Bulls now have enough grains, you now don’t have to fight for food. In the past, when you are battling against the humans, you were always at the vanguard, becoming the first to come in contact with the human army so that you can get more food. But now, that is no longer necessary. You can just state the reason that the Herculean Bulls had lost a lot during the fight with the Fighting Bulls. You can just hand the position of Vanguard over to other people. You can just stay at the back lines and relax.”

Wales stared for a moment before he laughed, “Right, Right. Brother you really are full of good ideas. Alright, we’ll do just that.”

Then Zhao Hai shook his head and said, “But Brother shouldn’t be celebrating early. This matter is only our guesses. We still don’t know if the Radiant Church is indeed behind this crisis. If they aren’t, then things would be more troublesome. But no matter what, Brother should opt to stay at the back lines. Even if you followed, you don’t have to take part in the battles. The Herculean Bulls cannot afford any more losses.”

Wales nodded, “Right, we should determine the cause of this matter first. In a few days we’ll go to the Mastiffs. They should be better off compared to other tribes since we had been sending them grains all throughout the winter.”

Zhao Hai nodded and said, “Good, then Brother can get news about the Prairie from there. Brother, I’ll exit first. If you need me, just send someone and I’ll go out.”

Wales nodded and watched Zhao Hai leave. When Zhao Hai returned to his tent, he looked at Laura and the others and sighed, “Am I being excessive? Helping the Beastman deal with the Humans?”

Laura smiled faintly and said, “It’s nothing. If this matter is really related to the Radiant Church, then it would also be good for the humans if war were to happen. Except for the Rosen Empire, the Radiant Church had already spread their influence around the entire continent. More and more people have become believers of the Church. Some of them even donated all of their own belongings to the organization. The existence of the Radiant Church isn’t a good thing for the people. Even if they aren’t eliminated, it would be best to have them controlled. Because of this, I completely agree with you dealing with the Church’s actions.”

Megan also nodded and said, “Big brother Hai, the Radiant Church had already caused too much death to my family. It is right that we should deal with them.”

Lizzy looked at Zhao Hai and smiled, “Elder Brother Hai, are you feeling uneasy? You don’t have to, think about it, war is very good for our clan. What does the Black Wasteland really need right now? It is more people. If the Beastmen and the Humans go head to head with each other, the first target would be the Aksu Empire. When war happens, a lot of people from the empire would surely be displaced. At that time, we can have people take them and bring them into the Black Wasteland and then give them land to work on. They would then become people of our Buda Clan. Our Clan has two main enemies right now, first is the Aksu Empire, the other is the Radiant Church. If the crisis of the Prairie was indeed because of the Radiant Church, then when the Beastmen sends their troops, the Radiant Church would be heavily affected. And with the Aksu Empire being the first to be hit by the attack, their losses would be even greater. At that time, Brother Hai would have dealt with two major problems. So why worry?”

After learning about how Zhao Hai does his things, Lizzy also decided to demonstrate her talent. She had always been a genius military strategist, her methods might be ruthless, but they were all very effective.

Zhao Hai sighed and said, “But the one who suffers the most in this situation would be the commoners. Especially those from the Purcell Duchy, because of our connection with them, I’ve been having second thoughts about this matter.”

Zhao Hai would get soft-hearted sometimes. He was only ruthless when it came to his enemies. Commoners weren’t his foes, he doesn’t have the heart to cause them suffering.[1]

Laura comforted him, “Brother Hai, this matter is set in stone. Think about it, if not for your presence, the Herculean Bulls would have already been extinguished. When that happens, the Beastmen would be placed in an awkward position, and a war would still happen. And that war would even be more chaotic than this one.”

Zhao Hai sighed again, “The Radiant Church is truly a calamity. Unfortunately for us, they have already infested the entire continent. It would be very hard to remove them.”

Lizzy frowned and said, “Elder Brother Hai, the rising of the Radiant Church is really very strange. Several hundred years ago, the Radiant Church was just a small church that Light Mages believed in. There were even some Light Mages that chose to believe in the Life God other than the Radiant God. However, after some time, the Church had suddenly become more and more powerful. From what I read in the Imperial Records, the Radiant God had descended, causing the Church to become more formidable until it reached its present scale. In just a short hundred years, the Church had become much more powerful than those Great Clans that had been around for a thousand years. There should be some secret going on behind the scenes.”

Zhao Hai stared, his face couldn’t help but change as he said, “Descent of the Radiant God? Is there really such a thing?”

Lizzy shook her head and said, “There aren’t a lot of things written on the records. But I think that it may be impossible. How can the Radiant God just descend?”

Zhao Hai forced a smile and said, “Why would it be impossible? What if there really are gods in the continent? What if those gods needed the faith of people in order to get stronger? If that is so, then it would make sense that the Radiant God would descend and get more followers. That way, he would get much stronger while at the same time suppressing the other gods.”

Lizzy and the others stared, they didn’t think that Zhao Hai would say this. Meg was confused and said, “Young Master, I don’t understand. Aren’t they gods? Do they also need to compete for power just like humans?”

Zhao Hai forced a smile and said, “Don’t’ think of gods as something special. They are just people who are more powerful. Since they are just people, then it would make sense for them to strive for power. If the continent did really experience a descent of the Radiant God, then the backing of this Radiant Church isn’t simple.”

Lizzy and the others felt that they were listening to words from the Book of Heaven. They had never heard of this description of the gods before. To them, what Zhao Hai said was too mysterious.

Zhao Hai cannot confirm that what he said was the truth. In any case, all of the novels wrote gods as this way. Even if the Ark Continent is different from those novels, it had Magic as well as Battle Qi. The possibility of this description being true is much higher compared to earth. Because of this, Zhao Hai believed that the gods of this world were just the same as those in the novels.

Zhao Hai let out a sigh and said, “It looks like we cannot completely eliminate the Radiant Church, since we might cause the Radiant God to be dissatisfied. For a god to descend on the continent, he certainly has his reason. If we go and eliminate his forces in the continent, they might get impolite. Even if our current forces can deal with 9th rank experts, we still cannot face a god. Our strength still falls short.”

Laura frowned, “Is this really the case? Brother Hai, are you sure that you’re not just thinking too much into it?”

Zhao Hai forced a smile and said, “I also hope that I’m just overthinking. But no matter what, we should avoid that scenario from happening. We cannot have huge troubles coming our way.”

Lizzy looked at Zhao Hai, then she faintly smiled and said, “If there really is a god, then I don’t think that we really need to be afraid of him. I believe that even gods doesn’t have a mysterious existence such as the Space. Brother Hai doesn’t need to worry too much.”

Zhao Hai smiled and answered, “I also believe that gods cannot have a thing such as the Space. Otherwise, they wouldn’t need to descend and get some followers. They can just snatch some of them and lecture them inside their Space.”

* * *

??? you literally killed innocent shopkeepers before??

Chapter 509: Meeting the Mastiff Clan

After mentioning the Space, Zhao Hai and the others’ moods relaxed. Just as Zhao Hai said, if those gods really have such a mysterious thing, then they wouldn’t need to go through the trouble of establishing churches. They can just capture people and have them populate their space and then lecture them in the god’s respective faith. For both faith and influence, this would be the most convenient method.

The group chatted for a while before Zhao Hai took them to play in the Prairie since they had nothing else to do right now. Although the Markey Family still had a lot of things to do, their headquarters were already relocated to Golden Island. Ever since it has been transferred to the island, Laura didn’t need to manage it all the time, she can just hand the tasks over to Kun.

Kun had worked as a housekeeper for the Markey Family for half of his life. His understanding about the family’s matters were very handy. Moreover, he had more knowledge about how the family’s internal workings ran than Laura. Because of this, he didn’t have any problems in managing the people from the family. Not only did he possess experience, all of the other housekeepers of the family were now answering to him.

In the past, Kun held a certain influence inside the Markey Family. It was only because of Laura that he quit being an official. Because of this, there were a lot of the family’s housekeepers who already knew him, making everything much smoother.

Therefore, the things that were left for Laura to do weren’t many. As long as something gets sent to her study, Cai’er can just have it sent to the Space for Laura to process. This made it easier for Laura to process things, giving her more free time.

In the past, when the Markey Family was still big, there were a lot of matters that needed to be managed. But now, after they changed their structure, the businesses that they had left were only 50% compared to before while keeping the original amount of managers. This gave the family an excess of managers, giving Laura much less things to worry about.

Additionally, with the Space, Cai’er can monitor those who dared to steal some profits. It was like having a highly effective investigator on hand. Those who didn’t reveal their workings in the light were reported to Laura and were promptly judged. After seeing this, the managers immediately became honest and started working hard.

The Markey Family being able to manage such a large scale business on the entire continent can also be attributed to their ability to manage their shops. Thus, all of their managers were surely talented in what they do. They just want to prove that Laura is unprepared to lead them, but it seems like it was now impossible to do so.

Because of the Space’s formidable abilities, Zhao Hai became successful in taking over the Markey Family.

Even if the Markey Family was already thinned out, and their income seem to have been cut short, their business was in fact doing much better than before.

The Robert Family that Zhao Hai had eliminated before was well known to be the majority suppliers for the continent’s daily necessities. The Markey Family also sold such goods, but they also focused on other businesses. But now that Zhao Hai had closed down on their other ventures, they became focused on selling daily necessities. Now that the Robert Family was gone, their market share on daily necessities were now taken over by the Markey Family. And adding on to their existing business, the Markey Family was now the largest supplier of daily necessities in the entire Rosen Empire. This made their profits in the empire way bigger than what they had before.

Every single person on the continent knew that what the Markey Family had today was only due to having Zhao Hai as their backer. In fact, the Markey Family can be considered to be the Buda Clan, in one way or another. Because of this, nobody dared to cause trouble with them in Rosen Empire.

Although the income of the Markey Family was lower than before, the continent’s impression of them had gone much better. Zhao Hai’s business etiquette was not overbearing like the Markey Family. Some bullying managers were also dealt with. Presently, the shops of the family were very amiable because of the Markey Family’s new way of approaching business.

Zhao Hai was very happy with this development. He knows that the Buda Clan cannot grow up too fast. With the Markey Family’s connections, they were growing up too fast, it was time for them to lay low.

Because of this, Zhao Hai decided to relax a bit. He brought Megan and the others to roam around the Prairie everyday. Since spring has arrived, the plains were now full of wandering beasts. Zhao Hai had also used this opportunity to collect some Magic Beasts for the Space. Unfortunately, the Space was yet to be upgraded, this made Zhao Hai quite impatient.

After three days, news had come from Wales, telling them that they would be leaving for the Mastiffs tomorrow. Their first agenda was to form an alliance with the Mastiffs, and the second was to ask for news about the Prairie’s situation.

Zhao Hai didn’t say anything. At the same time, Megan and Lizzy were enjoying their trip to the Prairie. Moreover, Wales greeted them everyday while serving them food and drinks. Megan and Lizzy were also learning from the Beastmen women how to make milk based products. The two of them looked like two city girls who went to the rural areas to play around, they were very curious about everything.

Seeing them smile, Zhao Hai didn’t say anything. Also, Zhao Hai was now feeling relaxed about his problem regarding having too much Magic Beasts inside the Space. The Markey Family had a lot of meat processing factories in their hands. Zhao Hai can just send his excess Magic Beasts for them to process.

There were a lot of people from the Markey Family, so Zhao Hai still cannot fully trust them. Because of this, Zhao Hao only relegated some basic tasks for them to do. But even in this case, they were still a great help for the Buda Clan.

The Buda Clan isn’t a millennium-old clan, they don’t have much of a background. In addition to their recent downfall, all of their assets were now useless. Now that the Markey Family was taken into their fold, even if they weren’t involved in internal matters, they can still  manage ordinary matters. For the Buda Clan, this was a great thing.

Zhao Hai believed that if the Prairie did come across a grain shortage, then his business here would get bigger and bigger. With the help of the Markey Family’s meat processing factories as well as their shops, he can make canned food and rations. Moreover, he can also sell those items through those shops, this would bring him no small profit.

Most importantly, after having those shops, he can also sell all of the things that were produced by the Space. He didn’t need to worry about someone cutting off their sales to pressure them anymore.

Zhao Hai was also making preparations to water the Bread Trees inside the Space. He had planted a lot of Bread Trees on the background of the Space, but he decided to have them grow naturally and didn’t use the Spatial Water to quicken their growth. However, the situation has already changed. He was now watering those trees with Spatial Water. He needed to produce a lot of Bread Fruits in order to deal with the food shortage of the Prairie.

After waiting for the Bread Trees to bear fruit, Zhao Hai moved Little Jin’s entire tribe into the Space. Since the Space’s environment was much better than Ape Island, Little Jin was very happy. Zhao Hai also transferred the Goldmetal Tree over to the Space. It was a pity that it wasn’t enough to upgrade the Space, however, it did increase the amount of metal produced inside as well as hardening the undead’s bones.

Zhao Hai was very satisfied with this result. The Goldmetal Tree was also growing properly inside the Space, moreover, at a rate much faster than before.

The next morning, Zhao Hai and the others went with Wales as they headed towards the Mastiff Tribes’ territory. Zhao Hai didn’t ride inside the cart that Wales provided, but instead he rode inside Alien. The undead mount was much more comfortable than any carriage. Zhao Hai had also invited Wales in as well as Mendez. Mendez’ tasks was very important right now. After their alliance with the Mastiff Tribe gets taken care of, this matter would be handed over to Mendez. He would be the Herculean Bull’s representative in any matters with the Mastiffs. One can say that Mendez was now considered to be the diplomat of the Herculean Bull Tribe.

Zhao Hai had Wales and Mendez inside Alien, all three of them were drinking inside. The other Herculean Bulls outside didn’t need managing, they also didn’t want to disturb the three.

Wales’ influence inside the Herculean Bull Tribe was very high. After all, he managed to recapture the Herculean Bull’s place as the Royal Tribe of the Cow-headed race. At the same time, Mendez was his right hand man, people of the Herculean Bulls naturally didn’t have anything to say about him as well.

Also, for Zhao Hai, these Beastmen held gratitude in their hearts. Zhao Hai made sure that they wouldn’t starve to death. Additionally, Zhao Hai took care of their logistics during their war.

Because of these three reasons, nobody went to disturb the three while they were drinking inside Alien. At the same time, nobody also disturbed them whenever they had a meal.

It took seven days from the main camp to reach the Mastiff domain. And they spent the entire time moving along. Although they were some Dog-headed tribes on the way, Wales didn’t bother them.

However, those dog-headed beastmen were still very accepting towards them. The Dog-headed race and the Cow-headed race were very close. Because of this, they treated the Herculean Bulls respectfully. After all, the Herculean Bulls are the Cow-headed race’s Royal Tribe.

Because of this, Zhao Hai and the others stayed inside Alien and would rarely come out. Only during mealtimes would they stop and go out to eat with everyone.

Seven days quickly passed by as Zhao Hai arrived inside the Mastiff’s main camp. But when he came this time, he felt that something was different. It seems like the camp was much bigger, and there were more tents within.

When Zhao Hai entered the camp, he learned why there were more tents inside. This was because there were a lot of tribes who gathered today. There was the Wolfhound Tribe, Shar Pei Tribe, Tosa Tribe, Bull Terrier Tribe, German Shepherd Tribe, Canary Mastiff Tribe, and others more.

These races were the warring force of the Dog-headed Race. They were an integral part of the fighting power of the race. Naturally, because of the relationship between the Dog-headed race and the Cow-headed race, these tribes’ relationship with the Herculean Bulls was also good. Wales had already met the Patriarchs of these tribes, and since these Patriarchs were of the same age as Wales’ father, all of them were very intimate with Wales.

Chapter 510: Telling the Reason

The Dog-headed race had a lot more members compared to the Herculean Bulls. Therefore, when Zhao Hai saw these Dog-headed races, he felt his eyes turn strange, there were too many of them.

After introducing themselves, Zhao Hai and Wales were welcomed into a big tent. Zhao Hai chose to not bring Laura and the others today, he just let them stay in the Space. Naturally, in the eyes of outsiders, they were all staying inside Alien.

Inside the tent, these Dog-headed tribe leaders were looking curiously at Zhao Hai. They knew that the Cow-headed Race had a Foreign Prince. Moreover, this new Foreign Prince was a big grain Merchant who had a lot of grain in his hand. The Herculean Bulls being able to reclaim their throne was closely related to this Foreign Prince.

It was because of this that those Dog-headed tribes didn’t have any aversion towards Zhao Hai. There were no Beastmen who disliked human Merchants, they were only on guard against them. But since Zhao Hai was a Foreign Prince of the Herculean Bulls, which made him half-beastman, the Beastmen present here naturally held a favorable impression towards Zhao Hai.

Buzeer looked at Wales and then smiled faintly, “Wales, you little brat. Your expression looks very good, it seems like your Herculean Bull Clan had gotten its strength back.”

Wales gave his respects to Buzeer and smiled, “Uncle Buzeer, we did indeed have a good winter. In the past years, we needed to ration all of the food that we have. But this time, we have a lot to eat, it’s natural that we’d look good.”

Looking at Wales’ expression, Buzeer couldn’t help but laugh and said, “Right, with Little Hai’s support, your days have been better. But you shouldn’t forget your uncle.”

Wales smiled and said, “in fact, one of the reasons that Little Hai came back to the Prairie was to bring him here. Uncle, you can tell Little Hai what you need, he can guarantee that he will give the lowest price to you.”

Buzeer looked at Zhao Hai and faintly smiled, “Little Hai, you really came at a fantastic time. Our Dog-headed Race do indeed lack food. How much can you provide us?”

Zhao Hai smiled faintly and said, “Uncle Buzeer, I can give you as much grain as you want. I also brought some Bread Fruit for you. Come take a look.” Then he took out a Bread Fruit and placed it on the ground.

Buzeer had never seen a Bread Fruit before, it was the same for Wales. Since the Herculean Bulls had an excess of food, Zhao Hai didn’t bother to show them this fruit.

Buzeer was confused as he looked at Zhao Hai and said, “Little Hai, what is this thing?”

Zhao Hai smiled and said, “Uncle Buzeer, this is a Bread Fruit. This fruit is very mysterious. You can see that it isn’t very big, but as long as you open its hard shell, the fruit pulp inside would expand. Each fruit can fill a stomach of one Herculean Bull.”

The Cow-headed race can eat much more than the Dog-headed race. So when Zhao Hai said his words, Buzeer looked at the fruit and said, “Is it really that amazing?”

Zhao Hai placed the Bread Fruit on the table and then turned to Buzeer and said, “Uncle Buzeer, this fruit can be eaten as is. But is can also be roasted before being eaten. What do you think?”

Buzeer looked at Zhao Hai as his eyes turned bright, “Little Hai, can we taste this thing first?”

Zhao Hai smiled and said, “No problem, Uncle can try it.” Then he took out some unopened Bread Fruits and handed them over to Buzeer and the others.

After the Buzeer and the others had eaten the fruit, they nodded. This thing was very good. Not only was its flavor good, it was also very convenient to store, it was a very useful thing.

Buzeer placed the Bread Fruit down and looked at Zhao Hai, “Little Hai, I want these things, how many do you have? Our Dog-headed race is extremely lacking in food, I want as much as you can provide.”

Zhao Hai smiled, “Uncle, as long as you tell me how much you want, I can certainly provide it to you. Also, I shall sell these Bread Fruits at half the price of Bamboo Rice.”

Buzeer became happy, he immediately said, “Good, fantastic! Little Hai’s words really makes me feel relieved. I want an initial 20 million at this time, what do you think?”

Zhao Hai smiled faintly and said, “Alright, I can give it to you anytime. Just go find me a place to take them out and then I’ll give it to you.”

Buzeer gladly got someone to prepare the place. Then the group continued to chat inside the tent. But this time, it was evident that the other Tribe leaders were more polite towards Zhao Hai. Being impolite to a merchant that can easily take out several million jins of food isn’t a wise move.

Seeing that the atmosphere had settled down, Wales turned to Buzeer and said, “Uncle Buzeer, I heard rumors that the entire Prairie is having a food shortage. Is this true?”

As soon as Buzeer heard Wales, he couldn’t help but sigh and said, “It’s true. If it isn’t then our Dog-headed race wouldn’t have a lack of food. I initially wanted to borrow some food from other races, but I didn’t think that they would have a deficit as well. Everybody’s days have been very bad.”

Wales and Zhao Hai looked at each other and saw a glint in their eyes. Wales immediately turned to Buzeer and said, “Uncle, can we talk alone?”

Buzeer looked at Wales’ expression and knew that he should have something important to tell him. He couldn’t blame Wales as he nodded and said, “Alright. Everyone! I’ll have to ask you to exit the tent, I have something to talk about with Wales.” The group didn’t object as they just nodded and stood up.

Seeing that everyone has exited, Wales immediately turned to Buzeer and said, “Uncle, you should know that our Herculean Bull Tribe had just suffered a disaster. I’m afraid that people might cause trouble for us in the future. I want to ask Uncle this time to help us out if ever people come to give us problems.”

Buzeer laughed and said, “You kid, that’s a small matter. I thought you’re being secretive because of something else. Don’t worry, with our relationship, we would surely assist you if you have problems.”

Wales bitterly smiled and said, “Uncle, this is only one thing. The other thing doesn’t only involve our Cow-headed race and Dog-headed race. It involves the food shortage of the entire Prairie. It seems like this one is of a larger scale. Little Hai believed that there may be people who deliberately caused this behind the scenes, and they are most likely the Radiant Church.”

As soon as Buzeer heard Wales, his expression changed, then he turned to Zhao Hai and said, “Little Hai, do you have any proof of this?”

Zhao Hai shook his head and said, “I don’t, I still need to investigate this matter. But uncle should know that last winter, the Radiant Church had colluded with the Fighting Bulls to control the entire Cow-headed race. After we destroyed them, the didn’t make any sound anymore, this is not common for them. But now, the Prairie just experienced a food shortage as spring started, isn’t this too much of a coincidence? Because of this, I concluded that this definitely had something to do with the Radiant Church. But since the Herculean Bulls needed to recover for quite some time, I can only ask Uncle to pass this information over to the Warring Clans to make them aware of this possibility.”

One could say that the organization that the Beastmen dreaded the most was the Radiant Church. These guys have always been creating conflict between Humans and Beastmen. They are the most hated people of the Beastmen. So whether this is true or false, the Beastmen would surely look seriously into this matter.

As soon as Buzeer heard Zhao Hai, he immediately nodded and said, “Alright, I’ll go report this matter as soon as possible. You can rest assured that this matter shall be looked into.”

Zhao Hai and Wales nodded. Then Wales added, “Uncle, Little Hai has a lot of food in his hand. Can you see whether there are allies of the Dog-headed Race that need food so that we can sell them some?”

Buzeer’s eyes turned bright, “Good, that is good. Our Dog-headed race is in good terms with the Bear Tribe. They had helped us before, but when they suffered a disaster several years ago, we weren’t able to help them. This had always made me guilty. Now that there is a food shortage, I think that the Bear Clan wouldn’t be faring well. If you can sell them grain, then it would be good.”

Wales smiled and said, “This is not an issue, Little Hai has a lot of grain. But Uncle, can you put in a good word for our Herculean Bulls Clan so that the bear Clan can also help us when trouble comes?”

Beastmen relations are solid, since the Dog-headed race also had a good relationship with the Cow-headed race, it didn’t take too long for Buzeer to nod and said, “This shouldn’t be a problem. If the Bear Clan really did lack grain and you manage to sell them some, then they would naturally give you a hand. I’ll have Buffon accompany you to the bear Clan, if you have him with you, they would certainly agree.”

Wales became happy and expressed his gratitude, “Thank you, Uncle. But if this shortage is really due to the Radiant Church, then I’m afraid that war will have to happen. Even if Little Hai has a lot of food in his hands, he cannot supply the entire Prairie. What does Uncle think about this situation?”

Buzeer nodded, then he coldly snorted and said, “Even if Little Hai can supply the entire Prairie, war will still happen if the Radiant Church is indeed behind all of this. We have to use our weapons to remind the Humans that the Beastmen aren’t easy to bully.”

Buzeer took a glance at Zhao Hai while he said this, he feared that it might influence Zhao Hai’s feelings. After all, Zhao Hai had their food in his control, it was what they needed the most at this time. But fortunately, Zhao Hai’s face was calm and it seems like Buzeer’s words didn’t give him any dissatisfaction.

Wales also noted Buzeer’s gaze, he faintly smiled and said, “Is uncle worried about Little Hai? You don’t need to worry about him, Little Hai has a huge enmity with both the Aksu Empire and the Radiant Church. He also wants the Beastmen to deal with the Radiant Church.”

Upon hearing Wales, Buzeer looked puzzled at Zhao Hai and said, “Little Hai is a Dark Mage, so it’s natural that you would have an enmity with the Radiant Church. But why do you have an enmity with the Aksu Empire?”

Zhao Hai forced a smile and said, “Uncle might find it funny, but my clan is originally a noble of the Aksu Empire. But when the new Monarch sat on the throne, he demoted our status from Duke to a Count. He also sent people to kill us. If not for some people giving us a hand, we might have all been eliminated. Because of this, I’ve always carried a huge grudge towards the Aksu Empire.”

Buzeer nodded, “Alright. The first one to be unlucky when the Beastmen declares war with the humans would be the Aksu Empire. You don’t have to worry about it, I’ll help you take revenge.”

Zhao Hai smiled bitterly and thank Buzeer. Buzeer then turned to Wales and said, “When war comes, I think that your Cow-headed race should be at the Rear Guard. You’ve had recent losses and need to slowly recover. At the same time, you also have Little Hai, so you don’t need to worry about food.”

Wales nodded and said, “I thank Uncle for his reminder. Little Hai also advised me about this and I agree. This is why I’ve been looking for people to form a relationship with. Otherwise, our Cow-headed race wouldn’t have enough status to decide this matter.”

Buzeer nodded, although the Cow-headed Beastmen were very skilled, they aren’t anything in the eyes of the big Warring Clans. Wales arriving at this conclusion meant that he had matured, and was now a true Patriarch of a Tribe.

Although the Beastmen are simple minded, their Patriarchs would need a bit of brain in order to secure their position. Buzeer understood what Wales was trying to do right now, he wanted to grow his Race. There was no harm in this, so Buzeer agreed.

Adding on to the fact that the Dog-headed race and the Cow-headed race had always been friends for generations, they would surely help each other. The more powerful the Cow-headed race gets, the more help the Dog-headed race can get from them. Buzeer was genuinely hoping that the Wales’ race would become strong.

Another point was Zhao Hai. Zhao Hai was now a Foreign Prince of the Herculean Bulls, he was also a big merchant. Such a person was greatly accepted in the Prairie. Naturally, people would want to form a connection with such a person. Since this is a good opportunity, Buzeer wouldn’t let this go. As long as Zhao Hai continues to sell them food at the current price, the Dog-headed race would continually get stronger and more prosperous.

Beastmen were straightforward people, but it didn’t mean that they are fools. Conversely, Beastmen Patriarchs aren’t simple characters. However, one couldn’t deny that Beastmen were more honest than Humans.  The Cow-headed Race were in a good relationship with the Dog-headed Race, so when the Herculean Bulls were in trouble, the Mastiffs helped them with no hesitation. Such a thing was rare for Humans unless they are eternal allies like the Buda Clan and the Crook Family. Otherwise, nobles wouldn’t do it, they were only interested in benefits. They are completely different from the Beastmen.

Buzeer lending Wales a hand, is just a matter of course, there wasn’t anything strange about it. Buzeer was a friend to Wales’ father, so he would naturally look after Wales. He also regarded Wales as the younger generation, and guiding the young ones was a job of the elders.

Chapter 511: Prairie Wolf Tribe

Buzeer reminded Wales because he was afraid that Wales would turn hotblooded and would participate in the war. If that happens, the losses to the Herculean Bulls would worsen. By then, the power of the Cow-headed race would decrease which wouldn’t be a good thing for the Dog-headed Race.

Buzeer didn’t expect that Zhao Hai had already reminded Wales. In all honesty, Buzeer was still on guard against Zhao Hai. This was because Zhao Hai’s emergence was too coincidental. He appeared just as the Herculean Bulls suffered a tragedy. Moreover, Wales, who had a good relationship with him, became the Patriarch, turning him into the tribe’s Foreign Prince. One could say that the one who benefited the most from the Herculean Bull’s tragedy was Zhao Hai. This made Buzeer suspect him.

However, the two matters that happened today made Buzeer erase his suspicions. First, he informed them about the possibility that the Radiant Church might have been the one behind the food shortage. Even if they still hadn’t confirmed it, he was still thankful to Zhao Hai.

Secondly, Zhao Hai had actually reminded Wales to not participate greatly in the war. From this point, Buzeer could see that Zhao Hai really cared about the Cow-headed race. Otherwise, he wouldn’t remind Wales.

After thinking about this, Buzeer looked at Wales and said, “Wales, in two days I’ll have Buffon bring Zhao Hai to meet with the Bear Clan. Are you going with them?”

Wales shook his head and said, “I can’t go with them, uncle. There are too many things to take care of back at the camp. I want to go back and deal with them, instead, I’ll have sixth brother accompany Zhao Hai.”

Buzeer, who was familiar with the Herculean Bulls, understood what Wales was talking about, so he nodded and said, “Alright, two Princes going together would be enough to show your sincerity. Right, since you have a lot of things to do, you can head back tomorrow. I’ll have Buffon guide Little Hai and Little Six to the Bear Clan.”

Wales nodded, “Then I’ll have to trouble uncle.”

Buzeer smiled and said, “This is just a small matter, there’s no trouble caused. Right, since you came here today, let’s go have a drink!.” Wales nodded, and then followed Buzeer as they headed out.

The Tribe Patriarchs of the Dog-headed race didn’t leave. They had set down some blankets and tables outside to drink and chat. There was also some Argali being roasted, this was already quite a luxurious feast for the Beastmen.

When these people saw Buzeer come out, they greeted him with a smile. Buzeer also greeted them and sat beside the table along with Zhao Hai and Wales.

At this time, the Argali has been roasted. Buzeer raised his glass and said, “There has been a great shortage of food for all of the Beastman race, and our Dog-headed race isn’t an exception. Fortunately for us, Little Hai has food and was willing to sell them to us at a low price. This is a huge help for us. Moreover, he is also a Prince of the Cow-headed race. Our Dog-headed Race has been in good relations with the Cow-headed race for many generations. So we shouldn’t treat Little Hai as an outsider, consider him as someone from our own side. Everyone should take care of him.”

These Tribe Patriarchs loudly cheered. Actually, they didn’t really need Buzeer’s words since they had already acknowledged Zhao Hai. Since Zhao Hai has food, even they would want him to be a Foreign Prince of their tribe.

Then it was now time to drink. When among Beastmen, it would be impossible for someone to refrain from drinking. If you don’t drink, then you wouldn’t be considering their face. So whether you like it or not, you would have to drink.

Therefore, it wasn’t a surprise that Zhao Hai was drunk once again. But even if he was drunk, he immediately sobered up inside the Space. After drinking two cups of Spatial Water, he was back to being functional again.

At this time, everyone was sitting in the living room. Zhao Hai looked at them and smiled, “We may come in contact with a Beastman Warring Clan in the next few days. I really want to see how formidable these Warring Clans are.”

Laura smiled faintly and said, “Warring Clans of the Beastmen have a very huge reputation in the Continent. I heard the things that you had discussed today. Even if the Bear Clan had some losses in the precious years, their fighting power still remained. They had also recovered somewhat in those years. At the same time, they are the simplest and the most honest Beastmen. It would be very good if we get into good terms with them.”

Zhao Hai nodded and said, “It’s very good to be in a good relationship with the Beastmen. What they didn’t lack here in the Prairie are Magic Beasts. Now that we have our own meat processing factories, all of those Magic Beasts would be very useful for us.”

The group nodded, then Lizzy said, “Elder Brother Hai, from my experience with the Beastmen these past few days, I’ve come to find that getting along with them is much easier than with Humans. I think we should focus our operations in the Prairie.”

Zhao Hai smiled and said, “I’ve also thought about that, but it can’t be that easy. If we really occupy the Beastman Prairie’s business, a lot of people would go and attack us. This is because we would be getting in the way of these people’s livelihood.”

Lizzy smiled and said, “I know about this point. But if the entire Prairie is huge, we can’t swallow all of the businesses here. We can also use this opportunity to establish relationships with the Beastmen. When the time comes, we can seize the bulk of the trade in the Prairie. As long as we allow others to have a small share of the business, the Nobles would have no reason to collectively attack us. We can just deal with them one by one.”

Zhao Hai smiled faintly and said, “There’s that, but I think we should wait and see how the Bear Clan sees us. The Bears are a big Warring Clan, it is very important for us to gain their trust.”

Laura and the others nodded, then Zhao Hai looked at the weather and said, “It’s already quite late. My ladies, any of you want to accompany me to bed?”

The faces of the women turned red, they couldn’t bear with Zhao Hai’s shamelessness as they turned around and returned to their rooms. Zhao Hai smiled and then headed towards Lizzy’s room.

The next morning, Zhao Hai went out of the Space quite early. Lizzy woke up much later because Zhao Hai had loved her heavily last night. When Zhao Hai was finished, he then went back to his own room and slept soundly.

After having their breakfast, Wales bid Zhao Hai farewell since he needed to head back to the Herculean Bull’s main camp. He can only leave Zhao Hai and Mendez behind.

When he received Buzeer’s order, Buffon immediately let of of what he was currently doing. He also had quite a few things to take care of at the Mastiff camp, but he had decided to hand them over to others.

While Zhao Hao stayed in the Mastiff camp for another day, he left behind the food that they required. He also left some daily necessities behind, gaining the gratitude of the Mastiffs.

The things that he had left behind were quite a lot, making these Dog Tribes happy. The Tribe leaders even competed as to which of them gets to trade with Zhao Hai first.

Naturally, Zhao Hai wasn’t impolite with these people. He just talked with them politely and took note of the locations of their camps.

The next day, Zhao Hai and Buffon’s group left the camp. Their numbers weren’t that many, only about 1000 people; 500 of them were from the Herculean Bull Tribe while the remaining 500 were from the Dog-headed Race.

The path between the Dog-headed Race and the Bear Clan wasn’t very far from the camp of a Wolf-headed race Branch, the Prairie Wolves.

The Prairie Wolves were a relatively large and strong branch of the Wolf-headed Race. Since they were close with the Dog-headed Race and the Bear Clan, the three of them had a good relationship with each other. But the relationship between the Dog-headed Race and the Bear Tribe was much better.

The Dog-headed race didn’t like to mingle with the Prairie Wolves. This was because the Prairie Wolves were one of the top Tribe within the Wolf-headed Race. Therefore, every time the Dog-headed Race and the Prairie Wolves come in contact, the Prairie Wolves would always look at them condescendingly. This made the Dog-headed Beastmen uncomfortable, especially the arrogant Mastiff Tribe.

The strength of the Mastiffs weren’t any less than the Prairie Wolves. It wasn’t even a problem for one Mastiff to face several Prairie Wolves. It was precisely because of this that the Mastiffs cannot bear with the haughty attitude of these Wolves.

The Wolf-headed Race’s domain was a very large one, they were also the Beastmen who hated Humans the most. Because of this, only a rare few humans would be allowed to trade with them. This made the food scarcity in the beginning of the years hit them the hardest. So in addition to their miniscule trades, they also steal food from merchant caravans. At the same time, they were also the most meat-eating race in the entire Prairie.

Because the Wolf-headed race always lacked food in the beginning of every year, they would have no other choice but to eat the Argali that they raise. Even if they eat a ton of Argali every year, this didn’t make the other Beastmen envy them, it was because this very act made them the poorest race in the entire Prairie.

However, one had to recognize that the Wolves were the most tenacious Race among the Beastmen. The weapons that they use were mostly made of animal bones. The clothes that they wear were all animal skins. They were able to stomach even the most nasty grain and meat.

Moreover, they were also the most annoying Warring Clan to fight against, it was because their battle prowess was just too strong. When a Wolf King issues an order, as long as he didn’t die and hadn’t ordered retreat, their entire force would continue to attack non-stop without retreating even one step.

All of the Beastmen gave the Wolf-headed race face, especially their Royal Tribe, which were the Snow Wolf Tribe. The tribe lived near the North Polar Icefield, one of the few Beastmen who lived there. Their fighting strength can only be described as terrifying. They almost didn’t eat grain, only meat. At the same time, given their harsh environment, almost every member of the tribe were capable of fighting.

The only Beastmen capable of contending with the Snow Wolves, were the Polar Bears and the White Tigers, which were also residing near the North Polar Icefields. The three of them were the most famous and strongest tribes among the Beastmen.

Like the Wolf-headed Race, the Bear-headed Race and the Tiger-headed Race were Warring Clans. Although each of them were grouped up into their own races, the territory that they held wasn’t in a single area, instead, they had a lot of domains in other areas. The domain of the Cow-headed Race simply cannot be compared with them.

For example, the domain of the Prairie Wolves aren’t any smaller than the Cow-headed race. But the Cow-headed Race is an entire race, while the Prairie Wolves were just one branch.

Chapter 512: Wolf King

Traversing through the Prairie Wolf domain would take five days, if one evades every camp it would take eight.

Buffon didn’t want to come in contact with the Prairie Wolves, so he had already planned eight days worth of travel through the Prairie Wolf domain. In any case, travelling a few days more didn’t matter, this matter wasn’t very urgent.

With Buffon, their travel went by smoothly. In a blink of an eye, four days had passed. They were now in the heart of the Prairie Wolf domain, so they needed to be extra careful.

A couple of days ago, Buffon can still stay inside Alien and drink alongside Mendez. But this time he can’t, he was outside and was paying attention. These Wolves were arrogant, but if they dared offend Buffon’s group, then they won’t be polite.

Zhao Hai was sitting in Alien’s separate room and was working with Laura to deal with some of the Markey Family and the Golden Island’s affairs.

There were now a lot of Merchants on Golden Island. Although the Rosen Empire had cut off all the trade routes towards the Aksu Empire, the Lyon Empire, Buddha Empire and the Ocean Waves Dynasty still needed a place to trade in. Adding on to the fact that Golden Island was the place where pirates sell their loot, making the prices cheaper, the Merchants cannot help but try their hand at business there.

Even if Kun was there to manage the island, he had stated that he cannot manage it forever. Therefore, there were a lot of matters that were passed over to Laura and Zhao Hai to manage.

At this time, Mendez was also right beside Buffon outside. He hadn’t been to the Prairie Wolf territory before, in fact, he rarely left the Cow-headed Race’s domain.

The Wolf-headed race didn’t have a lot of friends among the Beastmen. Few people wanted to befriend them because of their ruthless nature. A lot of people didn’t dare to speak badly of the Wolves to their faces, but they do so in secret.

Regarding the Wolves, Zhao Hai didn’t have much of a dislike towards them. The Wolves’ methods were just somewhat more extreme, if one compared them to those truly wicked humans, they would look cute.

While they were traversing, a sudden howl was heard. Buffon’s face changed as he issued a command, “Stop! The Wolves has come. Everyone be careful.” When Zhao Hai heard this, he walked out of Alien and stood on its head. He then gazed towards the direction where the wolf howl came.

Buffon knew the Wolves, if they didn’t stop, then they would be attacked. The howl was just a warning to make them halt their advance. If they chose to ignore it, then they would get into trouble.

Quite some time after the group came to a stop, they could see a group of cavalry in the distance. The mounts of these cavalry were giant wolves with three meters in height. Those mounted on top of them were people with Wolf heads and were about 2.5 meters in height.

This was Zhao Hai’s first time meeting someone from the Wolf-headed race. They had big wolf heads and had much fiercer appearances than even the fiercest Dog-headed Beastman. Their eyes seemed to be half-open and half-closed. But their eyelids would occasionally move, making people feel a chill.

These cavalry were all dressed in animal skins. Although they were tall, all of them were very skinny. They were so skinny that it looked like they didn’t have a bit of fat. The muscles under their skins looked like iron bars, one could see how strong they were. Meeting them can make people unconsciously step back, they seemed to always be on the verge of attacking. Zhao Hai couldn’t help but raise his vigilance towards them. They feel like the Undead; aggressive, organized, and made people not dare to look down on them.

The Wolves stopped five meters away from Zhao Hai’s group. Then one of them went forward and looked at Buffon, “Buffon, why did you come to our territory? You also have some Herculean Bulls with you? And even Humans?”

Buffon looked at the Wolf-headed Beastman and faintly smiled, “I turns out to be Seventh Highness. How are you? Is it your patrolling shift today?”

The Wolf Beastman seems to not buy Buffon’s politeness, his eyes opened slightly and said, “Buffon, you still haven’t answered me. Why are you here?”

Buffon smiled faintly and said, “Seventh Highness, we are just passing by. We have something to do with the Bears.”

Then the Wolf beastman looked at the Herculean Bulls and Zhao Hai and then said, “Going to the Bears along with the Herculean Bulls and Humans? What are you going to do?”

Even if the Wolf acted impolitely, Buffon seem to be used to it as he smiled and said, “It’s not that serious, we just heard that the Bears were having a food shortage. This is Zhao Hai, the Foreign Prince of the Herculean Bulls. He’s a big grain merchant, he has food in his hands. I just want to bring him to the bears and see if they want to buy some food.”

As soon as the Wolf Beastman heard Buffon, his eyes fully opened, then he stared at Zhao Hai and asked, “You have food?”

Zhao Hai smiled faintly and said, “I do”

Through the conversation between the Wolf Beastman and Buffon, Zhao Hai had understood the Wolves. They weren’t really dissatisfied with people, they were just used to speaking impolitely. They don’t know how to communicate with people, and they didn’t like to be polite either, they wanted to be more practical. Therefore, Zhao Hai didn’t waste any words when he answered.

The Wolf Beastman sized Zhao Hai up and said, “Where are your goods?”

Zhao Hai patted his chest and said, “In my Space Bag.”

The Wolf Beastman’s eyes lit up and said, “Our tribe wants your food. Just make sure it’s price isn’t too high.”

“This…” Zhao Hai hesitated. Then he turned to look at Buffon and Mendez, who both nodded. The two knew that as long as they get spotted by the Wolves, they would certainly buy some grain. In the Prairie, you can offend any other Beastman, just not the Wolves, they were known to bear a grudge.

Seeing them nod, Zhao Hai turned to the Wolf Beastman and said, “Alright, then please lead the way.” The Wolf Beastman nodded then turned around and headed towards the depths of the territory.

Zhao Hai didn’t enter inside Alien and just sat on its head. He turned to Buffon and said, “Brother Buffon, who was that person?”

Buffon smiled and said, “He’s called Hans. The Seventh Prince of the Prairie Wolves. His fighting strength is formidable, even if he’s still young, he’s already reached 7th rank. He’s the strongest expert in his generation.”

Zhao Hai said, “He seems like a very cold person.”

Buffon smiled and said, “He seems like it, but Hans is actually a good person. As long as you don’t offend the Prairie Wolf Trobe, he will not be unkind to you.”

Zhao Hai nodded. It seems like this Hans was just like what he thought. He really wasn’t a cold person, he just didn’t know how to get along with others.

These Prairie Wolves weren’t afraid that Zhao Hai would run away or be unable to follow them. They just stayed in front and had Zhao Hai and the others follow them peacefully.

After walking for three hours, the group could finally see a shadow of a camp. This camp was very big, it looked like a lot of tents interconnected to look like a single huge structure.

Hans didn’t stop and went directly into the camp. From what Zhao Hai can see, this camp was just like the camps of the Herculean Bulls and the Mastiffs. But instead of their respective races, the place was filled with Wolf-headed Beastmen.

Although the Dog-headed race and the Wolf-headed race looked quite similar, there were still differences between them. Only a few people can confuse wolves and dogs.

Even if the Prairie Wolves hadn’t revealed any hostility to Zhao Hai, their gazes towards him seem to be cold. Compared to the Dog-headed Beastmen, the wolves held a more aggressive aura in their bodies. This aura didn’t come from their expression, but it seems like it was ingrained in their bones.

These Wolves were also very curious about Zhao Hai’s group. To them, the group was strange, there was a Dog beastman, Cow beastman and a Human all in one.

The Herculean Bulls, Mastiffs, and Prairie Wolves were familiar with each other. Therefore, the Wolves knew that among this group, a royal from both races was present. So they knew that they cannot easily offend this group.

The Human, on the other hand, was a rare sight. This was because Humans rarely traded with their tribe. And in most cases where it didn’t go well, the Wolves would just kill them.

Zhao Hai and the others stopped after arriving outside a golden tent. Hans entered the tent and before long came out again. He looked at Zhao Hai’s group and said, “Father invites you in.” Then the three people nodded and entered the tent with Hans.

Compared to the golden tents of the Herculean Bulls and the Mastiffs, the golden tent of the Prairie Wolves was quite simple. The ground was covered with beastskin, and it had a fire pit in the middle. There weren’t any tables nor any decorations in the tent, the only other thing inside was an old wolf that was sitting on a chair.

After Hans entered the tent, he stood beside the old Wolf Beastman. The Old Wolf’s build was quite similar to Hans. Although he looked thin, one could see his hardened interior. Even if he had wrinkles in his face, they grew in a way that he seemed to be much more imposing.

The three immediately gave a salute to the Old Wolf at the same time, ““This one has seen the Wolf King.””

The Old Wolf nodded, then he scanned the three, he stopped his gaze at Buffon and said, “You are Buffon? How is your father?”

Buffon quickly replied, “Father is fortunately well.”

The Old Wolf nodded, then he turned to Mendez and said, “You’re a Herculean Bull? I heard that you Herculean Bulls had suffered a disaster last year.”

Mendez gave a bow and said, “Herculean Bull Prince Mendez has seen the Wolf King. Our tribe did indeed suffer a disaster in the winter of last year. The Fighting Bulls and the Radiant Church colluded to overthrow our tribe. Fortunately we managed to eliminate them.”

As soon as he Old Wolf heard Mendez, his eyes lit up and said, “You eliminated the tribe? Good. Who is the Herculean Bull Patriarch right now?”

Mendez quickly answered, “It’s my brother, Wales.”

Chapter 513: Dog-headed Race’s Friendship Flag

The Old Wolf nodded and said, “Your brother is quite the character. I also know about the Fighting Bulls, their strength isn’t weak. Adding the support of the Radiant Church, it was a surprise that you managed to eliminate them in a short time. That’s a great feat.”

Mendez smiled faintly and said, “We’re lucky to have the Mastiff tribe and our Foreign Prince’s help. Because of that, we managed to deal with the Fighting Bulls quite quickly.”

The Old Wolf looked at Zhao Hai and said, “You are Zhao Hai? The Foreign Prince of the Herculean Bulls?”

Zhao Hai felt some pressure from the Old Wolf, but he wasn’t bothered by it. He faced 9th rank experts before, so how could he care about the old Wolf. He just smiled and said, “I am indeed Zhao Hai.”

The Old Wolf King stared at Zhao Hai. When Buffon and Mendez met his gaze, they would express slight hints of fear, but this Zhao Hai was completely calm. This made the Old Wolf King interested in this Human.

After looking at Zhao Hai for quite some time, the Old WOlf King said, “Good, good. A Human becoming a Beastman tribe’s Foreign Prince, you’re methods are quite good.”

Zhao Hai faintly smiled and said, “The Wolf King overpraised me, I had no good methods. I’m nothing more than Brother Wales’ brother. I just gave the Herculean Bull tribe a helping hand when they got into trouble. They liked what I did so they decided to make me their Foreign Prince.”

The Old King looked at Zhao Hai and then smiled, “Young man, no need to downplay yourself. It’s impossible for a Beastman tribe to give the position of Foreign Prince casually. You surely gave them a huge helping hand. Hehehe. Right, I heard that you have a lot of food?”

Zhao Hai smiled and said, “I do. But the food in my hands is somewhat special. It is not the ordinary Bamboo Rice, but the never before seen Bread Fruit.”

The Wolf King looked at Zhao Hai and then said, “Take one out, let me see.” Then Zhao Hai nodded, he turned his hand as a Bread Fruit appeared before handing it over to the Old Wolf King.

The Old King tasted the fruit, then gave it to Hans. He turned his head to Zhao Hai and said, “Price?”

Zhao Hai smiled faintly and said, “A fourth of the price of Bamboo Rice.”

The Old King stared, then his eyes looked straight into Zhao Hai, “You’re not joking? A fourth of the price of Bamboo Rice?”

Zhao Hai smiled and said, “I wouldn’t dare joke with the Wolf King. Moreover, I don’t joke when it comes to business. The Wolf King doesn’t need to doubt me.”

The Old Wolf King looked at Zhao Hai and said, “If what you said is true, we want every Bread Fruit that you have.”

Zhao Hai looked at the Old King and smiled bitterly, “I’m afraid the Wolf King’s tribe cannot consume them all. Tell me how much you need and then I’ll give them to you.”

When he heard Zhao Hai, the Old King’s expression couldn’t help but change. He thinks that Zhao Hai was looking down on him, his anger couldn’t help but seep out as he said, “100 million jin.”

Zhao Hai smiled faintly and said, “No problem. I have the Bread Fruit in my Space Bag, I can give them to you later. The Wolf King can rest assured, you can have them as long as there is a suitable place to store them.”

The Old King looked at Zhao Hai, he knew that even if those Bread Fruits aren’t very big and heavy, when its pulp turns into bread, the 100 million jins would turn into hundreds of millions of jins worth of food. Can Zhao Hai really have it ready at any time?

The Old King said, “You’re serious?”

Zhao Hai smiled faintly, “I won’t dare crack a joke. I truly have it in me. I’ll let the Wolf King know that my territory produces these Bread Fruits. Moreover, the output of each tree is very high. For me, 100 million jin isn’t a lot. If the Wolf King wants more, I can provide you with 1 billion jin, I’ll give you 400 million jin first and then deliver the other 600 million jin five days later. You should know that the Space Bag has a limit. Although I have a lot of them with me, I cannot have that many in hand.”

The Old King looked at Zhao Hai and then laughed, “Good! Alright, let’s go with what you said, we’ll buy 1 billion jin of the fruit, according to the price that you stated. But I don’t have much Argali in my hands, I can trade with you using gold and silver, do you agree?”

Zhao Hai smiled and said, “That is not an issue. But I have some special requests. I want to collect unique Magic Beasts, if the Wolf King gives me some Magic Beasts, then I can give you a good discount.”

The Old King stared, he looked at Zhao Hai and said, “What kind of unique Magic Beasts?’

Looking at the Old King’s face, Zhao Hai knew what he was thinking. In the past, there would be some Humans who would take back Beastman Magic Beasts in order to research the Beastman’s cultivation. Although they didn’t succeed, the Beastmen still became stricter with regards to this matter.

Zhao Hai smiled faintly and said, “Some unique Magic Beasts and plants of the Prairie, some unique plants of the Wolf Tribe would be good as well.”

The Old Wolf King looked at Zhao Hai and said, “I still need to prepare these things. For now, I can pay you with some money, carpets, blankets, and some Argali in advance. What do you think?

Zhao Hai nodded and said, “Alright, I’m not in a hurry. I’ll first leave 300 million jin here since I still need to see if the Bear Tribe needs some food for themselves.”

The Old King laughed and said, “That stupid Bear would surely want some. Young Man, I can confidently tell you that your Bread Fruit wouldn’t be rejected by any Beastman. Alright, I’ll take 300 million jin first. When you go back here in five days, we’ll have your payment ready.”

Zhao Hai smiled and said, “The Wolf king can rest assured, I will certainly return in five days.”

The Old Wolf King nodded, then he turned to Hans and said, “Hans, we’ll go have a drink with Zhao Hai and Buffon’s group today. Prepare everything.”

Hans nodded, then he looked at Zhao Hai’s group before leaving the tent. Zhao Hao and the other naturally gave their gratitude towards the Wolf King.

After a day with the Prairie Wolves, Zhao Hai’s group proceeded to head towards the Bear Tribe’s domain. But this time, they had more guards at their side, they were Prairie Wolf Cavalry.

Zhao Hai didn’t mind them. At this time, Zhao Hai’s focus was on the Space as he counted the Bread Fruits in his storage. In truth, the number of Bread Fruits that Zhao Hai had was really huge. There are billions of tons of them, take note, tons not jin.

If he wasn’t afraid of frightening the Beastmen, he would’ve given everything to the Old Wolf King in one go.

Because they didn’t need to take detour, they arrived at the Bear domain two days later. Upon arriving at the border, the Prairie Wolves turned back. Although one can say that the relationship between the Bears and the Prairie Wolves was quite good, it still wasn’t a good idea to intrude upon their territory since it may cause a misunderstanding.

After saying their farewells to Hans, Zhao Hai and the others officially entered the Bear Tribe’s domain. This Bear Tribe wasn’t the Bear-headed Race’s Royal Clan, but was instead a branch, they were the Black Bear Tribe.

The Black Bear Tribe was also a Warring Clan of the Bear-headed Race, their strength was just next to the Royal Tribe, the Polar Bear Tribe. Like the Snow Wolf Tribe, the Polar Bear Tribe also resided in the North Icefields. Their strength being the strongest.

Even if the Black Bear Clan wasn’t the Royal Tribe of the Bear-headed race, their strength was still very formidable. Because of this, the prestige of their tribe was very high. There weren’t any members of the Beastman Race that would dare to disrespect them. The words of the Black Bear Tribe carry plenty of weight in the Bear-headed Race.

The Black Bear Tribe wasn’t a very hot tempered race. The Human’s view of them being very violent was completely wrong. In fact, the Black Bears were usually very warm, and with their clear eyes, one could tell that they were very simple and honest. This also contributed to the Black Bears’ good reputation in the Prairie.

It was the Humans deceiving the Black Bears that made the Beastmen very discontented with the Humans. And adding on to the fact that the Humans had always sold them food at a high price, this made the Beastmen receive Humans very badly. This sentiment may have possibly been received by the humans, thus explaining the food shortage this time.

But Zhao Hai didn’t know about this, he just felt that the food shortage was the work of someone in the shadows. Whether they were the Radiant Church or not was still left for investigation.

When they entered the Black Bear Tribe’s domain, Buffon immediately relaxed. Then he and Mendez entered Alien to share some drinks along the way.

Zhao Hai naturally wouldn’t reject them, so he took out some liquor as well as some snacks that he got from the Rosen Empire. He can now have these snacks whenever he wants since there were now stores specialized in selling these items on Golden Island, he also heard that their business was good. Since Kun, Blockhead and Rockhead were aware of his matters because of the Space, they immediately had some snacks sent over to Zhao Hai’s office. Zhao Hai can then use the Space to get those snacks and had them served to Buffon and Mendez.

After having everything prepared, the group poured themselves a cup of liquor. Zhao Hai then turned to Buffon and said, “Brother Buffon, tell me about the Black Bear Tribe. They aren’t as cold as the Prairie Wolves right?” In Zhao Hai’s eyes, the Wolf-headed races can be said to be cold. They had their eyes partially closed, as if afraid that they might kill a person when they opened them fully. With their indifferent looks and the external appearance, if there were people to be described as cold inside the Prairie, then it would be the Prairie Wolves.

Buffon smiled and said, “Rest assured, the Black Bear Tribe is very hospitable. They’re quite simple and honest. When you go visit them, they would surely give you the best reception that they can offer. I’m actually afraid that even if they are starving and were barely eating, they would still butcher a beast to welcome us. Naturally, all of these were in the premise that you are their friend. If you are an enemy, then their spiked maces would surely greet your face. Their spiked maces are one of the most feared weapons among the Beastman Race.”

Zhao Hai smiled faintly and said, “I really didn’t think that getting along with the Bear tribe would be so easy. Right, sixth brother, why didn’t you tell the Old Wolf King about our suspicions regarding the Radiant Church’s hand in the food shortage? Are you afraid that they won’t help?”

Mendez smiled and said, “The Wolf-headed race are even vigilant towards other Beastmen, so we can’t just tell it to them directly. We should take this matter slowly.” Zhao Hai nodded and didn’t say anything more. From what he understood of the Prairie Wolves, they would certainly think lowly towards Mendez and the other Beastmen.

Buffon also smiled and said, “That doesn’t really matter, as long as we help the Black Bears, then everything would be fine. The Prairie Wolves are just too vigilant towards other people, it would need a long time before they see you as a friend. Look, even if you provided them with 1 billion jin of food, they still didn’t give you their friendship flag.”

Zhao Hai smiled and said, “Then Brother Buffon, why didn’t your Mastiff race give me your friendship flag? I gave you fairly the same conditions.”

Buffon gave a bitter smile towards Zhao Hai, “You don’t need to waste words. Do you really think that we don’t want to give a friendship flag to you? Father actually wanted to give you our flag, but he was afraid of opposition. But as long as you stay and trade with us for a few more times, Father would take responsibility and hand you our Dog-headed Race’s friendship flag.”

Zhao Hai stared for a moment, then he asked Buffon for clarity, “Brother Buffon, did you just say the Dog-headed Race’s friendship flag? Not the Mastiff Tribe friendship flag?” After being with the Beastmen for this long, he knew that there were differences between friendship flags. The Dog-headed Race’s friendship flag was very different from the Mastiff Tribe’s friendship flag.

The Mastiff Tribe’s friendship flag refers to the Dog-headed Race’s royal clan’s friendship flag. This flag only represents the Mastiff Tribe, but the Dog-headed race’s friendship flag represented the entire Dog-headed Race. For this flag to be given to a person, it would need the approval of 60% of the Dog-headed Race’s branches. With the process of how this flag is given, one could see how important it was.

The Friendship flags of the Big Bellied Pig Tribe and the Giant Horned Bull Tribe that Zhao Hai acquired in the past only represented his good relations with those two tribes. The weight of those flags cannot be compared to the Dog-headed race’s friendship flag. If Zhao Hai gets ahold of that friendship flag, it would mean that he would be a friend of the entire Dog-headed Race. People who disrespect Zhao Hai would be similarly disrespecting the entire Dog-headed Race. This matter might even lead to a war in the Prairie.

Because he knows about the implications, Zhao Hai asked Buffon to clarify. Buffon understood why Zhao Hai asked his question, he smiled to Zhao Hai and said, “Of course its the Dog-headed Race’s friendship flag. Why do you think the leaders of the tribes were present with father when you arrived at our camp? When you entered our domain, father immediately sent word to summon the tribe leaders. Father wanted them to see your performance. Fortunately, you did great. I heard from father that it wouldn’t take a long time before our Dog-headed Race’s flag ends up in your hands.”

Zhao Hai was so happy he almost cheered. Seeing Zhao Hai’s expression, Mendez smiled and said, “Little Hai, you’re really luck kid. Do you know why the relationship between the Cow-headed Race and the Dog-headed race is very good? It’s because we mutually guard each other’s friendship flag. With our flags, you can almost walk sideways in the Prairie.”

Chapter 514: Black Bear Beastman

Zhao Hai laughed and said, “That’s great. Let’s see who dares to annoy me now.” If he was in the Human domain, Zhao Hai would be saying, “I really don’t care if I can walk sideways, as long as my business is in line.” However, he cannot say it in the Prairie since it would be equal to looking down on the Dog-headed race. When that time comes, he would be lucky to only have his friendship flag revoked.

Buffon laughed and said, “Don’t be overconfident. Our Dog-headed Race isn’t considered to be a Warring Race, it’s still good to behave yourself. If you meet those Warring Clans, they might even be impolite to you. But don’t worry, if you sell them food, they might even give you a friendship flag.”

Zhao Hai smiled and said, “Forget it, they might not necessarily befriend me. Come, let’s drink. Let’s take care about the Bear Tribe’s food problem first. I heard that they suffered a serious food shortage a few years ago. Since the Bear Tribe is a friend of the Dog-headed Race, we must help them.”

Buffon smiled and said, “We really should. The Black Bears are really good friends. If you befriend them, they would surely give you a hand later on. Even if they suffer a loss, they won’t hold back in helping.”

Zhao Hai nodded. From Buffon’s introduction, he had a certain understanding towards the Black Bears. They seem to be really good people. If Buffon was saying truth, then they’re worth paying a visit.

The three continued to drink inside. At the same time, the people outside doesn’t have anything to say about it. After all, Zhao Hai had also provided them with liquor and snacks to partake during breaks.

They travelled from day to night. They had also met a small Black Bear Tribe along the way, one of the various tribes in the Black Bear Territory. This tribe had about more than 300 people, a much smaller number compared to Zhao Hai’s group.

These Bear Beastmen were a very enthusiastic bunch. When they saw the Mastiffs, they immediately invited Buffon into their tent while having people slaughter some sheep to welcome the group.

Zhao Hai and the others didn’t prevent them from doing so. If they did, it would be like looking down on them. They just have to gift the tribe with some food when they left. These Bears might have food troubles, but Zhao Hai didn’t.

At night, Zhao Hai didn’t need to construct his own tent. He can just rest inside Alien since it was comfortable and warm there. Because of this, he can closely monitor the Bear Beastmen more carefully.

Although these Bears had large heads, they weren’t fat like those Pig-headed Beastmen. On the contrary, they looked pretty buff. They can even be compared to the Herculean Bulls.

However, Zhao Hai can see that they hadn’t been doing as well as the Mastiffs and the Herculean Bulls. They were only a small tribe of 300 so they didn’t have a lot of Argali raised. This time, to welcome Zhao Hai’s group, they slaughtered a bunch of them. Zhao Hai can see that they had almost run out of food.

To be honest, Zhao Hai’s heart was aching. These Beastmen were very likeable, but seeing how much Argali that they have right now and the fact that they can’t trade with Humans made Zhao Hai feel that the world has been very unfair to the Beastman race.

In fact, if one thought carefully, they can see that most of the wars between Beastmen and Humans were likely caused by the Human side. Take this time as an example, if the Humans did indeed withheld some grain, then what other choice do the Beastmen have other than to steal? Will they just die in starvation? Even Humans wouldn’t able to hold on, much more the ill tempered Beastmen.

Zhao Hai spent the night in the small Bear Tribe’s camp. When they prepared to leave in the morning, Zhao Hai left behind 5,000 jin of Bread Fruit for the Bears to consume. The Bears were naturally glad, they even want to pay Zhao Hai with their Argali, of which Zhao Hai strongly declined.

Things like these small transactions weren’t worthy of Zhao Hai’s concern. Tens of thousands of jins are too few for Zhao Hai. If he can make friends by giving those away, then that would be a good outcome.

After having their breakfast, Zhao Hai’s group left. Since they were already inside the Black Bear domain, they only needed another four day’s worth of travel to reach the main camp. The Black Bear Tribe was also quite a large one, so their domain would also be equally huge. But their main camp would be completely fixed, especially during the winter.

After four days of travelling and staying inside small Bear tribe camps, Zhao Hai can finally see the distant view of the Black Bear Tribe’s main camp.

At this time, a team of Black Bear Cavalry dashed out from the main camp. These people rode on top of four meter high black bears. Also, these Black Bears themselves were more than three meters high. One could feel pressure just by looking at these Black Bears riding their mounts.

Before long, the team arrived near Zhao Hai’s team. When their leader saw Buffon, he smiled and said, “So it’s Brother Buffon who arrived. Come with us to the camp quickly. Right, there are also some Herculean Bull brothers, welcome. There’s a human as well?”

When he heard the Bear Beastman, Zhao Hai understood that he was a frank person, expressing both closeness and distance in his words. When he saw Buffon, he immediately invited him to the camp, when he saw Mendez, he said his greetings. And when he saw Zhao Hai he expressed a bit of hostility.

Buffon jumped down from his mount and hugged the Bear Beastman and said, “Lieben, it’s supposed to be your patrol shift this time, why are you still in the camp? Have you been lazy again?”

Lieben cracked a smile and said, “You don’t know, but the tribe doesn’t have a lot of grain right now, we can only ration them out. There’s nobody who can eat fully right now, so we don’t have the energy to patrol around.”

Buffon didn’t expect that the Black Bear Tribe would reach this degree of shortage. It was still the beginning of spring, but the Black Bear Tribe was already rationing, it seems like their grain stores have really gone dry.

Buffon patted Lieben’s shoulder and said, “You don’t need to worry about that anymore. See this man? This is the Herculean Bull’s Foreign Prince, a big grain Merchant. He has a lot of food in his hand. After he traded with us, I brought him over here as well.”

Lieben looked at Zhao Hai and grinned, “Can a Human really become the Herculean Bull’s Foreign Prince? Good. Does he really have food in his hand?”

Buffon smiled and said, “Of course he has. I won’t dare deceive you. Escort us to the camp quickly.”

Lieben complied and led the group towards the main camp. They immediately headed towards the golden tent.

When they reached outside the golden tent, Lieben went inside to report while Zhao Hai and the others stood outside. Before long, Lieben went out and looked at the trio and said, “Buffon, the Patriarch asks you in.” Since Lieben didn’t ask Zhao Hai and Mendez, the two naturally wouldn’t follow. Buffon nodded to the two of them and then went inside the tent.

After quite some time, Lieben went out again and told Zhao Hai and Mendez, “The Patriarch invites you two in.” Then Zhao Hai and Mendez expressed their gratitude before entering the tent.

When Zhao Hai entered the tent, he noticed that there were a lot of people inside. Nearly 20 Black Bears were present, Buffon sat at a place in the left side of the tent.

In the place farthest from the entrance, a Black Bear was sitting. This Bear looked like he was in the prime of his life. His Bear eyes looked at the newcomers closely.

The two of them knew instantly that this person was the Black Bear Tribe’s Patriarch. After the two gave their respects, the Black Bear Beastman looked at Mendez and said, “You’re the Herculean Bull Prince Mendez?”

Mendez quickly replied, “Mendez has seen the Patriarch.”

The Black Bear nodded and said, “I know about what happened between you and Fighting Bulls. Good job in eliminating the Radiant Church.”

Mendez expressed his gratitude. Then the Black Bear turned his head to Zhao Hai and said, “You are the Herculean Bull Foreign Prince Zhao Hai?”

Zhao Hai smiled and said, “Zhao Hai has seen the Patriarch.”

The Black Bear Patriarch looked at Zhao Hai, “Since you’ve become the Foreign Prince of the Herculean bulls, this meant that you had helped them a lot. It seems like you’re not a bad person. Buffon said that you have a lot of food?”

Zhao Hai nodded and said, “I do have some food. It’s this one.” Then he put out a Bread Fruit and passed it along the Black Bears, having them taste it.

After Patriarch tasted the fruit, he nodded and said, “This is very good. But unlike Humans, we Black Bears eat a lot. How much do you have?”

Zhao Hai smiled and said, “I have a lot. This fruit is something that’s only grown in my territory. On the continent, only I have this thing. It’s still my second year trading in the Prairie, and I initially didn’t plan to sell a lot. But when I saw that there is a food shortage here, I decided to sell it to my friends, the Herculean Bulls and the Mastiffs. And since the Black Bear Tribe is friends with the Mastiffs, I came. After all, a friend of a friend is also a friend.”

The Black Bear nodded, then he said, “Alright, since you have a lot, our Black Bear Tribe wants all of it.”

Zhao Hai didn’t know whether to laugh or cry, these Beastman Patriarch really are too self-confident. They really think that they can buy everything that he has?

Zhao Hai quickly responded and said, “Sir Patriarch, you should tell me a specific amount. I really have a lot of food. Also, I’m afraid that you won’t want to have all of them. Even if the Bread Fruit can be stored for a long time, they can’t last forever. Especially when they burst, they can’t last for too long.”

Naturally, the Bread Fruit cannot burst by themselves. This was just Zhao Hai’s pretext. If he directly told the Black Bear Patriarch that they cannot afford all of his food, then the Black Bears would think that he was looking down on them. By that time, it would be impossible for him to be their friend.

Zhao Hai had already known that since the Black Bears had been deceived by a Human, they’re quite hostile towards them. This made Zhao Hai tread lightly with his words. He was even more careful this time than the time when he spoke to the Wolf King

Chapter 515: Intelligent Black Bear Tribe

The Black Bear Patriarch stared at Zhao Hai for quite some time, then seeming to remember something, he said, “Oh, right, yes, what’s the price of your Bread Fruit?”

Zhao Hai smiled and said, “A fourth the price of Bamboo Rice.” The one fourth price naturally referred to the price that other merchants sold Bamboo Rice. The Bamboo Rice that Zhao Hai sold was half of their price. Therefore, it would be impossible for Zhao Hai to sell his bread fruit according to his pricing of Bamboo rice, it was just too low.

Even then, this price still shocked the Black Bear Patriarch, he looked at Zhao Hai and said, “You didn’t speak incorrectly? Is it really a fourth the price of Bamboo Rice?”

Zhao Hai nodded, “It is. I’ve carried a transaction with the Prairie Wolf tribe earlier, I sold it to them at this price.” After mentioning the Prairie Wolves, Zhao Hai suddenly remembered that it was already six days since he left the Wolf camp. He should’ve given them the 700 million jin a day ago.

The Black Bear Patriarch looked at Zhao Hai for a long time then said, “I have to ask mister to take a rest first. We need to discuss this.” Zhao Hai nodded, then he went outside with Lieben. However, Mendez stayed inside the tent.

There was already a tent prepared for Zhao Hai outside. Zhao Hai didn’t become polite as he led Laura and the others inside the tent. Then he opened the monitor to see what the people inside the tent were talking about.

The Black Bear didn’t become polite and directly asked Mendez about Zhao Hai. They wanted to ask how he became a Herculean Bull Prince.

Mendez didn’t hide anything, he told everything to the Black Bears. He told them how they met Zhao Hai as well as the help that he did in defeating the Fighting Bulls.

The Black Bears were simple, but that didn’t mean that they were stupid. Upon hearing Mendez’ account, they knew that the reason how the Herculean Bulls were able to defeat the Fighting Bulls in a short time was Zhao Hai. No wonder Zhao Hai became a Foreign Prince.

When Mendez finished speaking, the Black Bear Patriarch nodded and said, “So that’s how it is. It seems like this Zhao Hai is really our Beastman Race’s friend. Since a friend came, how can we not serve him some nice wine. Lieben, prepare it immediately, we must invite mister Zhao Hai to drink with us today.” Lieben complied, then turned around to prepare.

Then the Black Bear Patriarch turned back to Mendez and said, “I also heard from Buffon that you have other reasons why you came here other than grain? Tell us.”

Mendez immediately replied, asking the Black Bear Tribe about how the Herculean Bulls needed backup. Buffon also helped, making the Black Bear Patriarch agree. After all, Zhao Hai was also now the Black Bear Tribe’s food supplier, this made the Black Bear Patriarch very grateful.

After saying this matter, Mendez moved on to their suspicion that the Radiant Church might have been behind the food shortage this time.

When the Black Bear Patriarch heard this, he immediately expressed his anger. Then he had someone to investigate this matter as well as pass this information over to the other big Warring Clans.

At this time, everything that they came for with the Black Bear Clan had already been taken care of. The only thing remaining was to have the food handed over.

The Black Bear Patriarch was now thinking about how much food he needs to trade with Zhao Hai. He really didn’t think about the matter about protecting the Herculean Bulls. To him, it was just nothing more than a statement. After all, the Mastiffs and the Herculean Bulls were already friends. Just as what Zhao Hai said, friends of friends were also friends. It was already implied that the Black Bears would help.

What their tribe lacks the most at this time was food. As long as their food problem is solved, everything would be easier to do. If the food remains unsolved, then they would suffer more losses.

However, since the time they were deceived by that Human Merchant, their Black Bear tribe has yet to recover to their former strength. If they want to trade with Zhao Hai, they cannot take a lot of things. So the Black Bear Patriarch was now wondering how much food they need to trade with Zhao Hai.

Buffon and Mendez have already invited to rest inside a prepared tent. Therefore, the only people left inside the tent were the Patriarch as well as the elders of the Black Bear tribe.

When an elder saw the frowning appearance of the Patriarch, he asked, “Patriarch, what are you worried about? Zhao Hai is here, wouldn’t he be able to solve our food problem?”

The Black Bear Patriarch sighed deeply and said, “We can indeed solve our food problem. I just don’t know how much we need to buy.”

The elder thought for a moment before he said, “Patriarch, I think we should just buy a little amount. If this matter is really caused by the Radiant Church, then war would surely come. As long as we participate, we can pillage some food from the Humans. So we really don’t need to buy too much food.”

When the Patriarch heard the elder, his eyes couldn’t help but light up, “Goodness, I didn’t think about that. We should buy a little bit, maybe several million jins at first. Then we’ll gauge from the situation whether we need more.”

The elders present all nodded. Zhao Hai, who was sitting inside his tent, couldn’t’ help but smile bitterly and turn his head to Laura, “Who said that Beastmen are simple minded? I’ll go beat him. From what I can see, these Beastmen aren’t simple, on the contrary, they’re very smart.”

Laura and the others smiled, then Megan said, “I didn’t expect these Beastmen to be so insightful as well. It seems like we cannot just underestimate them. Brother Hai, it looks like you won’t be making good profits this time.”

Zhao Hai smiled faintly, “They didn’t buy much because they had insider information. Right, we should leave some supply for Beast God City. That’s a center of authority for the Beastmen.”

Laura nodded, “When the Markey Family ended in my hands, I discovered that we had some businesses in Beast God City. But it seems like we had withdrawn them quite recently. But the shop is still there, we can take it over if we go. I’ve already sent some letters to Ah Tai, he should be cleaning that place up. Moreover, I’ve also given him some Bamboo Rice to sell there.”

Zhao Hai nodded, “That’s good. But he should have nothing left at this point. There’s a food shortage in the Prairie.”

Laura smiled, “Beast God City isn’t like other places. That place is the core area of the Beastman Prairie. If there’s a grain shortage, then their storehouses should be able to sustain them for some time. So you shouldn’t worry too much. Also, besides grain, I have also given Ah Tai some vegetables and fruit oil. I also told him to sell the grains last, taking care of the vegetables and oil first. If he sold everything, he would wait until we arrive.”

Zhao Hai smiled, “Alright, that arrangement is fine. After we talk with the Bears tomorrow, I’ll go back to the Wolf tribe and send them the remaining food. At the same time, I’ll go and tell them about the Radiant Church’s involvement in the grain shortage. Right, why do you think the Wolves wanted to trade us with money?”

Laura replied, “This isn’t strange. Huge Warring clans would sometimes use gold and silver for trade. Huge transactions are inconvenient if one doesn’t use gold. Also, the Wolf tribe has always been short on beasts. Don’t forget, the Wolf Tribes performs the most thievery towards Human Merchants among the Beastmen. Because of that, they have a lot of gold silver, which explains why they wanted to use those for their transactions.”

Zhao Hai nodded, “That is indeed the case. If one were to trade with Magic Beasts, it may become troublesome to do so in high numbers. Fortunately, we have good uses for gold and silver. Right, Laura, what do you think about having our own bank in Golden Island?”

When Laura heard him, she was confused as she asked Zhao Hai, “Brother Hai, do you really want to have a private bank at Golden Island? The waters regarding banks are very deep. Presently, all of the banks in the continent are in the hands of Royal Clans. If we make our own private bank, then we must prepare to offend some Royal Clans.”

When he heard Laura, Zhao Hai couldn’t help but regretfully shake his head as he sighed, “Forget it. If this is really the case, then we can’t make our own bank. We cannot bear to offend the people of the continent.”

Laura nodded, “Banks make a lot of money. Because of this, the Royal Clans naturally wouldn’t allow others to meddle with it. We should stop thinking about this matter.”

Zhao Hai nodded, the banks in the continent are much different than the banks back on Earth. Zhao Hai really wanted to try managing a bank, but when he heard Laura, he had no choice but to give up. He didn’t want to have a falling out with the Rosen Imperial Clan.

At this time, a voice was suddenly heard outside, “Is mister Zhao Hai in? The Patriarch invites you over for a feast.”

Zhao Hai complied, then he stood up before heading outside. Laura and the others also followed behind. When they got out of the tent, they also saw Buffon and Mendez who just came out. Not far from their tents, some Argalis were being roasted, there were some bulls on the pit as well. Such reception was already at a high standard.

Lieben asked Zhao Hai and the others to sit down. The Beastman’s way of eating were quite similar. If the weather is good, they wouldn’t’ eat inside the tent. This was because they cannot have open-air roasting indoors. For the Beastmen, not having an open-air barbecue was being unfair to the guests.

Zhao Hai was already used to this scene. After the group sat down, it didn’t take too long for the Black Bear Patriarch to come out. Zhao Hai and the others immediately stood up and offered their greetings.

The Black Bear Patriarch was now very polite towards Zhao Hai. After he invited the group to sit down, he turned his head to Zhao Hai and said, “I really want to express my gratitude to Mister Zhao Hai for coming to our Black Bear Tribe. You’ve really helped our tribe a lot.”

Zhao Hai smiled and said, “Patriarch is too polite. I am a Merchant, I came for business. Also, you’re friends who need food, so it is natural for me to offer it.”

The Black Bear Patriarch laughed, “Good, good. Since Mister thinks of us as a friend, then you’ll be our friend. Hahaha. Mister, take this cup. From now on, you’ll be a friend to our Black Bear Tribe.”

When Zhao Hai heard the Patriarch, he couldn’t help but be happy. He then raised his glass and returned the Patriarch’s gesture. What they were drinking right now was the most common Milk Wine of the Beastmen. Since Zhao Hai was still unfamiliar with the Black Bears, he chose to not provide his wine this time.

Chapter 516: Black Bear Tribe’s Friendship Flag

Beastmen are very strange, if you gave them any gift, no matter how precious, they would without a doubt accept it. Even if they knew that you’re just doing it to help them, they would still receive it with no hesitations. However, if you give them liquor during a meal, especially if you’re still not very familiar with them, they would think that you’re looking down on them. For them, this was a very huge matter.

But even so, the barbecue this time was very tasty. Even if it was Megan and Lizzy’s first time drinking genuine Beastman Milk Wine, its taste wasn’t that far from Zhao Hai’s distilled milk wine.

This meal made Zhao Hai and the others quite full, they also hadn’t drunk any small liquor. They were in the presence of Beastmen, the more you eat and drink, the happier the Beastmen get.

After eating their meal, it was already quite late. Therefore, Zhao Hai and the others returned to their tent. It seems like it would be impossible to talk about the grain with the Black Bear Patriarch today.

When Zhao Hai returned to his tent, he expected that nobody would come. But just after they entered the Space, Mendez and Buffon arrived. This surprised Zhao Hai, then he made Laura and the others go out of the Space again.

The two might look tipsy, but one could see that they weren’t that drunk. Zhao Hai served them some Spatial Water, but they didn’t drink it. Buffon looked at Zhao Hai and said, “Little Hai, we told the Black Bear Tribe about the Radiant Church’s involvement. But now it looks like we told them quite early.”

Zhao Hai stared, then Mendez guiltily smiled, “We did tell them a little bit too early. The Black Bear Tribe lacked grain, but they didn’t discuss this matter with us immediately. It seems like they wanted to wait until the war starts and snatch their food there. They’re not planning to buy a lot of food from you. Really, who said that these Bears as too simple? This is too insincere.”

Hearing their concerns, Zhao Hai came to an understanding. He couldn’t help but smile and said, “It’s fine, you’re thinking too much. The Black Bear clan is having a hard time, so it’s natural that they’d buy as little as possible. I’ll tell you the truth, if the Beastmen didn’t lack grain, I wouldn’t be selling the Bread Fruits. If I make these Fruits into liquor, I’d be getting multiple times more profits from them. You don’t need to worry about it too much.”

Mendez sighed, “Thank you, Little Hai. If there are more Humans like you, I think there wouldn’t be any more wars between Humans and Beastmen.”

Zhao Hai forced a smile and said, “People have ambition. As long as ambition is present, war will continually happen. Sooner or later, conflicts will appear. With my own strength, I couldn’t’ change everything, I’m just doing all I can to help.”

Mendez and Buffon sighed, they knew that Zhao Hai was right. This thing called ambition was impossible to control. Not to mention the Humans, Beastmen were the same. Otherwise, the matter with the Fighting Bulls wouldn’t have happened.

Buffon looked at Zhao Hai and said, “Little Hai, what do you plan to do next?”

Zhao Hai smiled and said, “I’ll head to Beast God City to take a look. The things I need to do here are almost done. Even if the Black Bears have other Warring Clan friends, we aren’t sure if they have huge problems regarding food. If they have ears around, they may even know about the war. So it’s probable that they wouldn’t buy any grain. I also want to go to Beast God City to see how willing the other Beastmen were when it comes to war since Humans might become the most undesirable people in the prairie.”

Buffon snorted, “ I don’t know about other humans, but you will definitely have no problems. Don’t forget, you’re now a Prince of the Herculean Bulls, you’re basically half beastman. If you want, you can head back to our main camp and wait of our Dog-headed race’s friendship flag.”

Zhao Hai smiled, “Forget it. If worse comes to worst, I can just return to the Herculean Bull tribe. Moreover, I’ve also received a new fief just recently, I still have a lot of work to do. It’s more likely that I’d need to return to Human Territory soon. Don’t worry, i won’t go too far.”

Mendez nodded, “Alright. In any case, if war does happen, Beastmen don’t generally kill humans in the Prairie, we’d only chase them away. You also have the Herculean Bull’s King’s flag, that should be quite useful.”

Zhao Hai nodded and then smiled, “Well, you don’t really need to worry about me. I’m just going to Beast God City in order to see the situation and maybe make one or two business deals.”

Mendez sighed and said, “I really think that war would definitely happen. But I really don’t want to fight the Rosen Empire. Little Hai shouldn’t worry about it.”

Zhao Hai smiled and said, “I won’t, my territory is a small island. It would be impossible for the Beastman’s attack to reach there.”

Mendez nodded, then he looked at the skies and said, “It’s already quite late, we’ll head back to rest. Little Hai, I think you should go hand your grain over to the Wolves as soon as possible. The Wolves are very mannered people, it wouldn’t be good if you go too late.”

Zhao Hai nodded, “Right, rest assured, I’ll go there tomorrow. You don’t need to worry, you go rest now.” The two nodded, then stood up and returned to their tent.

After that, Zhao Hai and the others returned to the Space. Then Laura looked at Zhao Hai and said, “It looks like we misjudged the determination of the Beastman Race. There is a huge food shortage in the Prairie right now, it doesn’t matter if this situation was caused by the Radiant Church, I think the Beastmen would still wage war regardless. They really need food.”

Megan looked at Zhao Hai and said, “Big Brother Hai, will the Beastmen run to the Black Wasteland? If they do, they might cause troubles.”

Zhao Hai shook his head and said, “They shouldn’t, the situation with the Black Wasteland didn’t happen in a day or two. All of the races in the Continent should know about the Poisonous Mist right now. Even the Beastmen wouldn’t’ charge towards it at this point. You don’t need to worry about it, we’re fine.”

Megan nodded, then Lizzy frowned and said, “Elder Brother Hai, what effects do you think this will have to the Rosen Empire? Didn’t the Empire prohibit trade towards Aksu Empire? Because of this, there would be less merchants who can go to the Prairie and trade with the Beastmen and sell them food. If this becomes the case, then wouldn’t the Rosen Empire be an accomplice in this war?”

When he heard Lizzy, Zhao Hai’s expression changed, the he said, “That makes sense. But I don’t think that it’s the Empire’s fault that the Merchants weren’t able to do business. Can Great Nobles really give up their profits? No! Especially getting profits from the Beastmen, they wouldn’t want to miss this opportunity. Therefore, I don’t think that it’s the Rosen Empire’s fault. If we really think too much into it, then it would be much more evident that this matter is caused by the Radiant Church.”

Laura and the others stared, they couldn’t understand what Zhao Hai was saying. Zhao Hai sighed and said, “You should know that the Rosen Empire didn’t want the Radiant Church to exist in its territory, this offended the Church. If the Radiant Church intentionally held the food from the Beastmen, they can push the fault to the Rosen Empire. When that time comes, the Rosen Empire would be in very huge trouble!”

Lizzy and the other’s complexion changed, they knew that if the Radiant Church can push the fault of this matter to the Rosen Empire, the Rosen Empire would be hated by the entire Continent. The Church’s move was using a borrowed knife to deal with another. Shifting the blame in this matter was a ruthlessly dirty move.

Lizzy was the one who cared the most about this situation, she immediately turned to ZHao Hai and said, “Elder Brother Hai, what do we do? If the Radiant Church’s plan goes well, our Rosen Empire would be isolated by the Continent.”

Zhao Hai nodded and said, “We should quickly write a letter to his majesty informing him of what happened here, and have the Empire get ready. The Radiant Church wanted to use this method to deal with us, I think they’re just waiting until the Beastmen declare war. We shouldn’t let this matter wait, let’s have his Majesty handle this matter and turn this into the Radiant Church’s bad luck. How to deal with this would have to be left to His Majesty, he has more understanding than me regarding these things. The only thing we need to do is inform him.”

Lizzy nodded, then Zhao Hai took out some writing materials and had Lizzy write a letter to the Emperor. Then he had it taken from his office back on Golden Island by Kun and sent to the Calci Family via blood hawk. Randolph can then send it to the Emperor.

The reason why Zhao Hai went through so much trouble was because he wanted people to not suspect him. He had the letter sent using a Blood Hawk since people already knew about it.

After completing these, Zhao Hai and the others felt relief and rested in the villa. However, they couldn’t help but feel a bit of fear inside. If the Radiant Church really did succeed, then the Rosen Empire would surely be in deep trouble. The Radiant Church can use this matter to splash some dirty water onto the Rosen Empire. With the number of their believers, it wouldn’t take too long before an uproar would happen against the Rosen Empire. The Radiant Church can then suppress the Rosen Empire, and may even force the Empire to allow the religion inside.

Although this information was still unconfirmed, but it was better to be on guard just in case the Radiant Church did indeed cause it. At this point, Zhao Hai was now utterly disgusted with the Radiant Church. In his mind, the image of the Church had now become an organization that would resort to all means just to accomplish their goals.

In order to deal with an enemy, they actually didn’t hesitate to cause an interracial war. If this matter was really proven to be caused by the Radiant Church, then they would definitely become an evil organization.

The next morning, after having their breakfast, the Black Bear Patriarch invited Zhao Hai over to the golden tent, making Zhao Hai postpone his plan of going to the Prairie Wolves.

Zhao Hai entered the golden tent, and unexpectedly, Mendez and Buffon were actually present. Zhao Hai then went to the Black Bear Patriarch and offered his greetings. The Patriarch returned the gesture to Zhao Hai as he asked him to sit down. After Zhao Hai sat down, the Black Bear Patriarch looked at him and said, “Mister Zhao Hai, I invited you today in order to discuss with you about the food.”

Zhao Hai nodded, then the Black Bear Patriarch continued, “I think mister already knows about how we were deceived by a Human Merchant years before. We have been unable to recover since then, so we really wanted to buy some food from mister. However, Mendez told us yesterday that the food shortage might have been artificial. If this is really the case, then we Beastman would be waging a war against the humans. During the war, we would be able to pillage some resources, so this time we can’t buy too much food from you.”

Zhao Hai looked at the Black Bear Patriarch. He already knew that the Black Bears wouldn’t buy too much food from what he heard yesterday. He thought that the Black Bear Patriarch would find an excuse to tell him. But he never thought that the Black Bear Patriarch would actually tell him the actual reason. This made Zhao Hai surprised.

He was too used to the false talk of Humans that he was startled when he met an honest person. Although Buffon and Mendez had told him that the Black Bears were honest people, Zhao Hai didn’t expect them to be very honest.

Seeing that it took a long time for Zhao Hai to respond, the Black Bear Patriarch thought that he was unhappy. He quickly added, “Mister Zhao Hai can feel relieved. Our Black Bear tribe would cooperate with you in the future. But this time, we really just need a small amount of food.”

Zhao Hai recovered, he quickly said, “Patriarch is too polite. This isn’t really a problem. I also understand the Patriarch’s reason. How much do you want?”

When the Black Bear Patriarch saw that Zhao Hai wasn’t unhappy, he smiled and said, “We’re going to buy 40 million jin first. Do you have this much?”

Zhao Hai smiled and said, “I can give it to you immediately. As long as Patriarch finds a place to receive them, I shall give them to you. I have more than 40 million in my hands right now.”

The Black Bear Patriarch looked at Zhao Hai, then he understood that Zhao Hai had a Space Bag. He immediately became happy and replied, “Good, fantastic. Mister can just place them outside. I’ll have some people clear a place out. Right, does mister want Magic Beasts as payment?”

Zhao Hai smiled and said, “You can also give me some gold and silver coins, those things aren’t really useful in the Prairie. You can also give me some Magic Beasts if your coins aren’t enough.”

The Black Bear Patriarch’s eyes turned bright, then he laughed and said, “Alright, Mister is really our tribe’s friend. Right, Lieben, immediately take our tribe’s friendship flag. I must give mister our Black Bear Tribe’s friendship flag.!” Lieben nodded, then he turned around to leave.

Zhao Hai stared, he didn’t think that he would be receiving a friendship flag this time. The Black Bear Tribe was a big Warring Clan, their friendship flag was really too important. One could say  that with this flag, he could surely walk sideways in the Prairie. There would be too few people who would dare offend him.

Chapter 517: Well Worth-it Transaction

Naturally, the Black Bear Patriarch didn’t do this on impulse. Since he was the Patriarch, hsi decisions were all very well thought out.

Zhao Hai might not deeply know the importance of Argalis, but how could the Black Bear Patriarch not? These Magic Beasts cannot be raised by humans and can only be reared in the Prairie. These beasts were generally coins that could give birth.

It can also be said that to the Beastmen, gold and silver were equivalent to stones. To them, those Argali were the things with value.

At the same time, Zhao Hai was also a Foreign Prince of the Herculean Bulls as well as a friend to the Mastiffs. With his connections, the Black Bear Patriarch naturally attached great importance to Zhao Hai.

Beastmen also regard relationships, in fact, they held it with great importance. This was because Beastmen held deep sentiments, and were deeply sincere. If the relationship between two parties was very good, then it was certain that they would help each other a lot.

The situation with the Black Bears wasn’t very good right now. Just as what the Black Bear Patriarch said, if they weren’t that poor, then they might have bought more food. It was just a pity that they don’t have much right now.

There were three reasons why the Black Bear Patriarch gave Zhao Hai their friendship flag. First, it was because the relationship between the Herculean Bulls and the Black bears was good. The second reason was to give the Mastiff tribe face. And the third reason was because Zhao Hai was a grain Merchant. Because of these three reasons, the Black Bear Patriarch decided to give Zhao Hai their tribe’s friendship flag.

Zhao Hai wasn’t polite, he immediately stepped forward and received the flag. Then he gave a bow and said, “My deepest gratitude to the Black Bear Patriarch. Rest assured, from this day onward, Zhao Hai would become the Black Bear Tribe’s friend. I naturally wouldn’t be stingy as a friend, so I’ll leave 50 million jin behind. The extra Bread Fruits would serve as my gift to the black Bear Tribe. The Patriarch must accept it.’

The Black Bear Patriarch didn’t expect Zhao Hai to casually give them 10 million jins of Bread Fruit. This wasn’t a small amount, one should know that some transactions between Beastmen and Humans wouldn’t reach 10 million jin. For Zhao Hai to give 10 million jins just like that was too astonishing.

The Black Bear Patriarch thought about what he just gained. 10 million jins of food for a friendship flag, this transaction was pretty well worth it.

The Black Bear Patriarch couldn’t help but laugh, “Alright, I’ll accept it. But Little Hai, do you really want to trade for gold and silver?”

Zhao Hai smiled and said, “Yes, we can just use gold and silver. I know that they might be useless to you, but they have value in my hands. So I might as well have them.”

The Black Bear Patriarch laughed, “Alright, then I’ll be impolite to you. Lieben, go have some people get the gold and silver that we have, those things are useless anyway. At the same time, go have a banquet prepared.”

Zhao Hai quickly said, “Patriarch, I’ll have to be exempted from the banquet. I need to go to the Prairie Wolf tribe today. While we were coming here, we’ve been stopped by them. Then we managed to make a transaction but I still haven’t given them the food. You can wait a moment while I send them the remaining Bread Fruits.”

The Black Bear Patriarch shook his head when he heard Zhao Hai, “Don’t worry, make that old thin Wolf wait for a while. They won’t die anytime soon. Right, what did he use to trade? Gold and silver?”

Zhao Hai nodded and said, “Partly gold and silver, partly Magic Beasts. Right, Patriarch, i want some unique Magic Beasts. I don’t care about what kind of beast as long as they are unique to the Prairie. I’d like plants as well, it would be nice if Patriarch can pay attention for me.”

The Black Bear Patriarch didn’t say anything for a moment, then he nodded and said, “Alright, I’ll give you two violent bears later. But we need to make an agreement that you shouldn’t hand them over to other Humans for research. They are our beast relatives.”

Zhao Hai smiled and said, “Patriarch can rest assured. I wouldn’t give them to any other Human. Moreover, I want those beasts not for research, I have other uses for them.” Then the Black Bear Patriarch nodded.

Zhao Hai watched the time and turned to the Patriarch, “Patriarch, I’ll go and hand the Bread Fruits to you. 50 million jin isn’t a a small number.” The Patriarch nodded and then Zhao Hai turned around to leave.

When Zhao Hai went out of the tent, Buffon smiled to the Black Bear Patriarch and said, “Patriarch is truly very fast in making decisions. It only took a small time before giving Little Hai your Friendship Flag. Very unlike my father, we really want to give Little Hai our friendship flag, but we still needed the approval of the various tribe leaders.”

The Black Bear Patriarch stared, he looked at Buffon and said, “Your Mastiff tribe also want to give your friendship flag to Little Hai?”

Buffon shook his head and said, “Not our Mastiff Tribe, but our Dog-headed race. Our Mastiff Tribe’s friendship flag wouldn’t be a big use to Little Hai. Because of this, father wanted to convince the other tribe leaders to give Little Hai our Dog-headed race’s friendship flag.”

The Black Bear Patriarch thought about it. Although the Dog-headed Race wasn’t considered to be a Warring Race, their fighting strength was very strong. Under the Warring Races, their strength could be considered to be the strongest. There were even some small Warring Races that aren’t necessarily stronger than the Dog-headed Race. If not for some of their branches being very weak, the Dog-headed Beastment would’ve already become a Warring Race.

For such a group to give Zhao Hai their friendship flag meant that they attached great importance towards him. It was at this point that the Black Bear Patriarch realized the value of his earlier transaction.

At this time, Zhao Hai had already released his Bread Fruits. The pile of fruits looked like a small hill. The Black Bears cheered at the sight of it. Then after being handed orders, they immediately went and stored it at someplace safe.

When Zhao Hai returned to the tent, Lieben still hadn’t come back. He was still managing the gold and silver that was needed to be given to Zhao Hai. The gold and silver needed wasn’t a small amount.

After Zhao Hai entered the tent, he gave a bow to the Black Bear Patriarch and said, “Patriarch, I’ll be heading to the Prairie Wolf tribe to give them the food. I shall come back immediately.”

The Black Bear Patriarch gawked, “Do you really need to go? I have already prepared the banquet.”

Zhao Hai smiled, “Don’t worry, I’ll come back right away.” Then he went out of the tent and whistled. Before long, a red silhouette came flying down. Before the Black Bears could respond, the figure had already fallen in front of Zhao Hai. The Blood Hawk’s body was now more than  three meters high and looked very majestic. Zhao Hai rode on the hawk’s back before it spread its wings and shot up into the air. It didn’t take a long time before he became a small dot in the sky.

When Lieben saw this, he immediately had other people move the gold and silver. Then he returned to the tent and told everything he saw to the Black bear Patriarch.

The Black Bear Patriarch responded, “Are you sure? The Hawk looked stronger than the Hawk-headed race’s beast? Does this mean that the Humans now have an Air Force?”

This was another difference between the Humans and Beastmen, the Beastmen have their own Air Force. They had a lot of Aerial Forces, they were divided between the Chaffinch, the Hawks, the Eagles, and so on. Because of their unique beasts, they can form their own Air Force. This aspect was the Beastman’s advantage against Humans.

However, the Beastmen’s Air Force have their own flight limitations and can’t fly higher than the Blood Hawk. They can only fly at low altitudes, enough for Humans to target them with Ballistas. Making an Air Force also wasn’t very easy, so their role in the Beastman Race wasn’t that huge.

Now that he heard that Zhao Hai had a flying Magic Beast that was also quite strong, the Black Bear Patriarch was startled. He didn’t know that the Humans also had their own Air Force.

After thinking about it, he couldn’t help but turn towards Buffon and Mendez. Buffon was also clueless about this matter. However, Mendez knew since Zhao Hai didn’t hide it from them. Even if the Beastmen have races that are suitable for Air Forces, they aren’t very numerous. At the same time, races like the Black Bears and the Herculean Bulls cannot have an Air Force, they were simply too heavy. Even if they can ride a Blood Hawk, they wouldn’t be able to do a lot of things on its back.

Mendez looked at the Black Bear Patriarch and knew that the other party wanted some answers. Therefore, Mendez didn’t hide the truth as he nodded and said, “They have, but not the Aksu Empire. Little Hai is now under the Rosen Empire, his wife was also the daughter of the Emperor. The Rosen Empire had begun to set up their Air Force, but it would take a while before they become operational.”

The Black Bear Patriarch nodded, “So it’s like this. That’s good, it wouldn’t be great if the Aksu Empire had their own Air Force. Right, why didn’t Little Hai give the Aksu Empire some of his hawks?”

Mendez smiled, “It’s because Little Hai has a grudge with the Aksu Empire and the Radiant Church. With such enmity, how could he give his hawks to the Aksu Empire? Instead, he couldn’t wait until the Empire gets eliminated.”

When the Black Bear Patriarch heard Mendez, he smiled and said, “Alright, that’s good. So this means that we don’t need to hold back against the Aksu Empire.”

Mendez smiled and said, “There’s also the Radiant Church. When we deal with the Aksu Empire, we can send word out that it was because the Radiant Church was holding food back from us. This would be Little Hai’s lesson towards the Radiant Church.”

The Black Bear Patriarch laughed, “No need to say more. I also find the Radiant Church to be repugnant. It is also highly probable that they are behind this food shortage, so we just cannot let them off. It’s a good idea to send a word out and make those Humans deal with the Radiant Church themselves. It would save us the effort of doing it.”

The people inside the tent laughed. While they were discussing about the Radiant Church, there was another person who was also thinking about the organization. And this person was none other than Zhao Hai’s Father-in-law, the Rosen Emperor.

Chapter 518: Dead Minister

When the Rosen Emperor received Zhao Hai’s letter, he couldn’t help but be shocked. He really didn’t expect the Radiant Church to use this method to deal with the Empire.

Although this information was still unconfirmed, the Emperor already believed it to be real. If the Church’s plan came to fruition, the Rosen Empire would be detested by the entire continent. There was even a possibility that the commoners would stop supporting them.

If the commoners start believing in the Radiant Church, then the Rosen Empire would be following the footsteps of other nations. They might even be even worse than the others. The Rosen Empire had offended the Radiant Church, it would be very strange if the Radiant Church lets this opportunity to punish the Rosen Empire go.

The Rosen Emperor thought that Zhao Hai’s letter came at a very timely manner. The Radiant Church still hadn’t started their plan, at this point, the Rosen Empire had the upper hand.

The Emperor immediately called his trusted ministers over and had them read the letter sent by Zhao Hai. These ministers were also nobles of the Rosen Empire, none of them were stupid. Upon reading the letter, they immediately understood the implications of this matter for the Rosen Empire.

When the Emperor saw their faces, he knew what they were thinking. Then he said, “I didn’t think that the Radiant Church would use this trick. This is really too ruthless. We’re lucky that Little Hai managed to inform us, otherwise, I don’t want to think about what would happen. Everyone, what do you think we should do?”

Then almost everyone’s gazes turned to Randolph. The Calci Family had been at odds with the Radiant Church for a long time. Moreover, Randolph was Zhao Hai’s Grandfather-in-law. Because of this, everyone wanted to hear Randolph’s opinion first.

When Randolph saw their gazes, he knew that he needed to talk. He  couldn’t help but coldly snort, “It would be bad if we didn’t know. However, since we found out about it, then there would be no way for the Radiant Church to succeed.  I think we should first spread this information, fully expressing the Radiant Church’s plans. We should make the first move, make the people side with us. When the Beastmen attack and ravage the Aksu Empire, even if the Radiant Church starts their plan, nobody would believe them.”

The Emperor nodded and said, “Randolph is right. I thought about this plan as well. What do all of you think?”

Jesse then added, “If the Beastmen really did have a food shortage just as Little Hai said, then we don’t have anything to worry about. However, once the Aksu Empire gets into trouble because of the war, refugees would come in droves. By then, we wouldn’t’ have any choice other than help them, otherwise, the Radiant Church would be using it against us.”

The Emperor nodded, “This really depends on how far the Beastmen go. If they get too ambitious, then the Aksu Empire would suffer a lot. The Beastmen army isn’t something that they can resist, at this time, we usually send some troops for support. But this time, I don’t want our soldiers to die in vain, let’s have the Aksu Empire pay the price first before sending support troops.”

Then another Noble said, “We should, but we cannot send too many. We are already convinced that the Aksu Empire has been colluding with the Radiant Church. But even then, we are already sure that Boris is certainly with the Radiant Church. If we dispatch troops to help the Empire, then they may be entering into the Radiant Church’s trap. How about we start with having the Aksu Empire recognize our sovereignty of Golden Island first, then have them make a public apology towards us. What does your Majesty think about this?”

The Emperor nodded and said, “Very well. We cannot just fall into traps. Good, if the Aksu Empire cannot take it, then we’ll send support. Pass this command, starting tomorrow, the Rosen Empire will enter 2nd alert level . Every information regarding the Radiant Church shall need to be passed on as soon as possible.” The people present complied, then they asked to be excused.

When everyone had left, the Emperor then talked with a serious voice, “What do you think about this matter?” He seems to be talking to himself, but at this time, a reply came, “Zhao Hai has performed well. It seems like he really does regard himself as a person of the Rosen Empire. And also, he doesn’t seem to be a person with great ambitions.”

The voice resounded in the hall, however, the Emperor doesn’t seem to be startled. This was because this voice came from someone belonging to a special Rosen Empire unit, a Dead Minister!

A Dead Minister didn’t mean that this minister was an undead. On the contrary, they were very alive humans. This man follows the Emperor everytime. The existence of these ministers were only known to the Rosen Emperors. Whatever the Emperor was doing, this minister will always be with him. Even if the Emperor was with his concubine in bed, they would act as an audience at one side. It’s just that nobody had ever seen them before.

Would the Emperor be comfortable in having someone with him all the time? The answer was of course not. But this rule has been present since the first Rosen Emperor. Nobody dared disobey this rule.

Because of this, no Emperor ever talked about their existence outside. These people’s existence was Rosen Empire’s biggest secret.

The Emperor nodded and said, “It seems like the kid is doing a good job in managing Golden Island. He’s also quite strong himself, but he doesn’t seem to want to expand. Giving Lizzy to him makes me feel relieved.”

The voice didn’t come, then the Emperor sighed and said, “If Little Hai didn’t send word early, then we might have been extinguished by the Radiant Church sooner or later.” The Emperor seems to be talking to himself right now, the voice wasn’t speaking anymore.

The Emperor also knew that unless he took the initiative and asked, the voice wouldn’t say anything. The Emperor also knew that the owner of the voice was still there. For how long he has been the Emperor, he still hadn’t seen this person. He only knew that this person was extremely loyal to the Rosen Imperial Clan.

On the other hand, Randolph, who just came out of the palace, immediately rushed towards his house. He wanted to tell Zhao Hai about the Emperor’s decisions. No matter what, this matter was brought to light by Zhao Hai. Randolph wanted Zhao Hai to know about this news.

Actually, he really didn’t need to tell Zhao Hai since the latter already knew. After Zhao Hai had the letter sent, he also made Cai’er pay attention to the Imperial Palace. Zhao Hai even found out about the existence of the Dead Minister.

At this time, Zhao Hai was already on the skies outside the Prairie Wolf camp. When he descended to the camp, the people became frightened. However, when they saw that it was only Zhao Hai, they relaxed.

Zhao Hai didn’t rashly go to inside the camp, he just stood outside and waited. Before long, Hans came, he looked at Zhao Hai with an indifferent expression and said, “You’re two days late.”

Zhao Hai smiled and said, “My apologies, there are matters that delayed me.” Hans nodded, then he turned around and walked towards the camp with Zhao Hai following him closely behind.

When he entered the golden tent, the Old Wolf King was already waiting for him. Upon seeing Zhao Hai, the Old Wolf King said, “Mister Zhao Hai, you’re late.”

Zhao Hai smiled faintly and said, “I’ve been unfair to the Wolf King. I’ve been delayed for two days because of some matter. But I have some information to tell you, once you hear this, your grievance towards the food would disappear.”

The Old Wolf King looked at Zhao Hai and said, “What is it?”

Zhao Hai then told him about the food shortage of the Prairie being possibly caused by the Radiant Church. He also told the Wolf King that the Beastmen might declare war against the Humans.

The Old Wolf King calmly listened to Zhao Hai and waited until he finished. When Zhao Hai was done, the old Wolf King looked at him and said, “Why did you tell me this? Now that you told me about this, I wouldn’t be buying anymore food.”

Zhao Hai nodded and said, “I know, but I must inform you about this. I don’t want to deceive you just for measly money. What I want is long-term cooperation with your tribe, I don’t want short-lived businesses.”

The Old Wolf King looked at Zhao Hai for quite some time before he laughed, “Good, good. It’s been quite a long time before I saw someone so interesting. Alright then, I’ll be impolite. This time I’ll get 300 million jin, nothing more. What do you think?”

Zhao Hai smiled and said, “No problem. Since I told you about this, then I already knew that this would happen. There are still many opportunities for business in the future. Right, since I don’t have anything else to do here anymore, then I’ll have to ask the Wolf King to give me permission to be excused.”

The Wolf King looked at Zhao Hai and said, “Why so anxious? Is there a problem?”

Zhao Hai smiled faintly and said, “I just want to catch up with the Bear tribe, The Black Bear Patriarch has prepared a feast and is waiting for me. I must head back to attend the event.”

The Old King nodded and said, “Since you have a prior engagement with that stupid bear, then you should go. Our Prairie Wolves need food every year, you have a lot of opportunities to come back here.”

Zhao Hai smiled, “Right, if the Wolf King needs anything else, then don’t hesitate to tell me. I can also supply things other than food, I have some daily necessities, ironware, salt, and a lot more things that you might want. Just tell me and I’ll have them sent over.”

The Old Wolf King nodded and said, “Well, there’s still the war. After that, we can start our cooperation. Hans, are Mister Zhao Hai’s things ready?”

Hans nodded and said, “They’re prepared.” Then the Wolf King nodded and said, “Then bring Mister Zhao Hai along to take it.” Hans complied and then turned to walk outside. Zhao Hai gave the Wolf King a salute before leaving as well.

Hans walked in front while Zhao Hai followed him. Before long, they arrived in front of a tent. There were two Wolf-headed Beastmen guarding the entrance to the tent. When they saw Hans arrive, they immediately bowed. Then Hans lifted the curtain to enter.

When Zhao Hai saw this, he knew that he was to follow Hans in. So he didn’t hesitate and immediately went inside. Once he entered the tent, Zhao Hai immediately knew why Hans brought him here. This tent was the Wolf-tribe’s treasure vault.

Chapter 519: Sun?

Handling gold differed between the Humans and Beastmen. Since the Humans use these precious metals as circulation currency, they would mold them into coins. However, Beastmen don’t use gold for trading since they have their Magic Beasts. Because of this, their gold were made into bricks.

The tent was entirely full of gold bricks, if one were to calculate, this was an absolutely great wealth. Hans looked at Zhao Hai, he wanted to see Zhao Hai’s face when he saw those gold bricks.

In the past, when the Prairie Wolves did business with Humans, Hans would also bring them to this tent. When Humans see this display, their saliva would flow out and would even forget about Han’s existence. Upon seeing the gold bricks, they were truly entranced, almost to the point of literally kissing and licking the bricks. Hans used to look at them and feel disgusted.

Hans wanted to see what expression Zhao Hai would have when he saw the gold. However, when he turned to see Zhao Hai, he couldn’t believe what he saw. This was because Zhao Hai took a small glance at those bricks before shifting his gaze elsewhere. It seems like, to Zhao Hai, those gold bricks were worth nothing.

Zhao Hai’s reaction made Hans surprised. Although Hans hasn’t gone to the Human territories before, he knew that they used gold and silver for trade. He knew how much wealth these bricks represented. The reason he brought Zhao Hai here was to see how greedy of a person Zhao Hai was.

The reason why the Wolf-headed Race had so little interactions with Human merchants was because they don’t trust the Human race. They think that the humans were too greedy. Therefore, if they did want to have a long-term cooperation with a merchant, they wanted to see first if they were greedy or not. This treasury was their test.

The Merchants who came here in the past were killed and then fed to Hans’ mount. This time, they wanted to see Zhao Hai’s performance and see whether he was worth having a long-term partnership with. If Zhao Hai was also very greedy, then for the Herculean Bulls, Mastiffs, and the Black Bears, they wouldn’t kill him. However, it would be very hard for Zhao Hai to do business with them again in the future.

Although Zhao Hai’s actions made Hans shocked, Hans was also very satisfied. At the same time, Zhao Hai was surprised internally as well. This was because this shouldn’t be a treasury, but a treasure trove itself! There are a lot of good things here, some of them Zhao Hai couldn’t recognize. However, just based on the fact that they were here, their value shouldn’t be very low.

Seeing that Zhao Hai was looking around, Hans said, “Sir, you can take these gold and silver bricks. Take the amount equal to your price for 300 million jin of food.”

Zhao Hai looked at Hans and smiled, “I’m really not in a hurry. To think that this is actually your treasure trove, I can’t help but leave the bricks alone. I want to pick something else in this room, if its value exceeds the food that I supplied, I can compensate it with more fruits. What do you think?”

Hans stared at Zhao Hai with a strange look. The reason with Hans’ expression was Zhao Hai’s misunderstanding. This wasn’t the treasure trove of the Prairie Wolf tribe, this was just a storage tent. In this tent, aside from gold, there were also strange things that the Prairie Wolf had gotten over the years. These things were useless to the Prairie Wolves, they couldn’t be researched either, these aren’t really treasures.

It was because of this that when Zhao Hai told Hans that he’d exchange these things for food, he couldn’t help but stare strangely. Seeing Hans’ expression, Zhao Hai became confused, then he asked, “What’s wrong? I can’t?”

Hans shook his head and said, “I’m unable to take responsibility for this. I must ask the Patriarch first. I’ll have to ask mister to come out with me in the meantime.” Zhao Hai nodded, then came out of the tent with Hans. While Hans went to look for the Wolf King, Zhao Hai waited in front of the tent.

The reason why Zhao Hai proposed this trade was because he saw a peculiar thing among the items inside the tent. It was a piece of metal inside a crystal bottle. This metallic thing looks very strange, it was boiling just like how water would, it also had some faint bluish flames surrounding it. If one wasn’t paying attention, they wouldn’t notice this thin layer of flame.

When Zhao Hai’s eyes located the item, he can feel something in his heart, it kept telling him that he needed to obtain it! Because of this feeling, Zhao Hai made this request to Hans.

Before long, Hans went back and then looked at Zhao Hai, “Mister, the Patriarch has given word. Since Mister is our tribe’s friend, then we won’t treat you unjustly. Mister, in truth, all of the items in this tent are worthless to our Prairie Wolf tribe. If Mister takes a liking to one, mister can just take it, then you can take the gold as we have discussed before.”

When Zhao Hai heard Hans, he couldn’t help but laugh and said, “His Highness Wolf King is really too polite. But I don’t want to be cheap towards the Wolf King either. The things inside this tent might be useless to you, but to me, they are very useful. I only need one thing, the bricks we can discuss later.”

Then he turned around to enter the tent, he took the strange metal in a bottle and then told Hans, “Hans, I want this thing. Since I have an urgent matter to take care of, I wouldn’t be saying goodbye to the Wolf King. If I have the opportunity later, then I would certainly give my greetings.”

Hans looked at Zhao Hai and nodded. He actually thought of Zhao Hai as a friend at this point. After all, Zhao Hai’s performance today had given Hans a good impression of him.

Outside, after saying his goodbyes to Hans, Zhao Hai got up to his Blood Hawk as it shot up into the sky. When he reckoned that nobody was now able to see him, Zhao Hai entered the Space.

After he entered the Space, a prompt was heard, “Source of pure energy detected. Combination of three attributes; metal, fire, and water. Assimilating pure energy into the Space. Growth of crops improved. Host’s physical body improved. Constitution improved from metal and wood to metal, water, fire, wood, and metal. The hosts can now control four elements. Asking host to work hard.”

When Zhao Hai heard this prompt, he was shocked. It was the first time that he had heard of something with three elements in it. In addition to metal, there was also fire and water, he didn’t expect that those two could actually coexist together. This thing was really too strange.

However, this was a good thing for him. In the past, Zhao Hai can only control metal and plants, but now, he can also control fire and water. This development was truly very good.

Although Magic also had fire and water elements, Zhao Hai can now be considered to be someone with a Divergent ability regarding Fire and Water. There was a huge difference between Water and Fire Mages and Water and Fire Divergent ability users.

When a Mage uses Magic, they generally do so through incantations. Additionally, they would also use the magic within their bodies to resonate with the magical elements, then they can cast their spells.

However, when the spell has been cast, there would be no way for a Mage to change its form. If you casted a Fireball spell, then it would be impossible for it to be transformed into a Fire Dragon. The Mage could only cast a Fire Dragon if he wanted one.

But a Fire element Divergent Ability was different, they can manually control fire. Once a Fireball has been released, they can mold it and make it into a Fire Dragon, or even a Fire Whip. If one compares Fire Divergent ability users to Fire Mages, then the Fire Mage would be a man who attacks using a stone while a Fire Divergent Ability user was a mason who can carve a stone into a statue. A Fire Divergent Ability user can be seen as an advanced version of a Fire Mage.

However, even if Zhao Hai acquired another two Divergent Abilities, he still needed to practice them just like what he did with the Metal and Wood element abilities. These abilities needed constant practice in order to be formidable.

Zhao Hai was very happy with this time’s harvest. Even if he didn’t know what the item inside the bottle was, it still gave him two new divergent abilities as well as improving the growth of the crops in the Space. These were very good things.

Upon thinking about this, Zhao Hai couldn’t help but turn his attention towards the crystal bottle and then opened it. When the bottle was opened, Zhao Hai didn’t expect the metal inside to immediately fly out of the bottle and moved up faster and faster. It reached to the point where Zhao Hai can no longer see it, but he could feel that there had been wonderful changes occuring in the Space.

In the past, even if the Space had the right temperature, the warmth that they felt seemed to be without life. Being on the Space’s outdoors felt just like being inside any other room, it felt very strange.

However, it was different this time around. Even if the temperature inside the Space didn’t have major changes, Zhao Hai could feel true warmth in his body, it felt very comfortable.

At the thought of this, Zhao Hai suddenly froze, then he patted his own head. Wasn’t this feeling very much like the sun? Was the thing inside the bottle not a metal, but instead a miniature sun?

At this time, a prompt was heard from the Space, “Unknown material detected. Crystalline properties, bottle-shaped. The origin of the material is unknown. The material’s properties are special, it can store everything without damaging it. Absorbing properties of material. Host’s energy is strengthened. Host may now crystallize his body instantaneously, may defend against any attacks.”

This made Zhao Hai thoroughly shocked, he didn’t think that there would be such a thing. He had unexpectedly acquired another Divergent Ability. He can actually change his body into a crystal? Then wouldn’t he become a crystal person? Will he be alive after then?

Just when he thought about these questions, a prompt was heard, “Host doesn’t need to worry about anything. The body’s crystallization happens in a cellular level. Host can just move normally. After the ability gets to an advanced level, Host can also turn other things into crystal. Host can just choose to withdraw the ability at any time.”

After Zhao Hai heard this sound, he couldn’t help but laugh. This ability was truly powerful. If this ability gets strong in the future, then if he took a piece of grass and turn it into a crystal, it would be able to pass as another weapon.

While storing the bottle carefully, Zhao Hai’s body flashed out of the Space. This bottle was very useful to him since he was not yet capable of turning things into a crystal. If he came upon things that he cannot store, the jar would be able to save him the trouble.

After having everything finished and going out of the Space, Zhao Hai was now back on the Blood Hawk. At this point, the Blood Hawk was already on the skies of the Black Bear tribe’s main camp, Zhao Hai immediately had the Blood Hawk dive down.

The people of the Black Bear tribe had already seen the Blood Hawk. However, when they saw the beast diving down, they couldn’t help but look at it curiously.

Zhao Hai didn’t control the Hawk and just had it go on its way. Before long, he was already in front of the Black Bear tribe’s main camp where the banquet was already underway.

Right now, the Black Bears were extremely polite towards Zhao Hai. Even if these people didn’t know about Zhao Hai, they still gave their greetings to the person who gave them food as well as the person who had their friendship flag.

Zhao Hai also greeted the other Black Bears before he headed towards the golden tent. The banquet there had already begun. The Black Bear Patriarch hosted the event while the elders were interacting with Buffon and Mendez. Laura and the others were also sitting at the side accompanied by other Black Bear women, the group were happily chatting and laughing with each other.

When the Black Bear Patriarch saw that Zhao Hai had already returned, he immediately invited him over to sit by his side. There, Zhao Hai can see a chair that was intentionally left empty, naturally saved for Zhao Hai. This made Zhao Hai surprised, the place at the left side of the Patriarch was a very important and respectable position.

However, he also knew that being polite was useless at this time. Overly polite people were heavily disliked by the Beastmen. Therefore, he immediately gave his greetings before arriving at the empty chair and sat down.

Seeing Zhao Hai sit down, the Black Bear Patriarch then held his wine glass up and said, “Today is a happy day. Our Black Bear Tribe has acquired a trustworthy Human friend, Zhao Hai. He has also received our friendship flag, he will be our Black Bear tribe’s friend from now on. Everyone, join me in cheering for our new friend!” Everyone simultaneously held their glasses up in the air and said, “Cheers!” Then they drank the liquor in the glass.

After refilling his glass, the Black Bear Patriarch once again held it up and said, “Our Black Bear tribe’s brothers, the Mastiff tribe, sent us information about the food shortage. They said that this may been the cause of the Radiant Church. I passed this matter over to the Lion-headed Race and the Tiger-headed Race to have it investigated. If this matter was indeed caused by the Radiant Church, then we must use our spiked maces and head to the Human territories to pillage some food. Everyone, prepare yourselves!”

All the Black Bears held their glass up again and cheered, “Yes! Yes! Yes!” Then they drank their second glass of liquor.

Then the Black Bear Patriarch held his glass for the third time and said, “But all of you should remember, no matter how much we hate Humans, Zhao Hai will always be our friend!” Then the people said in one voice, “Yes!” Before they drank their third glass of liquor. Then everyone was free to do what they want.

After continually drinking three glasses, the Black Bear Patriarch placed his glass down and turned his head to Zhao Hai and said, “Little Hai, what kind of transaction did you do with the Wolf tribe?”

Chapter 520: Arriving at Beast God City

When Zhao Hai heard the Black Bear Patriarch, he couldn’t help but smile faintly and said, “Before, they wanted my food. But when I told them about the war, they decided to not buy the remaining food.”

The Black Bear Patriarch stared for a moment before his complexion changed, he looked at Zhao Hai and said, “What? Did they dare to dishonor an agreement? Alright, tomorrow I’ll go and settle accounts with that Old malnourished Wolf.”

Zhao Hai immediately shook his head and said, “No, no. I already expected this before informing the Old Wolf King. You should know that their situation is much worse than the Black Bear tribe. Therefore, I told them that they might go into war and gain food there. Because of that, they decided to not buy the other food in my hands.”

The Black Bear Patriarch looked at Zhao Hai curiously before saying, “Little Hai, why would you do that? You are a Merchant, wouldn’t it be better if they buy your food?”

Zhao Hai smiled and said, “Not really. To tell you the truth, I really didn’t plan to sell those Bread Fruits to the Prairie. I can sell them elsewhere, and for more profit. Since the Prairie Wolf tribe are your friends, then they are my friends as well. I don’t really need to cheaply profit off of them. What I want is long-term cooperation with the Beastmen. For this goal to be attained, I couldn’t offend the Prairie Wolf tribe.”

The Black Bear Patriarch stared at Zhao Hai for a moment before he laughed and continually patted Zhao Hai’s shoulder. If this was in the past, Zhao Hai might not have been able to bear this beating. However, he was now an 8th rank expert and also had his body repeatedly strengthened by the Space. At this time, he doesn’t feel anything from the pats of the Black Bear Patriarch, instead he even felt that two of them had gotten more intimate.

The banquet went very smoothly, especially for the Black Bear Patriarch. Even if he calls the Old Wolf King bad names, one could see that the relationship between the two was very good.

Zhao Hai’s performance towards the Prairie Wolves also made the Black Bear Patriarch happy. Because of Zhao Hai’s actions this time, the Black Bear Patriarch can see that Zhao Hai was really the Beastmen’s friend. At the very least, he doesn’t look down on them like any other Human.

After the banquet, Zhao Hai and the others were already quite tipsy. Since, they didn’t have anything else left to do, Zhao Hai and the others returned to their tent and immediately drank two cups of Spatial Water. At the same time, Zhao Hai also informed Laura and the others about the changes inside the Space.

Although the Space didn’t level up, the changes inside were very big. Compared to the past where the only thing that they could feel was warmth, the Space was now more comfortable and more alive.

The most important thing was the change towards the farming grounds. Even if the growth of the plants on the farming ground weren’t slow, with the addition of the sun, it became even faster. It also seems like the plants looked much healthier than before.

Zhao Hai and the others were happy with this development. With the changes in the Space, they can also feel that the energy inside became thicker than before. At the same time, the energies were also more active.

Zhao Hai was very satisfied with the Space’s transformation, he slept very well that night. The next morning, Zhao Hai bade farewells towards the Black Bear Patriarch. No matter what, they needed to head towards Beast God City, they had someone waiting for them there.

Mendez and Buffon didn’t follow them and returned to their respective tribes. This time, their plans were very successful. The Herculean Bulls had gained a powerful ally with the Black Bear Tribe. For the Herculean Bulls, this development was great.

Buffon’s main task was just to escort Zhao Hai as well as help Mendez gain a good relationship with the Black Bear Tribe. However, he also gained a lot from this trip. At the very least, he already saw that Zhao Hai had gotten the friendship flag of the Black Bear tribe. The Mastiff tribe can use this information to convince the other Dog-headed Tribe leaders that Zhao Hai was a good friend.

During the trip, Zhao Hai was inside the body of Alien. However, one could see that there were flags erected on top of the undead beast’s body. There was the Herculean Bull’s King’s flag, the Big-bellied Pig Tribe’s friendship flag and the Black Bear tribe’s friendship flag. Even if Zhao Hai had a Dog-headed race’s flag, it was just a common flag, so it was basically useless. He also had the Giant-horned Bull’s friendship flag, however, he was already the Cow-headed Race’s prince, erecting that flag was just redundant.

Even so, the sight was amazing. The Herculean Bull’s King’s flag represented the entirety of the Cow-headed Race. The Beastmen regarded face very heavily. This was because they knew that once their face gets dragged into the mud, their race would get annexed by other races.

If people dared to touch Zhao Hai, this would mean that they were offending the Royal tribe of the Cow-headed race. This would mobilize the entire Cow-headed race, and their strength wasn’t something to be scoffed at.

Additionally, he also had the Black Bear Tribe’s friendship flag. This flag held greater importance. Even if it was only a friendship flag, this flag represented that Zhao Hai was a true friend to the Black Bears. If Zhao Hai were to be bullied and was made known to the Black Bear Tribe, then one could be sure that the Black Bears wouldn’t just sit by and do nothing.

Although the impact of the Big-bellied Pig tribe’s friendship flag wasn’t very great, it also indicated that Zhao Hai had been recognized by the Big-bellied Pig tribe. This was also something noteworthy to other Beastmen.

It can be said that even if the Beastmen and the Humans did go to war, there would be no Beastman who would act against Zhao Hai. It was because they would be offending multiple tribes while doing so, and nobody wanted to do such thing.

Zhao Hai’s target right now was Beast God City. Therefore, he didn’t go and deliberately contact every Beastman camp that he came across. Of course, proper contact was also necessary.

The distance between the Black Bear Tribe’s domain and Beast God City wasn’t very long, one could just travel for ten days before reaching the city. For the Beastmen, Beast God City was a sacred place. The more formidable the tribe, the nearer they were to the city. This also demonstrated their status. Beast God city was also the place where Beastmen can buy things more conveniently.

Because of his flags, Zhao Hai’s journey was very relaxed. All of the tribes that he met were very polite. All of them welcomed Zhao Hai as a friend.

Naturally, Zhao Hai wouldn’t just let them suffer a loss. So he left behind some grain as a gift to those tribes. This act made these Beastmen happy.

Zhao Hai and the others were also listening to rumors along the way. These rumors were about how the Radiant Church cut off all of the food heading towards the Prairie. It was directly passed on that the Radiant Church was behind this time’s food shortage.

This information was something that the Wolf-headed Race, Bear-headed race, and the Dog-headed Race released together. They released this information in order to have the other races prepare, at the same time, this was also used to pressure the other Warring Races.

This information was also like a dropped bomb to the Beastmen. Before long, the Beastmen in the Prairie burst into action, the entire place was boiling with anticipation. Even Zhao Hai can see the changes of the Beastmen just by looking at their eyes.

Zhao Hai knew that if he didn’t have those three flags, then those Beastmen may have already got to him and expelled him from the Prairie.

Although these Beastmen had their own internal thoughts, they still warmly received Zhao Hai’s group. This made Zhao Hai’s heart feel quite strange.

Zhao Hai didn’t dare release a Blood Hawk towards Beast God City at this time. Beast God City always had at least ten 9th rank experts in it all the time. Even if the Blood Hawk has become very strong, it cannot defeat a 9th rank expert. If the 9th rank experts misunderstand, then Zhao Hai’s troubles wouldn’t be very small.

The other races should have already known about his Blood Hawk. Although he was now the Prince of the Herculean Bulls as well as a friend of the Black Bears, the 9th rank experts guarding the City wouldn’t’ let him off if he dared to release a Blood Hawk right now.

After travelling for 10 days, Zhao Hai had finally arrived at Beast God City. What surprised Zhao Hai the most was the fact that the more they got closer to the city, the less they heard rumors about the Radiant Church and the food shortage. When he arrived at Beast God City, nobody was talking about it, this made Zhao Hai confused.

However, Zhao Hai’s thoughts were interrupted when he finally saw the famous Beast God City. The city had both the colors of green and red. With what Zhao Hai saw, the city seemed like a beast that was lying there, prepared to attack anyone who dared offend it.

As he came closer and closer to the city walls, Zhao Hai noticed that the pressure increased. Although Beast God City was just like any other stone city, it’s dark-red hue made people feel immense pressure.

Beast God City’s walls weren’t as tall as Carson City. The walls of the city was only about ten zhang(33m) high. However, since the city was placed on a flat and barren Prairie, it looked relatively tall.

Beast God City looked very lively. While he was yet to arrive at the City, Zhao Hai can already see tents people all around.

Zhao Hai looked at the tents and couldn’t help but feel strange. However, he also knew that building houses in the Prairie was much harder than making houses in Human territory. Tents were much more common here.

Before long, Zhao Hai arrived near a clump of tents. He could see Human merchants entering and leaving the tents here.

Zhao Hai had Alien stop before he walked out of Alien’s body. He wasn’t afraid of causing panic among the Humans, but instead he didn’t want the other Beastmen in the city to have an opportunity to blame him. It wasn’t a wise move to offend the Beastmen at this place.

When Zhao Hai went out of Alien, he immediately received the undead. Then he walked on foot towards the city. At this time, a carriage was fast approaching  Beast God City. This carriage was pulled along by a 4th rank Magic Beast Tiger-tailed Horse. The fighting strength of this Magic Beast was good. Even if it wasn’t the best when it came to speed, its strength was placed on the top among the 4th rank Magic Beasts.

Chapter 521: The Ugly Ah Tai

The horse carriage was something commonly seen in the Prairie. It was full of Beastman craftsmanship techniques, and it was very large as well. It wasn’t much smaller than the carriage that Randolph gave Zhao Hai.

The carriage quickly arrived in front of Zhao Hai’s group. The driver stopped the carriage and jumped down. When the person jumped to the ground, Zhao Hai was taken back. It was because this man was very tall, he was about two and a half meters tall, he also had a muscular body that wasn’t much less than those Beastmen.

This man wore a leather robe that looked very worn and ugly. His skin was also very black, he looked like a black person from Earth. If his body was just covered with hair, then one wouldn’t doubt him if he posed as someone from an Ape tribe.

When the man arrived near Zhao Hai’s group, he bowed to Laura and excitedly said, “Young lady, you finally came. Ah Tai was waiting for you for quite a while.”

It was at this point that Zhao Hai and the others understood that this man was the person that Laura sent to the Prairie, Ah Tai. Seeing this person’s appearance, Zhao Hai and the others couldn’t help but make a strange expression. Did Laura send Ah Tai to the Prairie because of his appearance?

Laura nodded and said, “Ah Tai, I haven’t seen you for a long time. You seem to have darkened some more. Come meet my husband, Zhao Hai.”

Ah Tai turned to Zhao Hai and bowed, “Ah Tai has seen the Uncle.” Zhao Hai wasn’t used to be called by this name, he couldn’t help but smile and said, “Alright, no need to be polite. It’s been hard for you these past few years. Also, you can just call me young master.”

Ah Tai looked up and honestly smiled, “Young Master, I really hadn’t been having it hard. I have something to eat and drink everyday, actually, it’s been very easy.”

Zhao Hai stared at Ah Tai. He never imagined Laura to send such an awkward looking guy to the Prairie. She was actually not afraid that he wouldn’t be able to sell properly.

Then Laura introduced Ah Tai to Megan and the others. While Ah Tai were meeting his wives, Zhao Hai paid attention to the surroundings. Around them were merchants who were somehow acquainted with Ah Tai. Zhao Hai could even see some of them pointing towards their direction.

Zhao Hai focused his ears and listened to the words of those people. He listened to a merchant on their side, “Look, isn’t that silly Ah Tai? Why did he run out of the camp?”

Another person answered, “Who knows? But looking at his respectful appearance, it seems like the person who came has an authority over him. I heard that this person might have been from the Buda Clan. From the undead earlier, it seems like it was Buda Clan’s Patriarch Zhao Hai.”

The person who previously spoke said, “If it is really possible for it to be Zhao Hai, Ah Tai is really unlucky. Now that the food is expensive, he actually dared to sell it at a cheap price. I’m afraid that this fool would suffer this time.”

The other person said, “Tone down your voice. I heard that this Zhao Hai isn’t a simple person. He became famous by being vicious and ruthless on the continent. If he heard our bad words towards Ah Tai, he might not let us off.”

The first person snorted and said, “Why do we need to be afraid? This is Beast God City. Violence wasn’t allowed in a thousand li radius around the city.  If someone dares to neglect this rule, the Beastmen wouldn’t let them off easily.” Although he said that, his voice was evidently much quieter.

The other person replied, “Don’t say that. Even if he cannot find trouble with us inside Beast God City, what would happen when we leave the city? This is Beastman Prairie, if he killed us here, our families would think that it was the Beastmen who did it.” Then the two of them went silent.

Zhao Hai now had a faint understanding of the situation. He turned around to look at the ugly man who was talking with Laura. If Ah Tai chose to sell the goods at the same price as those merchants, then Zhao Hai would truly be disappointed, but now it seems like he didn’t do so.

After Ah Tai greeted Laura and the others, he then invited the group over to the carriage. When Zhao Hai and the others were on board, Ah Tai immediately drove the carriage towards Beast God City.

Inside the carriage, Zhao Hai looked at Laura nd said, “Didn’t they say that the camps outside Beast God City were only temporary and sparse? How come there are a lot of people here?”

Laura smiled and replied, “It used to be like that, but now there were a lot more Humans who were trading with the Beastmen. Because of that, the Beastmen allowed them to set up shop outside the city. Because of that, Ah Tai also had his own place outside the city. However, since we managed to take over the Markey Family, Ah Tai had gotten a place inside.

Zhao Hai nodded, then he asked again, “What’s the difference between inside and outside the city?”

Laura replied, “There aren’t a lot of differences really. The amount of buildings inside the city are too small, tents were much more prevalent there. Also, since the soil inside the city were made from Beast Blood Earth and were heavily controlled by the Beastmen, only great families of the continent were able to have a place there. The weaker merchants can only go outside the city.” Zhao Hai nodded. At this time, the carriage had already entered the city.

Through the carriage’s window, Zhao Hai looked at the city. The insides of Beast God City was indeed very different from the outside. There were structures inside that were built using Beast Blood Earth. In front of those buildings, Beastmen were seen to be guarding the entrance. It seems like those buildings were very important and weren’t used for casual matters. In other places, large tents could be seen. However, these tents were tightly packed. The inside of the tent looked also the same as what would be seen in a normal house.

Words were written on the curtains of those tents. Some of them had names of the stores, at it seems like these shops were all selling assorted merchandise. Zhao Hai cannot see any shops that specialized on a certain product.

Before long, the carriage stopped in front of a tent. This tent was very big, and on its curtains were large letters that read, “Magic Lily Store.”

When Zhao Hai saw those words, he couldn’t help but feel warm. This Magic Lily Shop was a trademark of the Markey Family, but who would’ve thought that this shop was built by Laura herself.

There were two people outside this tent. These two doesn’t seem to be very large, but still looked very strong. Their build and faces was actually quite similar to Ah Tai.

Ah Tai jumped down from the carriage and then said, “Ah Da, go unload the things in the carriage. Ah Er, prepare some food and drinks for the Young Master and the Young Ladies.” The two complied and then turned around to get busy. They unexpectedly didn’t greet Zhao Hai and the others.

Ah Tai became somewhat embarrassed, he scolded the two and said, “Show your manners!” Then he turned to Laura and Zhao Hai before saying, “I’m sorry, Young Master, Young Lady, those two doesn’t have very good manners. I’ve shown you a disgraceful sight.”

Zhao Hai waved his hand and said, “It doesn’t matter, this is but a small thing.” Ah Tai felt relieved, then he led Zhao Hai and the others inside the tent.

Upon entering the tent, Zhao Hai couldn’t help but stare. This was because the furnishings in this tent were just like the furnishings in Laura’s Magic Lily Shop. However, there were only a few things left inside. There were a small amount of fruit oil present, the other places were quite empty.

Ah Tai embarrassingly looked at Laura and said, “Young Lady, forgive me. The grain and the vegetables are all sold out.”

Laura smiled and said, “That’s not a problem. You go take a break. I want to explore this place. I also remember how fragrant Sister-in-law’s barbecue was.”

Ah Tai smiled and said, “Young Lady actually remembers. Since we knew that Young Lady and Young Master were coming, I already had my wife prepare everything. Then, Young Master, Young Lady, please.” Then he led the group to a yard behind the tent.

Once they arrived at the yard, they can see that several smaller tents were also erected there. Ah Tai’s two sons can also be seen unloading the contents of the carriage into the yard.

Ah Tai directly led the group towards the tent in the middle. Just as he was about to open the tent’s curtain, the curtain was suddenly flung open, then a tall woman came out.

The woman seems to be about 40 years old. Although she was already old, and had wrinkles on her face, she was still attractive. Once could see that she was quite beautiful when she was a young woman.

When the woman saw Laura, her face couldn’t hide her excitement. She immediately arrived in front of Laura and sized her up before saying, “The Young Lady has surely grown up, you’re getting more and more attractive. Time really passes by quickly, in a blink of an eye, the Young Lady was already married. It’s a pity that I’ve not been able to participate in the ceremony.”

Laura smiled and said, “Sister-in-law, how have you been good these years? Did Uncle Ah Tai bully you?”

Ah Tai’s wife gave a quick glance to her husband and said, “As if he’d dare. Right, Young Lady, come quickly, I’ve prepared a lot of delicious food.” Then Ah Tai’s wife turned her gaze towards Zhao Hai while Zhao Hai also looked her in the eye.

Zhao Hai saw that Laura’s relationship with Ah Tai’s wife was very unusual. When she spoke to Laura, she wasn’t being polite. On the contrary, it seems like it was Laura who spoke to her with respect.

Then Ah Tai’s wife suddenly gave her greetings to Zhao Hai, “This one has seen Uncle. This one is called Pearl, people generally refer to me as Ah Tai’s wife. Sister-in-law would also do fine.”

Zhao Hai smiled bitterly, it seems like being called ‘Uncle’ was very common here. He immediately replied and said, “Thanks, Sister-in-law. You can just call me Young Master, Zhao Hai is good as well.”

Ah Tai’s wife smiled and said, “I can’t call you by name, so I’ll just call you Young Master.” Then she led Zhao Hai and the others to enter the tent.

The tent was very similar to an ordinary Beastman tent. Only the interior decorations were different, this one had more Human furniture in it.

There was also a furnace inside, of which several good slices of meat were being barbecued. There were also dishes on the sides, taking advantage of the heat to stay warm.

After Ah Tai’s wife got introduced to Megan and the others, she immediately invited the group to sit down on the carpet. She also served the group some tea before she spoke to Laura, “Young Lady, you sit here first. The vegetables are still not finished. When they are done, we can have our meal.” Laura nodded, then Ah Tai’s wife began to get busy, Ah Tai also helped her from the side.

Zhao Hai drank his tea and then turned to Laura, “Laura, are you very close with Sister-in-law?”

Laura smiled and said, “Not just sister-in-law, I’m also quite close with Ah Tai. Ah Tai was my mother’s guard while Sister-in-law was my mother’s maidservant. They were there while I was growing up.”

Chapter 522: Four Tribes

Zhao Hai nodded and said, “So it’s like that. That explains why you trust Ah Tai so much and also why sister-in-law isn’t very polite to you.”

Laura smiled and said, “Actually, Uncle Ah Tai isn’t suitable for business, he’s too honest. But him being in the Prairie is good, the Beastmen like his strength. He’s also a very strict person when it comes to status, he only wanted me to call him Ah Tai, I’m not allowed to call him uncle.”

Zhao Hai smiled, then he looked at Ah Tai with appreciation. Megan looked at Ah Tai and his wife and said to Laura, “Why do I think that Ah Tai is scared of sister-in-law?”

Laura looked at the couple and smiled, “That’s true, Uncle Ah Tai is very honest, and he also liked sister-in-law very much. However, because of his appearance, he chose to not dare confess. Later on, sister-in-law took the initiative and asked uncle to marry her, which made uncle happy. Since then, sister-in-law has always been favored by Uncle Ah Tai, almost to a point where he’ll always be following her.”

Meg sighed and said, “It’s been hard for them being in the Prairie for this long of a time. It seems like their appearances had already adapted to this place.”

Laura nodded and sighed, “I initially wanted someone else to head to the Prairie, but I just cannot find an appropriate person. It was the two of them who requested me to allow them to go, I really don’t want to let them go but I had to agree in the end because of their constant requests.”

At this time, Ah Da and Ah Er came in from outside. When the two entered the tent, Ah Tai immediately scolded them, “You two rascals, you saw the Young Lady and the Young Master earlier but you didn’t greet them. Go quickly give them your greetings now.”

The two nodded and then arrived to Laura and Zhao Hai before giving their greetings. Laura looked at the two and smiled, “Ah Da, Ah Er, you grow up very quick. You two weren’t this tall when I saw you a while ago.”

Ah Da laughed foolishly and said, “Yes, Young Lady, we’ve been having good food recently, so we grew bigger and bigger.” Ah Er nodded in support. When Zhao Hai looked at the two, he couldn’t help but laugh, they were too adorable.

At this time, Sister-in-law came and said, “Young Lady, Young Master, the meal has been prepared.” Laura and Zhao Hai nodded, then they stood up before heading towards the Magic Stove.

This Magic Stove was fabricated according to the customs of the Beastmen. The middle of the furnace was heated up using a magical formation while its rims were made of wide stone that could be made into small tables.

In the middle of the stove, a large flat iron pan was placed. The iron pan seems to be lathered with lard. Around it were plates with meat and vegetables.

Zhao Hai had a feeling of being out of place. He felt like he had returned to Earth and was having barbecue with his friends.

After Ah Tai’s wife asked them to sit down, Ah Da immediately gave them glasses before pouring them some wine. At this time, the lard had already melted, so Ah Tai immediately laid the slices of meat over to the pan.

After Zhao Hai and the others finished drinking, Ah Tai had already flipped the meats over, filling the entire tent with a pleasant smell.

Ah Tai held his wine glass up this time and then looked at Zhao Hai’s group and said, “Young Master, Young Ladies, since I wasn’t able to participate in your wedding ceremony, I can only offer you a toast right now. I wish you all to be happy and to have a completely joyful life.”

Zhao Hai and the others also quickly held their glasses up. Zhao Hai smiled to Ah Tai and his wife and said, “Thank you, thank you. I also wish for your family a happy and joyful life.” Then the group simultaneously drank from their glasses.

At this time, when Ah Da was about to refill their liquor, Zhao Hai quickly stopped him. He took the bottle and then served Ah Tai and his wife as well as Laura and the others with liquor. Then he lifted his own glass and said, “Ah Tai, Sister-in-law, you’ve been working hard for all these years. Let me offer you this glass of wine.” Ah Tai and his wife didn’t dare to dally as they immediately drank their glass of wine.

Then Laura also got up and poured the group another glass of wine before giving her greetings. The group still hadn’t eaten, yet they had already drank three glasses of wine.

Zhao Hai and the others had always greeted other Beastmen this way, so they had already formed a habit. At the same time, Ah Tai’s group had also dealt with Beastmen before, so this custom wasn’t strange for them.

After drinking three glasses of liquor, the group stopped, then Ah Tai quickly said, “Young Lady, Young Master, have a taste of this barbecue. I’ve just chopped this meat this morning, and they had now finished cooking. They are definitely delicious.”

Laura smiled and said, “Alright, I’ve been hungry for sister-in-law’s barbecue. They’re very delicious.” Then she grabbed a two-pronged fork next to the pan and got herself some few slices of meat. Then she sliced it with her knife before placing a morsel into her mouth.

Zhao Hai and the others followed her example, they forked some meat into their own plates then ate it. Not to mention the fragrance of the barbecue, the pieces of meat were also very large and thick. Even if they were cooked, they weren’t fully done. The meat was slightly red but it was very tender and delicious.

When Zhao Hai ate a piece of the meat, he nodded and said, “Delicious, this so delicious. Sister-in-law’s cooking is very good. If you open a shop selling these barbecue, it would certainly do very well.”

As soon as Ah Tai’s wife heard Zhao Hai, a smile blossomed on her mouth as she said, “If Young Master likes it very much, then you should eat more.”

The group continued to eat and chat. Before long, they had unconsciously ate until they are full. The only ones left eating were Ah Da and Ah Er. Zhao Hai and the others were now just drinking and chatting.

Ah Tai turned to Zhao Hai and Laura then said, “Young Lady, Young Master, there has been rumors going around Beast God City saying that the Beastmen may declare war with the Humans. They might expel Human Merchants. What do you think about this matter?”

Zhao Hai smiled faintly and said, “We already know about this, rest assured. Even if they do drive the other Merchants away, that doesn’t apply to us. We have the Herculean Bulls’ King’s Flag as well as the Black Bear Tribe’s friendship flag.”

Ah Tai nodded and said, “Since we have those flags, the Beastmen wouldn’t touch us. But Young Master, I’ve sold the grain that you’ve given me at normal price. Are you angry?”

Zhao Hai laughed and said, “Of course not, why would I be angry? That’s what you decided to do, so it’s no problem. Right, I’ve brought a new type of crop, you’ll be selling these later.” Then he showed Ah Tai a Bread Fruit.

The food that Zhao Hai gave Ah Tai in the past weren’t Bread Fruits, but instead Bamboo Rice. At this time, Zhao Hai took out the Bread Fruits.

When the Bread Fruit was opened and exhibited its pulp, the eyes of Ah Tai and his wife lit up. They dealt with the Beastmen for a long time, so they knew what they needed. This Bread Fruit would definitely be a favorite among the Beastmen.

Zhao Hai gave them the Bread Fruit and then had them taste it, then he said, “Only our Buda Clan has this Bread Fruit. No other people have this in hand. We shall mainly sell these fruits in the future, we have a lot of them. Moreover, we should also sell some daily necessities. The price of the Bread Fruit is half of Bamboo Rice. The price of the necessities shouldn’t be very high, maybe a bit higher than its price back on the Human territories.”

Ah Tai then said, “Young Master, isn’t this too low? This Bread Fruit is much more convenient than Bamboo Rice, it is cost-effective as well. It would still be popular even if we sell it at a high price. Also, those daily necessities, they still needed to be transported to the Prairie, that would cost us. If we do it just like what you said, we would be losing so much money.”

Ah Tai was an honest person, but it didn’t mean that he was stupid. He knew that when one travels to the Prairie, one would need to go through a lot of checkpoints. Delivering things to the Prairie would generally make the price of the items double. If one doesn’t increase the price of the item, they would generally lose out on profits.”

Zhao Hai smiled and said, “That’s not an issue. I’ve already calculated the sums, we won’t be losing money. Also, if we make a name for ourselves this time, when the Beastmen is done waging war with the Humans, we would become the largest merchant in the Prairie.”

When Ah Tai heard Zhao Hai, his eyes couldn’t help but lighten up, then he laughed and said, “Alright. Young Master’s words made me feel relieved. I certainly wouldn’t disappoint the Young Master.”

Zhao Hai smiled faintly and said, “I’ll tell you the truth, since the Buda Clan and the Markey Family have been combined, there aren’t a lot of people who would dare offend us. However, Ah Tai, you shouldn’t presumably think that we can monopolize the business of the Prairie. It’s impossible for that to happen.”

Ah Tai smiled and said, “Young Master can rest assured, I fully understand.”

Zhao Hai nodded and said, “Since the Markey Family has been here for quite some time, we should have some tribes that we directly supply, right? Do we have a deep relationship with them?”

Ah Tai nodded and said, “Before the takeover, the Markey Family supplies four large tribes with food and daily necessities. The four tribes are the Fire Fox tribe, Black Panther tribe, Gibbon tribe, and the Gold-ringed Eagle tribe. These four tribes are all branches of Warring Races. Each year, their food and necessities consumption are quite large. However, the Markey Family’s business only accounts for 20 percent of their food supply and 10% of their daily necessity supply.”

When he heard Ah Tai, Zhao Hai couldn’t help but frown and said, “What’s the problem? Why is it like that?”

Ah Tai sighed and said, “This isn’t really a mystery. Even if the goods of the Markey Family are of high quality, their prices were also significantly higher than the other merchants. If not for the fear of having their supply monopolized, those four tribes wouldn’t be buying from the Markey Family. This year, even if the Prairie was having a food shortage, those four tribes didn’t buy any food from the family. The amount of daily necessities that they bought didn’t increase either.”

Zhao Hai couldn’t help but sigh, he really cannot understand why the Markey Family acted this way. Not only did they offend everyone on the continent, they were also quite overbearing in doing their business. They really think that they were soaring in the heavens and thus became conceited. If Zhao Hai didn’t deal with the family, other people would attack them sooner or later.

Zhao Hai nodded and said, “Alright, I understand. Do you know the addresses of these tribes? I plan on visiting them when I have time.”

Ah Tai nodded and said, “I know, these four tribes are quite famous in the Prairie. It’s very easy to look for them. The Fire Foxes are well-known prophets among the Beastmen. Their abilities are also special. It was said that their spirit technique can summon fire attributed beasts and their attacking abilities are very strong. The Black Panther tribe are one of the very few assassin tribes among the Beastmen. Their stealth techniques are very formidable. The Black Panthers were the people who clashed with Human assassins during wars. The Gibbon Tribe are one of the main forces of the Beastmen. They dual wield scimitars, and their movements are very flexible. They are the ones who generally attack the walls of Human cities. The Gold-ringed Eagle tribe are also one of the main battle force of the Beastman Race. Their bodies aren’t’ very huge, but they are very skilled in archery. And because of their unique mount, they were also one of the most famous aerial scouts in the Prairie.”

Zhao Hai nodded, “That’s good. It seems like now is not the right time to visit them. The war between the Beastmen and Humans are inevitable. It would be impossible to sell food at this time since the Beastmen are going to pillage them from the humans. You don’t need to get busy at this time, just stay here in Beast God City. I don’t think that this war would go on for too long. As soon as the war is over, we should try to be the first to establish new connections to the Beastmen. It’ll be the opportune time to form partnerships with the tribes.”

Ah Tai nodded and said, “Young Master can rest assured, I know what to do. I originally have a cooperation with the Pig-headed Race. But they are just too far and is only a commoner race. Recently, I’ve been planning on getting in touch with the Tiger-headed race. If we can get a partnership with them, we won’t be worrying about where to sell our goods later.”

Zhao Hai nodded, the Tiger-headed Race and the Lion-headed Race are considered to be the Royal Races of the Beastmen. These two races have innumerable amounts of subordinate and slave races under them. Because of how much excess manpower they have, they can fully devote themselves into improving their fighting strength. Because of this, they have become leagues stronger than the other Beastman races. Adding on to the fact that these two races were very rich, Zhao Hai wouldn’t worry about not selling his goods anymore.

Chapter 523: The State of the Human Merchants

Zhao Hai was very satisfied with Ah Tai’s work ethic. This may be because of his personality. It explains why he was able to thrive here in the Prairie. He also heard from Ah Tai that he was able to make many friends among the Beastmen.

But Zhao Hai kept calm, he knew that since the Beastmen were getting ready to fight the Humans, the chances of Ah Tai’s plan with the Tiger Race succeeding wouldn’t be big.

However, Zhao Hai didn’t say anything since he didn’t want to dampen Ah Tai’s enthusiasm. It wouldn’t be good for Ah Tai, if he doesn’t have a spirited attitude, he wouldn’t have a lot of Beastman Friends.

After eating their meal, Zhao Hai and the others didn’t leave. They entered one of the tents that Ah Tai arranged and rested. At the same time, Ah Tai’s wife also offered them some milk tea.

Although ordinary tea was available, milk tea was instead served. This was because since they had eaten meat, milk tea would be better for them. Another reason was because they were in the Prairie, ordinary tea was rare, Beastmen weren’t used to drinking it.

Zhao Hai had interacted with the Beastmen for quite a long time, so they were already used to drinking milk tea. Zhao Hai took a sip and sighed, “I didn’t have the opportunity to get a tea tree all this time. I really want to plant one in the Space.”

Laura smiled and said, “What’s wrong, Brother Hai? Do you really like to drink milk tea?”

Zhao Hai smiled faintly, and didn’t respond. He cannot tell Laura that he didn’t really like drinking milk tea. What he wanted was classic green tea.

Megan didn’t care about any of these, so she turned to Zhao Hai and asked, “Big Brother Hai, what do we do now? Now that Ah Tai told us that the war between the Humans and the Beastmen is about to start, do we stay here or do we return to the continent?”

Zhao Hai smiled and said, “Don’t worry, at this point the continent should be very chaotic. Father-In-law has already arranged to inform all of the people in the continent about the Radiant Church’s hand in the Prairie’s food shortage. And because of their move, the Beastmen are now planning its big attack on the Aksu Empire. All of Aksu Empire’s residents know that if the Beastmen wage war against humans, the Aksu Empire would be the first to suffer. The Radiant Church should have fallen in favor right now, but not to a point where they can’t control it. We can wait for a moment until we confirm that the Beastmen would indeed attack the Humans, then we can return back to the continent.”

Megan became confused, “Why would we return to the continent at that time?”

Zhao Hai smiled and said, “Only when the situation starts would the continent go into turmoil. If we there at that time, there would a possibility for us to get some people. Don’t forget, we are friends with the Purcell Family and the Iksa Family. Their territories are bordering the Beastman Prairie. At that time, we can go to them and recruit some talented people into our territory.”

Laura smiled and said, “I’ve heard that the Purcell Family hasn’t been doing too well these times. When you helped them in the past, the Aksu Empire came to know about your relationship. Because of that, the Empire went and fully suppressed them. At the same time, your relationship with the Iksa Family has been revealed as well, which led to them also being suppressed. The two families have had it hard these past few months.”

Zhao Hai’s expression turned cold, then he snorted and said, “If the Aksu Empire didn’t do this, I might have helped them in this crisis, I might even prevent the Beastmen from attacking. But now, it seems like they needed to be taught a lesson.”

Laura and the others understood what Zhao Hai meant. Since he had a lot of Bread Trees as well as the Farming Ground, Zhao Hai can definitely provide food for the entire Beastman Race. If the Beastmen have food, then they would naturally stop their plan of pillaging the Human territories. Even if the Beastmen are hot blooded, they also know that wars bring death. They know that war wasn’t a good choice.

But Zhao Hai didn’t want to give the Beastmen a lot of food. He wanted this war to happen. Not only would the upcoming conflict deal a heavy blow to the Aksu Empire, it would also bring bigger trouble to the Radiant Church.

In the following days, Zhao Hai and the others stayed inside the store. He brought out some Bamboo Rice as well as some Bread Fruits and daily necessities. He stocked the store full of goods.

But restocking a shop wasn’t generally this fast. Not only the Magic Lily Shop, all other Human shops were also like this. Their shipments this time had gotten quite scarce, this made them very anxious.

When these Human merchants came to the Prairie, they didn’t know about the Beastmen’s food shortage. They also didn’t know that the Beastmen were going to attack the Humans. Because of this, they followed their usual practice and brought the same amount of goods to the Prairie once spring came. This was because they knew that this was the time where business with the Beastmen yielded great profits. It was the time when the Beastmen would crazily purchase goods to stock up because they had eaten their stores during the winter. If one brings some goods to sell at this time, they wouldn’t be worried of not making a profit.

But this year’s situation was different. When the Merchants came, business was doing great as usual. However, when information came that the Radiant Church was behind this time’s food shortage and that the Beastmen were going to send troops towards the Human territory, the sales volume of these Human Merchants dropped in a single day. Right now, they weren’t able to make the same amount of transactions as they did in the past. With how low their profits came, these Human Merchants wished that they could just die.

These merchants knew that if the Beastmen attack Human lands, their goods would be left unsold. This was because as long as Beastmen pillaged the Human territories, they would have enough food in their hands to merit not buying anymore.

And these Human Merchants have brought a lot of things to the Prairie this time. But now, the goods would have to rot here because they knew that they would probably be driven out once the war starts. It would be impossible for them to bring those goods back to the Human lands, they don’t have any choice than to just leave them here.

But even if the Beastmen didn’t touch the things that they left behind because of their principle, once they leave, nobody would take care of their goods. Before long, those things would slowly get damage, this was equal to losing everything.

Zhao Hai had also seen the situation during these past few days. He knew that the merchants had been bleeding money at this time. He was also certain  that these people didn’t have any relationship with the Radiant Church, they might even have an enmity with the organization. Otherwise, the Church should’ve already informed them, making them avoid jumping into this fiery pit.

Upon thinking about it, Zhao Hai understood another aspect of the Radiant Church’s plan. If the Radiant Church succeeds and has all the blame shifted to the Rosen Empire, these merchants would detest the Empire. And when the Church emerged and the Merchants discovered that those affiliated to the organization didn’t suffer any losses, they would be joining the Radiant Church. When that happens, the Church would then control the Merchants in the Prairie. They would then have a bargaining piece against the Beastmen. The Church’s plan was truly brilliant.

If not for Zhao Hai foiling the church’s plan, then both the Rosen Empire and the Beastmen wouldn’t have any good days.

But now that Zhao Hai was aware of the Church’s plan, he naturally wouldn’t let them succeed. Zhao Hai observed these merchants for several days. The Merchants have reached a point where they were just left grasping on straws. They cannot bring their goods back, but they couldn’t sell it as well. The only reason why they haven’t left Beast God City yet was because they can still make one or two transactions each day. They hoped to sell as much as possible to minimize their losses. They only planned to leave once the Beastmen started to drive them out.

This gave Zhao Hai see an opportunity. He can buy the goods of these Merchants since they’re going to be abandoned anyway. If he buy these things, he would be solving the Merchants’ greatest problem. He can also form a good relationship with these Merchants. They would then be grateful to him and they might even affect the Radiant Church’s relationships with other merchants, preventing the food shortage from happening again.

After thinking of this, Zhao Hai immediately told his plan to Laura. Regarding business matters, Zhao Hai always wanted to hear Laura’s opinion. Laura’s gift of commerce was something that no normal person had.

After Laura heard Zhao Hai’s idea, she immediately gave her approval, she also thought that this was a good plan. Upon arriving at their decision, they quickly had Ah Tai go out and see those Merchants as well as see their bottom line.

Ah Tai’s nickname was Silly Ah Tai. Because of this, the other merchants’ vigilance towards him was very low. Adding Ah Tai’s careless appearance to the formula made the merchants even less on guard. It didn’t take a long time before Ah Tai managed to get their bottom line.

The requests of the Merchants weren’t high. In their opinion, they already lost out. If they can just recover a little bit of their capital, then they would be happy.

Chapter 524: Alliance

After knowing the bottom line of the merchants, Zhao Hai decided that he would buy all of their goods. Of course, he wouldn’t buy them at a high price. He would make the merchants lose a little. However, even with this, he expects that the merchants would still feel grateful to him.

This even also gave Zhao Hai more understanding regarding the Beastmen. When the Beastmen declares war with the Humans, they would drive all of these merchants away. In this case, the Humans would generally leave their goods behind. Then the beastman can then choose whether to take those or not.

But according to the past convention, the Beastmen wouldn’t touch these commodities, they will just leave those to rot. In order to survive, Beastmen would take their weapons and attack the Human lands, however, they wouldn’t touch these left over merchandise in Beast God City. This was one of the strange and respectable aspect of the Beastman Race.

Zhao Hai also knew that if the Beastmen does expel the Human merchants, then the merchants would surely suffer big.

The majority of Beastmen tribes do their trades with Magic Beasts. The Humans would bring their goods to the Prairie to have it traded with some Magic Beasts of which were then taken back to human lands to be processed. The markup from this process would be the merchant’s main source of profit.

If the Beastmen drives them away, then that would mean that the war is already near. If they bring the Magic Beasts, then they would find it difficult to cross the Human border. Even if they did pass through, the money that they would shell out will be very big, it can even be several times more than normal. As the matter stands, it would be very disadvantageous for them. One could even say that during this war between the Beastmen and the Humans, it would be the Merchants who didn’t know of the matter that would be losing a lot of money.

Because of this, Zhao Hai planned to trade with these humans using money. Presently, he has a lot of money in his hands. He even had some unnamed crystal cards, these cards have not been used so far. There really aren’t a lot of places where Zhao Hai can spend money, so he decided to spend them here with the Human Merchants. After all, it was the Human Merchants that use crystal cards the most.

Zhao Hai had been in Beast God City for nearly ten days now. And during these ten days, rumors about the Radiant Church and the food shortage have finally started to spread throughout the city. Moreover, it was known that the Lion and Tiger Races had already confirmed the authenticity of this news. The Beastmen were now officially starting to prepare for their attack towards the Human territories.

But even if the information had already been passed on, the Beastmen from Beast God City still didn’t drive the Human Merchants away. This basically means that the Beastmen still hasn’t decided when their attack would begin. However, everybody knew that it would be happening sooner rather than later.

Right now, the Human Merchants in Beast God City were feeling like they were ants inside a hot pot. They knew that the time the Beastmen left for them was running out.

At this time, Zhao Hai made his move. He made Ah Tai invite the Human Merchants to Magic Lily Store. Then he made Laura and the others prepare some food while Zhao Hai discussed transaction to the Humans present.

Before long, the Merchants had followed Ah Tai to Magic Lily Shop. They actually didn’t care about Ah Tai, but they didn’t dare to not give Zhao Hai face.

Zhao Hai was the Buda Clan’s Patriarch, he was already very famous among Humans. Naturally, this fame was due to his mercilessness and ruthlessness.

These merchants knew that the people that died on Zhao Hai’s hands had already reached several hundred thousand. Just thinking about the numbers made their scalp numb. Since Zhao Hai invited them, they didn’t dare to not go. However, everyone was frightened. They didn’t know why Zhao Hai was looking for them.

These merchants followed Ah Tai towards the shop’s courtyard. Meanwhile, Zhao Hai was standing there while waiting for them to arrive. When he saw the merchants, Zhao Hai immediately stepped forwards to meet everybody. He gave a bow to the Merchants and said, “Zhao Hai Buda welcomes you.”

ZHao Hai checked, these merchants were medium level nobles of the continent. They couldn’t rely on Great nobles and were naturally unaffiliated with the Radiant Church. Zhao Hai invited them in to propose an alliance.

The statuses of these merchants were very different from Zhao Hai’s. They didn’t dare accept Zhao Hai’s bow, so everyone almost simultaneously gave a bow back.

Zhao Hai looked at their faces and faintly smiled, “I’ve been in Beast God City for ten days already. However, because of the matters that I needed to handle, I only had the time to invite all of you today. I’ve been very disrespectful. I’ve invited everyone today to gain better understanding of each other. After all, everyone of us are merchants of this city.”

Although these merchants had heard of Zhao Hai’s name and actions before, they didn’t have a chance to meet him in person. In all honesty, with their status in the continent, they don’t have the qualifications to meet Zhao Hai.

Because of this, they didn’t understand Zhao Hai and what kind of person he was. To the people present, Zhao Hai was a Dark Mage that killed several hundred thousand people. In their minds, Zhao Hai’s image was that of a gloomy and murderous man.

However, the Zhao Hai that they saw this time was completely opposite of their expectations. Although Zhao Hai looked very ordinary, he had a warm smile plastered on his face. At the same time, his body’s aura dispersed an amiable aura, making people unconsciously feel intimate towards him.

These Merchants were now thinking that this Zhao Hai must be an impostor. How could a God of Death, capable of killing countless people, have this kind of warm smile? This was a huge contrast to what these merchants expected, making them dumbfounded.

Zhao Hai didn’t care about their reactions, he just smiled faintly and said, “Everyone, please come in. I’ve prepared some liquor for you all. I invite all of you to have a few cups with me.”

The merchants recovered, then after quickly expressing their gratitude they entered the tent with Zhao Hai .There were also some food present inside. Naturally, the most important course was Sister-in-law’s barbecue.

Now that everything was prepared, Zhao Hai invited the merchants to sit down. Ah Tai sat down as well. Naturally, Laura and the others weren’t present. Humans and Beastmen were different, after all. If Laura and the others were present, these merchants would probably feel uncomfortable. Not only them, the women might also feel some discomfort.

After having everybody settled down, Ah Tai went on and personally poured them a glass of liquor. This liquor was naturally red wine and not the milk wine that the Beastmen generally serve.

After having the wine, Zhao Hao held his glass up and said, “Meeting everyone here in the Beastman Prairie is a happy matter. We’re all fellow humans, we should help each other in the future. Everyone, share this cup with me.”

The statuses of these Merchants weren’t very high. Therefore, they hadn’t been able to have any contacts with people of Zhao Hai’s status. In their opinion, Zhao Hai was someone that they weren’t able to meet casually.

Therefore, when these merchants saw that Zhao Hai was speaking with them in a friendly manner as well as eating a meal together with them and even proposing a toast. Every one of them felt very excited, so they immediately held their glasses up.

Then they simultaneously drank the wine. Then Zhao Hai didn’t urge them to drink anymore, he then got them to eat the dishes. He invited them to eat the barbecue as well as the vegetables that were prepared. Zhao Hai was now in the company of Humans, not Beastmen. If he urged them to drink three glasses, they might get angry.

Although Zhao Hai’s status was higher than these people, he didn’t have any enmity with them so he didn’t want to create it unnecessary. At the same time, it wouldn’t be good to his plan of alliance if they felt any dislike towards him..

After some time eating and feeling somewhat full, Zhao Hai said, “Today, I’ve invited all of you because I have a matter to discuss.”

These Merchants knew that Zhao Hai wouldn’t ask them to eat a meal for no reason. Sure enough, it came. They had waited for this moment to arrive, therefore, they weren’t surprised when Zhao Hai brought it up. They just gave Zhao Hai a curious expression.

Zhao Hai looked at them and said, “Are you having a bad time right now? The Beastmen and the Humans are going to have a war soon. I’m afraid it wouldn’t take a long time before the Beastmen drives everybody back to Human lands. When that time comes, everybody would probably suffer a loss.”

When these Merchants heard Zhao Hai, they faces immediately turned gloomy. They knew that what Zhao Hai said was correct. But they also knew that they cannot do anything about it.

Zhao Hai continued, “I think that everybody already knew why they fell into such a situation. I can tell everyone here that the rumors that you’ve been hearing are all real. This matter was caused by the Radiant Church. They wanted to deal with the Rosen Empire using this method while at the same time dealing the the Beastmen as well. In the end, all of you have become sacrificial victims. In the eyes of the Church, all of you are unimportant people, not worth reminding. Moreover, they also used you to hinder the Beastmen.”

The Merchants might appear calm while listening, but one could see deep anger in their eyes. Looking at their expressions, Zhao Hai knew that this was the time to express his intent, so he continued, “Everybody knows my identity. You also know about my enmity with the Radiant Church. But me telling you this information wasn’t to defile the church. This matter would be confirmed by the Beastmen sooner. I had everybody come today in order to present a proposal. I want everyone here to join me in an alliance.”

When the Merchants heard Zhao Hai, they couldn’t help but stare blankly. Everyone of them were puzzled at Zhao Hai. They seem to not understand what Zhao Hai just said. Alliance? With Zhao Hai’s strength, does he really need an alliance with them?

Zhao Hai looked at them and said, “You’ve seen the strength of the Radiant Church. They gave an order and then so many merchants suddenly stopped their trade with the Beastmen. It is obvious that their influence is very huge. After the war, the Radiant Church may use those merchants to rule the commerce of the Prairie. If we don’t make an alliance, how can we possibly resist them? They won’t sell food to the Prairie today, but what would happen if they suddenly drop the prices one day? What can we do? Because of this, I wanted to set up an alliance!”

Chapter 525: Vassal

The merchants present knew what Zhao Hai meant. They knew that what he said was true. After the war between the Beastmen and the Radiant Church, those merchants controlled by the Radiant Church would definitely return to do business in the Prairie. The merchants present also knew that the commercial might of those people would be very strong, this was because they have the Radiant Church’s support.

As Zhao Hai said, these Radiant Church people cannot be allowed to sell their food in the Prairie. If they decide to cut their prices, everyone not on their group would certainly suffer some losses.

But if their alliance get set up, they would become a power that couldn’t be underestimated. Most importantly, these merchants can use this alliance as a way to have a connection with the Buda Clan. Even if they cannot do business in the Prairie anymore, they can just shift their operations on the Buda Clan’s Golden Island. The island now embodied its name, as long as merchants do business there, they would certainly gain massive wealth. Moreover, that place was much safer than the Beastman Prairie.

Zhao Hai looked at their expressions and didn’t say anything. He wanted to give these merchants a choice. He believes that since these people were able to to do business with the Beastmen, especially in Beast God City, these people certainly understood the situation.

Sure enough, the merchants looked at each other for a moment and then nodded. Then one of them turned to Zhao Hai and said, “Mister Zhao Hai, we agree to the alliance. Sir shall be the leader of our group. What rules does sir have?”

Zhao Hai faintly smiled, he didn’t think that these people would be this surprisingly calm. He quickly answered them and said, “Actually, our corporation is completely a business alliance. I only hope that everyone would share information with one another. Also if one has goods with no buyer while someone has a buyer but with no goods, I hope that you would cooperate with each other. This way, the two parties would benefits from the profits. Naturally, the split of the money would depend on your prior agreements. Also, if someone wanted to deal with one of us, I hope that everyone would help in resisting. This way, we can become stronger and stronger. Does everyone agree?”

When the Merchants heard what Zhao Hai said, they all bowed. They now believed that Zhao Hai really did want to form an alliance with them. The question of the man earlier was just in fact, a test. They wanted to see whether Zhao Hai just wanted to have benefits in the alliance. Now it seems like Zhao Hai was not just trying to gain benefits, he really did want everyone to help one another.

The merchant earlier held his wine glass up and said, “Alright, we’ll do what mister asks. Mister, my name is Milton Curry, from the Curry Family. What name would our alliance have?”

Zhao Hai smiled and said, “A name isn’t important, let’s just call it Merchant Alliance. Everyone shall introduce each other later. I also hope that our alliance won’t just be here in the Prairie. When we return to the Human Lands, let’s still be allies. If one has difficulties, everyone should do everything in their abilities to help. Can everyone accept this?:”

The merchants looked each other and then nodded. Milton then turned to Zhao Hai and said, “We accept. The establishment of this alliance only gives us benefits with no harm. But we’re afraid that mister would have to suffer some losses. After all, our families aren’t very great.”

Zhao Hai laughed and said, “That doesn’t matter. The alliance’s benefits to my Buda Clan aren’t small either. Everybody should know that our Buda Clan is still an emerging family. Our connections simply cannot compare to the other Great Clans. Forming an alliance with you is also a form of having new connections. For our Buda Clan, this benefit is very big.”

When Milton heard Zhao Hai, his beating hard finally relaxed. In the end, Milton lifted his glass and said, “Sir can rest assured. Later on, our Curry Family will be considered to be a vassal family of the Buda Clan. If mister wants something done, you can just approach us.”

Zhao Hai stared blankly, he didn’t think that Million would actually declare this. While Zhao Hai was still dumbfounded, the other people also raised their glasses and one by one said the same thing as Milton. These people are all Patriarchs of medium-ranked Families, so they also had the authority to declare so.

Zhao Hai didn’t quite understand why they did this. If one becomes a vassal, a lot of control would be lost. At the very least, they wouldn’t be making decisions just like this one anymore.

Actually, this shows how Zhao Hai still didn’t understand the circumstances in the continent. On the continent, all Great Nobles have their own vassal families. Although those vassal families needed to listen to the Great Nobles, they would also benefit a lot from being a vassal. They can have the Great Noble take care of problems that they weren’t able to take care of. For medium-rank families, this was a huge thing.

Although the Buda Clan was still an emerging family, the strength that they have was tyrannical. Additionally, Zhao Hai was the son-in-law of the Calci Family as well as the Rosen Emperor, also the Buda Clan is in an Eternal Alliance with the Crook Family, while also being normal allies with the Shelley Family. These connections were something that middle-ranked Noble clans like Milton’s didn’t have. Now that they have the opportunity, they naturally wouldn’t let it go.

Zhao Hai looked at Milton and the others and said, “Alright, I’ll take all of you in. From now on, all of you are vassals of my Buda Clan.”

Milton and the others showed happiness in their face. The benefits that they just received were too great. The merchants immediately put down their glasses as they stood up and gave Zhao Hai a salute. From this point on, they were now Zhao Hai’s men.

Zhao Hai also received their salute. He was now a half-lord for Milton and the others, so he naturally would receive their ceremonies. After this ceremony, Milton and the others were officially his subordinates.

After Milton and the others gave their salute, Zhao Hai had them sit down, then after this he said, “I won’t always be in the Prairie. If you have anything to inquire, you can just find Ah Tai. Then he shall relay your words to me. Right, I have another matter to discuss with all of you.”

Milton immediately said, “Mister, please tell us.”

Zhao Hai waved his hand and said, “I don’t need anything from you, I want to help you instead. All of you brought a lot of goods this time since you didn’t know about what would happen. When the Beastmen drives all of you away, those goods would all go to waste. I want to buy all of your goods. Of course, I won’t buy them at a high price. You may take a few losses, but it wouldn’t be a lot. Also, I will use crystal cards in the transaction, not Magic Beasts. What do all of you think?”

Milton stared, then with evident happiness, he replied, “Sir, that’s fantastic. We absolutely agree. However, wouldn’t mister lose too much?”

Zhao Hai smiled and said, “Didn’t you see the three flags outside the tent? With those flags, the Beastmen wouldn’t be driving me away.”

Milton and the others stared, they didn’t know the significance of those three flags. The only thing they knew was that they were Beastman flags. They also have Beastman flags, but they would still be driven away.

Zhao Hai looked at their confused expressions and couldn’t help but gawk. Then he suddenly remembered that there weren’t a lot of people who knew about the different Beastman flags. Thus, it was also possible that Milton and the others had no idea about them.

Zhao Hai then looked at Milton and the others and said, “Those flags aren’t the same as your flags. I’m very sure that the Beastmen wouldn’t drive me away, so you can all just sell those goods to me. Rest assured, I won’t let you suffer too much loss.”

Milton and the others nodded, they felt that a huge stone in their hearts has finally dropped. They were now very grateful to Zhao Hai. It was because if Zhao Hai didn’t do this, then their losses would definitely be huge.

When he saw that Milton and the others nodded, Zhao Hai smiled and invited them to sit down again. Then he took out some milk wine that he made and placed it on the table.

This was the first time that these people had tasted this kind of liquor. Their status was insufficient, and adding on to the fact that this liquor was quite rare, they simply didn’t have the chance to taste it.

The meal lasted for a couple of hours before the group dispersed. After the meal, Zhao Hai instructed Ah Tai to go to those merchants and check the purchase before giving them the money. This would allow the merchants to leave Beast God City as soon as possible.

The merchants already knew about this matter, so they didn’t oppose to it. In all honesty, if it weren’t for them wanting to sell as much as possible to recoup their losses, they would have already left the Prairie. The war between the Beastmen and the Humans was inevitable. They would only get in danger if they stay here for too long.

They had no choice but to stay, the majority of them rely on the profits of these goods to run their families. If they couldn’t at least recover their capital, then they would have a bad time in the future.

Zhao Hai and the others had already decided on the price beforehand. Although the price was much cheaper than selling to the Beastmen, it wasn’t pitifully low. Even if they suffer some losses, the merchants were still satisfied. Amidst the situation between the Beastmen and Humans, this result was already fortunate for them.

Zhao Hai returned to his own tent and then drank several cups of Spatial water. Then he told the matter of vassalage to Laura and the others.

After the group listened, Laura smiled and told Zhao Hai, “Although we’ll suffer a few losses after having them as our vassals, this development is good for the overall situation of the Buda Clan. Having vassal families is good.”

Megan nodded and said, “Those guys had it cheap. Raising this matter at that moment made it impossible for Brother Hai to decline. Those guys are surely some sly fellows.”

Lizzy smiled and said, “I think they also saw that Elder Brother Hai was acting too well, so they wanted to ask that question to test him. They actually didn’t expect Brother Hai to agree immediately, those guys are really lucky.”

Zhao Hai looked at the three awkwardly, he really couldn’t understand. It was clear that it was the Buda Clan who got vassals. But from Laura and the others’ mouths, it seems like the merchants had gotten something good.

Laura knew that Zhao Hai didn’t know much about Noble matters, so she took the liberty to explain it to him. A medium-ranked noble being a vassal to a Great Noble wasn’t a shameful thing. On the contrary, it was a good thing. After becoming a vassal, these clans would be able to do some things easier than when they were still independent.

Moreover, if someone offends them later, they can also ask the Great Clan to act on their behalf. Being a vassal was like being under a Great Noble’s umbrella of protection. Benefits such as these are very hard to find.

Don’t think that these medium-ranked nobles had such beautiful lives. In reality, they always find themselves stepping on the tip of their toes, especially those who weren’t vassals of Great Noble Clans. These medium-ranked nobles always move carefully because they fear offending the Great Nobles. If they ever offend one, then they might face the fate of being extinguished. Because of those reasons, these medium-ranked nobles were always careful and cautious in everything they do.

But most of them didn’t have any good qualities that would attract Great Nobles. Even if they voluntarily side themselves to a Great Noble Clan, it wasn’t always certain that they would be accepted. Now that Zhao Hai had them in his fold, this was equal to having a strong power at their back. Although they will now need to offer yearly tributes to the Buda Clan to appease Zhao Hai, the benefits that they will get completely overshadowed it.

After listening to Laura’s explanation, Zhao Hai finally understood the matter. However, he didn’t regret his decision of accepting Milton and the others. He knew that the present connections of the Buda Clan were pitifully low. All of their information came from the Calci Family, which made Zhao Hai very passive. Now that he had Milton and the others, the Buda Clan can now have its own intelligence network. Handling matters in the future would be much more convenient.

Zhao Hai wasn’t a person who wants to be under the control of others. Therefore, he doesn’t want to always depend on the Calci Family for information. This would make the Buda Clan always bow their heads down to the Calci Family and Zhao Hai doesn’t want that. So Zhao Hai planned to establish his own influence.

And Milton and the others were going to help him achieve his goals. Although Milton and the others weren’t strong families, these people came from different parts of the Continent. As long as they have the support of the Buda Clan, they can only get stronger and stronger. Then, they can slowly form their own net of influence of which the Buda Clan was in the very center. With this, the Buda Clan would also start to get bigger and bigger, and will slowly get stronger and stronger.

Chapter 526: Eviction

The Buda Clan has already established its might in the continent because of Zhao Hai’s effort as well as the Space. However, when it came to personal connections, they couldn’t even compare to low-ranked nobles families. The Buda Clan’s background was just too thin.

Currently, the connections that the Buda Clan had include: the Calci Family, Crook Family, Rosen Imperial Clan, Shelley Family, Purcell Family, and the Iksa Family.

But one has to know that these families were already very powerful. Even the Iksa Family, they have the title of a Duke. Although they aren’t a Grand Duke’s family and had their own principality, they were still Old Nobles of the Aksu Empire. The help that Zhao Hai can get from them was not very much.

Because of this, Zhao Hai wanted to establish his own circle of influence. And Milton and the others gave him this opportunity.

All of the Great Clans in the continent had their own personal web of influence. This web was something that their clans have woven for many years. Since the Buda Clan didn’t have such a web, Zhao Hai had began to weave it right now.

Therefore, Zhao Hai placed great importance towards Milton and the others. No matter what, it was these people who voluntarily sided themselves to the Buda Clan. So Zhao Hai decided to help them out as much as possible.

In the following days, all of the Human merchants who participated in Zhao Hai’s banquet had shipped their goods to Magic Lily Shop. At the same time, Zhao Hai also took out those unmarked crystal cards and handed them over to the merchants.

These merchants understood that if they return to the human lands while carrying either Magic beasts or coins, they would surely fork some of them out on the road. But if they have these crystal cards, they can just place them on their pockets. And when they come across a checkpoint, they can just choose to not declare its existence.

Because of this, the merchants were very grateful to Zhao Hai. If it wasn’t for Zhao Hai, they would suffer huge losses. At this point, the situation in Beast God City was not getting intense, it was time for them to leave. After handing their good over to Zhao Hai, they immediately left Beast God City.

When these merchants left, Beast God City became somewhat desolate. This made the other merchants who were still there scared. Therefore, they also decided to leave.

The merchants that Zhao Hai invited to his banquet were thoroughly investigated by him. These merchants were from medium-ranked families that didn’t have a lot of background. They didn’t have any connections to a Great Clan, nor did they have a relationship with a Noble affiliated with the Radiant Church. Those who didn’t fit into this criteria weren’t invited by Zhao Hai.

When the Radiant Church implemented their plan, they didn’t inform the Great Clans beforehand. Therefore, since these Great Nobles had no idea, they also sent their merchants over to the Prairie.

At the same time, there were also merchants affiliated with the Radiant Church present. But they were in the minority. They only came because they were sent by the Radiant Church to monitor the situation with the Beastmen.

When Zhao Hai went to investigate the prospective nobles that he wanted to invite, he checked them very carefully. He asked Cai’er to carefully look into their backgrounds as well as the situation of their families. He wanted to make sure that they wouldn’t have any connections to either Great Nobles or the Radiant Church. If there’s a hint of the two criteria on them, then Zhao Hai didn’t go and send an invitation.

But even so, the group that allied with Zhao Hai weren’t the minority. At the same time, these merchants also have a lot of shops outside the city. So when they left, they caused unrest towards the other merchants who were left behind. Moreover, as days passed, more and more Beastmen came to Beast God City, and their gazes were going less and less friendly. A lot of merchants have already retreated, especially those with Great Noble backing, they can still afford the loss. Those who still stayed were also preparing their things to leave.

Naturally, Zhao Hai wouldn’t let this opportunity go. He immediately had Ah Tai go and contact these people and made them sell their goods over to him. And of course, the price that he bought wasn’t as good as what he gave Milton’s group.

These merchants knew that Zhao Hai was using the fire in order to get their goods. However, they had no choice but to agree. At the very least, they can still recover some of their losses. If they don’t agree with Zhao Hai, then they’d be left with no money.

And Zhao Hai would pay them using crystal cards. These cards aren’t very rare in human lands, but in the Prairie, they were uncommon. For those merchants, these crystal cards were very attractive.

Every merchant who came to the Prairie to do business wasn’t a fool. They knew very well how cost-effective crystal cards were compared to bringing along large amounts of Argali. After Milton and the others left, Zhao Hai’s business became better. Everyday, more and more merchants came to Zhao Hai to sell their goods.

The prices that these goods were sold at were much lower than their selling price in the Human lands. Since Zhao Hai had a lot of spare cash in hand, then he would naturally jump on this opportunity to get cheap goods.

A month after Zhao Hai arrived in Beast God City, the Beastmen finally issued their expulsion order. Ordering all Human merchants to leave Beast God City within three days, otherwise, the Beastmen would become impolite.

With the issuance of this order, the Human Merchants knew that it was the end. In the past, they chose to not sell their goods over to Zhao Hai, but now they were very anxious. All of them immediately sold every goods they have over to Zhao Hai at a very low price. Then after receiving the money, they immediately left.

The Beastmen in Beast God City had seen Zhao Hai’s conduct, but they didn’t say anything. In all honesty, the Beastmen didn’t hate these merchants who bring their goods over to the Prairie. Because of this, they chose to not attack them, and instead just drove them away.

On the other hand, Zhao Hai’s three flags made the Beastmen very shocked. This was the first time that they have seen a Human bearing a Beastman tribe’s King’s Flag as well as a Friendship Flag.

Three days later, no other Human was present in Beast God City aside from Zhao Hai’s group. This made the Beastmen look at Zhao Hai and the others strangely. It was very much like when Humans notice a very strange creature among them.

Zhao Hai didn’t care about any of these. The reason why he stayed this time was to wait for Wales and the Black Bear Tribe to arrive in Beast God City.

Wales and the others didn’t let Zhao Hai wait for too long. Ten days after all of the Humans left Beast God city, the Black Bear Tribe arrived.

When Zhao Hai heard that the Black Bear tribe had come, he immediately went to greet them at the gate of Beast God City. While waiting on the gate, Zhao Hai saw a cavalry unit in the distance. When Zhao Hai focused his eyes, he could see that all of the cavalry were mounted Black Bear Beastmen. Their numbers reached 30 thousand, and their movements were filled with great cadence. This cavalry unit completely blotted out the ground, making it black. This scene could make one feel overwhelmed.

However, this cavalry unit didn’t enter Beast God City but stopped just around five li away. Only a few hundred Beastmen separated and continued on to the city. Before long, the group arrived in front of the city gates.

From this group, Zhao Hai can recognize the Black Bear Patriarch as well as Lieben. At this time Lieben was holding a flag in one hand, this was the war flag of the Black Bear Tribe.

Zhao Hai quietly stood on his place as he observed the group gradually slowing down. As soon as the Black Bear Patriarch arrived at the city’s gates, Zhao Hai immediately stepped forward and offered his greetings, “Zhao Hai has met the Black Bear Patriarch.”

The Black Bear Patriarch went down from his mount and stretched out his arms before grasping Zhao Hai’s shoulders and saying, “I knew you wouldn’t leave. Hahaha. When I go finish what I need to do, I’ll go find you, let’s go have a drink.” Then he gently shook Zhao Hai before letting go.

Zhao Hai smiled and said, “Alright, then I’ll go prepare the food and drinks to welcome the arrival of the Patriarch.”

The Black Bear Patriarch nodded and said, “Alright. Little Hai, I still have matters to attend to. I’ll be leaving first, I’ll find you at your place later.” Then he turned around and rode his mount before heading towards the city. Zhao Hai also led Ah Tai to walk back to Magic Lily Shop.

At this time, Ah Tai was looking utterly shocked at Zhao Hai. His contact with the Beastmen wasn’t short, but he haven’t seen a Beastman being so warm towards a Human before. The Beastmen being good guests wasn’t false, but there were Beastmen who had been able to learn how to deal with Humans from a long period of being in contact with them. For example, if you want to do business with the Beastmen, you need to go visit them in their tribes and sell them the product there. You shouldn’t expect the Beastmen to take the initiative and come to you.

The Black Bear tribe was a big warring tribe. And they had been in contact with Humans for a long time. However, with how they were deceived by a human in the past, they were one of the more hostile Beastmen when interacting with Humans. It was virtually impossible for these Black Bears to be able to warm up to a Human.

Ah Tai can also be considered to be one of those humans who had been able to make transactions with the Black Bears. When the Black Bear Beastmen make transactions, they would always be on guard, as though they were talking to a thief. Very much unlike today, where the Black Bear Patriarch hugged Zhao Hai while at the same time taking the initiative to invite him for a drink.

It was at this point that Ah Tai understood that Zhao Hai’s flags should be special. No wonder the Beastmen didn’t expel them while all of the other Humans were driven out. None of them even went close to Magic Lily Store during the expulsion. At the same time, many Beastmen also came to greet him, and their attitudes were very enthusiastic.

When Zhao Hai and Ah Tai returned to the store, Zhao Hai immediately instructed Laura and the others to prepare something to eat. At the same time, Zhao Hai had also put out some seafood for them to prepare. He wanted the Black Bear Patriarch to be surprised by his display so that he could get entertained.

Ah Tai’s family were not very used to Zhao Hai’s mystical methods. They also helped Zhao Hai prepare everything while they waited for the Black Bear Patriarch’s arrival.

While they were preparing, a clamour was heard outside. Zhao Hai went out to take a look only to see the Black Bear Beastmen. The Black Bear Patriarch led ten other Black Bears as well as Lieben to Zhao Hai’s Magic Lily Shop.

Zhao Hai immediately invited the Black bear Patriarch and Lieben’s group to the store’s back courtyard. After they entered the tent, Ah Tai immediately served each of them some milk tea.

After the Black Bear patriarch took a sip of the tea, he smiled to Zhao Hai and said, “Little Hai, you’ve been having a great time recently. I’ve heard about how you bought all of the goods from the other Merchants. What are you planning to do? Sell them at a high price for profit?”

Chapter 527: Crazy Aksu Empire

Zhao Hai smiled and said, “Not really, I just think that those goods would be wasted when the Merchants leave. You Beastmen won’t touch those things, so they can only rot here over time. Since it’s a pity, I bought them. Then when the war ends, then wouldn’t it be good if I’ll sell them to the tribes for a low price? Those things wouldn’t be wasted, I would get some profits, and the Beastmen benefit.”

The Black Bear Patriarch nodded and said, “That’s good, Hahaha. Kid, the things you do really makes me smile. We Beastmen benefit a lot from it.”

Zhao Hai smiled and said, “That’s natural. I’m considered to be Half-Beastman right now. So of course I wouldn’t cheat you. Patriarch, please come in, I’ve prepared some food and drinks inside.”

The Black Bear Patriarch nodded, then followed Zhao Hai inside. In addition to the seafood, Zhao Hai also had sister-in-law’s barbecue prepared.

There were no words to be said regarding Sister-in-law’s barbecue because it was simply too good. But the seafood was something else. Even if the Black Bear Patriarch has been the leader of the Black Bear Tribe for a long time, he hasn’t been able to eat seafood before, so he was happy to eat this meal.

Zhao Hai didn’t ask about what the Black Bear tribe were planning to do since these were possibly the Beastmen’s military secret. If he asks these types of questions, the Black Bear Patriarch might get suspicious of him.

Zhao Hai heard that the Black Bear patriarch has been fooled by a Human before. Because of this, he became even more distrustful of the Humans. Even to Zhao Hai, there were some times where he didn’t trust him.

When the Black Bear Patriarch took his leave, Zhao Hai prepared to receive Wales and the others. When he meets Wales, then he would return to the Human territories.

The second day after the Black Bear tribe arrived, the Prairie Wolves came. Zhao Hai received them as well.

This made Ah Tai startled again, he knew about the reputation of the Prairie Wolves. He couldn’t believe that Zhao Hai would become friends with them.

Even if he wasn’t as polite as the Black Bear Patriarch, the Old Wolf King still had a friendly chat with Zhao Hai. Zhao Hai also invited the Old Wolf King over for a meal.

Naturally, in these two occasions, Zhao Hai didn’t serve ordinary Milk Wine, he used his own distilled milk wine. This made the Beastmen very surprised, they have drank Milk Wine for all their lives, but they didn’t think that Milk Wine would become this delicious.

Four days after the arrival of the Prairie Wolves, Wales and Buzeer came. The relationship between the two tribes were good, and since the distance from their camps were also quite far from the city, the two decided to come together. Zhao Hai naturally didn’t have anything to say about this, he just went and invited them over for a drink.

What surprised Zhao Hai this time was Buzeer going to him and handing their race’s friendship flag over.

The Beastmen in the City were now looking at Zhao Hai with strange looks. These Beastmen didn’t understand how Zhao Hai, a human, was able to have such a good relationship with their race, especially towards the Dog and Cow-headed race. Seeing how they interact with each other would make one think that they were the same as a family. This really made the Beastmen confused.

In the coming days, Beastman tribe upon Beastman tribe continuously arrived at Beast God City. But what they did was the same as the Black Bears. All of them were left outside while their Patriarchs entered the city.

Although they were cooped up inside the city, Zhao Hai can clearly see every action that they did through the monitor.

The reason why these Beastmen tribes came here and discussed their military plans was because the some Warring Races have their bases here. These were the Lion-headed race, Tiger-headed race, and the Fox-headed Race. Because these royal tribes resided in the City, all the other Beastmen decided to convene their forces here in order to have a common point.

Even if these royal tribes reside in the city, their main camp was in another place. Because of their status, having their main base in the Beastman Race’s holy city would startle the other Beastmen. Therefore, they decided to have their camp elsewhere in order to avoid chaos.

After Wales and the others arrived, Zhao Hai welcomed them and then prepared to leave Beast God City. At this point, the Beastmen already knew that there were friendship flags of the Black Bear Tribe and the Dog-headed Race shown in front of Magic Lily Shop, so nobody went to disturb the place. When Zhao Hai left, he also took those flags away with him.

Then in front of the Beastmen, Zhao Hai called over his Blood Hawks before riding them and then shot straight into the sky. This surprised a lot of Beastmen. They didn’t expect that the Humans would already have their own aerial mounts. For the Beastmen, this wasn’t good news.

When he reached a place beyond the eyesights of the Beastmen, Zhao Hai and the others immediately flashed into the Space. Then from the Space, they went to to the Purcell Duchy.

The Purcell Duchy was in full preparation mode. They had already received the news that the Beastmen were getting ready to attack the Human lands. Moreover, this attack was not a small pillaging party. With how strong the full might of the Beastman Race was, the Purcell Family was not confident in resisting them.

Zhao Hai sat in his carriage as he calmly looked at the residents of the Purcell Duchy. Although the Duchy was fully prepared, Zhao Hao still felt strange. The Purcell Family had been in full defensive mode this time, however, Zhao Hai cannot see any other troop from the Aksu Empire. This situation is too unbelievable.

This move of the Beastmen wasn’t planned in secret. The Beastmen made sure to announce their attack, and a pretty large announcement at that. In that case, it was impossible for the Aksu Empire to be unaware of the situation. So why didn’t the armies of the other Nobles come to support the Purcell Duchy? Did they think that the Purcell Family can single handedly block the Beastmen army?

The location that Zhao Hai appeared in was a remote place in Casa City. At the same time, the carriage that he rode in was a very ordinary one, so no one noticed him.

People were starting to leave Casa City right now, but most of them were low-ranked nobles. They took their own belongings and had their entire families leave the City. At the same time, the commoners of the city stayed put. This was because they didn’t know where to go if they left.

Almost all of the commoners’ properties were inside Casa City. If they leave the city, they would become refugees who had nothing. When they arrive at other cities, they would have nowhere to live. And if they didn’t starve to death, they would still become slaves.

The commoners were hoping that the Duchy’s army would be able to drive the Beastmen away. However, they didn’t know that this feat was almost impossible to achieve.

When Zhao Hai arrived at the Grand Duke’s mansion, he immediately had Shun send a letter. In his trip to the Prairie this time, Zhao Hai didn’t bring Shue and Shun. Instead, he left them at Iron Mountain Fort and instructed them to help Green prepare the place. This was because Zhao Hai was planning to receive some refugees into the Black Wasteland.

However, when Zhao Hai went to Casa City, he immediately called Shun and Shue over. If Zhao Hai didn’t have the two, then he wouldn’t have someone in hand and things would be very inconvenient.

After Shun delivered the letter, it didn’t take a long time before the mansion’s housekeeper came out and invited Zhao Hai to enter through the back door.

When Zhao Hai arrived at inside the mansion and went out of his carriage, Evan was already waiting to welcome him. Evan walked towards Zhao Hai and laughed, “Great, Little Hai. You really are a good kid. The Buda Clan is now at the height of its power, you’re actually making Uncle envious.”

Zhao Hai smiled and said, “Uncle is too polite. Rest assured, I’m not only here to see how the Beastman attack the border.”

When Evan heard Zhao Hai, his smiling face immediately vanished. He turned his head to Zhao Hai and said, “Let’s go in and talk in the living room.” Then he welcomed Zhao Hai inside and sat with him in the living room. He also had a servant serve them some tea. At the same time, a guard was present to guard the door.

After sitting down, Evan sighed and said, “My Purcell Family is done. I’m afraid that we’re already doomed.”

Zhao Hai knit his eyebrows and said, “Uncle Evan. When I came here, I noticed that some nobles are fleeing. At the same time, I didn’t see any other armies beside yours. Did the Aksu Empire decide to not support you?”

Even answered through clenched jaws, “Don’t talk about those bastards with me. Ever since the time you helped me, those bastards of the Aksu Empire started to embarrass me, but I endured. This time, when I received information about the Beastman attack, I sent over a letter to the capital, asking for support. But I didn’t expect those bastards to decline. They told me that the Empire has been short on supply and assembling an army would take a long time. They said that if the Beastmen attack before the reinforcements arrive, then I would have to continue resisting. They are basically telling me to drive my heart straight into a Beastman sword. Those bastards aren’t humans.”

Zhao Hai frowned, he didn’t expect that the Aksu Empire would actually do this. Are they really going to play around with an Empire’s subject’s life? Why would they do this?

Zhao Hai frowned and then looked at Evan, “Uncle Evan, did they really say that? Do they not know that the Beastmen are planning to ravage the Aksu Empire? Have they gone crazy?”

Evan sneered, “Since the continent knew, how could they not? The commoners outside now have a massive dislike towards the Radiant Church. However, those bastards at the capital still regard the Radiant Church as an honored guest. I even heard that some Noble Families were receiving priests of the church like how they receive Dukes.”

Zhao Hai cannot believe what he just heard. What was a priest? They were the lowest position in the Radiant Church. If they were compared to Noble titles, then they would be the lowest third-class Baron. Why would they receive priests as though they were Dukes? Are they insane?

Chapter 528: Life Combustion

Looking at Zhao Hai’s expression, Evan couldn’t help but smile bitterly, “Can’t believe it? But that is the truth. This isn’t something found only in the capital as well, even here in the Purcell Family, there are people who completely devoted themselves to the church. These people have gone fanatical, they would even sacrifice everything that they have for the sake of the Radiant Church.”

Zhao Hai looked at Evan, he seemed to understand what was going on. These people were surely brainwashed by the Radiant Church.

Religion was a very fearful thing. It can make people do a lot of crazy things, Zhao Hai just didn’t think that the Radiant Church’s influence can go this far.

Evan looked at Zhao Hai’s expression and sighed, “Without the Empire’s support, how could our measly forces resist the Beastman attack? My Purcell Family is surely done after this event. But the most pitiful in this situation are the commoners, they will be the ones who will suffer the worst.”

Zhao Hai frowned, he knew how complex the present situation of the Purcell Family was. He can help these people from the city by taking them into the Black Wasteland. He can even take the entire Purcell Duchy with no problems. However, the trade-off would be his secret being exposed.

Most importantly, the current situation of the Purcell Family was even more complex than he had imagined. If the Purcell Family really did have some Radiant Church fanatics, then he cannot bring the family into the wasteland. It would be hard to say what the church can do to his territory. Even the might Beastman Race weren’t able to escape the movements of the church.

Evan looked at Zhao Hai and calmly said, “Little Hai, I only need to ask you for one thing. I want to have some members of the Purcell Family join you in returning to Golden Island. If our family can survive this crisis, then they can return. If we can’t, then I can only request you to take care of them for a couple of years so that the Purcell Family name can survive.”

Zhao Hai looked at Evan. He knew that Evan had already thought of the worst possible outcome. He wanted to leave a seed for the Purcell Family.

Zhao Hai didn’t decline, he nodded and said, “Alright, I can assure you of this. But Uncle, I also have one thing to ask. Can you check for me and see if there are people who are willing to leave with me to Golden Island? You should know that our Buda Clan is short on people right now. And if the Beastmen attack, these commoners would definitely be killed. But make sure that they are innocent and are not affiliated with the Radiant Church.”

Evan nodded and said, “This is not a problem, I can arrange it. There are a lot of people who wants to leave right now, but they just don’t know where to go. They don’t have any means of survival in other cities, and may even be demoted into slaves. I don’t want them to see them like that, so I shall definitely help you with this matter.”

Zhao Hai nodded and said, “Then I’ll have to trouble Uncle Evan. I hope that you can take care of this matter as soon as possible. Just have them group up here while I go to see how the Iksa Family is doing.”

Evan nodded, “You should go see their situation as well. In consideration for you, the Iksa Family had been helping us as well. I heard that the Empire sent some troops over to their territory. However, it seems like the family was placed under house arrest.”

Zhao Hai stared, then his complexion changed, “Really? This bastard Aksu Empire, what do they want to do? Have they really become the puppet of the Radiant Church?”

Evan calmly replied, “It’s highly probable. If the Empire wasn’t, then how could the Empire act like this? This action is equal to offending all the Nobles. In the future, no Noble would listen to them.”

Zhao Hai sighed, he really couldn’t understand the Radiant Church. What was their purpose in doing this? Did they want to get the attention of the Royals? With the current situation, all of the Royals in the continent would be suppressing the Church.

After watching the sky, Zhao Hai stood up, then he turned to Evan and said, “Uncle Evan, since it’s still early, I’ll head to see the Iksa Family’s situation. I’m afraid that they’re currently in danger.”

Evan nodded, “Little Hai, you go leave from my family’s secret passage. I’ve already had few days to prepare, so you don’t have to worry too much about me. Go save the Iksa Family first.”

Zhao Hai stared, he didn’t expect Evan to allow him to use the Purcell Family’s secret passage. This was one of the Purcell Family’s greatest secret.

Zhao Hai understood Evan’s action, this was Evan’s way of telling him that he has his complete trust. However, Zhao Hai didn’t need the secret passage, he shook his head and said, “No need to use it. I have my own means.”

Evan knew that Zhao Hai has flying beasts, so he didn’t say anything. He nodded his head and escorted Zhao Hai to the door and to his carriage before it left the mansion.

After Zhao Hai entered his carriage, he immediately flashed into the Space and went to Laura and the others. Since the women are in the Space, they heard Evan and Zhao Hai’s conversation. Laura immediately turned to Zhao Hai and said, “Brother Hai, I just had Cai’er pay attention to the Iksa Family’s situation. The family is fine, but they are currently under house arrest. However, we didn’t receive any letters from the Blood Hawk.”

Zhao Hai nodded, then he immediately got the monitor to display the Iksa Family’s situation. The Iksa Family’s mansion was surrounded with soldiers. Robert couldn’t do anything because he was trapped inside. Fernand’s situation wasn’t any better, he seemed to be beaten, his body looked like a damp sack.

Zhao Hai looked around and couldn’t see a shadow of a Blood Hawk, it might be possibly killed off. It seems like the Aksu Empire sent some 9th ranks to deal with the Iksa Family, otherwise they wouldn’t have been able to restrain it.

Moreover, the Iksa Family also had 9th rank experts, so if these experts haven’t been dealt with, then it would be impossible for the Iksa Family to be placed under house arrest.

After thinking about this, Zhao Hai immediately had Cai’er scan the place, looking for other 9th rank experts present. Ordinary people might not be able to spot a 9th rank expert, but Cai’er is different. Cai’er’s present strength was certainly greater than any 9th rank expert.

After some time, Cai’er finally found some 9th rank experts in Sarte City. Moreover, there were four of them. These four were placed in a position where they surrounded the Iksa Family mansions. Looking at the their appearances, it seems like all of them were from the Radiant Church.

Zhao Hai immediately looked at Bell’s situation. Bell’s people were also placed under house arrest. Zhao Hai knew that Bell might have been exposed, otherwise he wouldn’t be implicated in this event. It seems like the Radiant Church was really waiting for him.

Zhao Hao looked at the four 9th rank experts. The four of them doesn’t seem to have any special qualities, they weren’t any different from other 9th rank experts.

Knowing that he couldn’t wait for a long time, Zhao Hai immediately flashed and appeared inside Fernand’s room. Fernand’s current state was very miserable. His whole body was fully wrapped with bandages to the point where only his head was visible, of which was beaten black and blue. Even if his mother was taking care of him, it seems like nobody used Light Magic to heal him. Otherwise, he wouldn’t be in such a pitiful state.

Fernand seems to be unconscious right now because he wasn’t making any movements in his bed. Zhao Hai looked at Fernand’s condition and couldn’t help but feel an aching in his heart. In truth, his time with Fernand wasn’t that long. Fernand was a playboy as well, someone whom he generally didn’t like. The two of them being friends was something almost impossible.

However, fate moves in strange ways, even if the disposition of the two seem to be in conflict, they still became good friends in the end.

Zhao Hai arrived by Fernand’s bedside and whispered, “Brother Fernand, Brother Fernand. Can you hear me?”

Seeing that the person on the bed wasn’t replying, Zhao Hai immediately used Light Magic. Fernand’s face turned much better, then his eyelids moved slightly. When Zhao Hai saw this, he became happy as he said, “Brother Fernand. You’re awake.”

But it seems like Zhao Hai wasn’t noticed. Immediately after Zhao Hai talked, Fernand opened his eyes and then bellowed, “Bastards, my brother will come! He will certainly not let you off.”

Zhao Hai stared, Fernand froze as well. He stared at Zhao Hai for a moment before turning over on his bed and jumped off. He threw his weak body towards Zhao Hai and said, “Brother, why have you come just now? I’ve been bullied to death by those bastards.”

Zhao Hai stared, he didn’t know whether to laugh or cry, he patted Fernand’s back and said, “It’s alright, Brother, no need cry. Since I came, I will surely take revenge for you.”

It was at this point that Fernand stopped weeping, he anxiously let go of Zhao Hai and said, “Brother, taking revenge isn’t a good idea. The other party has several 9th ranks, they managed to kill all of my family’s foreign elders. You need to leave quickly.”

At this time, a chilly voice was heard, “Leave? He couldn’t escape now.”

When he heard this sound, Fernand’s face paled, his expression was as though a disaster just happened. He looked at Zhao Hai and bitterly smiled, “Brother, it seems like you couldn’t get away now. The 9th rank has noticed you.”

Zhao Hai smiled faintly and said, “I’ve already seen a lot of 9th ranks. It’s alright, brother, you come with me. Let’s see how great this 9th rank expert really is.” Then he led Fernand out of the room.

Outside, Zhao Hai can see the four 9th ranks that Cai’er has spotted before. All of them flew over to the mansion and surrounded the small yard that Zhao Hai was in.

Zhao Hai just stood there and calmly looked at the four 9th rank experts before he sneered, “The Radiant Church really has a lot of good methods. They actually wouldn’t stop at anything just to deal with me.”

The 9th rank expert looked at Zhao Hai and nodded, “What you said is right. The Pope has given the order to execute you at all costs. The Radiant Church had already expended a lot of people in dealing with you, this time you will certainly die.”

Zhao Hai smiled, “It wasn’t yesterday that the Radiant Church had started to deal with me, yet I still lived. On the other hand, you have lost a lot of 9th ranks. This really makes me amazed at how much 9th rank experts your Radiant Church has.”

The 9th rank looked at Zhao Hai and coldly snorted, “No need to waste your breath. Zhao Hai, you are now our Radiant Church’s number one enemy. Until the day we eliminate you, my Radiant Church wouldn’t be peaceful. To eliminate you, we wouldn’t hesitate to bring it all. Our lives belong to the church, so we shall sacrifice our lives for the Church. Zhao Hai, you shall die today!”

Zhao Hai laughed, “Not necessarily. Do you really think that 9th ranks can kill me? Who do you think you are?”

The 9th rank snorted, “Without perfect preparations, how can we dare to kill you? Do you really think that the Church is clueless about your secrets? Zhao Hai, it’s time for you to die.” Then several lights came out of the hands of the 9th ranks as they shot into the four corners of the mansion.

Zhao Hai stared as the lights fell before it formed a dome around the mansion.

Zhao Hai didn’t care, he can just ask Cai’er to return him to the Space. This transparent dome was unable to touch him.

From his speculation, this dome should be some kind of Magical Formation. It seems like the Radiant Church wanted to deal with him using this formation. Zhao Hai didn’t move, he just stood there and looked curiously at the 9th rank experts.

The 9th ranks were whispering words as though they were doing incantations in the sky. While they were murmuring words, one could visibly see their faces slowly turn wrinkly.

When Zhao Hai saw this, his expression changed. He knew that these 9th ranks are consuming their Life Force, it seems like they were prepared to sacrifice their lives with this move.

Zhao Hai looked all around and then turned his head to the dumbfounded Fernand and said, “Brother, immediately inform your family to gather by my side. The Radiant Church is using a strange Magic.”

Fernand stared, he didn’t care about anything that Zhao Hai said in the end as he immediately said, “Alright!” Then he ran towards the mansion.

But it seems like the wrinkling of these 9th ranks were getting faster and faster until their faces turned pale white. The sense of crisis that Zhao Hai felt was getting more and more pronounced. It seems like these four people aren’t simply 9th ranks of the Radiant Church.

These four should have a special method in order to collaboratively use this strange Magic. This Magic should be very formidable, and the Magic Formation surely wasn’t a simple one. It seems like it would be impossible to break this dome from the inside.

Chapter 529: Two Choices

Zhao Hai calmly looked at the 9th rank experts as they were quickly getting older. One must know that a 9th rank expert’s lifespan was very long. Moreover, from what Zhao Hai saw of their appearance, these 9th ranks can still live for a long time, at the very least 3500 years.

Now they were growing old so fast that it would seem like they were riding a fast car which is running on the road of time. It was as if the time around them were 100 or 1000 times more than normal people.

Zhao Hai’s expression stayed calm, his body beneath his clothes had now turned into crystal. He fully trusted the Space, and since it said that his body would become unbreakable upon crystallization, Zhao Hai chose to directly face these four 9th rank experts.

Since the beginning, Zhao Hai had always indirectly battled his opponents. Besides the time when he fought Terry, Zhao Hai had always been in the back, casting spells and summoning undead.

This has something to do with his character. He just doesn’t want to directly fight, he thinks that the way that Mages fight was the safest.

But now was not the time to do that, if he entered the Space at this moment, then his secret would have been exposed. In addition, he was still in the Iksa Family mansion, if he entered the Space, he would be putting the Iksa Family in peril.

Although the Space possessed marvelous abilities, it cannot forcibly absorb mindful beings. Therefore, Zhao Hai can only stand there and wait for Fernand to bring his family to his side then have them transported into the Space.

At the same time, ever since Zhao Hai was able to crystallize, his mind changed a little bit. He wanted to try how strong his body was. Even if he cannot withstand this attack, he still had Cai’er and the Space. As long as Fernand’s family is in the Space, he can confidently and boldly accept this strike.

Naturally, the attack of the opposite party still needed to be prepared for quite some time. But Fernand wasn’t stupid, he knew that every second counts. The other members of the Iksa Family aren’t stupid either, when they saw what the 9th ranks were doing, they immediately knew what kind of attack it was.

They were very clear about how powerful 9th rank experts were. Although the Iksa Family still had their secret passage, this passage can only be a decoration in front of a 9th rank expert. After Fernand shouted, all of them immediately convened to Zhao Hai’s location.

Zhao Hai didn’t have the time to be polite with them, he immediately issued a heads-up, “In a while I’m going to send you to a strange place. But don’t worry, some people would be there to receive you. So don’t get too startled.” Then Fernand and the others made an effort to nod.

Robert’s influence in the Iksa Family was very high, so when he shouted at the crowd, they immediately calmed down. One must know that the Iksa Family had a lot of members. It was a miracle to be able to shut them up in a short period of time.

Zhao Hai carefully observed the four 9th rank experts. The lives of these four were soon coming to an end. The wrinkles on their faces started overlapping, the hair on their head were starting to fall, old people spots were starting to appear, even their teeth were falling off.

However, they still didn’t stop chanting their incantations. It was as though they didn’t have any idea of what was happening to their bodies.

Then Zhao Hai turned his attention to the Iksa Family. Seeing that they were prepared, he immediately brought all of them into the Space.

And just as Zhao Hai sent the Iksa Family to the Space, the four 9th rank experts said their last syllable. Then all of them violently shook before turning into a mist of blood. After then, something appeared on the skies, it seems like there was another sun that appeared. It looked very bright and terrifying.

The light seemed to be like an Energy Ball from a certain novel that Zhao Hai had read back on earth. The ball of light crashed into the mansion. But how strong was this ball of light? Zhao Hai didn’t have time to think about this as the attack collided with his head.

Fortunately, Zhao Hai’s entire body has now been crystallized. Zhao Hai felt the light hit his head and then his clothes vanishing. It was not only his clothes, the building in his surroundings has been eradicated. The ground, the cyan stones were gone, no need to say about the plants. Everything around him completely vanished.

Zhao Hai just stood there without entering the Space. This was because the ball of light hadn’t been able to damage his current body.

And also, he didn’t dare open a spatial crack to enter the Space. Even though he wasn’t affected at all, Zhao Hai felt how formidable this attack was. If this ball of light were to penetrate the crack and enter the Space, Zhao Hai didn’t know what would happen to the people inside. And he didn’t want to dare take the risk.

Since this ball of light couldn’t harm him, it was much better for him to stay outside. But Zhao Hai didn’t know that while he stayed outside, Laura and the others were very anxious for him inside the Space.

Zhao Hai made Laura and the others receive the Iksa Family. The Iksa Family had now reached its end, they can only depend upon the Buda Clan to survive. Because of this, Zhao Hai wasn’t afraid of the family betraying him. Moreover, since he was planning to transport the family to Iron Mountain Fort, even if they knew his secrets, it would be impossible for them to pass it on.

When the Iksa Family initially entered the Space, all of them were somewhat anxious. But when they saw Laura and the others, they calmed down. But even if the Space’s villa was huge, it can just barely fit 100 people, so it was impossible for the entire Iksa Family to be accommodated there. Laura asked them to rest first before they can be transported to Iron Mountain Fort.

At this time, what Laura and the others were worrying about was the situation outside. Therefore, after they invited Robert into the villa, they surrounded the monitor and looked at the situation outside.

But it was unfortunate for them that the screen was entirely white, they couldn’t see anything. After the light vanished, the scene made Laura and the others breathe in a cold air.

The City Lord’s mansion has completely been wiped off the map, they couldn’t see a single piece left. In the original location of the mansion, a giant hole was left. This hole looked like a crater that a meteor had created, it had a depth of 30 meters.

What made Laura and the others uneasy was the fact that they couldn’t see Zhao Hai in that crater. Zhao Hai didn’t even leave behind a shadow.

When Laura and the others were about to panic, Zhao Hai suddenly walked in from outside. But he already had his clothes changed, what he had on was now an ordinary Mage’s Robe.

Seeing Zhao Hai come, Laura and the others relaxed. Actually, Zhao Hai didn’t intend to be missing. But since his clothes were fully gone, he cannot just appear naked inside the villa and be seen by the Iksa Family, he wasn’t an exhibitionist. Therefore, after he entered the Space, the changed his clothes first before entering the villa.

When he entered the villa, he was immediately welcomed by Laura and the others. They looked at his left and right to see that he was really alright.

Seeing their expressions, Zhao Hai faintly smiled and said, “I’m fine, no need to be worried. But Laura, I’m sorry for destroying the clothes that you gave me.”

After he said that, Laura didn’t know whether to laugh or cry, “Who cares about the clothes. As long as you’re fine, it’s alright. Go see Uncle Robert quickly, I don’t think his mood is fine.”

Zhao Hai nodded, then he entered the villa’s living room. Robert and Fernand were waiting for him there, when they saw him, they immediately stood up.

Zhao Hai gave Robert a salute and then asked them to sit down, “Uncle Robert, from what I can see with the situation, there was no way for the Iksa Family to return to the Aksu Empire.”

Robert smiled bitterly, “I already thought up to this point. Ever since our Foreign Elders were killed, I knew our Iksa Family is finished. To be honest, if not for you appearing, our Iksa Family might have gone extinct. Not matter what, I must thank you, Little Hai.”

Zhao Hai waved his hand and said, “Uncle Robert, you’re too polite. If not because of me, your Iksa Family wouldn’t have been implicated with this situation. Since you came here, I will be clear to you. This place is our Buda Clan’s greatest secret. Nobody except members of my Buda Clan knew about it, even my father-in-laws don’t know about this. Now that the Iksa Family know about it, I can tell you that it would be impossible for you to go back.”

Robert nodded. As soon as he entered the Space, he felt the difference inside. He was also a Mage, so he was sensitive to energy. He can feel how active the energy inside was, and it was also quite rich, many folds compared to outside. This place was certainly not a simple one.

Zhao Hai looked at Robert and said, “Uncle Robert, I can only give you two choices. First, you’ll go to the Black Wasteland. I’ll tell you, the poisonous mist in the wasteland was made by me. The Black Wasteland is where the root of our Buda Clan was established. The Milk Wine that we drank before was made there, we also have other factories in that place. In there, you will have absolute security. Moreover, I’m also prepared to buy a massive amount of slaves. If you settle down in the Black Wasteland, I can have the capable people of the Iksa Family help me manage them.”

Robert nodded, he thought that this choice was good, but he wonders what Zhao Hai’s second choice was. So he asked, “The second choice?”

Chapter 530: Robert’s Shock

Zhao Hai smiled and said, “The second choice is to go to Golden Island. That place is also the Buda Clans’ territory. After you head there, you can do administrative work for the Island. But to make sure that you don’t pass on some information, I will have to make undeads watch over your day to day lives.”

Robert knitted his brows. He clearly knew what Zhao Hai meant, they cannot expose the existence of this place. Therefore, if they go to Golden island, they would always have an undead right beside them and they wouldn’t have anything to say about this matter.

If they go to the Black Wasteland, there’s no need for the undead. This was because the wasteland was a completely closed off environment,  it was impossible for outsiders to come in, while Zhao Hai wouldn’t easily allow the people inside to go out. So if they go there, they can move very freely without being monitored.

On the other hand, Golden Island has contact with the outside world. Although the Iksa Family was now on its low point, Robert was still hoping that they can still show their faces to the continent. This would make the people know that the Iksa Family survived, that they still exist.

However, being monitored everyday was very uncomfortable. Robert was now having a hard time making up his mind, he didn’t know how to handle this matter.

Looking at Robert’s appearance, Zhao Hai smiled and said, “Uncle Robert doesn’t need to worry about this right now. I shall first take you to the Black Wasteland later, you can slowly deliberate your decision there. If you decide to stay there, I wouldn’t oppose. And if you decide to go to Golden Island, I will certainly bring you there.”

Robert nodded, this matter needed to be thought through properly. He cannot stay in the Space for a long time. So after Zhao Hai talked about this matter to Robert, he immediately sent the family into the Black Wasteland.

Robert was now certain that the Space was Zhao Hai’s magical property. Otherwise, it wouldn’t be able to transfer people everywhere.

There are a lot of people in the Iksa Family but they can definitely be accommodated inside Iron Mountain Fort. Moreover, when they arrived at the fort, Robert and the others were shocked. They didn’t think that the legendary barn hills and untamed rivers of the Black Wasteland would have such a beautiful castle. Moreover, this castle has been producing some of the continent’s highly sought after products.

Robert was surprised because the Black Wasteland was already considered to be the continent’s most mysterious place by the Nobles. He didn’t expect the the Buda Clan would have their roots here.

It didn’t take a long time before Robert came to like the place. Most of the people here have marks of slaves, however, they weren’t slaves anymore. There were Beastmen here as well, but these Beastmen were strangely full of hospitality and friendliness.

Most importantly, Robert can notice a certain kind of thing within these people. They were all full of vigor, as though they were working hard to have a better life. This kind of vigor was rarely seen in the continent.

When Robert heard Zhao Hai say that the Black Wasteland had been transformed, and that all of the lands can now be cultivated, Robert was once again shocked.

Robert was the Patriarch of the Iksa Family, a well-known family of the continent. Therefore, he had full understanding with regards to the Black Wasteland.

The Black Wasteland was the continent’s biggest plain. Although it was placed in the north, and can only be cultivated on one season, it was an undeniable fact that if the Black Wasteland were to gain an ability to grow crops, it would certainly be the continent’s largest granary.

If not because of this, the continent wouldn’t have spent a lot of time and energy to research the wasteland. This was because its topography was fantastic. Once one was able to grow crops here, their influence in the continent would certainly soar.

What Robert didn’t expect was that the place where the continent had spent a long time on researching was solved by Zhao Hai this easily. Robert now understood why Zhao Hai didn’t make Golden Island the Buda Clan’s main base. Golden Island was an important hub for maritime trade, it can certainly bring a lot of profit to the Buda CLan. But compared to the Black Wasteland, the island was still a long way off. You can’t always exchange food with money, but you can always exchange money with food.

After knowing that the Black Wasteland can now grow some crops, Robert almost immediately decided to stay here.

The Black Wasteland was very huge, one could definitely establish their own nation here. With the continual rise of the Buda Clan, the development of the Black Wasteland would become better and better. If the Iksa Clan can be an influential family in the Black Wasteland, their reappearance in the future would be much better.

Robert knew that it would be impossible for the Buda Clan to hide the existence of the Black Wasteland forever. So people of the continent would surely know of the wasteland’s situation in the future. Therefore, the Iksa Family can still show their faces to the continent, only this time quite beautifully.

But Robert also knew that this matter wouldn’t be easy. After all, the Iksa Family had been enjoying their place in the continent. With how desolate the Black Wasteland seemed, he was afraid that his family members wouldn’t be able to get used to it.

Although Robert was the Patriarch, he cannot just ignore the thoughts of his family members. He wasn’t a dictator, he needed to listen to the words of the family elders.

On the other hand, Zhao Hai was hoping that Robert’s family would decide to stay inside the Black Wasteland. Compared to Golden Island, the Black Wasteland needed managerial talents more.

After all, the Iksa Family was also a Great Clan in the past. Although there weren’t a lot of people who came this time, Zhao Hai knew that those present were the elite members of the family.

The plan of the Radiant Church this time was very simple. Since they want to eliminate the Iksa Family, then they surely wouldn’t let their elites off. They wanted to sacrifice the lives of four of their 9th rank experts in order to achieve their goal of extinguishing both Zhao Hai and the Iksa Family. Exterminating a Great Clan was both easy and hard. There were two ways of doing so; First, it was to kill all of their 9th rank experts, this way they’ll lose their power backing. The second was to kill all of their elites. This would inhibit the growth of the family, and would thus vanish in the future.

The Radiant Church chose to use the two methods to deal with the Iksa Family. They killed the family’s 9th rank expert first, then concentrated their effort of eliminating the elites along with Zhao Hai. Therefore, even if there weren’t a lot of people who came with Zhao Hai, all of them were elites of the family. As long as they learn a bit, they would become independent managers. This would be a huge benefit to the Black Wasteland’s development.

Because Zhao Hai had such intentions, he decided to show Robert and the others the Black Wasteland first. He believed that if they saw the Black Wasteland, they would certainly feel attracted to it.

Obviously, he succeeded, Robert was moved. The current Black Wasteland cannot be considered to be on the same level as Golden Island. However, since it can now be cultivated, its potential was endless. For Robert and the Iksa Family, being in the Black Wasteland was much more attractive than being in Golden Island.

On Golden Island, they would be safe, yes, but what can they do then? On Golden Island, they can only become a Merchant Clan at most. If they wanted to regain their former glory, it would be impossible to accomplish it in the island.

For Robert, this was unacceptable. They were a Great Clan in Aksu Empire, with a name renowned in the Continent. How could they be comfortable with being a rich Merchant Clan? Therefore, Zhao Hai decided to show them the Black Wasteland’s potential, and have them tie their family to the Buda Clan’s chariot.

Zhao Hai also asked Robert if they needed anything right now. After all, Iron Mountain Fort cannot be compared to their past situation.

But Robert told him that they were alright They already have some daily necessities, and they were eating and drinking properly as well. The only thing they were unfamiliar with was the lack of contact with the outside world.

Zhao Hai didn’t ask Robert to bring the Iksa Family’s properties out. Such words can only make Robert misunderstand and make him think that Zhao Hai wanted to swallow the Iksa Family.

After settling the Iksa Family down, Zhao Hai returned to the Iksa Family’s territory. He wanted to see how Bell was doing. Bell’s identity might have been exposed, so he cannot stay here. In any case, Bell can also be considered to be one of the powers of the Iksa Family, the Radiant Church wouldn’t certainly let him off.

Zhao Hai’s fight with the 9th rank experts caused quite a stir. Sarte City was now under martial law.

Zhao Hai turned his attention to the state of Bell’s Family. Presently, the family had vanished from Sarte City. It seems like Bell was already ready to leave, but with the 9th rank experts, he cannot leave. Now that the 9th ranks had died, he naturally fled immediately.

Seeing this situation, Zhao Hai felt relief. He believed in the escape route that Bell prepared, that man wasn’t a simple person.

Since nothing noteworthy was left to see in Sarte City, Zhao Hai left. He went to find Evan and told him about what happened to the Iksa Family. Then he had Evan release this information into the continent. He must make all of the Clans in the continent know about what happened to the Iksa Family. This was also another form of attack towards the Radiant Church.

What the Radiant Church had done was very excessive, they even had the Aksu Empire under their control. If Zhao Hai spread this information, the other countries in the continent would surely be on guard against the church. Zhao Hai wanted to see if the Radiant Church would still dare to act so rampant.

Chapter 531: Evan’s Hesitation, Robert’s Decision

Evan still hasn’t received the information about the Iksa Family. After all, it just happened, if people died, it would be impossible for him to know.

After Zhao Hai returned to Casa City, he directly went to the City Lord’s Mansion. Evan didn’t expect Zhao Hai to come back this quickly. But he knew that Zhao Hai had a lot of secrets, so he just disregarded it and invited him over to the living room.

After they sat down, Zhao Hai told Evan everything regarding the happenings in the Iksa Domain. Evan was startled, he knew that even if the Iksa Family didn’t hold the title of Grand Duke, their might wasn’t much worse compared to the Purcell Duchy. But now, their clan was almost equal to being eliminated, the Radiant Church was truly ruthless.

After relaying the event, Zhao Hai didn’t immediately ask Evan to spread the information. He looked at Evan’s expression first. He knew that Evan cannot just leave his properties here. If he tells everything straight to Evan, even if he didn’t understand the choices, Zhao Hai was afraid that he would follow in the steps of the Iksa Family.

Zhao Hai hadn’t given up in drawing the Purcell Family into the Buda CLan. The Buda Clan badly needed talents right now. As the Clan gets bigger and bigger, the talents that it needed would also get more and more.

The Markey Family’s people were now helping to manage Golden Island. In addition to their prior businesses, not too many of them were free to help the Buda Clan.

The Buda Clan itself had a few number of people. But even if the Iksa Family were added to their numbers, don’t forget about the 100 thousand Beastman slaves that were still coming as well as the 100 thousand slaves that he bought from Carson City. With over 200 thousand slaves, how much people does the Clan need in order to manage them? The slaves who became citizens and can now write aren’t fit for the job, they still needed prior managerial skills. If the Purcell Family were to join, then their number of talents would surely increase.

However, the Purcell Family’s situation was much complex than the Iksa Family. The Radiant Church had already seeped into the Purcell Family. Therefore, even if Zhao Hai wanted to take them in, he still needed to be careful in doing so.

Evan had told Zhao Hai about the existence of Radiant Church fanatics inside the family. However, he didn’t tell Zhao Hai how he plans to deal with them, nor did he express his intention to. Maybe Evan wanted a way back if he cannot take the pressure. He may look for the Radiant Church for help, so he decided to keep those people as insurance.

Zhao Hai told Evan about the Iksa Family’s situation because he wanted Evan to see what the Purcell Family might become. It was so that Evan wouldn’t dream of going to the Radiant Church in the future.

After Evan heard him, his expression changed. He didn’t think that the Radiant Church would be this ruthless. If the Radiant Church would deal with him the same way, what would happen to the Purcell Family?

Zhao Hai stayed silent, he just calmly sat there while looking at Evan. He wanted to know what Evan would do. Now that the pieces were laid down in front of Evan, Zhao Hai wanted to know which one the Purcell Family would choose, the Radiant Church or the Buda Clan.

Evan stayed silent for quite some time, he was deciding on a hard choice. He knew that if he chose the Buda Clan, then the Purcell Family would lose everything that they had in the Purcell Duchy. After then, the Purcell Family would become the vassals of the Buda Clan, this was not the best outcome.

But if he sided with the Radiant Church, then he was afraid that the Radiant Church might renege on their agreement. At that time, he would lose literally everything.

Most importantly, this matter wasn’t something that he could decide along. Even though the Purcell Duchy had undergone changes and he has now accumulated a lot of influence, he still needed to ask for the Elder Assembly’s opinion regarding their stance against the Radiant Church.

In truth, Zhao Hai was now disappointed with the Purcell Family. The way they handled matters was both overcautious and indecisive. Even if Zhao Hai had told them about what happened to the Iksa Family, they were still hesitating.

Evan clearly expressed his support for Zhao Hai since the beginning. But even if the Purcell Family supported Zhao Hai, they still left behind a leeway for themselves. They wanted to support two sides, which was utterly impossible.

Zhao Hai sighed inwardly, then with a serious tone, he said, “Uncle, I’ll be leaving this matter for you to think about. I won’t be disturbing you. I shall stay here for a couple of days, if you have any matter to tell me about, you can just go to Laura’s original place. As long as you go there, I will go and meet you.”

Evan didn’t expect Zhao Hai to leave, he wanted Zhao Hai to stay here. He didn’t know what to say right now and couldn’t open his mouth. In the end, he can only sigh and then escorted Zhao Hai out.

He also knew that for Zhao Hai to be able to bring the Buda Clan into this height in just one year, he surely had some fortuitous encounter. He wasn’t someone to be underestimated. Zhao Hai certainly knew about what was going on in his mind, therefore Zhao Hai wanted to leave.

Regarding this situation, Evan felt helpless. In his heart, he wanted to aid Zhao Hai. But as a Patriarch, he needed to compromise with the world. A matter that decides the family’s fate wasn’t something that he can just decide on his own.

After Zhao Hai boarded his carriage and left the City Lord’s Mansion, he found a desolate place and then flashed to the Space. He didn’t go to Iron Mountain Fort, he just stayed in the Space and looked at the responses of both the Iksa Family and the Purcell Family.

It was assured that the Iksa Family would side with Zhao Hai. From today’s events, they had lost all of their 9th rank experts. And with their enmity with the Radiant Church, it was impossible for them to return to the continent.

If they did return, then the Radiant Church wouldn’t even need to move. Other jealous Aksu Empire Nobles would certainly be interested in their properties and their lives.

Therefore, the choices that the Iksa Family needed to decide on was simple. It was either to stay in the Black Wasteland or to go to Golden Island.

Zhao Hai knew that the Iksa Family would want to convene in order to decide on this matter. He wanted to have a look about what the Iksa Family decided on.

On the other hand, Zhao Hai can almost correctly guess what the Purcell Family’s decision would be. The Elder’s Assembly still held great influence, their authority was too big. There were even times where Evan cannot do anything about it. And it would be impossible for these elders to discard all of the properties that the Purcell Family had accumulated just to side with the Buda Clan.

However, Zhao Hai still hoped that they would come up with a satisfactory response. So he wanted to pay attention to their decision.

Naturally, he couldn’t let those people take care of spreading the Iksa Family’s matter to the continent anymore. Therefore, the immediately wrote a letter and sent it over to Kun. Kun would then hand the letter off to Randolph and then in turn hand it over to the Rosen Emperor. With their combined efforts, it would only take a short time before this matter would be spread around the continent.

While Zhao Hai was thinking about this, the Iksa Family had truly gathered together and discussed what to do. Green was very good towards the Iksa Family, he handed a region of the fort for their own use. The place was still unoccupied, so the Iksa Family can use it in the meantime.

Robert was now accompanied with some core members of his family. Besides Robert, there were ten other people present, Fernand wasn’t qualified to participate in this meeting.

Robert looked at the eyes of those present and sadi, “Our Iksa Family had truly experienced a disaster. We’re almost to a point of being extinguished. It was fortunate that Little Hai was able to save us, allowing our further survival. But for Little Hai to save us, he had exposed the Buda Clan’s biggest secret. Leaving the Buda Clan would be impossible.”

The other people present weren’t surprised, they weren’t stupid. Even if Zhao Hai hadn’t told them about the Space, they can still guess what it was. Therefore, Robert’s words didn’t startle them, it was completely expected.

When Robert saw their expressions, he couldn’t help but nod. These people didn’t disappoint him, then he continued, “Little Hai has now given us two choices. First is to stay here, in the Black Wasteland. Second is to go to Golden Island. I want to hear everyone’s opinion.”

The people present looked at each other and then one of them said, “Patriarch, can’t our family divide our members between the Black Wasteland and Golden Island?”

Robert thought for a moment and said, “It should be possible. But from what I can see, our Iksa Family needs to have a focused direction. We can only look and see which situation is better for us.”

Then the elder who talked earlier said, “What is the difference between the two places? Now that we know about the Buda Clan’s secret, wouldn’t Zhao Hai have any methods to silence us? In that case, I think we need to consider those before deciding.”

Robert nodded and said, “Naturally there are. Everyone knows about the Black Wasteland. Once we enter the wasteland, then exiting would be difficult. Therefore, he can just leave us to freely live here, nobody would be monitoring us. Moreover, once Zhao Hai brings his slaves here, we can help him manage them. If we go to Golden Island, an undead would accompany us in order to ensure that the Buda Clan’s secret get exposed.”

The people in the room frowned and felt embarrassed, this matter was surely hard to decide on. Then the elder thought for a while before turning to Robert and said, “Patriarch, your opinion?” Then the other people also turned their attention to Robert, they wanted to hear his thoughts.

Robert wasn’t polite and directly said, “I want our family to focus on the Black Wasteland. The Black Wasteland might be inferior to the continent, but everyone here certainly knows what would happen if it were to be cultivated. With so much land, can the Buda Clan manage it alone? The Black Wasteland’s size is enough for it to be a country. If we help the Buda Clan set this country up, what do you all think will happen to our Iksa Family once the Black Wasteland get unraveled in the continent?”

As soon as the elders heard Robert, their eyes turned bright. They were smart people, the immediately understood what Robert meant. This outcome was much better than being protected. If the Buda Clan established their country in the future while the Iksa Family was their subordinate, the status that they would have would certainly not be small. Being a Grand Duke might not even be difficult to attain.

After seeing the expressions of these people, Robert continued, “Our situation would be different if we go to Golden Island. If we go there, our actions would be monitored. Even if Zhao Hai doesn’t deal with us, we would still be losing our freedom. Even if Golden Island was a big place as well, our family doesn’t have any 9th rank experts so we would still need to depend on the Buda Clan. In the end, even if we get rich, we can only be a Merchant Clan. Therefore, I wanted our Iksa Family to settle in the Black Wasteland.”

The elders nodded, they were convinced by Robert. Then Robert said, “Our Iksa Family isn’t the same as the original Iksa Family. If we want to reveal our faces again, we cannot leave the Buda Clan. Since we would be depending on the Buda Clan either way, why won’t we get power and prestige as well. Why would we only settle on being rich?”

The elder who spoke before nodded and said, “Just as the Patriarch said, I also believe that this is an opportunity for our Iksa Family. Even if our family had been doing beautifully in Aksu Empire, we still didn’t get our hands on the title of Grand Duke, we cannot establish our own Duchy. In my opinion, our time with the Aksu Empire has come to a dead end. But now that we have the opportunity to advance, we should grab into it. If the Buda Clan established their own country in the future, our Iksa Family would surely have a high position. Therefore, I completely agree with the Patriarch’s opinion. We should stay with the Buda Clan and help them develop the Black Wasteland fully.

The other Iksa Family elders nodded as well. This made Robert relax. Since the Iksa Family had decided on their future, they would now fully support the Buda Clan.

Chapter 532: Angrily Rebukes

Zhao Hai calmly looked at the screen, he wasn’t surprised by the Iksa Family’s decision. He just didn’t expect the Iksa Family to fully dedicate themselves to the Buda Clan. They had fully become the Buda Clan’s vassals.

Most importantly, Robert and the others mentioned the founding of a country. To be honest, Zhao Hai didn’t see himself establishing his own country. He just wanted the Black Wasteland to be a place of freedom, a place very different from the outside world.

But founding a nation? This idea didn’t fit with Zhao Hai. He had always regarded himself as a small person, with a nerd’s personality. He sometimes had a feeling of inferiority and low self confidence.

Even if he had his current status, he was still very careful, which was one of his shortcomings. With his current strength, even if he revealed the situation of the Black Wasteland, which power would dare to face him? As long as he reveals the Black Wasteland, more people in the continent would go and trust him. This would immediately solve the Buda Clan’s manpower problem.

However, Zhao Hai still prefers to be careful. He wanted to reveal it little by little. It’s nice to be cautious and sometimes timid. There are times when too much courage can cause a person’s downfall.

The words of the Iksa Family made Zhao Hai feel overwhelmed. He didn’t know which direction the Buda Clan would step into in the future. He just wants to develop the Black Wasteland for now. He didn’t even think about founding his own country.

Zhao Hai also knew that there were many things that compelled him to be what he is today. If there weren’t any outside factors, he may have even spent his days comfortably in the Space, along with his wives and family.

Laura and the others sat beside Zhao Hai, so they also heard the words of Robert and the others. They didn’t think that Zhao Hai would actually make his own country, they knew Zhao Hai’s disposition very much. Zhao Hai wasn’t an overly ambitious person, everything he does was only to done in order to improve the Buda Clan’s living conditions. And unlike people who were hell-bent on contending for the world’s supremacy, Zhao Hai was just a man who wanted to live comfortably. This point was already made clear to them long ago.

Seeing that Zhao Hai had not spoken for quite some time, Laura couldn’t help but talk to him, “Brother Hai, what are you thinking about?”

Zhao Hai turned his head to Laura and smiled bitterly, “I was thinking about Robert and the others’ words. I didn’t expect them to want me to establish my own country.”

Laura smiled, “In fact, the Iksa Family’s words are right. The Black Wasteland is very large and relatively closed off. It is entirely possible for us to establish our own country here. We talked about that before, do you remember?’

Zhao Hai smiled faintly, “Laura, you know how unambitious I am. What I said before was just an analogy. I really didn’t intend to make my own country.”

Laura smiled, “I know, but Brother Hai, you should know that the Iksa Family was only willing to wholeheartedly side with us because they believed in the Buda Clan’s potential. In their minds, the Buda Clan would certainly establish a country in the future, and it would become the most formidable country in the continent. Because of that, they decided to join us. Brother Hai, there would be a lot more people who would throw themselves under us in the future. But if we don’t achieve the goals that they imagined, they would be disappointed with us.”

Zhao Hai frowned, to be honest, he didn’t like this idea. However, what Laura said was right, a lot of people wanted to follow the Buda Clan because they believed in the clan’s potential. If he didn’t  express any ambition, he would be letting those people down.

Nobody wants to remain obscure, especially the Iksa Family, who were once a Great Family of the continent. They don’t want to hide forever. They will help the Buda Clan for one purpose, and that was to gain a higher title when the Buda Clan gets very strong. At that time, their reveal would be very spectacular.

After thinking about this, Zhao Hai couldn’t help but sigh, he nodded and said, “Right, we should think about this issue. In the future, the Buda Clan would have more and more members. It would come to a point where a Clan system wouldn’t be able to work. The only way forward is to establish our own country.”

Laura nodded, “But the country that we will build would be different from the others. It would be one that has our ideals and heart put into it.”

Zhao Hai smiled faintly and said, “Right, we should build one that would be our own. But this matter would have to wait, it still isn’t the right time. Moreover, establishing a nation needs huge investments. The Black Wasteland is still very empty, we still have a lot of things to do.”

Laura nodded, “Making a country isn’t easy. One problem that we have is the fact that Iron Mountain no longer produces Iron. We need to think of solutions for this thing.”

Zhao Hai nodded, “We do need to solve that. But we don’t need to be anxious about that right now. I think that the Iksa Family would also help us with this preparation.”

Laura nodded, then she turned her head to look at Megan and Lizzy and said, “Megan, Lizzy, what do you think?”

Megan and Lizzy looked at each other. To be honest, the two of them were very startled right now, they didn’t think that Zhao Hai would be discussing this matter. Establishing a country was a huge matter.

However, they still felt excited. They had never thought of establishing a country before. This idea was too crazy and too exciting!

Megan then said, “That’s good, great. We should make our own country. This idea is really good.”

Lizzy had the same sentiment, she couldn’t hide the excitement on her face as she nodded. Seeing their expressions, Zhao Hai couldn’t help but sigh inside, they didn’t know how difficult it was to make a country.

Zhao Hai slowly shook his head, he knew that this matter would be in the far too distant future. The Black Wasteland severely lacks people, making a country here would be impossible.

Zhao Hai changed the scene towards the Purcell Family. Then Zhao Hai became surprised because the Purcell Family didn’t meet inside their conference room, but in their living room instead. Elders weren’t the only people there, even Ruyen was participating as well as the other younger generations of the family.

The scene had been like this for quite a while. The room was in total chaos, the elders were talking while Evan had an ugly expression. It looks like the decision that they’d settled on wasn’t something that Zhao Hai would like.

Zhao Hai knit his brows, then he turned his head to Cai’er and said, “Cai’er, what did they just discuss? ”

Cai’er replied, “Evan proposed that the Purcell Family should leave the Purcell Duchy behind and go with the Buda Clan. He said that it would be the best for the family if they were to re-establish themselves in Golden Island. However, the elders didn’t agree. What they wanted was to reconcile with the Radiant Church.”

Zhao Hai frowned, Cai’er continued, “The elders stated that the Purcell Family came to this point because they had helped us, making them have a falling out with the Radiant Church. If they didn’t help us in the past, they the Radiant Church wouldn’t have targeted them, and the Purcell Family would have no problems.”

At this time, a voice was suddenly heard. It was a woman’s voice, when Zhao Hai and the others turned their attention back to the monitor, they saw that it was Ruyen.

Ruyan stood up and said loudly, “All of you shut up! Did you hear what you just said? Reconcile with the Radiant Church? How would you do that? Don’t you know how the Radiant Church does things? If we rely on the Radiant Church, the final result would be them annexing our Purcell Family. Is that what you people want to see? Are you really from the Purcell Family?”

After Ruyen talked, an elder coldly snorted and said, “Ruyen, I don’t think this is the place for you to talk. How can you be sure that the Radiant Church would annex our Purcell Family? And going to Golden Island? If we go there, we would be depending on the Buda Clan to survive, is that good? What? Do you also want to marry Zhao Hai? Stop dreaming, he’s now the Rosen Emperor’s son-in-law. He wouldn’t take a liking towards someone like you.”

The elder’s words made Ruyen pale, she was angry right now, “If Zhao Hai didn’t take care of the Radiant Church, we would have already been eliminated by Boris. But now, you wanted to rely on the enemy, you really have no courage. You are not worthy to be a person of the Purcell Family.”

Another elder talked, “Ruyen, speak cleanly. And who did you call an enemy? And how do you think we got this enemy? It’s because of Zhao Hai. If it weren’t because of Zhao Hai, then we wouldn’t be offending the Radiant Church. Then our Purcell Family wouldn’t have reached the point that we’re in today.”

Ruyen coldly snorted and said, “If it weren’t for Zhao Hai, would our Purcell Family survive from our previous food shortage? You remember how the food prices were supposed to inflate? Who do you think is behind all that? It’s Boris, he had always wanted to eliminate our Purcell Family since a long time ago. If it weren’t for Zhao Hai and Laura, then our Purcell Family would find it hard to survive that time. You fools, always living in your fantasies. Do you really expect the Radiant Church to help us? They just want an excuse to infiltrate our family and gain control. Even a fool can see it. But now you people really wanted this to happen, this is making me sad for the family.”

Zhao Hai stared at the fuming Ruyen. He didn’t expect Ruyen to take his side. But what she said was true, it seems like he had underestimated Ruyen, she’s actually not just a fragile vase.

Chapter 533: The Final Decision

Laura was similarly surprised that she said, “I didn’t think that Ruyen would have that side of her. When I saw her before, she seemed like a fragile little miss.”

Zhao Hai didn’t say anything and just quietly stared at the screen. After Ruyen’s speech, the elders immediately went to refute. In any case, the elders only wanted one thing, and that was to reconcile with the Radiant Church and not to depend on the Buda Clan.

Seeing this situation, Zhao Hai couldn’t help but sigh, “It looks like there has been no good result. It seems like the Purcell Family has finally come to an end.”

Just as Zhao Hai imagined, Evan wasn’t able to change the Elder Assembly’s final decision. When the elders and the others left, Ruyen remained and looked at her tired father, “Father, you should know that siding with the Radiant Church would mean the end of our Purcell Family. The Radiant Church has been doing well, they even have the Aksu Empire in their hands. However, this would also increase the vigilance of other nations. At this time, going to the Radiant Church’s side wouldn’t be a good idea.”

Evan sighed and said, “I also know about that, however, it’s useless. If the Elder’s Assembly is determined, even the Elder Origin Sword Saint wouldn’t be able to do anything about it. Alright, no need to talk about this. I’ll go talk to elder Origin Sword Saint about this. I’ll have him follow you and the younger generation to go towards Golden Island. You shall establish your branch of the Purcell Family there. No matter what happens in the Duchy, at the very least our Purcell Family can survive.”

Ruyen stared, she looked at Evan and said, “Father, isn’t this bad? We are still to young. Even if Elder Origin Sword Saint is with us, it would be very difficult for our family to recover again.”

Evan shook his head, “That’s the only thing we can do. No need to talk about this any longer, you go and leave.”

Ruyen couldn’t bear to look at Evan, so she turned around to leave. Evan sat alone in the room for quite some time. Then he sighed, stood up, and headed outside.

While looking at the screen, Zhao Hai knew that Evan would certainly approach Origin Sword Saint. The Purcell Family had reached a point between life and death. Seeing from the elders’ reactions, it seems like they had already been bought by the Radiant Church. The reason why the Radiant Church wasn’t able to fully infiltrate the Purcell Family was Origin Sword Saint. The prestige of Origin Sword Saint was vastly renowned in the continent. Even if the Radiant Church were to send 4 or 5 9th ranks, they still wouldn’t be confident in stopping Origin Sword Saint from escaping.

The Radiant Church had already lost so much 9th rank experts. If they were to lose more in the Purcell Duchy, then it would be impossible for them to move any more freely. Therefore, they chose to buy out the Purcell Family’s elders.

Zhao Hai turned his head to Laura and the others then said, “It looks like it can only be like this. Cai’er, pay attention to the state of the Purcell Family. After they are ready, tell me and I’ll go pick them up. Let’s go see Uncle Robert.” Laura and the others nodded, then they went back to Iron Mountain Fort along with Zhao Hai.

The sky has already turned dark, but Iron Mountain Fort still stayed bright. It was because Cai’er emitted a faint light to illuminate the building. Therefore, even if it was already dark, people can still be seen walking around the castle.

Zhao Hao and the others directly went to the part of the fort where the Iksa Family were staying. Since this place was an old castle, there aren’t a lot of courtyards inside. Zhao Hai can only divide an area for the family to live in.

Zhao Hai and the others arrived at the part of the castle before long. When they were seen by a person from the Iksa Family, they were immediately led towards Robert’s room.

While inside his room, Robert received the notification that Zhao Hai was waiting outside. The two spoke briefly before they entered the living room.

After having sat down, Zhao Hai looked at Robert and said, “Uncle Robert, have you become familiar in living here? Do you have any other needs? You can just send your requests to Grandpa Green.”

Robert smiled and said, “I’ve already been familiarized with the place. This place is good, in fact, it is very good. If I told other people about the state of Iron Mountain Fort, I think that nobody would believe me.”

Zhao Hai smiled and said, “That is good. I might get busy in the following days. I have already prepared to release your family’s demise to the entire continent, letting the people know about the Radiant Church’s ruthlessness. Uncle Robert, do you have any disagreements about this?”

Robert shook his head and said, “Why should I disagree? Go let the people in the continent know how terrible the Radiant Church is.”

Zhao Hai nodded, and said, “Rest assured, I wouldn’t make the Radiant Church have any better days. You should take a rest here in Iron Mountain Fort and get acquainted with what is happening here. If you want to go to Golden Island, then we need to wait until the situation outside calms down a bit. After that, I will have someone send you to the island.”

Robert shook his head and said, “Little Hai, no need. The family has already reached an agreement. Starting today, the Iksa Family would be a vassal of the Buda Clan. We are willing to help the clan in managing the Black Wasteland.”

Zhao Hai acted surprised as he stood up and said, “That’s fantastic. Thank you, Uncle Robert. Thank you so much. But I still hope to have some people in your family head to Golden Island and do business for your family. Or they can also help us manage the island. Do you agree?”

Robert looks at Zhao Hai and smiled faintly, “You don’t need to inquire me about this. We shall go send some of our members to do business as well as help you manage the island. In any case, Golden Island is after all a goose that lays golden eggs.”

Zhao Hai laughed and said, “Alright, then that matter is decided. But you still need to rest here for a few days. I’ve already arranged for your stay, you don’t need to worry about anything. Right, since you’re staying in Iron Mountain Fort, you need to get acquainted to the place. I’ll tell Grandpa Green tomorrow and have him take you for a walk around the fort so that you can learn as much as possible about the place.”

Robert nodded, “Alright, then I’ll be troubling Housekeeper Green.” Zhao Hai smiled and said, “It’s not much of a trouble. Uncle Robert, I’ll be leaving first. I have something to discuss with Grandpa Green.” Robert nodded and then escorted Zhao Hai out.

After Zhao Hai got outside, he immediately returned to the Space and went to Golden Island. He must go see Kun and ask about the letter that was handed over to him.

Golden Island was now very prosperous. A lot of merchants were passing in and out of the harbor. With the amount of arrivals coming to the island, they were even compelled to make a new harbor.

Golden Island’s tax rate was very low, and pirates were also coming here to trade, which in turn attracted merchants. This situation showed that Zhao Hai’s initial strategy was correct. This freeport did indeed become very popular.

Kun was reviewing some documents at this time. Although he had the help of the Markey Family, he was still very busy. With the amount of things needed to be done in the island, it was evident that they still lacked manpower.

Zhao Hai wasn’t polite, he directly opened the door and walked in. When Kun saw Zhao Hai walk in, he immediately placed his pen down and laughed, “Little Hai, you returned. You really make this old man smile. Why did you come, you want me to take a rest?”

Zhao Hai laughed and said, “Can anybody work harder than you? With how you work, nobody would believe you if you say that you’re old. Laura has a lot of things to do as well, don’t even mention me.”

Kun snorted and said, “Don’t you dare deceive me. What do you guys really do? Forget it, don’t tell me. But you can’t forget about my state here. There’s a serious shortage of manpower here. We need to solve it as soon as possible.”

Zhao Hai nodded and said, “Don’t worry, some people will come soon. I think you already know about the Iksa Family. Some of them will come to the island soon. You’ll be able to relax then.”

Kun released a breath of relief, “That’s good. I’ve been very exhausted these days. You might not know, but Golden Island now has more than 5 thousand shops. It’s already quite exhausting dealing with these shops. But there’s still the new roads that needed to be constructed, and there the new harbor as well. All of these thing really do make me tired.”

Zhao Hai smiled, he didn’t have anything to say about this matter. He can only continue, “Grandpa Kun, have you sent the letter to the Calci Family? This matter needs to be passed to the continent as soon as possible.”

Kun nodded and said, “I’ve already handed it over to the Calci Family, no need to worry about this. The Radiant Church had fully destroyed themselves this time. This information was enough to make all the Royals and Great Nobles hate them. It wouldn’t be too long before they collapse.”

Zhao Hai coldly snorted and said, “Not necessarily. Even if all that happened, the Radiant Church still had the Aksu Empire in their control. In the end, they can still preach inside the empire, that wouldn’t be necessarily bad for them. Even if the Nobles and commoners of the Aksu Empire objects in the future, the Church should have already acquired enough fanatics to not care about what happens.”

Kun nodded and said, “I really didn’t expect that the Aksu Empire would come under the control of the Radiant Church. The Church really has a lot of good methods. From what I can see with the Markey Family, if we hadn’t exterminated them, they would eventually fall into the Radiant Church’s hands.”

Zhao Hai sighed and said, “The Radiant Church uses religion as a toll to control the people little by little. People would think that it was harmless at first, but when they finally notice, it would have already been too late.”

Kun nodded and said, “How about the Purcell Duchy, how is the situation there? Did the Beastmen already arrive? When will they attack?”

Zhao Hai shook his head and said, “It seems like the Purcell Family’s elders were already bought out. They fully resisted the idea of asking the Buda Clan for help. As for the Beastmen, I really don’t have any information. But I think it wouldn’t take a long time. After all, the Prairie is already out of food.”

Kun nodded then he said, “Right, is there any way to pull some people from the Purcell Family?”

Chapter 534: Seeing Marriott

Zhao Hai shook his head and said, “That would be very difficult. Now that the Aksu Empire is under the control of the Radiant Church, I suspect that they already have people inside the Purcell Family. If we were to get some of them, then it would be very likely that we would get some of the Radiant Church’s people as well.”

Kun frowned and said, “What should we do? Both the Golden Island and Black Wasteland is in badly need of people. If we miss this opportunity, where can we get people?”

Zhao Hai smiled faintly and said, “Grandpa Kun, don’t forget that war is approaching. In addition to the amount of dead, the number of slaves would increase as well. Their prices would be cheap because they aren’t trained. Additionally, I can also turn the deceased into undead and have them take command of the people in the wasteland. This should somewhat solve our problem with manpower.”

Kun sighed and said, “It looks like we can only do it like this. You have ordered 100 thousand of slaves before, but since the situation has become tense, I think the slave trader wouldn’t be able to send them any sooner.”

Zhao Hai nodded, “You don’t need to worry about this too much. After waiting for the war to settle, Brother Wales would be delivering 100 thousand slaves over to me. Moreover, I can also exchange some more slaves from the other Beastmen tribes. With those slaves, I think Black Wasteland would have no problems with numbers.”

Kun nodded, “I hope that happens. Right, Little Hai, a couple of days ago, a Slave Merchant approached me. He wants to make a shop in the island. What do you think?”

Kun knew that Zhao Hai didn’t have any favorable impressions towards Slave Merchants. Therefore, he wanted to ask Zhao Hai if he agrees. Zhao Hai thought for a moment before saying, “I agree. In any case, even if they don’t have a shop here, we still need to buy some slaves. If they have shops here, then that would make our lives much easier.”

Kun nodded, “Alright, I’ll go send the approval. What are you planning to do next? Will you go back home or would you visit the Purcell Duchy?”

Zhao Hai replied, “There aren’t a lot of matters to take care of back at home. I don’t need to take personal command as well. On the other hand, I needed to pay careful attention towards the Purcell Duchy. The family has prepared to have Origin Sword Saint escort their younger generation to come to Golden Island. I still need to receive them while at the same time see how the Purcell Family develops and understand the Radiant Church’s next move. The church is our biggest enemy, we have to pay close attention.”

Kun nodded, he also thinks that what Zhao Hai said was right. But he still frowned and said, “I think monitoring them from the Space is enough, no need to personally go there. When the war between Humans and Beastmen comes, do not participate. If you do so, trading with the Beastmen would be more difficult in the future.”

Zhao Hai nodded, “I will not only refrain from helping the Humans, I would even help the Beastmen instead. Since the Aksu Empire had become the Radiant Church’s, they certainly wouldn’t let their territory get ravaged by the Beastmen. Since it was definite that the Church would move, I don’t want the Beastmen to suffer a lot. The Beastmen hold grudges very seriously, if they lost too much, then I’m afraid they would wage war every year. And I can’t let the Radiant Church have that.”

Kun knit his brows, then he sighed. He didn’t say anything, to be honest, since he was a native to the Ark Continent, he was in disagreement with Zhao Hai’s method. Helping another race to deal with one’s own was something that he didn’t approve of.

However, he had to recognize that the Radiant Church was the Buda Clan’s greatest enemy while Zhao Hai was very close friends with the Beastmen. Considering the Buda Clan’s future, it was a no brainer that Zhao Hai would help the Beastmen.

Zhao Hai also knew about Kun’s thoughts. However, in Zhao Hai’s eyes, the Beastmen were more lovable than the Humans. This wasn’t Earth, Zhao Hai didn’t need to worry about any ethnic differences here. In Zhao Hai’s mind, his true race were the Chinese back on Earth. To him, the Humans in Ark Continent were just another intelligent race. Therefore, supporting the Beastmen instead of the Humans didn’t give him even a bit of pressure.

Zhao Hai wanted to continue the topic, he looked at Kun and said, “Grandpa Kun, after the Calci Family and the Rosen Empire passes the information about the Iksa Family, you should also use the Markey Family to spread it around. The continent must know about it in the shortest period of time.”

Kun nodded, “Rest assured, I have this matter prepared already. Right, Little Hai, you should go find the people from the Shelley Family. The Shelley Family is the continent’s biggest Hotel businessmen. Their information network had penetrated the entire continent. Even with the suppression of the Radiant Church, their businesses were still able to thrive. So it shouldn’t be a problem for them to pass this information over. This would certainly be achieving twice the result with half the effort.”

Zhao Hai thought for a moment before nodding, “Alright, I’ll go head to the hotel.” There was now a Shelley Hotel in Golden Island, and it was currently the highest structure ever built. The Architecture was also top notch. And naturally, its business was doing very well.

Most importantly, Zhao Hai came to know that the manager of this hotel was Marriott, the manager of Sky Water City’s Shelley Hotel. When Golden Island became open for business, he immediately arrived and became the hotel branch’s manager.

Zhao Hai’s business with the Shelley Hotel had been going on all these time. The Fire Fishes, the vegetables and the Milk Wine had become the hotel’s selling point. Therefore, it was already assure that the hotel would help Zhao Hai.

Although the Radiant Church had been suppressing the hotel, this didn’t affect its business too much. From the years of doing business in the continent, the family had made various dealings with Great Clans and Royal Families. They used money and benefit to weave their large net, therefore, they weren’t afraid of the Radiant Church’s attack.

On the contrary, thanks to the Haven products, the hotel’s business had been going better than before. The suppression of the Radiant Church was only a superficial thing to them.

The reason why Lionheart was able to prevail while dealing with the Shelley Family was because he was in the Rosen Empire and was supported by the Rosen Royal Clan. Otherwise, Lionheart might have already been dealt with a long time ago.

The Shelley Family was extremely good in doing business. Just considering business prowess, they were a lot stronger compared to the Markey Family. The only reason why the Markey Family was able to rise faster was because they used shady methods. They would marry into some Merchant Family, establishing ties with them, and then had all of their successors killed off. This would essentially make all of that family’s assets belong to the Markey Family. It can be said that compared to the Shelley Family, the Markey Family were using despicable methods to gain wealth. But in terms of talent, they were way behind compared to the Shelley Family.

It was because of these reasons why Zhao Hai was able to extinguish the Markey Family in one fell swoop, this method cannot be used against the Shelley Family.

After many years of spreading out, nobody knew the exact number of the Shelley Family’s members. How about the experts of the family? Nobody knows. Additionally, there were a lot of people who had been helped by the Shelley Family. If people were to really deal with the Shelley Family, the family can just invite countless experts to deal with the enemy.

All of this was because of one rule made by the Shelley Family. No matter who it was, once they enter the hotel, the hotel would completely guarantee the safety of that person. Once the person leaves the hotel, the hotel wouldn’t be in charge anymore.

This rule might look like nothing. But if someone were to offend a person and was then chased, he can always enter the Shelley Hotel and feel assured that the hotel would protect him. Once this person manages to get away, they would definitely be grateful towards the Shelley Family.

If the person was an ordinary man, then it might not be a big deal. However, what if this person was an expert? What if he becomes strong later on? Then he would definitely want to repay the hotel. This way, the Shelley Hotel had amasses quite a number of people who would come and help them. Additionally, even if these people wanted to repay, the hotel might not even agree. They might also use their power to help the person to improve. This way, even if the Shelley Family had limited strength, nobody can really gauge how big their backing was.

But the real reason why the Shelley Family was able to survive all these years was their choice to handle their matters in a very low-key manner. Generally, they wouldn’t participate in any fights or struggles, minimizing the amount of enemies that they would acquire while making friends everywhere.

Zhao Hai was sitting in his carriage as it headed towards the Shelley Hotel. Although it was already evening, the hotel was still brilliantly illuminated. The place was very busy, it quickly became a landmark on Golden Island.

The carriage that Zhao Hai was using right now was a carriage commonly used in the island. It wasn’t very beautiful, compared to the other carriages on the island, it was a bit bad.

Zhao Hai arrived at the front door of the hotel and then went down from his carriage along with Shun. Shue stayed at the naval base while Laura and the others simply didn’t come.

As soon as Zhao Hai’s carriage arrived, a person from the hotel immediately came and bowed to Zhao Hai, “The hotel welcomes the arrival of Mister. I ask Mister to come with me.” Zhao Hai nodded and then walked towards the hotel.

Inside the hotel’s hall were a lot of people. There were groups of two of three standing there and chatting. After the attendant guided Zhao Hai in, he immediately asked, “Does Mister want a reservation or a meal?”

Zhao Hai shook his head and said, “I’m here to see Manager Marriott. Is he in?”

The attendant stared, one must know that Marriott held great influence in this hotel. And since the Shelley Family and the Buda clan were in good terms, the hotel was extremely cared for by the Buda Clan. There were a lot of people who approached Marriott and asked him to help them say a few good words to Zhao Hai for them.

However, Marriott was a man of principle, so he didn’t help those people and decided to live in private. He would generally decline visitors. Any ordinary person cannot even see him. One should make an appointment first if one wanted to meet him.

The attendant didn’t recognize Zhao Hai. So when he heard that Zhao Hai wanted to see Marriott, he froze. This was because everybody who wanted to see Marriott would need to make an appointment first. Wanting to see Marriott through the attendants was a useless method.

However, the attendant managed to recover immediately as he said, “Sir, the manager is extremely busy. If mister wants to meet the manger, mister needs to file for an appointment. If you have no appointment, it would be very difficult to see the manager.”

Zhao Hai smiled and said, “It doesn’t matter if he is busy. Just go tell him that Zhao Hai wants to see him. I’m sure he can find time to meet me.”

Zhao Hai’s remark not only silenced the attendant, it silenced the entire hall as well. It must be said that in Golden Island, it was normal if people didn’t know who the Rosen Emperor was. However, not knowing Zhao Hai was definitely impossible.

Therefore, everybody present knew who Zhao Hai was. When they heard Zhao Hai say his name, all of them looked at him with awe. The attendant even appeared very excited, he immediately replied, “Alright, I’ll go call the manager right away.” Then he ran towards the offices.

After the attendant ran away, a humming sound was heard as the people in the hall were talking with one another. Some of them even wanted to approach Zhao Hai, but they were afraid of being disrespectful. Therefore, these people just stayed where they are and took occasional glances at Zhao Hai.

Seeing the actions of these people, Zhao Hai immediately gave a short bow and said, “Everyone, since I have some matters to discuss with Manager Marriott today, I won’t be able to accomodate any of you. But in the future, I hope we can have a meal together.”

The people present immediately returned the salute. At this time, Marriott walked out of his office and then went towards Zhao Hai and bowed to Zhao Hai, “Sir Marquis has arrived. I apologize for not being able to welcome you.”

Zhao Hai laughed and said, “I must say, Brother Marriott, you’re being overly polite. What relationship do we have, why do you need to say all these fancy greetings? Go, go, let’s go and have a drink. I wanted to drink so badly.”

Marriott laughed and said, “Alright, then come in.” Then he led Zhao Hai into his office.

After Zhao Hai entered the office, a nearby Noble immediately turned to his friend and said, “That was Zhao Hai Buda? The Buda Clan’s Patriarch? That’s what he looks like? I heard that he is a God of Slaughter, how can he be so friendly?”

His friend smiled and said, “You don’t know, but I heard that Zhao Hai is very special. He is only ruthless to his enemies while he is extremely kind to his friends. You can see it from Marriott, he is only a manager of the hotel, but since Marquis Zhao Hai used to know him, the Marquis acted very friendly when they chat with each other.”

The Noble nodded, then his face expressed his regret, “Why didn’t I get to know him before he became a Marquis, who knows where I could have been right now.”

His friend laughed and said, “Continue dreaming…..”

Chapter 535: Overly Popular Bread Fruit

Zhao Hai and Marriott entered inside Marriott’s personal reception area. Although this hotel had just finished being constructed, this reception area was still luxuriously decorated, it even looked much better than back in Sky Water City.

After they sat down, Marriott looked at Zhao Hai and smiled, “Little Hai, why’d you find time to see me today? Do you need something?”

Zhao Hai smiled faintly and said, “I want your Shelly Family’s help in a matter.”

Marriott smiled, “Don’t be polite, just tell me.”

Zhao Hai laughed and then said, “Haha, alright, take a look at this first.” Then he handed a stack of papers over to Marriott. The stack contained the events that happened to the Iksa Family. Every detail was carefully written in those papers, this was the thing that Zhao Hai had prepared before.

Marriott received the stack of papers and then carefully read them. Marriott was a very calm and smart man, he grew up in the Shelley Family since he was a child, so he had certain understandings about different struggles in the continent. However, what the Radiant Church did was really quite excessive even to him.

Although only the Iksa Family’s matter was written on the stack of papers, Marriott had already speculated that there was a problem with the Aksu Empire. Otherwise, such a situation wouldn’t have happened. If this was truly the case, the problem was much bigger than he had imagined.

After some time, Marriott placed the papers down and then looked at Zhao Hai, “Is this real? How did the Aksu Empire respond?”

Zhao Hai sighed and said, “Of course it’s true, the Iksa Family is now with me and in a very safe place. The Aksu Empire didn’t have any reactions to what happened. Not only did they not respond, they still went on and dealt with the Purcell Family. The elders of the Purcell Family have now been bought out, restraining the Purcell Family from cooperating with my Buda Clan. Because of this, I suspect that the Aksu Empire had now come into the control of the Radiant Church.”

The conclusion that Zhao Hai reached was the same as the one that Marriott had in mind. Therefore, Marriott nodded, he agreed with what Zhao Hai said.

Then Marriott looked at Zhao Hai and said, “What do you think about this?”

Zhao Hai snorted and said, “The Radiant Church had been too rampant. They actually dared to control a big Empire. Later on, I’m prepared to hand this information over to father-in-law, making him spread the message to the entire continent. The Markey Family shall help with this as well. So I hope the Shelley Family can also aid me in releasing this information. We need to let the continent know what kind of organization the Radiant Church really is.”

When Marriott heard Zhao Hai, his eyes turned bright and then deeply looked into Zhao Hai’s eyes, “Alright, Little Hai, we’ll be giving you a hand.”

The reason why Marriott agreed immediately was because the Radiant Church was also suppressing the Shelley Family quite recently. Even if the family had withstood and was not afraid of the Radiant Church, they cannot deal with the Radiant Church just like how they did with Grand Duke Lionheart.

Zhao Hai laughed and said, “Alright, then that matter is settled. However, don’t release the information immediately. When it’s time, I’ll have Grandpa Kun inform you.”

Marriott nodded, “Then that’s settled. Right, do you want to stay and have a couple of drinks?”

Zhao Hai shook his head and said, “I can’t, I still have some other things to do today. I need to head back and deal with those. Moreover, I’ll be leaving Golden Island immediately.”

Marriott nodded, “alright, then I won’t stop you. But the next time that you come here, you must drink a couple of glasses with me.” Zhao Hai nodded with a smile, then turned around to leave. Marriott escorted Zhao Hai to his carriage before returning back to the hotel.

After entering the hotel and greeting the guests, Marriott returned to his own room and wrote a long letter regarding the Iksa Family as well as Zhao Hai’s request. He then had it sent to the Shelley Family’s headquarters, he wanted to know the family’s thoughts on this matter.

Marriott has promised Zhao Hai that he’d help, so he wouldn’t renege on his words. Moreover, he also has the authority to make such a decision. But he still need to inform the family about this matter, this still needed to be discussed.

The Shelley Family was the Buda Clan’s ally, it wasn’t a problem if they wanted to help. However, there are many ways to lend a hand, the problem was how to do so.

When Zhao Hai returned to the naval base, he immediately went to the Space to have a rest. Nothing new happened in the Purcell Duchy, Ruyen and the others were also not yet ready.

Honestly, Zhao Hai didn’t want to make contact with Ruyen. First, it was because of the previous events. He feels very embarrassed if they were to meet. The second was because Ruyen had annoyed him before, he didn’t want that event to be repeated in the future.

The next day, Zhao Hai silently paid attention to the Purcell Family. At the same time, he was also observing the events back in the Beastman Prairie.

The Prairie was now fully prepared. They needed to attack the humans no matter how much they had prepared. Because of the food shortage, they needed to go into action, therefore, they didn’t have the time to store up some rations. The only thing that they can do was bring along some Argali while they advanced.

Argalis weren’t quick, so they affected the march of the Beastmen. Moreover, the Argalis would go ill once they enter Human territories. It was because of this reason why Beastmen would generally prefer to have rations.

But unfortunately, they didn’t have the time to prepare rations, they simply didn’t have time.

In this fight, each race prepared their own food and weapons. Then everybody arrived at a certain place before they set out in order to pillage the human territory.

It was because of this solidarity that the Beastmen weren’t afraid of fighting all out. Naturally, if their losses were too high, they would retreat. After all, a race with small numbers would generally be swallowed up.

Seeing how prepared the Beastmen were, Zhao Hai reckoned that it would take less than a month before they arrived at the border of the Purcell Duchy. At that time, the war would truly begin.

He also looked at Ah Tai and the others. Ah Tai’s current situation was very good. The Beastmen knew that the shop had close relations with the Wolf, Bear, Dog, and Cow-headed races. Therefore, nobody went to the shop just to cause some trouble.

And there was also one thing that made Ah Tai very popular, it was the Bread Fruit. In this war, the other tribes’ food can only be Argali. It was because it was the most convenient thing they could bring at current time.

However, the Prairie Wolf Tribe, Black Bear Tribe, Dog-headed Race, and the Cow-headed Race had some Bread Fruit. The Bread Fruit was extremely convenient. One could immediately eat it as soon as it was opened, it didn’t even need cooking.

It was the first time that the other Beastmen saw such a fruit, this made them jealous. And when they heard that this fruit was provided by Magic Lily Shop, all of them became impolite, especially the huge Warring Clans, they immediately went to purchase some from Ah Tai.

Among them were the Tiger Clan that Ah Tai intended to contact. There were also a lot of tribes inside the Tiger-headed Race. The one that Ah Tai wanted to come in contact with were the Bali Tiger Tribe.[1]

The Bali Tigers weren’t the biggest tribe in the Tiger-headed Race. But they were deemed to be the most attractive among them. Their appearance also had the general tiger stripes, but the way the stripes were arranged made them very beautiful.

But they should not be underestimated just because they were attractive, their fighting strength wasn’t weak at all. Among the Tiger-headed race, they can me ranked along the middle parts.

Because Ah Tai had prior inquiries with the Bali Tigers, they were the first ones who had gotten some Bread Fruit.

For the Beastmen, this Bread Fruit became very important in this war. The fruit was both convenient and can last a long time. It was not only their convenience that attracted the Beastmen, the most important thing was that the fruits weren’t Argali. Argalis were the most treasured commodity of the Beastmen, so they want to save them as much as possible.

The reason why the Beastmen didn’t bring some Bamboo Rice was because it was very inconvenient. Not only were they hard to bring, they don’t last long either. More importantly, with how much the Beastmen eat, they would need to bring large amounts of pots in order to cook the rice. This would further hinder their advance.

On the other hand, the Bread Fruit can be eaten immediately after it was opened. It expands as well, making one fruit enough for one Beastman. For races with small appetites like the Wolf-headed race, one fruit could sustain two people. Therefore, the Bread Fruit became the Beastmen’s number one choice for war rations.

Ah Tai didn’t become polite, Zhao Hai had instructed him to use this opportunity to establish his reputation. But he wasn’t prepared to sell too much Bread Fruit. If the Beastmen approached him, he would tell them that Zhao Hai only left him no more than 300 million jin of Bread Fruit.

300 million jin might sound like a lot. But for the entire Beastman Race, it was just akin to pouring a cup of water towards a burning carriage, it was utterly insufficient.

Ah Tai was also smart, he directly asked the Black Bears to come forward and be the ones to inform all of the Beastmen about his meager 300 million jin supply of Bread Fruit. If they wanted to buy some, they needed to divide the amount among themselves.

The Beastmen didn’t embarrass Ah Tai. Moreover, even if the Beastmen always get in disagreement with each other, they were unnaturally in one mind when it came to war. Therefore, the big Warring Clans acquiesced and divided the Bread Fruits among themselves.

Later on, they had found out that the Prairie Wolves had the most supply of Bread Fruit. This made them force the Prairie Wolves to sell some their fruits and trade them for Argali.

The Wolves agreed to this arrangement, they had bought the Bread Fruits for gold, but it was now exchanged for Argali. For the Prairie Wolves, this trade was very cost-effective. In normal times, if they took some gold to other Beastmen to trade for Argali, they would be seen as idiots. Therefore, the Wolves didn’t hesitate and agreed immediately. They left some Bread Fruits for themselves and then sold the other ones.

* * *

It’s stated in the raws as Li Tiger. But I don’t know what those were, so I went with the closest sounding one.

Chapter 536: Purcell Family’s Tragedy

The Prairie Wolves weren’t wealthy, so now that an opportunity has arrived, they certainly wouldn’t let it go. At this time, they were actually feeling regretful. They regretted that they turned down the prior 1 billion jin of Bread Fruit that Zhao Hai intended to give them. When they heard that they were about to head to war, they kept the 300 million jin and declined the remaining amount. If they knew that this situation would happen, they wouldn’t have declined the 1 billion jin.

But it was always too late to regret, they can only settle on their gains this time. On the other hand, the one who gained greatly was Ah Tai. Not only did he establish a relationship with the Bali Tigers, he also managed to promote the Bread Fruit. In the future, the fruit would certainly become popular in the Prairie.

Zhao Hai also knew about this development. Although he had countless amounts of Bread Fruit in the Space, he wasn’t planning to take those out right now. If he gave them the Bread Fruit, the Beastmen would stop attacking the Human territories. Zhao Hai wanted the Beastmen to wage war right now.

It wasn’t because Zhao Hai hated them, it was because he doesn’t want to wipe the buttocks of the Radiant Church. This incident was caused by the Radiant Church, so even if a lot of civilians were to die, Zhao Hai wanted the Radiant Church to remember this lesson for a long time.

The Radiant Church was his enemy, and Zhao Hai wasn’t a saint either, so he certainly wouldn’t help the Radiant Church. This war, for him, was a very good thing.

Since there weren’t any problems with the Beastmen, Zhao Hai shifted his attention to the Purcell Duchy. It wasn’t only the Purcell Family that he was looking at, he also focused on the other people in the Duchy. He wanted to see what the Radiant Church would do. And he also wanted to see which ones were the spies of the Radiant Church.

The Space’s functions were now quite formidable. Since he already had the map of the entire continent, it was natural that he also had the map of the entire Purcell Duchy. Because of this, it was very easy for him to monitor the Duchy.

After two days of surveillance, Zhao Hai finally found some people of the Church. These people were experts, but they weren’t 9th ranks. 9th rank experts aren’t cabbages that can just be plucked, the Radiant Church had painstakingly trained them for years, so they cannot just send casually send them.

Among the people that were sent, there were some 8th ranks mixed in. The majority of them were 7th and 6th ranks, which numbered around 2 thousand. The 8th ranks, on the other hand, only amounted to about 500. One could see the Radiant Church’s strength just from this exhibition.

Besides these people, there were also armies of the families surrounding the Purcell Duchy. As soon as the Purcell Family falls, they would immediately come and occupy the Duchy.

Seeing this situation, Zhao Hai understood that the Aksu Empire definitely wouldn’t let the Purcell Family off. The family would have to be sacrificed to the Beastmen, completely eliminating the Purcell surname from the continent.

After thinking about this point, Zhao Hai cannot help but have a taunting smile on his face. His ridicule was of course meant for the elders of the Purcell Family. For a meagre benefit, they took their entire family to its demise.

Fortunately for the Purcell Family, they had two smart members. At the very least, Evan and Ruyen’s minds were in the right place. Zhao Hai also knew that these elders might have not acted out all for the sake of benefits. They might have also thought about the Purcell Family. However, they didn’t really understand the Radiant Church, therefore they managed to make this mistake.

The Purcell Family elders might be selfish, but they weren’t fools. They knew that they only had their current power because of the Purcell Family. If the Purcell Family were to vanish, then they would become nothing.

The reason why they rejected the idea of moving to Golden Island was because they received some promises and benefits from the Radiant Church. At the same time, they were also afraid of losing their current status.

If the Purcell Family were to move to Golden Island, the place was the Buda Clan’s domain and wasn’t the Purcell Family’s. When they arrive there, they wouldn’t be able to have the influence that they had in the Purcell Duchy. Because of this, they went all out in opposing to move to Golden Island. They had held into the hope that the Purcell Family might be able to keep the Purcell Duchy.

Another two days later, Zhao Hai saw that Ruyen and the others have prepared themselves. So he immediately left the Space and flashed to the Purcell Duchy. There were now a lot of commoners who had left and some were still on the process of leaving. The Purcell Duchy were now having food problems, if they didn’t leave, they would die of starvation.

But these commoners didn’t have any resentment towards the Purcell Family. The family had always been good to them, the prices in the Duchy weren’t high, the taxes were kept low, and most importantly, cases of them bullying the commoners were very rare. Also, their schools were cheap as well, there were commoners who had their children attend these schools. This made the Purcell Family very popular among the commoners.

Although these commoners didn’t know about high-level affairs, they can still roughly guess that the Aksu Empire had already given up on the Purcell Duchy. Which made the commoners even more dissatisfied towards the Empire.

The reason for that was Zhao Hai’s continual propaganda. He let the people of the Aksu Empire know that the Beastman’s attack to the the human lands this time was caused by the Radiant Church.

Now that the Beastmen were coming, the Aksu Empire actually didn’t send any troops to support the Purcell Duchy, this made the commoners very discontented of the Empire.

Then there was another news that came to the Purcell Duchy. It stated that the Radiant Church had become honored guests in the Royal Capital. The nobles were respectful to them, even the Emperor was very polite when interacting with them.

This information was just like a blasting fuse, making all of the Purcell Duchy commoners furious towards the Aksu Empire’s Royal Clan. It was already known that the Beastman attack was caused by the church, but they actually didn’t do anything about it. Instead, they even accepted the church as honored guests. They didn’t even send some reinforcements to the Duchy, stating their neglectful stance towards the commoners.

At this time, the Purcell Family had also taken action. They sent some people from the family and organized the commoners in leaving the Duchy. This was because the Duchy would soon become a battlefield.

These commoners weren’t willing to leave, however, the Purcell Family urged them to. The Purcell Family knew that they don’t have the ability to keep these commoners safe. They couldn’t even guarantee the safety of their own family, so how could they guarantee the safety of these commoners.

The commoners understood as well that the Purcell Family won’t provide any help even if they stayed. Some of them had friends and families in other places, so they chose to go there. For those who didn’t have both friends and families, they still needed to leave the Duchy.

When Zhao Hai arrived at Casa City, there weren’t a lot of people left inside. Zhao Hai didn’t care about any of these and just took his carriage towards the Grand Duke’s Mansion.

Zhao Hai already expected the commoners to leave, but he still paid attention to them. When the commoners were leaving, the Radiant Church didn’t act too hard on them. This may be because the Church knew that their current actions were already excessive. If they were to act hard on these commoners, the other commoners of the Aksu Empire might feel discontented with them.

Seeing that these commoners were safe, Zhao Hai felt relieved. Although he wanted these commoners to go to the Black Wasteland, he understood that this situation wasn’t realistic.

When Zhao Hai’s carriage entered the back gates of the Mansion, he saw Evan already waiting for him there. Even was now used to the mysterious appearance and disappearance of Zhao Hai.

He had sent people in Casa City to look for Zhao Hai, only to know that Zhao Hai wasn’t inside the city. But when Zhao Hai’s carriage heads to the mansion, the guards at the city gates were always not aware of his arrival, this fact made Evan very confused.

Most importantly, Zhao Hai always came at the right time. With a slightest bit of trouble, Zhao Hai would appear. Like this time, they had just finished preparing and haven’t informed Zhao Hai yet, but he actually came to the mansion.

After inviting Zhao Hai to sit down, Evan looked at Zhao Hai and said, “Little Hai, since you came, I think you already know that we are ready.”

Zhao Hai nodded, “I do, but not only that. I also must tell you that the Radiant Church had sent 2000 thousand experts as well as 500 8th ranks. At the same time, there were also armies on the surrounding borders of the Purcell Duchy. All of them are waiting for the Purcell Family to fall before they charge and secure the territory.”

Evan made a ridiculing smiled and said, “I’ve already guessed this for a long time. Those guys surely wouldn’t let us go. It is a pity that the people in our family are still living in their fantasies. But fortunately for us, Elder Sword Saint agreed to my opinion. He will be bringing Ruyen and the others to follow you. Later on, I’ll have to depend on you to look after Ruyen.”

Zhao Hai nodded, “Rest assured, I shall looked after them. If there’s an opportunity later on, I shall help them regain the Purcell Family’s status.”

Evan let out a long breath and then said, “I’ll be depending on you. If you think that they’re worth helping, then help them. If they’re not, then as long as you let them live a happy life, I would be able to rest assured.”

Zhao Hai looked at Evan and then said, “Uncle Evan, you should come as well. If you’re present, I believe that the Purcell Family would reappear much more beautifully.”

Evan shook his head and said, “That’s a bad idea. Everybody can leave, but not me. I am the Purcell Family’s Patriarch. If I leave, then the Purcell Family would certainly come to its end. I’d rather die in battle here. I will not leave.”

Zhao Hai sighed, he knew that any more urging would be useless, Evan was adamant on staying.

Chapter 537: Final Request

Evan has his own pride, Zhao Hai understood this, he had his own pride as well. Therefore, he didn’t say anything else after Evan expressed his intention to stay. The only thing he could do right now was to look after Ruyen.

Seeing that Zhao Hai didn’t say anything, Evan knew that Zhao Hai had understood him. Then Evan looked at Zhao Hai and said, “Little Hai, I want you to promise me one thing.”

Zhao Hai looked at Evan, then he couldn’t help but sigh inwardly. He can probably guess what Evan was about to say. But this request would place Zhao Hai in an awkward situation.

Looking at Zhao Hai’s frown, Evan knew that Zhao Hai wouldn’t immediately agree. He couldn’t help but sigh and said, “Little Hai, Uncle is begging you. This would be my last request.”

Zhao Hai knew that Evan was already thinking that he would die. Even if Evan wasn’t killed by the Beastmen, the Radiant Church would still not let him off. The Radiant Church knew about his relationship with Zhao Hai. The church might let the other insignificant members of the Purcell Family go, but they definitely wouldn’t spare Evan. Another reason was because Evan was the Purcell Family’s Patriarch and was in total opposition of the Radiant Church, his existence would make the church’s plans to control the Purcell Family very hard.

Zhao Hai sighed, then he looked at Evan and said, “Uncle, tell me, I’ll listen to it.”

Evan looked at Zhao Hai and said, “You should have already guessed it. I want you to marry Ruyen. Little Hai, marrying Ruyen is not only for her sake, but also to my Purcell Family. After this event, the family would surely decline. These people are still too young, if you don’t have a connection with them, it would be very hard to let them follow you. I will pass the position of Patriarch to Ruyen so that they would listen to your words. I believe that under your leadership, the Purcell Family would grow much better.”

Zhao Hai smiled bitterly, he already expected Evan’s request. He was engaged with Ruyen before, then when the Buda Clan met their misfortune, Ruyen wanted to break their engagement. And adding on to Ruyen’s reputation, Zhao Hai has no reason to marry Ruyen. His current identity was now beyond Ruyen’s level.

However, he had no other way but to consider Evan’s request. Evan already expects to be killed, he already knew that he would die. With how Evan helped their family in the past, Zhao Hai couldn’t just decline his request.

Evan looked at Zhao Hai’s reaction, he was afraid that Zhao Hai would decline. He didn’t lie, in fact, he only wanted Ruyen to marry Zhao Hai. It didn’t matter what happens to their relationship in the future. As long as this connection exists, people would still give the Purcell Family a little bit of face.

And as he said, the people who would follow Ruyen were the younger elite generation of the Purcell Family. But they were still too young and full of vigor. With the disaster of the Purcell Family, those youths would certainly panic. Even if Ruyen had the title of Patriarch, it wasn’t certain that they would follow her. But it would become a completely different matter if Zhao Hai was present.

Who was Zhao Hai? He’s the Buda Clan’s Patriarch, the son-in-law of both the Calci Family as well as the Rosen Emperor, he’s also the lord of Golden Island, and was deemed as one of the most powerful Patriarchs in the continent. These statuses were enough to make one shake upon meeting him. As long as the Purcell Family establishes a connection with him, the family would have hope for the future.

In fact, it wasn’t only Zhao Hai who can safeguard the family’s future. There’s one other person who can, and it’s Origin Sword Saint. He’s a 9th rank expert, as long as he appears, people will certainly behave.

However, Origin Sword Saint has his own matter to take care of, so he couldn’t always take charge. In fact, Evan also had a small worry about Origin Sword Saint. The Saint wasn’t young anymore, nobody knew how long he has left to live. If he died, and the Purcell Family wasn’t able to produce another 9th rank, then the family would be over. They would never recover in the future.

If Ruyen gets married to Zhao Hai, everything would be different. The Buda Clan had more than one 9th rank expert under their wing, everyone in the continent knew this. If the Buda Clan doesn’t fall, then even if Origin Sword Saint died, the Purcell family wouldn’t be afraid of anything with the Buda Clan as its backer.

Zhao Hai thought for quite some time, when Evan was about to open his mouth, he said, “Uncle Evan, I can’t promise this to you right away. You should know that I’m already married right now. I still need to discuss this with my wives as well as with Grandpa Green. And just like you, I don’t only represent myself, but the Buda Clan as well.”

When he heard Zhao Hai, Evan can only sigh. Although he felt down, he knew that he cannot force Zhao Hai about this right now.

Evan nodded, “Alright, please consider this matter slowly. Ruyen and the others are now prepared. You take them away whenever you want.”

Zhao Hai nodded and said, “I can take them away right now. In fact, I already have my Spatial Magic prepared. I can deliver them to Golden Island at the shortest amount of time. This is why I can still appear in Casa City even if you can’t find me.”

Evan nodded, he already guessed something in line with this. He then said, “When they arrive at Golden Island, you must take care of them. I have given the majority of the Purcell Family’s riches to Ruyen. I hope they can live even a little bit better.”

Zhao Hai nodded, he didn’t say anything more and just stood up. Evan stood as well and then the two headed outside silently. Before long, the two of them arrived at a remote courtyard in the mansion. Even if this courtyard was isolated, its perimeter was heavily guarded.

When he entered the courtyard, Zhao Hai saw Ruyen. Ruyen was standing inside the courtyard and stared at the city’s walls. He didn’t know what she was thinking about, but Zhao Hai can see the sadness in Ruyen’s eyes.

After hearing the sounds of footsteps, Ruyen immediately turned her head and saw Evan and Zhao Hai coming in. For a moment, Ruyen’s eyes flashed a hint of desolateness.

Ruyen once hated her father. In her mind, her father was incompetent. However, her father actually managed to use an opportunity and snatched the power of Patriarch. Even if she was regretful, she still tried her hardest. Now, some important tasks were even handed over to her.

Zhao Hai, who had changed his name, was also one of the people who she disliked the most. So in order to break their engagement, she even gambled her own reputation, and then succeeded in the end. However, Zhao Hai has now become the Patriarch of one of the most powerful family in the continent. Moreover, he also has gained beautiful wives as well as a Noble status much higher than Ruyen’s.

Ruyen had completely lost confidence upon seeing these two people. But she was convinced that she can’t be wrong this time. The Purcell Family can survive if they work with the Buda Clan. Relying on the Radiant Church would only bring disaster to the family.

Ruyen walked to meet them and then gave her greetings to Evan and Zhao Hai, “I’ve seen Father and Marquis Zhao Hai.”

Evan nodded, Zhao Hai returned the courtesy, “Lady Ruyen is too polite. I came today to meet you.” Ruyen nodded, then she said loudly, “Everybody, gather around!”

Before long, young men and women came out of the rooms of the courtyard. The oldest of them was about to reach 30 years old while the youngest one looks just over 10. They numbered less than 100. One could say that they are the Purcell Family’s hope for the future.

When these people came out, they had a slight reluctance on their faces. But when they saw Evan, the expression disappeared as they stood there obediently.

Evan looked at them and said, “All of you are elites of the family. You should already know the family’s situation right now, so I won’t say anything more. You will follow Zhao Hai to Golden Island today. You are the last hope of the Purcell Family. If the family were to fall today, all of you should establish yourselves in Golden Island and pave road for the future of our Purcell Family. Do all of you understand?”

Everybody simultaneously said, “We understand!”

Evan nodded, “This operation will be headed by Ruyen, you must always listen to her when you arrive at Golden Island, you should listen to Zhao Hai as well. If the family were to survive this ordeal, you may come back here. If we don’t, then Ruyen will become the family’s Patriarch. You must obey her orders.”

These youths couldn’t help but look at each other in dismay. They didn’t expect Evan to say those words today. Most importantly, they were puzzled about Evan handing the position of Patriarch over to Ruyen.

Evan looked at them and coldly snorted, “Do not think that this is my decision, the Elder’s assembly agreed to it as well. Do you think that I’m deceiving you?”

The youths’ expressions changed, then they said, “We won’t dare!”

Evan gave a nod, “Good. Ruyen, receive the scepter.” Then Evan placed his hand inside his robe and put out a scepter. This was the scepter of the Purcell Family’s Patriarchs.

Ruyen received the scepter with a serious expression. Then Evan turned his head towards the others and said, “Remember, all of you are the hope of the Purcell Family. If the family suffers disaster, all of you would have the responsibility to revive it. I don’t have a lot of requests for you, only that you must stay united. If you are united, you can do a lot more. You understand?”

The youths answered, “We understand!”

Evan then said, “Alright, you shall be following Zhao Hai. Remember, no matter what you see, you shouldn’t be surprised. Don’t talk to others about it as well. If you do, then I will have Ruyen use her power as the Patriarch and punish you for betrayal!”

Betrayal was a grave offense with regards to a family, it was even punishable by death. So upon hearing Evan, the youths became surprised. Then they immediately focused on what would happen next.

At this time, a shadow suddenly appeared on Evan’s side. Then everybody bowed towards the shadow, including Evan, “We’ve seen elder Origin Sword Saint.”

Origin Sword Saint nodded, then he turned to Evan and said, “I’ll be handing the family over to you. Remember, even if you die in battle, you cannot lose face for the Purcell Family. Don’t worry about the children, I shall take care of them.”

Evan nodded and said, “Yes elder, rest assured.”

Then Origin Sword Saint turned his head to Zhao Hai and said, “Patriarch Zhao Hai, I would have to trouble you this time.”

Zhao Hai was very respectful to the old man. He bowed and said, “Sir Sword Saint is too polite.” Then he took out his Magic Staff and muttered an incantation. After some time, he waved the Magic Staff as a rift appeared in front. Then Zhao Hai turned his head to Ruyen and the others then said, “Have everyone line up and enter the rift one by one. Upon entering the rift, you will notice that there will be a fog around you. But don’t panic and move around. Just stay inside and before long another rift would appear, then you can use that to exit.”

The youths present stared blankly into the rift. Although they had heard about Space Magic, they hadn’t actually seen one in person. Now that a spatial rift appeared in front of them, they couldn’t help but feel uncomfortable.

Origin Sword Saint didn’t hesitate and immediately stepped into the rift. When he entered the others reacted and followed him in one by one. The last one to enter the rift was Ruyen.

After Ruyen walked in, Zhao Hai turned and bowed to Evan. He didn’t say anything else and just entered the Spatial Rift. After seeing the rift shrink, Evan couldn’t help but feel a little strange in his heart.

At the same time, the people inside the Space were feeling strange as well. They were currently surrounded by a dark mist. But when they saw their other companions, they hearts settled a little bit.

But the most surprised of them all was Origin Sword Saint. One shouldn’t forget that he was a 9th rank expert and can scan everything around him using Mind Power. Therefore, when he stepped into the Space, he immediately scanned his surroundings.

And surprisingly, his Mind Power cannot penetrate the dark mist. It was as if they were in a completely different pocket of reality. He hasn’t experienced such a situation before, this made him quite surprised.

At this time, another Spatial Rift appeared in front of them. Then they head Zhao Hai’s voice, “Everyone, please head out according to the order that you entered earlier. You don’t need to hurry, so don’t push each other.”

Origin Sword Saint didn’t care so much, he just lifted his legs and stepped out. Others followed his lead as they went out of the Space one after another. When they arrived outside, they couldn’t help but gawk. This was because this wasn’t the Golden Island that they were expecting. They weren’t even on land. They were currently at sea, on board a five-masted ironclad ship.

Chapter 538: The Sword Saint’s Shock

The people looked around in surprise. They didn’t think that they would be transported into a ship, they expected to be at Golden Island when they come out.

Origin Sword Saint looked around and then turned his head to smile at Zhao Hai, “Patriarch Zhao Hai is really careful. This old man admires that.”

Zhao Hai quickly smiled and said, “Sir Saint is too polite. Sir can rest inside a cabin for now. In one day, we shall reach Golden Island.” Origin Sword Zhao wasn’t polite, he nodded to Zhao Hai and then turned around to enter the ship. Then he was led by an undead towards one of the rooms.

Seeing that Origin Sword Saint went in, the other Purcell Family youths quieted down. Zhao Hai looked at them and then turned his head to Ruyen, “Ruyen, an undead will come and arrange a room for you. You go rest first, we’ll be arriving at the island tomorrow. We need to do this so that people wouldn’t get too suspicious. But rest assured, this region is under the control of my Buda Clan, we are completely safe here.”

Ruyen had a complex expression when she looked at Zhao Hai before she said, “Then I’ll follow Sir Marquis’ arrangement.”

Zhao Hai smiled and said, “Ruyen, you’re too polite. No matter what, our two families have been friends for generations. We’re also in the same generation, calling me Brother Hai is fine. Don’t call me Sir Marquis, it makes me feel like an outsider.”

When Ruyen heard Zhao Hai, she couldn’t help but stare. Then after looking at Zhao Hai for quite some time, she murmured, “Thank you, Brother Hai.”

Zhao Hai smiled faintly and said, “You’re welcome.” Then he waved his hand as an undead came over. He turned his head to the others and said, “Everyone, these undead will be leading you to your rooms. Remember, a room can have up to four people.”

The Purcell Family youths were very obedient. They knew the identity of Zhao Hai. Even if he’s still young, Evan was already polite to him. The youths also knew that even if Evan held a higher title than Zhao Hai, with regards to their influence in the continent, Zhao Hai certainly held the upper hand.

Although these Purcell Family youths were considered as elites, they wouldn’t be able to hold a candle against Zhao Hai’s identity. Therefore, when met with Zhao Hai’s words, all of them can only follow just like how a child obeys an adult.

A five-masted ship is spacious. And with the crew being undead and didn’t need to rest, there was ample room for all of the youths to be accommodated. Settling 100 people wasn’t a problem at all.

Then Zhao Hai made sure that Ruyen had been settled, naturally she was alone on her room. After arranging for Ruyen’s accommodation, Zhao Hai didn’t enter the space immediately. Instead, he went to visit Origin Sword Saint. Just as he was about to knock on the door, he heard Origin Sword Saint’s voice, “Patriarch Zhao Hai, come in.”

Zhao Hai pushed the door and then went in. This room was specifically prepared by Zhao Hai. There weren’t anything much inside it, only a table, and a bed. The room was not large, having those furniture was already enough. The other rooms of the Purcell Family youths, on the other hand, only had two bunk beds.

Zhao Hai gave his greetings and said, “Is Sir Sword Saint comfortable? If you need anything just say it, an undead will come and serve you. I just hope that Sir doesn’t get put off.”

There were a lot of people in the continent who found the undeads very repugnant. Therefore, when he heard Zhao Hai, Origin Sword Saint faintly smiled and said, “You’re too polite. This man is already old, I can accept almost anything. Right, since Patriarch came to visit, are you here to tell me about your Space Magic?”

Zhao Hai stared, he finally understood that 9th ranks weren’t only strong, they were also wily foxes just like this old man in front of him. He quickly replied, “So Sir Sword Saint had already found out.”

Origin Sword Saint nodded and said, “I haven’t seen Space Magic, but I’m fairly sure that it isn’t the same as what you just did. Moreover, since I reached 9th rank, I can use Mind Power to scan my surroundings, but even my Mind Power was unable to scan your Magic. This feat alone is very outstanding, therefore, I reckoned that it might not be Space Magic, but instead a Space-type Divergent Ability.”

Zhao Hai nodded, “Sir Sword Saint’s eyes are truly blazing like torches. It is indeed a Space-type Divergent Ability. I came here to discuss this matter. Sir Sword Saint, please come along with me.” Then a Spatial Rift suddenly appeared right beside Zhao Hai.

Origin Sword Saint looked at the Spatial Rift next to Zhao Hai. He clearly saw that when Zhao Hai made this rift appear, he wasn’t whispering any incantations. It seems like the incantations that he did earlier was just a facade for others to see.

Origin Sword Saint didn’t say anything else and then stepped into the rift, then he was followed by Zhao Hai. But when the Sword Saint entered the Space, he couldn’t help but get shocked. This Space was completely different from what he had in mind. There was a blue sky above as well as green grass below. If it weren’t for the villa, Origin Sword Saint might have mistaken it as a part of the Beastman Prairie.

At this time, Zhao Hai appeared by his side and said, “Sir Sword Saint, this is my Space, a Divergent Ability that I had acquired. This is an independent Space, and here, I am a god. The reason for my Buda Clan’s sudden rise was this.”

Origin Sword Saint turned his head at Zhao Hai, he was puzzled, then he asked, “Since this is the case, why did you reveal it to me?”

Zhao Hai smiled and said, “Because I believe that Sir Sword Saint wouldn’t reveal it to anyone. Right, I think Sir Sword Saint can feel it, the energy inside this place is about ten times as much and as active as outside. This is a very good place to cultivate in, my Buda Clan’s 9th rank experts are all practicing here.”

Origin Sword Saint then asked, “How many 9th ranks does the Buda Clan have? Where did they come from?”

Zhao Hai smiled and said, “Altogether, our Buda Clan has 40 9th rank experts. These 9th ranks came from the Carrion Swamp. They are the same ones that signed an agreement with the Human 9th ranks in the past.”

Origin Sword Saint stared at Zhao Hai. He didn’t think that the Buda Clan would have that much 9th rank experts. And these 9th ranks actually came from the Carrion Swamp.

Looking at Origin Sword Saint’s expression, Zhao Hai faintly smiled and said, “This Space can be upgraded little by little. It wasn’t this powerful at the start, but it became stronger and stronger as time passes by. The Carrion Swamp’s 9th ranks agreed to stay here because the Space’s water can solve the Carrions Swamp’s toxin.

Origin Sword Saint understood what Zhao Hai meant. The Carrion Swamp has one of the most powerful poisons in the continent. If it weren’t for the poisonous mist, it wouldn’t have become one of the Continent’s five forbidden areas.

Since Zhao Hai can solve the Carrion Swamp’s poison, this made the 9th ranks able to go in and out of the swamp freely, no wonder they decided to join his side. Then when Origin Sword Saint thought about the Black Wasteland’s situation, his expression couldn’t help but change as he asked, “The Black Wasteland’s poison was your making? Did you do anything to the Black Wasteland as well?”

Zhao Hai nodded and smiled, “I did, I transformed it. The soil of the Wasteland can now be planted. To be honest, with the strength of my Buda Clan, overthrowing the entire Aksu Empire wouldn’t be a problem. I just don’t want to do it.”

Origin Sword Saint believed these words. With 40 9th rank experts, destroying the Aksu Empire would be very easy. He just couldn’t understand why Zhao Hai didn’t want to.

Zhao Hai looked at Origin Sword Saint and said, “Sir Sword Saint should know about the matters of the continent. Nobles, especially Great Nobles, aren’t only powerful, they also had their members hold key positions in their respective nations. Although our Buda Clan has a lot of experts, we severely lack good leaders, we don’t have any members who held great positions on any royal courts. If we overthrow the Aksu Empire, what advantages would it bring to the clan? If I sit on the throne, then I’m afraid I would just get overturned by the other Great Nobles, and they would be the only ones benefiting from this event. So I might as well let the Buda Clan stay as a Great Noble family. Then we would be able to survive despite our small numbers while at the same time discouraging other people from bullying us. And also, the Black Wasteland is very big, I can just opt to make my own country here. Wouldn’t it be interesting if I make my own country instead of snatching one?”

Origin Sword Saint didn’t expect this to be the case after he listened to Zhao Hai. But he had to agree that Zhao Hai was right. It wasn’t always a good idea to be a monarch. In fact, Royal Families in the Ark Continent are just Great Clans who managed to have other Great Clans become their vassals. At the same time, controlling a country and it’s nobles involved a lot of matters and intricacies.

The Buda Clan was only a small Family that is very strong. If Zhao Hai had great strength, did it mean that he would find it easy to be a King? Not necessarily. Even if he became a King with his own effort, it was possible for him to be overthrown by the collective might of the other Nobles. This would only end in the Buda Clan’s embarrassment.

The Buda Clan’s position right now was correct, and Zhao Hai’s decisions were the right ones. Origin Sword Saint didn’t expect Zhao Hai to have thought about things up to this point. He wasn’t blinded by strength, which was a rare thing for people in Zhao Hai’s generation.

Zhao Hai turned his head to Origin Sword Saint and said, “I invited Sir Sword Saint into the Space to have you cultivate here. If Sir Sword Saint becomes stronger, it would be very good to both the Purcell Family and my Buda Clan. As for the Purcell Family youths, Sir Sword Saint doesn’t need to worry about them much, I’ll take good care of them.”

When Origin Sword Saint heard Zhao Hai, he hesitated for a bit before he nodded, “Alright, then it’s settled, I’ll be cultivating here.”

Zhao Hai smiled and said, “That’s great. Later, I’ll have someone introduce you to the Space. It would be best for Sir Sword Saint to speak to Ruyen tomorrow. Naturally, you can’t tell her about the Space. You can just tell her that you’re going into closed door cultivation. Otherwise, they would panic when they notice your disappearance.”

Origin Sword Saint nodded.

Chapter 539: The Emperor’s Worries

The next day, the ship arrived at Golden Island. It sailed directly to the military port and docked at the naval base. After arriving, Origin Sword Saint approached Ruyen and told her that he would need to do closed-door cultivation. Ruyen knew that this thing was normal for 9th rank experts, so she didn’t say anything.

The reason why Zhao Hai invited Origin Sword Saint over to the Space was not because Zhao Hai was kind. Zhao Hai knew that the more a person stays inside the Space, the more amiable they were towards Zhao Hai. Origin Sword Saint was a 9th rank Human expert, so how could Zhao Hai possibly let this opportunity pass.

Naturally, this didn’t mean that he didn’t intend to help the Purcell Family. On the contrary, he would support the Purcell Family youths who came to Golden Island. Therefore, for the Purcell Family youths, it wouldn’t matter if they had a 9th rank expert to command them or not.

Moreover, the Purcell Family had now entered the same situation as the Iksa Family. But the Iksa Family had the better state, they still had their elites as well as their Patriarch. On the other hand, the Purcell Family now only has they younger generation. Even if they were full of energy, they were still very inexperienced.

In this case, what the Purcell Family needed was not a 9th rank expert, but a stable environment that would make them safe and allow them to grow at a stable pace.

After arriving at Golden Island, Zhao Hai arranged a place for Ruyen and the others to stay in. Then he asked Ruyen whether they wanted to make their own business in the island or help the Buda Clan manage the place.

Naturally, Zhao Hai wouldn’t be giving them too much of an authority. He would just have them do ordinary office work, allowing them to accumulate some experience. If they chose to do business, Zhao Hai would provide them a place to set up shop.

Ruyen was an intelligent woman, she knew that this decision would affect the Purcell Family’s future. Although Ruyen didn’t express it, she knew that the chances of the Purcell Family surviving back in the Duchy was very small. The group in Golden Island might very well be the final hope of the Purcell Family.

It was precisely because of this that Ruyen was thinking carefully about what they would do next. It was at this point that Ruyen admired Zhao Hai. The Buda Clan’s past situation wasn’t as good as what they were in right now, however, Zhao Hai still managed to rise up in a short period of one year. This feat was too astonishing.

Ruyen thought for a moment before she went to discuss this matter with the others. In the end, they decided that they older people would have to do business on the island, allowing the Purcell Family to have excess income. As for those who had little experience, they would help the Buda Clan in managing the affairs of the island and learn along the process.

Zhao Hai agreed with Ruyen’s decision. Some of the group had experience in management, they had helped the family do their businesses in the past. So having them do business was the best choice. This would make them accumulate more experience while earning money for the Purcell Family at the same time.

As for the younger ones, even if they were specifically chosen by the family, they didn’t have much experience. They still needed to learn a lot more. So the best choice for them was to help the Buda Clan in managing Golden Island.

Zhao Hai immediately arranged for Ruyen’s matters. He also gave Ruyen and the others a patch of land and built a house for them. This was Ruyen’s request, she didn’t want to always live in the naval base.

Ruyen’s appearance was soon made known to the people on the island. These people already knew about the relationship between the Purcell Family and the Buda Clan. Therefore, when they saw the youths of the Purcell Family in the island, they immediately understood what was going on.

Almost all of the Nobles in the continent would do the same thing as the Purcell Family. When they encounter something that they weren’t confident in dealing with, they would send some of their younger generation to a safe place. This would save their bloodline and would allow their family to reappear in the future.

And nowhere is much more appropriate than Golden Island. Since the Purcell Family and the Buda Clan were friends, it was natural that the Buda Clan would take care of these Purcell Family youths. Additionally, because of how powerful the Buda Clan was, it was impossible for other people to covet the property of the Purcell Family. Because of this, not only would the Purcell Family live in the island in peace, their trades would also be very positive. Perhaps their rise would come sooner than later.

But after Zhao Hai arranged all of these, he didn’t guide them anymore. The business atmosphere in Golden Island was very good. Swindlers and scammers rarely appeared because these practices were banned in the island. If one defrauded another, the Buda Clan would judge them based on their sin and then would be disallowed from entering the island again.

Although Ruyen and the others were newcomers, the people in the island already knew of their relationship with the Buda Clan. Because of this, nobody dared to make a move on them.

The reason why Zhao Hai left them to themselves was so that they could experience hardships themselves. Otherwise, they wouldn’t be able to get valuable experience. If everything were given to them on a silver platter, the Purcell Family wouldn’t be able to prosper.

What Zhao Hai needs to do now was to pay attention to the situation back in the Purcell Duchy. Almost all of the other nobles in the Duchy had already left. The Purcell Family was now divided, by Evan’s decision, Ruyen and the others were sent to Golden Island. The only people left in the Duchy were the direct line of the Purcell Family as well as the Purcell Army. The entire Duchy had turned into a dead landscape, it was almost impossible to see another person there right now.

Zhao Hai also felt helpless regarding this situation, but he couldn’t make a move. There were a lot of armies that surrounded the Duchy but none of them even set foot inside. This made Zhao Hai impatient.

Just as Zhao Hai was planning to go to the Duchy, a notification came from Kun. The Rosen Emperor was looking for Zhao Hai and was asking him to return to Carson City.

Although Zhao Hai didn’t know the reason, he knew that if it wasn’t important, the Emperor wouldn’t go and summon him. Therefore, he immediately went to the Space and transported to his castle outside Carson City.

Even if he wasn’t always in the castle, it was still kept clean because of the servants that he brought here in the past. Zhao Hai rested inside the castle and then on the next day he sat on his carriage and headed to Carson City.

After Zhao Hai arrived at the Imperial Palace, he was immediately escorted to the Emperor’s study. His status was the Emperor’s son-in-law, therefore he as his own special privileges inside the palace.

Inside the study, the Emperor was sitting there looking at some documents. Zhao Hai took a step forward and said, “This one has seen Father-in-law.”

The Emperor looked up and said, “Come, sit.” Zhao Hai nodded and then sat on one side. The Emperor placed the document down and looked at Zhao Hai, “I hear that you have a good relationship with the Beastmen?”

Zhao Hai nodded, “I do. I’m friends with the Cow-headed Race and Dog-headed Race. I also have good relations with the Black Bear Tribe and can also be considered to be an acquaintance of the Prairie Wolf Tribe.”

The Emperor nodded and then said, “Do you know the true purpose why the Beastmen are attacking the Human domain?”

Zhao Hai stared, “Does father-in-law not know? The Beastmen wanted to attack because the Radiant Church limited their food. So they wanted to retaliate.”

The Emperor frowned, “Is it only this reason?”

Zhao Hai smiled and said, “Father-in-law overthinks too much. The Beastmen are people who are easy to get along with. If the Radiant Church didn’t tamper with their food supply and created a food shortage in the Prairie, there wouldn’t be any war. Therefore, Father-in-law doesn’t need to worry too much.”

The Emperor sighed, “I have no other choice but to worry. I heard that the Beastman army this time is very large. If they extinguish the Aksu Empire and decided to continue on to our Rosen Empire, our losses would be huge.”

Zhao Hai shook his head and said, “Father-in-law, you think too much. The Aksu Empire wouldn’t be that easily eliminated. Also, we have the Lifeline Canyon, it wouldn’t be easy for the Beastmen to fight over there. But I have an idea, we can stockpile more than a few jins of food. The Beastmen only attacked because of food. If they actually come to us, we can just resist for a short time and then sell them some food for a low price. After that, they would surely retreat.”

The Emperor knit his brows and said, “If this happens, then wouldn’t it be similar to the Beastmen admitting defeat?”

Zhao Hai smiled and said, “This is only an arbitrary plan. After all, the situation might not even occur. We are also stockpiling some food until the end of the war because at that time, the Aksu Empire’s fields and granaries would surely be left ravaged. The price of food would then skyrocket. Even if it doesn’t affect our Rosen Empire, we can still sell them our stockpiled food, it will surely net us a huge sum of money.”

The Emperor looked at Zhao Hai, then he faintly smiled, “Kid, you’re really a madman when it comes to money. Hahaha. But what you proposed is good. Even if this stockpile comes unused, it wouldn’t bring us any harm. However, I still hope that you’d take the opportunity and contact the Beastman and ask for their bottom line. It would be best to keep them away from our territory as much as possible.”

Zhao Hai nodded, “I understand.”

The Emperor nodded and then looked at Zhao Hai and said, “How is the relationship between you and Lizzy? Why hasn’t she come back to visit me after your marriage? Go have her come home tomorrow. I want to see if you dared to bully her. If you did, I wouldn’t forgive you.”

Zhao Hai smiled faintly and then bowed, “Alright. Father-in-law can rest assured, I’ll have Lizzy come here tomorrow. However, since she’s quite busy, I cannot tell you the exact time.”

The Emperor snorted and said, “I don’t care about the time. You must make her come home tomorrow.”

Zhao Hai couldn’t help but nod. He wasn’t lying, Lizzy and the others were truly very busy. They had a lot of matters to work on. But since the Emperor requested it, he wouldn’t dare decline.

Chapter 540: Big Chess Board

At this time, Zhao Hai was focusing his attention on the Purcell Duchy. Naturally, he wouldn’t disregard the state of the Aksu Empire.

Presently, the Aksu Empire was studded with people from the Radiant Church. Zhao Hai had also seen that the recent Emperor was already dead. The one sitting on the throne right now was Boris. However, he held zero power in court, the true people controlling the Aksu Empire were from the Radiant Church.

This development was both expected and unexpected for Zhao Hai. He thought that no matter what the did, the Radiant Church would still keep the Emperor’s life. Making him into a puppet was a good idea. Zhao Hai didn’t expect that they would actually kill the Aksu Emperor.

For several days, Zhao Hai had been looking at the arrangements in the Purcell Duchy. It seems like the crisis of the Duchy was deliberately made. The Empire wanted the Beastmen to ravage the Duchy first before their armies swoop in and eliminate the Beastmen after.

It looks like the Radiant Church wanted to show the continent that they can lead a war as well as rule a country.

And aside from establishing their reputation, they can also openly eliminate the Purcell Family as well as severely wound the Beastmen. When the Radiant Church’s reputation soars, sending missionaries to other nations would become much easier.

Their ambition was big, and their plan was good. But they had underestimated Zhao Hai’s ability. It was impossible for them to know that Zhao Hai was already aware of their entire plan.

The Rosen Empire also intended to help the Aksu Empire. However, the Aksu Empire wasn’t relying on their help in the first place. They wanted to repel the Beastmen independently so that they can establish their might in the continent.

After Zhao Hai found out about these things, he wasn’t worried about the Rosen Empire but instead he was thinking about the Beastmen. Fortunately the Beastmen were still in transit towards the border, when they arrive, Zhao Hai would then go and tell them.

The Radiant Church had a lot of things that they prepared in order to deal with the Beastmen. The church had sent some experts to lie in ambush inside the Purcell Duchy. They weren’t there to kill the Beastmen, but instead to deliver poison. Even if this poison was not lethal, it can make its victims weak, losing their ability to defend. This was Radiant Church’s trump card against the Beastmen.

From the conversations that he heard, Zhao Hai knew that this plan hasn’t been going on for a day or two. When the old Emperor was alive, this plan was already underway. The elimination of the Buda Clan was only part of it. They haven’t even thought about eliminating the Purcell Family in the past. But since Zhao Hai had become too great of a threat, they changed their plan and decided to destroy the Purcell Family.

On the other hand, the poison was made by a long-term research conducted by the Radiant Church. This stemmed from the observations made by the Human Merchants while they were trading in the Prairie for a long time.

Zhao Hai also heard that if the poison was taken alone, it wouldn’t have any effect. It would need to be use along with another drug. In preparation for this day, the Radiant Church had been using the other drug on the food that they had been trading in the Prairie all these years. This drug was something that reacts with the poison and only then would they weaken the victim. The effect would only show itself when those two are present.

The Radiant Church did it this way because they knew that the Beastmen would be bringing Witch Doctors along with them as they marched on to war. When they stop in a place, the Witch Doctor would sample the water supplies present. Once they confirm that the water is safe, only then would the other Beastmen consume it. The Beastmen decided to do this because of their previous fight with the Humans. In that battle, the Humans used poison which crippled a large number of beastmen.

Although the Radiant Church cannot do this again and have the Beastmen take both of the poisons at the same time, but one shouldn’t forget that the Beastmen were already eating one of the poisons for years. As time goes by, the Beastmen would have this drug accumulated in their bodies. As long as they consume the other poison, they would certainly have a reaction. Even if the poison cannot kill them directly, it will still sap them off of their fighting strength. After that, the Radiant Church would be able to slaughter as many Beastmen as they want!

This plan of poisoning the Beastmen as well as controlling an Empire was already carried out by the Church more than a decade ago. This dedication was truly scary.

In this plan, the Aksu Empire, Rosen Empire, and the Beastmen became the chess pieces of the Radiant Church. If Zhao Hai didn’t appear, the Radiant Church would’ve been in a better situation than now.

In truth, although they were enemies, Zhao Hai had a huge admiration towards the Radiant Church. If the two of them didn’t have any enmity, Zhao Hai might’ve even considered joining the Radiant Church.

This was an organization that would resort to all means and has the patience and perseverance to get what they want. No wonder they became one of the most powerful influences in a short period of time. They were quite diligent in everything they did.

From Zhao Hai’s perspective, the Radiant Church was evil. But in the eyes of the Radiant Church, they were not. In their minds, they needed to eliminate any threat to the church in order to ensure their safety in future.

But it was unfortunate that Zhao Hai was enemies with them. Although he admired the Radiant Church, he needed to destroy all of their plans. Otherwise, Zhao Hai would be the one to suffer bad luck.

After knowing about all of these, Zhao Hai made his move. He secretly snatched the two poisons from the Radiant Church and then brought them to Iron Mountain Fort. After that, he handed them over to Shun’s mother, making her help analyze them.

Shun’s mother, Suju, was an expert in poisons. While she was in Iron Mountain Fort, she continued on with her research. Now, her skill in making poison has become very good.

After a couple minutes of investigation, the ingredients of the two poisons were already identified. It was true that ingesting them individually wouldn’t have any effect. But once they were used together, they would become a strong poison.

After using Spatial Water, Suju confirmed that it did have an effect as an antidote. However, curing the poison would still take some time. Normally, it would be fine to wait, but in the battlefield, time is of the essence.

In the end, Zhao Hai decided to bring the mixed poison in to the Space. The Space can analyze poisons and also produce an antidote. Zhao Hai hopes that the Space wouldn’t disappoint him.

And the Space did indeed do what Zhao Hai expected. The Space absorbed the poisons, improved the Space’s insecticide, as well as having the Spatial Water cure it immediately. Zhao Hai then brought some of the Spatial Water over to Suju to study. After some time, Suju confirmed that the Spatial Water can now solve the poisons. Moreover, it was very effective.

It was just a pity that they didn’t have a microscope right now. If they did, they would be able to study the poisons and the Spatial Water much more carefully. At this time, they weren’t able to make their own antidote.

Even if Zhao Hai was somewhat disappointed, he still accepted it. After all, the poison had been solved. This was akin to rendering the Radiant Church’s trump card useless. If the Radiant Church wanted to succeed right now, they would need to go through a lot of difficulties.

Of course, the Radiant Church wasn’t entirely relying on the poisons, they had also accumulated a lot of experts and as well as the entire army of the Aksu Empire. They were going all out in dealing with the Beastmen, there weren’t even some defenders left in lifeline canyon!

The Radiant Church knew that if the Rosen Empire used this opportunity to invade the Aksu Empire, then they would become the entire human race’s enemy. Therefore, the church decided to withdraw every soldier stationed in the canyon and had them help fight the Beastmen.

In order to deal with the Beastmen, they even prepared a fleet. This fleet only had one goal; it was to transport a well-equipped army to the interior of the Beastman Prairie and have them wreck havoc there, forcing the Beastmen to retreat. As long as they managed to repel the beastmen with their own strength, the Radiant Church would win, while both the Beastmen and the Rosen Empire lost.

In such big battles, 9th ranks generally opted to not participate. Most of the experts who would fight were 8th ranks or lower. This was because if 9th ranks participate, not only would they devastate the battlefield, they would also cause a catastrophe for the continent. They may cause other races to come and participate, and in the end, it would become a war of the entire Ark Continent.

But Zhao Hai didn’t really expect that this was the case. From what he can see, as long as someone had a 9th rank expert, there would only be a small amount of things that they cannot solve. For example, in this war, 9th ranks would have already been flying all around the place. Zhao Hai didn’t think that this time, no 9th rank was willing to make a move. The strength of both armies were now dependent on the lower ranked experts.

However, Zhao Hai came to understand this arrangement. In Ark Continent, 9th ranks are akin to nuclear weapons, one cannot just use them casually. Unless a clan comes close to being eliminated, 9th rank experts wouldn’t generally go out. Just like when two countries go to war back on earth. It was simply impossible for them to use nuclear weapons.

Zhao Hai approved of this, 9th ranks cannot simply be sent out. This was because 9th ranks were very strong. An ordinary soldier would just become like an ant in front of a 9th rank’s might. If a 9th rank decides to kill ordinary soldiers, then it wouldn’t be impossible for them to kill a thousand in one attack. If 9th ranks participate, then the casualties of the war would exponentially increase.

The Radiant Church was fully prepared for this war because they had already anticipated it for a long time.

On the other hand, the Beastmen were poorly prepared. Because of how they needed to move hastily, one could even say that they were in a disadvantageous position in this war.

The Beastmen also knew about this. However, they still needed to wage war. If not for their need of food for survival, they wouldn’t be going to battle.

But they didn’t know that this war had been orchestrated by the Radiant Church from the very beginning. Each step that lead to this point was carefully calculated by the church.

If Zhao Hai doesn’t help, the Beastmen would surely lose a lot this time. They will lose a lot of warriors as well as face the problem of food shortage. At the same time, the Radiant Church was also lighting a fire inside the Prairie. This would certainly make the Beastmen lose their spirit.

The Radiant Church was playing chess on a huge board. They took everything into consideration, aside from Zhao Hai’s existence. Zhao Hai disrupted their plans time and time again. Zhao Hai had now become an annoying piece on the board. With how Zhao Hai had been meddling in the church’s affairs, he had already become a thorn on their path.

By monitoring the Radiant Church in Aksu Empire, Zhao Hai managed to find out the plans of the Radiant Church. The person who came to the Aksu Empire this time was an Archbishop, a person with a position directly below the Pope. This person was very familiar to Zhao Hai. He was Lindsey Becker’s father, the most influential and powerful Red-robed Archbishop of the Radiant Church, Lundi Becker!

In the past, Lindsey Becker went to attack Zhao Hai, only to be turned into an undead in the end. Zhao Hai also acquired a non-directional teleportation scroll from Lindsey’s body. This task has been given to him by his father. But Lundi didn’t expect his son to get killed, therefore, his enmity towards Zhao Hai was very big.

But Zhao Hai had to recognize how powerful of a person Lundi was. He was one of the key participants when the Radiant Church formulated this plan. Under his influence, the plan slowly unfolded until it came to this point. Once couldn’t deny how fierce this person was.

The Radiant Church had attached great importance to this plan. Otherwise, they wouldn’t have sent an Archbishop to Aksu Empire to assume command. The only reason why they only sent Lundi was so that the commands would go on smoothly. The Archbishops of the church weren’t exactly very harmonious. If a lot of them were sent, they would only fight amongst themselves. Therefore, handing everything over to Lundi was already enough. This also showed Lundi’s place inside the Radiant Church.

Naturally, if everything fails, the responsibility would fall into Lundi’s hands.

Zhao Hai calmly monitored the movements of the church. He now became a spectator in this game of chess. He was waiting for the right opportunity to destroy the entire plan of the Radiant Church. And this opportunity was not far away!

Chapter 541: Iron Wall Fortress

Even though Zhao Hai knew about these matters, he couldn’t tell it to anyone. This was because he wouldn’t be able to explain how he was able to get his hand on these information.

But Zhao Hai still prepared, this Beastman attack was an excellent opportunity. Even if the Radiant Church had a fool-proof plan, they didn’t expect Zhao Hai to be on the sidelines, looking at their entire plan clearly.

If the Beastmen didn’t attack the Human race for food, then Zhao Hai might have helped the Purcell Duchy. But since the Beastmen were doing this for survival, Zhao Hai chose to just look at the situation for now.

The Beastmen arrived on time, they had finally arrived outside Iron Wall Fortress. Before long, Beastmen tents covered the entire area outside of the Wall.

However, the Purcell Family didn’t give up. They gathered a large number of troops in the Fortress and prepared to face the Beastmen head-on.

Right now, the Purcell Family wasn’t thinking about anything else. They didn’t run away nor give up because they still had their Noble honor.

Nobles were a very special group. They were born with a status higher than the commoners, and they can enjoy things that commoners wouldn’t be able to in their entire livers. They also held the admiration of the masses. But at the same time, they also have a responsibility to protect the commoners.

The Purcell Family was already aware that they wouldn’t be spared this time. Even the elders who opposed going with Zhao Hai understood that the only way for them left was to stay and fight for the honor of the Purcell Family.

Fighting for honor might sound laughable, however, this wasn’t the case for Nobles. A Noble without honor cannot be considered to be a Noble. This was Ark Continent’s unwritten rule.

If a Noble faces their enemy head on and dies, not only would they win respect, their families would gain reputation as well. But if a Noble escapes without fighting, his whole family would be despised. Then it wouldn’t take a long time before that family declines.

Therefore, Nobles regarded honor the same as their own life and death. And now the Purcell Family was prepared to face the Beastmen and fight to the last man. They needed to fight for their territory until the bitter end.

For this battle, the Purcell Family had done all the preparation that they can. Although they had given the majority of their money to Ruyen, as a millenium-old clan, they still had ample money left. When they had the people in the Duchy leave, they also gave a lot of money to the families of their soldiers as settlement. In fact, one could even say that this settlement was equal to buying the lives of their soldiers.

Even if the Purcell Family wasn’t one of the strongest millenium-old families, they were still one. They had established their own principality. They also treated the soldiers in their Duchy like family members. And like family, the soldiers were very loyal towards the family. Because of this, one couldn’t just underestimate the might of the Purcell Family.

The entire continent’s attention were now focused on Iron Wall Fortress. The people of the continent were no strangers to battles between the Beastmen and Humans. However, this was the first war between the two that attracted a lot of people’s attention.

The main reason for this attention was the Purcell Family. From what the people can see, the Aksu Empire had chosen to give up on the Purcell Family. Otherwise, they wouldn’t be this unsupportive.

Moreover, some rumors from the Rosen Empire and the Calci Family were also starting to spread. With the help of the Buda Clan and the Shelley Family, the people came to understand why the Aksu Empire chose to do this.

The Nobles of the continent weren’t fools. After seeing how the Radiant Church acted inside the Aksu Empire, they immediately believed the rumors. In a blink of an eye, the Great Nobles of the continent started to focus their sights towards the Radiant Church.

The Great Nobles of the other countries didn’t attach great importance to the Radiant Church. To them, it was just a church, how could it be powerful. But as soon as the rumors spread, they immediately paid careful attention. An Empire was just occupied by the Radiant Church. How did they manage to do that?

Therefore, the people paid attention to this war not only because it was a war between two races. They also wanted to see how the Radiant Church responds.

In truth, the response of the Radiant Church disappointed these Great Nobles. This war wasn’t between two families, it was a war between two races. No matter what the Radiant Church thinks, they should still provide help for the Purcell Family. After all, the Purcell Family were also Humans.

But instead, the Radiant Church had actually chosen to sacrifice the Purcell Family. The Great Nobles didn’t consider why the Radiant Church chose to do this. They only knew that the Radiant Church gave up on helping the Purcell Family.

While the people’s attention was on the Purcell Duchy, Zhao Hai actually arrived at the Cow-headed race’s main camp. In this war, the Cow-headed Race didn’t request to be on the forefront, but instead opted to stay at the rear part of the army. They became responsible for looking after the Argali as well as delivering some food to the front.

Even if the Cow-headed Race weren’t the strongest Beastmen, their strength was still not bad. In the previous wars, they even performed very well. When they suddenly asked for such a position this time, it wasn’t a mystery why the other Beastmen became surprised.

However, the other Beastmen also knew about what happened to the Cow-headed Race. Therefore, they understood this decision. Moreover, the Radiant Church’s action of snatching some Beastmen children became known. The Radiant Church would brainwash those children before placing them inside a Beastman Tribe and had them wreck havoc inside. This finding became a great merit towards the whole Beastman Race. Because of this nobody looked down on the Cow-headed race. On the contrary, they held great admiration towards them. The other races also made a thorough investigation with their members to see if there were spies among them.

Not to mention the common races who found 1 or 2 spies, the Warring Races actually found a lot of them amidst their members. This made those races extremely angry. Their present goal was now to teach the Radiant Church a lesson. Nobody got angry because of the Cow-headed Race’s retreat to the backlines. Instead, with the help of the Black Bears, the Cow-headed Race had also managed to form a relationship with the Tiger-headed Race.

Having a connection with such a huge Warring Clan brought huge advantages to the Cow-headed Beastmen.

So now, Wales was having a very comfortable time. He was currently part of the Rear army and was only taking care of the food and commodities. They didn’t have any fighting duties but were one of the people who ate the best. To Wales, being in the rear army was a very luxurious position.

Naturally, this is only his opinion. To the other Beastmen Races, being in the Rear Army was not a good idea. Although the Rear Army was the most relaxed in battles, they were also the ones who received the least after the war.

But Wales didn’t care about any of these, he has Zhao Hai so he was not living simply. The most important thing to the Cow-headed Race right now was to recover and gain some strength.

The fighting force of the Cow-headed Race was composed of the Herculean Bulls as well as other strong tribes. And among them, the Herculean Bulls were the most familiar with Zhao Hai. So when he came to their camp, the other Cow-headed Tribes were looking at him and became very vigilant.

However, the Herculean Bulls knew Zhao Hai, so when the other tribes were introduced to him, they instantly became very hospitable. Just a short time after Zhao Hai arrived at the camp, he was already invited into Wales’ tent.

Although the Beastmen loved drinking, they only consume small amounts of liquor when going to war. Therefore, what Wales offered to Zhao Hai this time was milk tea.

Wales looked at Zhao Hai and said, “Little Hai, how can you come here at this time. This is too dangerous for you. If any Human is present, you wouldn’t be able to come back to the Human domain in the future.”

Although Wales didn’t have much contact with Humans before, he was very clear about how Humans think. If the Humans knew that Zhao Hai went to visit him, then Zhao Hai would be hated by the entire human race in the future.

Zhao Hai smiled faintly and said, “Brother doesn’t need to worry. I can guarantee that nobody saw me this time. Also, Brother, I came this time to tell you something about this war.

Wales nodded, he held absolute trust towards Zhao Hai. He believed that Zhao Hai wouldn’t deceive him. Therefore, he nodded and then waited for Zhao Hai’s words.

Zhao Hai told Wales about what he knew, the poisons, the Radiant Church’s plan, and so on. Then Zhao Hai said, “Brother, the war this time was completely anticipated by the Radiant Church. Their aim was to push the Beastmen to war so that they can repel the Beastmen with their own strength, establishing their might to the continent. And at the same time, they would thoroughly harm the Beastmen.

Wales cannot believe what he just heard, “So you’re telling me that the Radiant Church sacrificed the Purcell Family in order to use the poison and deal with us? That’s terrible news.”

Then Zhao Hai put out a water bag and handed it over to Wales, “Brother, have a Witch Doctor examine the water in this bag. Then have someone drink it, then you’ll be able to confirm the Radiant Church’s plan.”

Zhao Hai knew that facts speak louder than words. Before he went to visit Wales, he already had this water bag prepared. The water in this bag contained the second half of the Radiant Church’s Poison. After all, the Herculean Bulls were also one of the research subjects of the Radiant Church.

Chapter 542: Beast King

In fact, the Radiant Church was very annoyed regarding this as well. Initially, their plan of eliminating with the Herculean Bulls was part of the plan for today. They wanted to deal with the Herculean Bulls using the Fighting Bulls, then have them take the Rear Army. Then in this war, the Fighting Bulls would administer the poison from behind the Beastmen Army. This was to double their chance of the plan succeeding.

However, they didn’t expect that Zhao Hai’s appearance would actually make their plans fail. But fortunately for the Radiant Church, the Herculean Bulls had already ingested the first part of the poison. Because of this, the church’s plan can still be more or less realized.

In fact, the cooperation between the Radiant Church and the Fighting Bulls wasn’t as good as it seems. Although the Church used the Fighting Bulls to deal with the Herculean Bulls, they had never thought of letting the Fighting Bulls off. Therefore, whether it be the Fighting Bulls or the Herculean Bulls, both of them were given the first part of the poison.

Wales wasn’t polite and immediately received the water bag. Then he went to find a Witch Doctor and had them examine the liquid inside the bag. And naturally, the answer that the Witch Doctor gave was that it didn’t have any problems.

Zhao Hai couldn’t help but be curious when he saw the Witch Doctor. The Doctor was actually from the Water Buffalo Tribe. He didn’t expect the Water Buffalo Tribe to produce Prophets, Witch Doctors, as well as Shamans.

When Wales heard what the Witch Doctor said, he immediately went to get a Herculean Bull warrior and had him drink the liquid in the bag. Although the warrior didn’t know why, he still obeyed and drank from the bag. Even if he only took a sip, a minute after he placed the bag down, he was already affected by the poison and softly fell to the ground. Although he hadn’t been directly harmed, he had completely lost his ability to fight.

Zhao Hai immediately got a cup of Spatial water and saved the Herculean Bull. Then after that, Zhao Hai had all of the Cow-headed Race drink some Spatial Water. Naturally Wales didn’t oppose to it. On the contrary, he urged his fellow Beastmen to drink Zhao Hai’s water. While the Beastmen were drinking, Wales took the water bag and went to look for the Mastiff Tribe.

Going from race to race was the best thing to do right now. If Zhao Hai directly went to the Lion and Tiger-headed Tribes, most of them wouldn’t believe him.

Zhao Hai didn’t go to the Dog-headed Race along with Wales. Although he was also friends with the Dog-headed Beastmen, he was still busy feeding water to the other Cow-headed Beastmen. Therefore, he made Wales go by himself.

After the Dog-headed Beastmen heard Wales, they were startled. Then they went to look for a Mastiff Warrior to test it out. In the end, the result was the same as with the Herculean Bull Warrior. Naturally, Wales also brought some of Zhao Hai’s Spatial Water to cure the Mastiff Warrior.

However, just to be sure, Buzeer went to look for a half-beastman slave and had him drink the poisoned liquid. The result was that the half-beastman slave wasn’t affected at all.

Half-beastman slaves didn’t have a high status in the Beastman Prairie, they weren’t fighting races either. It would be a waste to give them poison. Therefore, most Beastmen slaves remained unaffected by the poison.

After the testing, Buzeer finally believed that the majority of the Beastman Races were poisoned. He immediately sent someone to invite Zhao Hai over. Zhao Hai had also brought enough Spatial Water. Therefore, the Herculean Bulls started to go to the other Cow-headed Beastmen and had them drink the Spatial Water.

The status of the Herculean Bulls among the Cow-headed Beastmen was very high. So these beastmen were very trusting towards the Herculean Bulls. Not to mention drinking the Spatial Water, even if they were asked to drink dirty water, they would still do it.

After Zhao Hai arrived at the Dog-headed Beastman’s camp, he immediately retold the story to Buzeer. Then he took out some Spatial Water and gave them to the Dog-headed Beastmen to drink. After having drunk the water, the Dog-headed Beastmen tested themselves again. But now, they weren’t affected after drinking the poisoned water anymore.

Buzeer attached great importance to this matter. He knew that if the Radiant Church succeeds in executing this plan, the Beastmen would be suffering huge losses.

Buzeer immediately took the water bag and went to see the Bear Tribe along with Zhao Hai. The Dog-headed Beastmen couldn’t talk with those big Warring Tribes. But the Black Bear Tribe was different, it was itself a big Warring Tribe. They had enough qualifications to discuss matters with the other Warring Tribes. Therefore, Buzeer decided to look for the Black Bear Patriarch.

The Black Bear Patriarch personally led their army this time. In the past few years, the Black Bears haven’t had the greatest lives among the Beastmen. After they were deceived by that Human Merchant, they had never managed to recover. Because of this, even their status as a Warring Tribe became under crisis.

But even if the Black Bears have been struggling, they still managed to keep their formidable strength. In front of their might, even the Tigers and Lions would have to withdraw. Nobody dared to provoke the Black Bears.

The news that Buzeer brought was also deemed important by the Black Bear Patriarch. After asking from Buzeer and learned that this came from Zhao Hai, he instantly believed it. He trusted that Zhao Hai wouldn’t lie to him. In giving this message, Zhao Hai wouldn’t gain any benefit, so he didn’t need to lie to them.[1]

The Black Bear Patriarch immediately sent this message over to the Tiger-headed Race. Compared to the Lion-headed race, the Black Bears had a better relationship with the Tigers. At the same time, the leader of the Beastman coalition was also from the Tiger-headed Race,

The Tigers also held this matter at great importance. This was because the information that Zhao Hai just brought would directly affect the outcome of the war. Therefore, they immediately had the Black Bears invite Zhao Hai over.

Zhao Hai already expected this to happen, but he still had some disguise. At the very least, he changed his looks. Now, he looks older than his actual age, he looks like a 30-year old man.

This time, because the Beastmen were attacking as one, they only have one golden tent. This golden tent also belonged to the Tiger-headed Beastmen.

Zhao Hai followed a Tiger Warrior into the golden tent. This was the first time that he had seen a Tiger-headed Beastman up close. The Tiger Warriors looked very powerful. Each one of them had about the height of 3.5 meters. They also had eyes that seem to see through a person’s soul.

Zhao Hai knew that the Tiger Beastman had a type of innate skill. This unique skill was called Soul-Shaking Gaze. On the other hand, the Lion Beastmen had their own unique skill as well. This skill was called Soul-Seizing Roar.

It was because of these abilities that the two Races can become candidates for the Beastman Race’s Royal Tribe position. Their innate skills were something that other Beastmen couldn’t face. Especially the Tigers’ Soul-Shaking Gaze, this skill was truly formidable. As long as a Tiger Beastman looked at a person, that target would immediately feel frightened and lose spirit. If that target was an enemy, their souls would be shaken, rendering them unable to move.

On the other hand, the Lions’ Soul-Seizing Roar was not as good as the Tigers’ ability. Their ability can only used for the first time. After using it once, their effect would become less than before.

Moreover, the Lion-headed Race’s fighting strength was a bit lower than the Tiger-headed Race. This made the overall strength of the Tigers much stronger than the Lions. Therefore, the Tigers were able to suppress the Lions.

When the Tiger Warrior looked at Zhao Hai, he became surprised. Under his gaze, Zhao Hai didn’t have any unusual reactions. This made the Tiger Beastman very curious.

After Zhao Hai entered the tent, he saw that various Patriarchs of various races were present. Among them were Wales, Buzeer, the Wolf King, and the Black Bear Patriarch. The other Patriarchs were people he hadn’t met before. Then on the center of them all, a Tiger Beastman was seen sitting down.

This Tiger Beastman seemed to be quite old. The hairs on his face had already turned white. However, this aspect actually made him look much more wise. When Zhao Hai saw this Tiger, he suddenly remembered a sentence, Old tigers are treasure troves of Knowledge! This Tiger Beastman gave Zhao Hai the same feeling.

Zhao Hai gave his greetings to the Tiger Patriarch first before giving his greetings to the others as well. Those who knew Zhao Hai were being polite to him. After all, from the Black Bear Patriarch said, Zhao Hai was the owner of Magic Lily Shop. Zhao Hai’s identity was very attractive to these Beastman Patriarchs.

The Tiger Patriarch stared at Zhao Hai for some little time, then he suddenly smiled and said, “Young man, why would we believe the information that you brought?”

Zhao Hai smiled and said, “Honored Beast King, do I have any reason to lie to you? I have great enmity with the Radiant Church, it’s an enmity of life and death. At the same time, I’m the Cow-headed Race’s Foreign Prince, if I harm the Beastmen, then I would only be helping the Radiant Church, and in turn, harming myself. I believe any sane person wouldn’t dare to do so.”

Although the leader of the Beastmen wasn’t fixed, but no matter who the leader was, all of them were referred to as Beast King. Therefore, Zhao Hai’s greeting wasn’t wrong.

The Beast King looked at Zhao Hai and said, “You said that our attack is part of the Radiant Church’s plan. That they had poisoned the waters of the Purcell Duchy while waiting for us. Is this true?”

Zhao Hai nodded and said, “It is. This plan was executed by the Radiant Church for a long time. They were now unsatisfied in just being a church, they wanted to control a country, and then completely brainwash their citizens. This is the current state of the Aksu Empire. His Majesty Beast King should know what would happen if the Radiant Church came to control the entire Aksu Empire. This would be akin to cutting the passage of Humans going into the Beastman Prairie. After that, Human Merchants who would want to trade with the Beastmen would find it hard to come to the Prairie. With this arrangement, the Radiant Church would be able to control the life and death of the entire Beastman Race.

Even if the Beast King’s expression didn’t change, the expressions of the others did. They were very clear about what happens if the Radiant Church came to control the Aksu Empire. From this point, all of them knew that Zhao Hai didn’t deceive them, he was telling the truth.

Zhao Hai then added, “This matter will also have a similar impact to the Humans. Once the Radiant Church succeeds in repelling the Beastmen, their momentum would be able to soar into the skies. There wouldn’t be anyone who would be able to contend with their influence. And as their enemy, I would be one of the first ones to experience bad luck.”

* * *

??? Radiant Church will be screwed

Chapter 543: Arrangement

The Beast King stared at Zhao Hai and said, “You’re a Human. Would you dare stab your race at the back?”

Zhao Hai smiled faintly and said, “Your Majesty, if I may speak discreetly. My purpose this time is to deal with the Radiant Church. Moreover, I’m different from other people. In my opinion, the Beastmen are the same as Humans, just same intellectual beings of the Continent. I don’t think that the Beastmen are any worse than the Humans, and at the same time, I don’t think that the Humans are any worse than the Beastmen. I think everyone is equal. To tell you the truth, if the Beastmen decides to invade the Human domain, even if I’m the Foreign Prince of the Cow-headed Race, i would still make a move to stop the Beastmen. And since the Beastmen are doing it for survival, and is now about to fall into the Radiant Church’s trap, I couldn’t just sit still and watch. In the end, I’m still the Foreign Prince of the Cow-headed Race, I also consider myself as half-Beastman.”

The Beast King and the other Beastman Patriarch looked at Zhao Hai in surprise. They didn’t think that Zhao Hai’s answer would be something that they didn’t even think about.

Especially when Zhao Hai said that if the Beastmen would invade the Human domain, he would step in and help resist them. It wasn’t only the Beastmen Patriarchs who were surprised about this, even Wales was startled.

The Beast King looked at Zhao Hai and then suddenly laughed. His laughter was in a low sinking voice, it even seemed to resemble a roar. It was a very thick laughter, it shook the entire tent.

After some time, the Beast King stopped his laughter and turned his head to Zhao Hai, “Good, young man. You really are a genuine friend to the Beastmen. I believe you. This information that you’ve brought is very important to us. I’ll have to ask you to provide the antidotes to the poison.”

Zhao Hai didn’t expect the Beast King to be this open-minded. But Zhao Hai still nodded and then put out a canteen. He passed the canteen over to everyone inside and had them drink from it. After that Zhao Hai said, “I’ll have to request His Majesty to prepare wooden barrels. I’ll have them filled up with the antidote. After curing the poison, you won’t have anymore issues.”

The Beast King nodded, then looked at Zhao Hai and said, “Young man, once this war ends, don’t forget to visit our Giant Tiger Tribe when you return to the Prairie. Our race lacks almost everything, we’ll buy anything you bring to us.”

Zhao Hai smiled faintly and said, “I’m honored to gain the recognition of His Majesty. I’ll certainly go visit in the future.”

The Beast King nodded, then he waved his hand to Zhao Hai, allowing him to leave the tent. Soon after Zhao Hai left the tent, the Beast King looked at Wales and said, “Patriarch Wales, you understand this Zhao Hai the most. Is he really sincere in what he said?”

Wales didn’t hesitate to nod and said, “Yes, Zhao Hai isn’t an ordinary Human. He lives up to his own words and doesn’t like to talk empty. From the first time that I’ve met him, I’ve never seen him look down on other Beastmen. In fact, the first friendship flag that he gained wasn’t from our Herculean Bull Tribe, but from the Big Bellied Pig Tribe. After I met him, I immediately had someone go check and indeed, the friendship flag was willfully given by them to Zhao Hai. I also know that he’s feeling very indignant towards our current situation right now, so he will naturally do his best to help us.”

The Beast King nodded, then he turned to Buzeer and said, “Patriarch Buzeer, tell me what is your thinking.”

Buzeer nodded and said “i agree with Wales’ views. Little Hai is a good person. In fact, if he wanted to harm us, we wouldn’t even know that this matter was because of the Radiant Church.”

Without waiting for the Beast King to speak, the Old Wolf King added, “I also think that this Zhao Hai is a person who could be trusted. He is very different from the other Humans, this we saw from the first time we met him. Otherwise, our Wolf Tribe wouldn’t have traded with him.”

The Black Bear Patriarch added as well, “I believe Little Hai wouldn’t deceive us. I think the most important thing we need to do right now is to send some people back to the Prairie, informing all of the tribes to pay attention to the Human fleet. It’s for certain that the fleet had elite troops within. If we don’t do anything about that and make them land on the Prairie, the damage that they can do would be certainly huge.”

The Beast King nodded and said, “Hawk Tribe Patriarch, immediately send this information over to the Prairie. Have some smaller tribes group up and head towards the shorelines. Make them prepare to engage the disembarked Human troops. I don’t believe the Humans can compete to our own Cavalry. Also, have some Prophets help them defend. The Humans might have sent some Mages to help in this operation.”

The Hawk Tribe Patriarch immediately nodded. He knew that this matter was very important for the entire Beastman Race. He cannot be careless in this, he must then assemble his most capable men to accomplish it.

The Beast King then looked at the others and said, “The Humans are already expecting our attack, they’re now waiting for us inside the Purcell Duchy. This is not a good news for us, but it can also be an opportunity for our Beastman army. The Wolf Tribe, Tiger Tribe, Lion Tribe, Leopard Tribe, Dog Tribe, and also the Hawk Tribe need to stand by. In the next few days, we would have the other Tribes carry an attack towards the Purcell Duchy. But remember, this is only a diversion, our main offense would not be situated there. Those Tribes that I mentioned earlier will need to get your most silent mounts and use them. In the following evenings, we shall be shifting our offense towards the Iksa Family Domain. The Iksa Family is no longer in control of that place. Moreover, there are armies stationed there, waiting to ambush us in the Purcell Duchy. We will do the same to them. Your strengths aren’t weak, so you would be able to overwhelm the domain in a short period of time. After that, when the armies turn towards you, lessening the troops focused on the Purcell Domain, we shall then go all out in overcoming Iron Wall Fortress. With our two fronts, we should be able to advance much easier.”

These Beastmen don’t accept any orders from anyone during peacetime, especially the Big Warring Races. Every one of them held equal status. Even the Beast King couldn’t casually throw out some commands for them to follow. However, since it was wartime, the Beast King’s words held very heavy authority.

Therefore, the people in the tent immediately issued a shout of agreement. Then they went on to prepare their troops. These Patriarchs were veterans in combat, the Beast King only needed to tell them where and when to attack, anything else can be managed by them.

After all, each race had their own preferences of attack, and the most familiar with them were the Patriarchs. The only thing that the Beast King needed to do was provide them with a direction.

After these Patriarchs left the tent, they gawked. They were presently looking at their tribemates happily drinking the antidote. And when they walked closer to look, it wasn’t actually water, but instead liquor.

This was a way that Zhao Hai came up with. He gave them liquor because Beastmen preferred wine over water.

Zhao Hai had only remembered this point after he left the tent. So he put some Spatial Water into the liquors before he handed them over to the Beastmen. Not only would it have the effect of an antidote, the Beastmen would also enjoy drinking it more.

When Wales asked Zhao Hai what happened, he felt relief. Even if the Beastmen weren’t permitted to drink too much liquor during wartime, it wasn’t prohibited. Disallowing the Beastmen to drink was an utterly impossible thing to do.

Zhao Hai went with Wales in returning to the Herculean Bull Tent. After they sat down, Zhao Hai looked at Wales and said, “Brother, since this matter had already been completed, I think I need to head back. I cannot be here for too long.”

Wales nodded, “Brother should head back. Rest assured, we’ll surely let the Radiant Church suffer a big loss this time. If possible, we would surely flatten the entire Aksu Empire to take revenge on your behalf.”

Zhao Hai smiled and said, “That would be really good. But Brother, you must pay attention. If the other Beastmen still wants to fight after clearing the Aksu Empire, you should stop them. I’ve already become quite famous in Rosen Empire, it wouldn’t be good too attack them. At the same time, after you clear the Aksu Empire, I will talk to the Rosen Emperor and have him trade food with the Beastmen in a cheap price. This arrangement is greater than fighting, I’m sure the other Beastmen would agree.”

Wales nodded, even if the other Beastmen weren’t familiar with Zhao Hai, he was. He fully knows that Zhao Hai has an Undead Army numbering about a million. Moreover, some of them were Beastmen, imagining how strong they were made Wales shudder inside.

Actually, Wales had underestimated Zhao Hai. At this point, Zhao Hai’s undead had already reached 1.5 million. And these undead are all equivalent to 8th rank experts.

1.5 million 8th ranks? Such an army can ravage the entire Human Continent. Naturally, Zhao Hai didn’t do so. Such actions would only make him the enemy of all the races. He still doesn’t have the ability to defend himself if he became the enemy of everyone in the Ark Continent.

Zhao Hai looked at Wales and said, “Brother, take care of yourself. When the war ends, I’ll go to the Prairie and have a drink with you.”

Wales laughed and said, “Alright, I’ll wait for you. I believe this war would end quickly. As soon as we finish attacking the Aksu Empire, I expect that the end would be too soon.”

Zhao Hai smiled faintly and didn’t say anything more. But he still regarded Wales’ words. Whether it be the Radiant Church or the Aksu Empire, both of them had underestimated the combat power of the Beastmen. They thought that with their plan, the Beastmen would surely suffer a lot. But now that the Beastmen had known their arrangement, the trump card that they had prepared was now useless. It would now be very difficult for them to succeed. At this point, the Beastmen wasn’t afraid of anyone.

After chatting with Wales for quite some time, Zhao Hai left the Beastman Camp. He then walked towards the direction of the Prairie before vanishing to the Space when no one can no longer see him.

At this time, Laura and the others were inside the Space. Although Laura was busy with handling the Markey Family, she still loved staying inside the Space. The atmosphere inside the Space was very good, and it was also very comfortable inside. It was no wonder that people were reluctant to leave.

Aside from handling the Markey Family’s matters inside the Space, Laura had also chosen to simply live inside the Space. In fact, Zhao Hai did the same, he was now mainly staying inside the Villa.

Lizzy was now back at Carson City’s Imperial Palace. Naturally, that was only for formality. In reality, the majority of her time was spent inside the Space. She would only exit during the times where she would accompany the Emperor. The Emperor didn’t know about any of these, he thought that Lizzy wanted to stay here with him, this made him unbearably glad.

Seeing that Zhao Hai had returned, Laura and the others went to greet him. Everything that Zhao Hai said and did while in the Beastman camp was known to them. After seeing the arrangements of the Beast King, Laura and the others knew that the time of war was already decided.

After the group sat down, Laura looked at Zhao Hai and smiled, “Brother Hai, isn’t this just like watching a play? To be honest, I think that there would be no suspense in the result of this war.”

Zhao Hai smiled and said, “It is indeed like a play. With the Beastmen’s arrangement, the Radiant Church wouldn’t be able to gain any advantage. Even if the Beastmen didn’t go all out, all of their troops were still the elite. This attack would certainly give a lesson to the Radiant Church. With how the church underestimates the Beastmen, the result of this war wouldn’t be a huge mystery.”

Lizzy frowned and said, “Big Brother Hai, what if the Radiant Church goes all-out desperately, making their 9th ranks move? You should know that the Radiant Church are able to do this.”

Zhao Hai’s brows wrinkled and then said, “That is possible. But I think that the Beastmen should already be prepared for this outcome. After all, this war is extremely important to their survival. It would be impossible for the Beastmen to prepare poorly. Cai’er, in the Beastman Camp, can you spot any 9th rank experts?”

Cai’er shook her head and said, “Not in the Beastman Camp. However, I can detect several 9th ranks outside the camp. From what I can see there were no less than ten 9th rank Beastman experts.”

Zhao Hai nodded, then he turned his head to Laura and the others and said, “I thought so. You should have seen the Beast King, he isn’t a simple character. He can’t allow their army to be overly underprepared. After all, elites of the Beastmen Race came to participate in the war. If a 9th rank was to come and eradicate them, the damage done to the Beastmen would surely be severe.”

Megan nodded and said, “I also think that the Beast King isn’t simple, just by what I can see in the monitor. Although he is a Beastman, his temperament doesn’t have any difference compared to Human Monarchs. Even his Majesty the Emperor looked worse compared to him.”

Lizzy wasn’t offended, instead she nodded and said, “That’s true, compared to the Beast King, my father looked less domineering. Most importantly, the Beast King seemed to be a veteran fighter himself. No wonder he can make decisions in such a short period of time.”

Chapter 544: The Fight Begins

Zhao Hai smiled and said, “He became the Beast King, how could he be so simple? Beast Kings are different from Human Monarchs. Beast Kings aren’t permanent, if the Beast King becomes unqualified, he would immediately get dethroned.”

Laura nodded, and then said, “I think this is a great method. This way, they would gain a good leader that will benefit the entire Beastman Race.

Zhao Hai faintly smiled, “This is in line to the nature of the Beastmen. They need a strong leader, but that leader must also gain their recognition.”

Megan then said, “Big Brother Hai, since the Beastmen changed their point of attack to the Iksa Family, will the Purcell Family be more relaxed?”

Zhao Hai shook his head and said, “Not necessarily. The Beastmen would still be doing an attack to Iron Wall Fortress as a diversion. But don’t expect that this diversion would be any weak. Moreover, once they pierce through the Iksa Domain, the attack on Iron Wall Fortress would certainly turn more violent. The Beastmen wanted to advance in two directions since this would derail the Radiant Church’s preparations.”

Megan sighed and said, “So you’re saying, that there’s only a small chance for the Purcell Duchy to be spared?”

Zhao Hai sighed, he already thought about this situation. It was already on his mind when he asked Evan to leave. No matter which way the Beastmen move, the Purcell Family would still suffer bad luck.

The position of the Purcell Family determined their fate. Their territory was too close to the Beastman Prairie. Because of this, once the Beastmen decided to attack, they would be the first ones to experience it.

Fortunately for them, the relationship between the Beastmen and the Humans were going peacefully in the past few years. Because of this, the Purcell Family has been living good lives. And as a result they had increased their grain trade towards the Prairie. This would not only bring them profits, it would also provide the Beastmen some food, making them refrain from attacking the Duchy.

The Beastman Prairie is too big, but there were still Beastmen who couldn’t have their own land there. Therefore, once the Beastmen go to war with the Humans, the latter would definitely have a hard time. So the Humans weren’t willing to act unreasonably and spite the Beastmen’s rage.

Laura also sighed, then she turned her attention to the screen and said, “Who knows how many people are going to die in the Aksu Empire.”

Zhao Hai sighed as well, “We can only accept this outcome. Don’t forget, if it weren’t for us, not only would there be deaths in the Aksu Empire, a lot of Beastmen would die as well. The Radiant Church are planning genocide, they’re religious maniacs, that’s what they do.”

Laura felt helpless, she knew that what Zhao Hai said wasn’t nonsense. The people of the Radiant Church had clear intentions. They always regarded all of those who didn’t believe in the Radiant God as heretics. And for the Church, the Beastmen were the greatest heretics out there. If the Radiant Church managed to deal with all of the Beastmen Elite at this time, then the other Beastmen wouldn’t be able to fare very well.

Lizzy looked at the monitor and said, “We shall see what the Radiant Church would do in the next few days. But in my opinion, they are going to fail this time. However, this shouldn’t be affect them in a big way. After all, they only sent in a Red-robed Archbishop this time. Also, the bulk of their manpower was still from the Aksu Empire. They didn’t use much of their own strength.”

Zhao Hai nodded and said, “But with this failure, their reputation should suffer quite a blow. And with their occupation of the Aksu Empire, those other countries that they had been friends with would become more vigilant. They would be afraid of falling into the same state.”

Lizzy nodded, “That would be better. The Radiant Church’s present influence had gone too big. This is a bad thing for the stability of the Continent.”

Zhao Hai nodded, then he looked at the Beastmen on the monitor. They didn’t make a move immediately, and were still in the middle of preparation. Since there was nothing else to look at, Zhao Hai looked at the others and said, “Alright, let’s take a break. I think the Beastmen will move tonight. Let’s wait until then and watch.”

Laura nodded, then she looked at Zhao Hai and said, “Now that the entire continent knows the bad things that had happened to the Iksa Family as well as the current situation of the Purcell Duchy, they would surely start to pay attention towards the Radiant Church. The Radiant Church should be attaching great importance to this war, otherwise, they would be placed in a disadvantage once they get defeated.”

Zhao Hai agreed, “I think that the Radiant Church already understood this point. However, they are too convinced of their flawless preparations. But they didn’t expect us to have the scissors that would cut a hole in their plans.”

As soon as Laura and the others heard Zhao Hai, they smiled. After looking at the time and chatting for a few moments, all of them took a rest. Zhao Hai believed that the Beastmen would take action in this evening. He wanted to see how they plan to move.

It was not only Zhao Hai who thought about this, the entire continent was also paying attention. They wanted to know how the Beastmen would start the war. Although they didn’t know about the Radiant Church’s poison, they knew about the arrangements that the church has made. They wanted to know how the Beastmen would get cornered.

The night after Zhao Hai’s visit to the camp, the Beastmen made their move. By the Beast King’s orders, the assigned races left the camp in batches. They didn’t immediately go towards the Iksa Family’s territory. Instead, they turned around and headed back to the Prairie.

With regards to understanding the Prairie, the Humans cannot compete with the Beastmen. Therefore, what they decided to do right now was to head back to the Prairie and the circle around towards the Iksa Family domain, this way they cannot be seen by Humans.

The Prairie was too large that it would be impossible for the Humans to send their assassins and observe the movements of the Beastmen.

Zhao Hai sat in the Space and calmly looked at the movements of the Beastmen. He knew that the war was starting. But in this war, his contribution was only the information that he gave, he will not be involved firsthand. At the very best he can be described as a bystander.

Laura also observed the Beastmen’s movement. After looking at the monitor for a while, Laura turned her head to Zhao Hai and smiled, “Brother Hai, if another person tells me that the Beastmen are dumb, I would scold them like child.”

Megan and the other ladies were observing as well. The movement of the Beastmen were done discreetly. They didn’t move a lot of troops nor did they take them all. They left some in order to act as decoys, confusing the enemy. This actions were very remarkable, one that deserved merit.

Zhao Hai forced a smile and said, “The Beastmen aren’t really dumb, they are just seen like that because of their temperament and the way some of them easily trust people. Right, no need to talk about that. It seems like there’s nothing else to see right now. Damn, we miscalculated, I slept too much during the day. Now I cannot sleep anymore. My wives, should we do something else?”

When they heard Zhao Hai, they stared for a moment before they understood. All of their faces couldn’t help but get red, then Laura snorted and said, “All of us are here. Can you handle it? Are you going to be okay?”

Zhao Hai seemed offended as he said, “I will prove it today!” Then he threw himself towards Laura and the others as a squeal was heard in the villa.

The next morning, the Beastmen started their attack on Iron Mountain Fort. Their attacks were loud like thunder but was weak like raindrop. Although they looked aggressive, their contact with the enemy was not really a lot.

This made Evan and the others surprised. They understood that this wasn’t how the Beastmen were supposed to fight. Did the Beastmen change their ways?

Zhao Hai knew that the Beastmen didn’t change, they just didn’t want too many casualties in this deceptive attack. Although Zhao Hai can just tell these matters to Evan, he chose to refrain from doing so. There were times where a person cannot be too selfless.

If he tells Evan about the Radiant Church’s poison and Evan connects it to the response of the Beastmen, Evan would find out that he leaked the information to the Beastmen. If Evan knows, then it wouldn’t take a long time before everyone in the continent knows. When this spreads, Zhao Hai would become a traitor to the eyes of the other humans. And this wasn’t something that Zhao Hai wanted to see.

Although in the mind of Zhao Hai, the Humans and the Beastmen were no different. But in the Ark Continent, the two of them were distinct. This sentiment wasn’t something that Zhao Hai can change alone.

If he makes the Humans know that he helped the Beastmen deal with other Humans, then he would certainly become the Human race’s number one enemy. He will turn into a traitor, this was not a wonderful outcome.

Because of this, Zhao Hai didn’t tell Evan about the situation of both the Radiant Church and the Beastman Race. After all, Evan and the others were already convinced that they’d die, and Zhao Hai also needed to consider the entire Buda Clan.

The Beastmen weren’t fools, they knew that if their deceptive attacks were done halfheartedly, people would start to doubt. Therefore, when evening came, they also made a night assault. This made Evan prepare for battles at night in addition to the  battles at day.

Naturally, the night assault didn’t succeed, but this also dispersed some of the doubts that Evan had. But at the same time as the assault on Iron Wall Fortress, the relocated Beastman army proceeded to head towards the Iksa Family’s territory. The Hawk Tribe then sent this information over to the Beast King at the soonest possible time.

Now, the Radiant Church was playing a game with the Beastmen. The Radiant Church had opened a poisonous bag for the Beastmen to crawl into. But the Beastmen actually put out an act while at the same time, sending a knife to cut the bag at the side. If the Beastmen succeed, then the Radiant Church would have to take a long time before they can recover.

The Radiant Church wasn’t aware that the Beastmen had already found out about their poison plan. They had always thought that the Beastmen would obediently go enter their trap. The Radiant Church’s understanding about the recent encounter was that the Beastmen had come from afar and still hasn’t adapted to the environment, which explains the weakness of their initial attack.

Chapter 545: The Radiant Church’s Hope

The next day, the Beastman attack on the Wall had suddenly become violent. The Beast King understood that if the Beastmen were to continue on with its half-hearted attack, the Humans would start to look down on them. Therefore, he made the army increase the intensity of their assault. This motion can also shield the other group much more effectively.

Sure enough, the continent began to focus their attention towards Iron Wall Fortress. The Humans were very familiar with the Beastman Race, they knew that the Beastmen had combat capabilities not lower compared to the Humans. At the same time, the Beastmen weren’t mindless fighters as well. Then can also do advanced movements such as carrying out reconnaissance missions, especially the Hawk Tribe. With their flying abilities, their scouts were vastly better than the Humans.

Because of this, the Radiant Church had placed a large amount of their army in the Iksa Territory while leaving the Purcell Family to face the Beastmen alone. This way, when the Beastmen see the heavily armored soldiers in the Iksa Territory, they would think twice in attacking there and would instead opt to attack the Purcell Duchy. This was the script that the Radiant Church had written for the Beastmen.

And so, the Beastmen were fully cooperating in this play. They launched a frantic attack at Iron Wall Fortress, making the Purcell Family suffer huge losses. The Beastmen’s losses weren’t small either, but they were used to it, this was the Beastmen’s way of attack, frantic, and without a shred of holding back.

This crazy attacking method of the Beastmen was something that only few humans can withstand. Therefore, ordinary human armies wouldn’t go to field battles with the Beastmen. This was because they were aware that the Beastmen Cavalry would have its greatest strength in the field.

Although the Heavy Armored Infantry of the continent can cope with the Beastman Cavalry, that consideration was only made against general Beastman Cavalry. When it comes to the Big Warring Races, those Heavy Armored Infantry would become totally powerless.

Naturally, the Humans also had a way of dealing with these Beastman Cavalries. Most Beastmen didn’t have any armor, but Humans have Heavy Armor Cavalry. The charge of these Heavy Armor Cavalry can be lethal against the Beastmen. However, creating Heavy Armor Cavalry was extremely expensive. Even a powerful empire such as the Aksu Empire only had a few of these cavalries on hand.

Also, Beastmen weren’t very good at siege warfare. Beastman wars generally happen on the flat fields of the Prairie, with both cavalries going head to head with each other. Because of this, the Beastmen didn’t have much experience when it came to attacking a city.

On the other hand, Humans were experts in siege warfare. In the entire human history, most of its battles were siege battles. So they were knowledgeable about attacking and defending a city. Therefore, in a war between Beastmen and Humans, the most important thing that Humans could do was barricade a city and establish a line of defense. Stacking them layer by layer in order to stop the Beastman attacks.

The people wanted to see when the Beastmen can break through Iron Wall Fortress. One must know that Iron Wall Fortress was very famous in the Continent. This was because the Fortress was able to block a Beastman attack in the past. Now, the people want to see if the Purcell Family can make a miracle this time.

The Beastmen  attacked Iron Wall Fortress for seven days. Although these these seven days weren’t long, they weren’t short either. One must know that the Beastmen had sent an army that exceeded 1 million soldiers. While at the same time, the defenders were numbering less than 100 thousand.

And these 100 thousand people were all the soldiers that the Purcell Family can send out. All of them were already convinced of their deaths, this made the battle even more fierce.

In seven days, the Purcell Family had lost nearly 50 thousand people, but the Beastmen had lost close to 100 thousand. The battle loss ratio numbered 1 to 2. This was something rare for a battle between Humans and Beastmen. Because of the innate disadvantage in strength by the Humans, their losses should be higher than that of the Beastmen. For the Beastmen to lose more than the Humans was something that was very abnormal.

However, only the Purcell troops knew that the army that was attacking the Fortress wasn’t the main force of the Beastman race. With their main force not participating, it was natural that the battle loss ratio would be like this. If the Main force of the Beastmen would attack right now, then they’re afraid that they would not be able to defend.

Evan and the others knew about the Beastmen from their past battles. In the past, the Beastmen would send their Main Force 2 or 3 days after the initial skirmish. But this time, 7 days had already passed, but the Warring Tribes were still not in sight. What was happening?

And at this moment, a shocking news spread out to the Continent. On the seventh evening after the attack on the Purcell Duchy, the Iksa Family was suddenly attacked by a large group of Warriors from Big Beastman Warring Tribes. Although the Radiant Church had stationed a large army in the Iksa Domain, they were still caught off guard by the Beastman assault. The Beastmen Cavalry quickly pierced through their defense line and ravaged through their formation. This led to the three hundred thousand army inside the Iksa Domain to throw their helmets down and abandon their armor in order to escape, they were completely routed!

The force that attacked the Iksa Family was the Main Force of the Beastmen army. They were the elite of the elites, and they were highly experienced in battles. With them numbering 100 hundred thousand, they were able to swiftly deal with 300 thousand human soldiers. The battle can only be described as a textbook victory.

Both the Human forces and the Radiant Church didn’t expect the Beastmen to attack like this. The continent immediately went into an uproar. They didn’t think that all of these crazy Beastman attacks towards the Iron Wall Fortress were only a cover for their surprise attack on the Iksa Domain.

Even if they lost 100 thousand in attacking the Fortress, it was definitely worth it. They had managed to rout a 300 thousand Human army as well as occupy a very large Domain in the Human Territory.

One should know that even if the commoners of the Purcell Family withdrew, the commoners in the Iksa Domain didn’t. This was because there was an army stationed here, and they have gathered a lot of supplies. But now, all of these supplies fell into the hands of the Beastmen, aiding them in overcoming their food crisis.

The Radiant Church clearly didn’t expect the Beastman attack, they had been caught off-guard. All of their previous plans were starting to form cracks. Fortunately, they still had room for movement. The Church immediately withdrew some of their troops in the Purcell Duchy and prepared to lead them to encircle the Iksa Domain.

But just as the Radiant Church troops were being mobilized, the beastmen began to attack Iron Wall Fortress non-stop from day to night. Although the Purcell Family were doing their best to block the Beastmen offensive, they couldn’t block it in the end. At the last moment, Evan was forcibly carried away by some loyal subjects of the Purcell Family. The direction that they were retreating to was Stony Mountain.

This was a hidden move orchestrated by Zhao Hai. After he left Ruyen and the others at Golden Island, the requested Origin Sword Saint to act. Origin Sword Saint convened with some of the Purcell Family’s loyal 8th ranks secretly. Origin Sword Saint asked them that no matter what happens, they should protect some important members of the Purcell Duchy and had them retreat towards Stony Mountain. Once they retreat to Stony Mountain, their lives would certainly be protected.

Origin Sword Saint’s words were much more powerful compared to Evan, therefore, those 8th ranks didn’t disagree. So they immediately grabbed Evan and then rode some Magic Beasts that they prepared before. Carrying food and water with them, they immediately headed straight to Stony Mountain.

The Purcell Family members who escaped this time numbered less than 200 altogether. Majority of these people were Foreign Elders of the Family, in fact, most of them were 8th rank experts.

The Beastmen didn’t pursue them this time. They didn’t pay any attention to measly 200 people. What they were eyeing right now were those soldiers that were heading towards the Iksa Domain to encircle the 100 thousand Beastmen.

Once again, the Radiant Church didn’t expect that just as they transferred the troops, the Beastmen would suddenly break through Iron Wall Fortress. Now, the troops that the Radiant Church had sent over were in fear of being sandwiched by two Beastmen armies.

The Radiant Church expected the Beastmen army in Iron Wall Fortress to be just a normal decoy, their fighting strength shouldn’t be that strong. The Main Force should be the 100 thousand that just attacked the Iksa Domain. They didn’t expect that the decoy would become another attacking force and had broken through Iron Wall Fortress in one stroke, becoming a threat to the Church’s  armies.

Passive! The Radiant Church had turned passive. One must know that the force that was currently occupying the Iksa Domain were the collective forces of various Warring Tribes, and were numbering 100 thousand. At the same time, the 1 million Beastman army that had just broken through Iron Wall Fortress were at their back. This made the Radiant Church army feel a sense of crisis.

But the Radiant Church didn’t give up, they were still hoping that their trump card would have some use. They still have the poison that they had prepared. Even if the Iron Wall Fortress was broken through, the experts sent to the Purcell Domain were still there, lying in ambush.

These people were waiting in the Purcell Duchy for the time when the Fortress falls. As long as the Beastmen enter the Duchy, they would immediately be poisoned, then the Radiant Church can deal with the Beastmen Army easily.

In the mind of the Radiant Church, even if their plans were somewhat derailed, they were still heading towards the right direction. The losses that they incurred in the Iksa Domain was nothing remarkable. Having a victory in the Iksa Domain might even make the Beastmen complacent, making the Radiant Church’s plan much easier to implement.

At the same time, the two-pronged attack by the Beastmen still gave some losses to the Radiant Church. But this was what they exactly need, they wanted the Beastmen to enter the Aksu Empire before they start to clean them up in one swoop. That way, the Beastmen would have no opportunity to escape.

Chapter 546: Negotiations

The ideal situation is good, but reality is different! This might have been the current mindset of the Radiant Church. They wanted to deal with the Beastman Race alone in order to gain prestige. They had rejected the help of the Rosen Empire and several nations in order to show their own strength.

One should know that if Zhao Hai didn’t help, then the Beastmen might possibly suffer a huge loss. But that and right now were two completely different matters.

The people from the Radiant Church thinks that their poison can deal with the Beastmen. But they haven’t thought that the Beastmen were already aware of this, and had also drank the antidote.

Since the Beast King knew about this plan of the Radiant Church, therefore, he decided to cooperate with the Radiant Church. This way, he would reverse the situation and make the Beastmen the ones who would sweep the Church’s troops in one blow. And when the Aksu Empire is devoid of its defenders, then the Beastmen can do whatever they wanted to do.

Information was truly important, having and not having information can change everything. And it was evident that the Radiant Church had lost in this aspect.

After the Beastmen entered the Purcell Duchy, they didn’t destroy anything and just started to loot. Everything that they find useful was carried off.

This was also the goal of the Beastmen for this war. However, they also did it deliberately. They wanted to slow down their offensive and give the Radiant Church some time to make their move.

The Beastmen gave the Radiant Church some time because they wanted them to think that things are all going according to their plan. This way, the Radiant Church would drop their vigilance. And then the Beastmen can use this opportunity to thoroughly deal with the Radiant Church.

The time for all of this to pass might be very long, but in fact, it only happened for a short time. Upon entering the Purcell Duchy, the Beastmen directly became a threat to the left wing of the Church’s army. But they didn’t go and attack the army immediately, instead they went to occupy the Duchy first. Although the Purcell Duchy people had left, it was impossible for them to carry everything that they had. Moreover, the Purcell Family didn’t burn the granaries of the Duchy. Therefore, the Beastmen had gained a lot in pillaging the Duchy.

The Radiant Church wanted the Beastmen to do exactly this. If the Beastmen immediately attacked the Radiant Church, then it would be very troublesome, the Church’s losses would surely be big. But since the Beastmen stopped for now, this gave the Church the opportunity to lay their ambush.

Although the Radiant Church had prepared to use poison to deal with the Beastmen, the poison would need to be administered through either food or water. But it was difficult to poison the food right now. After all, the grains were under the care of the Purcell Family in the past, it wasn’t easy to lace them at that time. Therefore, the only choice they had right now was the water.

But everyone shouldn’t forget that water does flow. Even if it was well water, it was still running water. If one places poison in it, then it would be purified after several days. Therefore, one needed to find an opportune moment to administer the poison.

If the Beastmen continued to attack the troops of the Radiant Church, then the Radiant Church wouldn’t have found an opportunity. But since the Beastmen stopped, then the opportunity for them to deliver the poison has come.

The Radiant Church couldn’t help but thank the Beastmen secretly. But what they didn’t expect was that they were spied on by the Black Panther Tribe.

The Black Panthers were dark attributed Beastmen. Their innate talents were quite formidable, they were the Beastmen version of Human assassins. Therefore, they were the ones who were responsible for facing the Human assassins. After the Beast King knew about the Radiant Church’s plan, he had some 8th rank Black Panthers check the water sources near their camps. When a Human was spotted, the Black Panthers didn’t stop them, their movements were just reported over to the Beast King.

Just on the third day after the Beastmen entered the Purcell Duchy, the Black Panthers had seen people from the Radiant Church poison their water source. So they immediately passed this information to the Beast King. Once the Beast King heard about this, he knew that the time for action was drawing close. Therefore he immediately sent  Hawks towards the Iksa Domain and coordinated their actions with the Beastman army there.

At this time, the Purcell Family people had already reached Stony Mountain. Upon arriving, Zhao Hai was already there waiting for them.

When Evan saw Zhao Hai, his eyes couldn’t help but turn red. Then with a sincere voice, he said, “Little Hai, thank you. If it weren’t for you, I might have already died.”

Zhao Hai smiled and said, “Uncle, you can’t blame me for being good. Right, come with me to the courtyard. Then we’ll head to Golden Island.” Evan and the others already understood what Zhao Hai meant. So they didn’t say anything else and just nodded, then they went to the courtyard together.

After arriving, Zhao Hai didn’t take Evan to Golden Island using the Space. He wanted to use a Blood Hawk to send Evan and the others to the shore and had them take a boat to Golden Island.

This time, most of the people who came with Evan weren’t from the Purcell Family. The majority of them were Foreign Elders. Although they are loyal to the Purcell Family, and haven’t left Evan after all this time, Zhao Hai still cannot be assured that information about Space would not be spread around.

The reason why he revealed his secret to Origin Sword Saint was because Zhao Hai knew how attractive the Space was towards the 9th rank expert.

The energy in the Space was very active, moreover, it was very rich. For 9th rank experts, it was the best place to cultivate in. Such a place can may allow them to break through the last barrier and get more powerful. For a 9th rank expert, this was a very big deal. Therefore, Zhao Hai was not afraid that Origin Sword would tell others about the Space.

After resting at Bluestone Villa for some time, Zhao Hai made them board the Blood Hawks. Zhao Hai rode a Blood Hawk as well. Then he delivered the group to the shore and had them board a ship towards Golden Island. He didn’t go with them since he still had to watch a play.

After the Radiant Church delivered the poison towards the water sources of the Beastmen. They stayed at the water source and waited for the Beastmen to fetch some water.

What worried the people of the Radiant Church was that the Beastmen might have fetched some water the day before. If they will not get water, then the poison would not be delivered.

But when the Beastmen started to continually fetch water, moreover, it was a lot, the people of the Radiant Church immediately got excited.

After eating their meal, the noise Beastman camp surprisingly became quite. The people from the Radiant Church wanted to confirm and entered the Beastman camp to take a look. Presently, there were a lot of Beastmen who were on the ground and can’t get up. When the people were about to kill some, they immediately heard a Hawk’s cry. This frightened the people from the Radiant Church. They were finally reminded about the Hawk Tribe. Therefore, they immediately left the camp and notified the Radiant Church.

After confirming that those people had left, the Beastmen immediately got up and livened up. But this time, it wasn’t for leisure, it was instead to prepare to receive the attack of the Radiant Church.

They knew that once the Radiant Church heard succeeded in poisoning them, the Church would definitely send people to attack. Once they arrive expecting to kill the Beastmen, the Beastman army would then strike them immediately and then extinguish the remaining Radiant Church army.

When Lundi Becker received the word, he immediately issued an order for an all-out attack. But little did they know, the Beastmen were already preparing an encirclement and were only waiting for the Radiant Church’s army to come forward.

The next events can be clearly predicted. When the Radiant Church’s army entered the Beastman’s encirclement, they were immediately eliminated. Then the Beastmen proceeded to push through deeper into the Aksu Empire. The two armies looked like two unstoppable arrows as it pieced the empire. They were rarely met by any resistance, this was because most of their soldiers were already killed off by the Beastmen.

The entire continent was shocked, the Radiant Church was shocked, and most importantly, the Aksu Empire was shocked. At this point, the Aksu Empire had already lost all forms of resistance.

The Beastman army had already eliminated about 2 million Aksu Empire soldiers, this was almost equal to the Empire’s entire national defense. One must also consider that fact that they had lost a lot of people at Golden Island. The Aksu Empire was now very weak.

The Beastmen didn’t go too far this time. Instead of dealing with the commoners, they directly pillaged the Nobles, especially those who had connections with the Radiant Church.

Additionally, every time they take over a city of the empire, they would wantonly shout that the reason for their assault towards the Aksu Empire was the Radiant Church’s involvement in their food shortage.

Originally, this news had already spread on the continent, but it was only hearsay and wasn’t confirmed. But now that the Beastmen were saying it, how could it be wrong? This immediately made the Radiant Church the most despised people in the Aksu Empire.

The Beastman attack was also peculiar this time. They didn’t go and take some humans to be their slaves. They just came and grabbed some food, they didn’t rob the commoners and only pillaged the storehouses of the Nobles as well as the national granaries of the Aksu Empire.

Actually, the Beastmen were still harming the commoners with this action. Because the national granaries were robbed, the grain market of the Aksu Empire would surely be affected. The prices of food would rise and the commoners would suffer. But the commoners weren’t thinking about this, the Beastmen not robbing them was already a blessing.Their minds were on something else.

The Aksu Empire cannot fall right now. So they had to seek aid from the Rosen Empire. The Rosen Empire also complied and negotiated with the Beastmen.

Naturally, the Rosen Empire didn’t want to wipe the Radiant Church’s buttocks. Therefore, they didn’t go and resist the Beastman army. Instead, the directly went and negotiated with the Beastmen.

Although the Beastmen hasn’t overrun the entire Aksu Empire, one might as well consider it as so. But when the Rosen Empire sent people to negotiate, they immediately stopped. After all, the strength of the Rosen Empire was something that they needed to consider. If they involved the Rosen Empire in this war, the Beastmen would suffer a lot more losses.

The Beast King was also a very astute person. Their attack against the Humans had gone smoothly. Although they had lost some men, compared to their previous wars, this time was the one they had lost the least while having the biggest harvest. And at this time, if the Humans were to agree to trade them grain at a fair price, they would immediately retreat.

Just as what Zhao Hai has thought before, the Beastmen didn’t want to occupy the Human Domain. They weren’t interested in Human lands. In their view, the Prairie was their home, it was where their root was. If they settle inside Human territory, then a time would certainly come when they would become as weak as the Human race.

In the minds of the Beastmen, the Humans were very weak, this was their belief. Therefore, they preferred to drink and sing on the Prairie.

The Beast King making the decision to stop was also largely because of Zhao Hai. When Zhao Hai left the Beastman camp, the Beast King sent someone to go and fetch Wales. Naturally, the Beast King asked Wales about Zhao Hai’s strength. And when Wales told him, this made the Beast King look at Zhao Hai in another light.

Although the Beast King appreciated Zhao Hai before, he didn’t care too much about him. But when he heard Wales say that Zhao Hai had a 1 million Undead army, he immediately took Zhao Hai seriously.

One could say that the most annoying thing for the Beastmen to face were the Undead. This was because one cannot obtain any advantages against the Undead, If one doesn’t have the means to deal with the Dark Mage, then one shouldn’t dare go and offend them. For the Beastmen, doing so would only bring them losses. Zhao Hai can just attack the Prairie and make some undead along the way, this was truly something terrible to think about.

The Beast King also understood that they were now in Human Territory. If they offend the Rosen Empire as well as Zhao Hai, the terrifying Dark Mage, it certainly wouldn’t be a good thing for the Beastmen. And this time, the reason for their attack on the Aksu Empire was to get some food. As long as the problem of food is solved, then they would return to the Beastman Prairie. After all, they had already acquired a lot of things.

The purpose of the negotiation of the Rosen Empire was to let the Beastmen retreat. Additionally, the Rosen Emperor believed in Zhao Hai’s words and hoarded a lot of food in advance. Now that they had the stockpile they can go and talk with the Beastmen. They would have the Beastmen retreat, and later on, they would provide a food supply to the Beastmen at a fair price.

No country liked to go to war, especially a war that the Radiant Church had started. This would only result in them cleaning up after the Radiant Church’s mess. This made the other monarchs unhappy, if they were to send people to help, how many of them would have to die? They don’t want this outcome.

Chapter 547: Damaged Vitality

Benefit! Everything was for benefit! The Beastmen went to war because of benefits, the Radiant Church plotted war with the Beastmen for benefit, the Rosen Empire stepped in for benefit as well.

Speaking about sentiment to these big influences was a behaviour of a complete idiot. Even the stern and straightforward Beastmen move according to benefits. If they cannot get any benefits, they they wouldn’t hesitate to continue on with this war. The reason why the Beastmen went to war was because they knew that they can get benefits out of it. But the Humans didn’t like war, it was because they cannot gain anything about it. It was this simple.

The negotiations were conducted very smoothly. The Beast King wanted a result where they can get grain at a fair price. This way, the Beastmen can get more benefits.

Naturally, they also knew that if they conquer the Humans, the Humans can continue to plant some grains for them. But at the same time, they also knew that it was impossible for them to rule over the Humans. They can gain benefits in this war, but it was impossible to conquer the Humans because of the vastly different cultures. Since the Beastmen cannot rule the Humans for too long, they’d rather settle for an agreement on selling food at a fair price.

However, after bargaining for the price of food, the Beastmen made a request. They demanded that the Radiant Church should be severely punished. This war was after all caused by the Radiant Church.

Regarding this request of the Beastmen, the negotiators from the other nations had differing thoughts. Some of them had relationships with the Radiant Church, while some of them did not.

However, if they don’t comply, the Beastmen might decide to stay and attack again. Even if they repel the Beastmen, what did they obtain? Nothing. This was an outcome that the various nations didn’t want to see.

In the end of the day, the representatives from the other nations decided that they would comply with the Beastmen’s demands first. In any case, after the Beastmen left, the judgement would still depend on their respective countries.

After obtaining a satisfactory result, the Beastmen finally returned to the Prairie with a large amount of food that were compensated to them by the Aksu Empire. However, things among the Humans weren’t finished yet.

The Aksu Empire’s vitality has been severely damaged. But the Rosen Empire cannot just let the Aksu Empire go. You had made your own trouble, and we helped you solve it, and you want to place that in the past? How could that be possible?

Therefore, the Rosen Empire and the others made demands towards the Aksu Empire. Among those demands were money while some had others. The Rosen Empire didn’t ask for monetary compensation, they only had one request. And that request was to give the Purcell Duchy to the Buda Clan as a fief.

The Buda Clan being a Noble of the Aksu Empire wasn’t false. But, there was an ongoing resentment between the two. Even children in the continent knew about the enmity between the two. Therefore, it was a non spoken decision that the Buda Clan was no longer a part of Aksu Empire.

But even so, the Buda Clan was still a Marquis in the Aksu Empire, and they also had their own fief. They were also people of the Aksu Empire.

However, the Rosen Empire’s request placed the Aksu Empire in a very awkward position, so the agreement was still put on hold. The Aksu Empire was in its weakest state, while the Rosen Empire’s condition was still as smooth as silk, left completely unharmed. The Rosen Empire can definitely demand for a piece of territory. If the Rosen Empire would occupy the lifeline canyon, the Aksu Empire would be in trouble.

But if they comply to the Rosen Empire, it would be equivalent to placing a thorn on the side of the Aksu Empire. Under this circumstance, the Aksu Empire’s future wouldn’t be so good.

Like the Rosen Empire, the other three countries also put forward their own demands. They didn’t ask for land, after all, they were too far away from the Aksu Empire. Getting land would be useless. Instead, they demanded a huge amount of money as compensation. This made the Aksu Empire not know what to do.

This time, it wasn’t one Empire that were making things difficult for them, but instead four Empires working simultaneously. The Aksu Empire cannot even think of what to do next. Most importantly, most of their forces were already gone. Which made their power of negotiation very weak.

The reason why the Rosen Empire didn’t conquer the Aksu Empire was because the latter had just suffered defeat under the Beastmen. If they invade the Aksu Empire, they would be looked down by everyone on the continent.

But even if the Rosen Empire cannot invade the Aksu Empire, they can still make an outrageous demand, enough to economically cripple the Aksu Empire.

If the Aksu Empire were still in its most flourishing time, they might decline to the Rosen Empire’s demands. But it was unfortunate for them that they were currently in their lowest point. This weakness was not only in terms of military power, this also included their damaged economy.

Although the Beastmen didn’t take anything away from the commoners, they still emptied the national granaries of the Aksu Empire. Moreover, they also killed some Nobles of several cities and then snatched their belongings, especially the grain. Because of this, one can consider that the economy of the Aksu Empire had been held back for at least 20 years. In this case, if they don’t agree to the demands of the Rosen Empire as well as the other countries, then the four countries would definitely choke their economy. When that happens, it would be impossible for the Aksu Empire to return to its original state.

Most importantly, the two northern strategic places of the Aksu Empire, the Purcel Duchy and the Iksa Domain, has been completely destroyed. The two families had ran to Golden Island, this was something that the continent already knew. Moreover, the vitality of these two families were damaged severely as well. They simply don’t have the ability to continue managing their former territories. This was also the reason why the Rosen Empire proposed that the Aksu Empire would give the Purcell Duchy over to Zhao Hai.

However, the Aksu Empire understood that no matter what happens, they cannot hand that territory over to Zhao Hai. If they gave it to the Buda Clan, the Aksu Empire would get pincered once the Rosen Empire decides to attack in the future. Therefore, they had a difficult negotiation with the Rosen Empire.

There is only one thing in the Aksu Empire’s mind, as long as their territory wasn’t divided, they wouldn’t counter any demands from the Rosen Empire.

In fact, everybody had already seen it, the Rosen Empire didn’t really want the Purcell Duchy. They only wanted to get better benefits.

After an arduous conversation between the two sides, the Aksu Empire agreed to compensate the Rosen Empire with a huge amount of money. At the same time, they also removed all of the tariffs given to Rosen Empire’s traded commodities.

But what made people feel strange was the unusual disappearance of Zhao Hai. One must know that the Rosen Empire had used his name in negotiating with the Aksu Empire. However, he still didn’t appear even at the very end. This was really not like Zhao Hai’s action.

In reality, Zhao Hai was also very busy in the past few days. He was currently collecting war corpses. The war had produced a lot of corpses, moreover, the majority of them were strong soldiers. They corpses were incredibly useful to Zhao Hai.

This war between the Beastmen and the Humans had made more than 1 million corpses. Some of these bodies were buried by the Beastmen, but some were not. After all, Zhao Hai also knew that if corpses were left out for too long, diseases would start to take form and might even start an epidemic. Therefore, he decided to take those corpses and make them into undead.

Even so, Zhao Hai was still aware about the negotiations. But he didn’t think too much about it. He knew from the very beginning that it would be impossible for the Aksu Empire to agree. Although the Aksu Empire was currently weak, the Rosen Empire still wouldn’t go too far in causing them trouble.

On the other hand, Zhao Hai despised the people of the Radiant Church. Everyone was now aware that Boris had become the emperor, but by then, the Radiant Church had already left the Aksu Empire.

Zhao Hai hated the action of the Radiant Church, this was just like the Church had just left behind their ally and ran away.

Currently, Boris didn’t have the best appearance in the world. Dealing with the Purcell Duchy and the Iksa Domain was his idea. But now that they had failed, the Empire had been placed in a very bad situation. If the Aksu Empire wasn’t given 20 years, then it would be impossible for them to recover.

Even if they recover 20 years later, their strength wouldn’t be the same as before. Not only would they compensate the Beastmen, they would also give some compensations to the four other Empires. This truly damaged the Aksu Empire’s core foundation.

After the negotiations were settled, the Aksu Empire started to officially recover. But this time, the Radiant Church had already become the most hated people in the Aksu Empire. Nobody inside the Aksu Empire had any good feelings towards the Church. One could say that if the Radiant Church wanted to preach here again, it would be more difficult than in the Rosen Empire.

Now that the restoration of the Aksu Empire had started, what they most needed was nothing else other than food. They needed large quantities of them in order to stabilize the market prices. And they need large quantities of them to resume production. After the negotiations with the other empires, the other empires agreed to sell a large amount of food to them at a low price. This had greatly eased the food problem of the Aksu Empire.

Among them, the most famous one was Zhao Hai, who brought a large amount of grain to the Purcell Duchy. This played a very important role in the reconstruction of the Duchy.

The Purcell Duchy and the Iksa Domain now has new lords. The nobles in these two places were the most loyal men of Boris. They hated Zhao Hai before, but they had no choice but to welcome him at this time. This was because whether it be the Purcell Duchy or the Iksa Domain, both needed large amounts of grain in order to settle the residents down.

The grain that Zhao Hai brought, wasn’t the Bread Fruit, but instead the ordinary Bamboo Rice. Zhao Hai believed that the Bread Fruit was more popular among the Beastmen.

Chapter 548: Cooperation

While the Aksu Empire was reconstructing, an upsurge of Anti-Radiant Church sentiment had unknowingly spread out on the continent. This time, it wasn’t only the Rosen Empire, but all countries were starting to do so.

However, the Radiant Church still had their 9th ranks. It wouldn’t be good for the nations to go too far. However, the Radiant Church’s momentum has evidently slowed down.

The reason why the Radiant Church was rapidly growing before was because they had recruited a large number of Nobles into their fold. And this was because they had brought a lot of benefits for these Nobles.

However, in recent times, the Radiant Church had suddenly left their allies, which was maybe good in their opinion. However, it wasn’t for their subordinates, therefore, the church had been pushed into becoming passive.

The Radiant Church had already behaved. Besides the Rosen Empire and the Aksu Empire, the others had now started to fully suppress the church. Their followers were now decreasing massively. It was now very difficult for them to regain their original momentum.

Besides all of these, it was still impossible for the Empires to extinguish the Radiant Church. The church had 9th ranks, for the Great Nobles, these experts were effective deterrents.

Under the suppression of the big Empires, the only thing that the church can do was to best maintain their strength. But a lot of Nobles still decided to withdraw from the organization

One the other hand, Zhao Hai didn’t care much about all of these. He was currently on Golden Island, discussing the future development of the Buda Clan to Evan and Robert.

Zhao Hai had already told the secret of the Space to Evan and Ruyen, but for the other members of the Purcell Family, they were still on observation. Those people weren’t the same as the Iksa Family which hadn’t been infiltrated by the Radiant Church. In truth, Zhao Hai still wasn’t comfortable with those from the Purcell Family.

Although the Buda Clan’s territory didn’t increase, their reputation in the continent did. This was because the Rosen Empire had used the clan’s name as a bargaining chip to negotiate with the Aksu Empire. The Buda Clan was now famous in the entire continent.

The future of the Buda Clan is mainly based on the Black Wastelands, where it was possible to create a country, Now that the Iksa and Purcell Family were already rootless and floating refugees, if they don’t side with the Buda Clan, they it would be difficult for them to appear on the continent in the future.

In the end, what Zhao Hai and the two others decided on was that the Iksa Family would send a team lead by Fernand to Golden Island in order to do business. At the same time, Ruyen would be sent back to the Purcell Duchy. A large amount of grain was brought by Zhao Hai to the Duchy, which helped establish their business there. Now, Zhao Hai wanted to use this opportunity to make a trade network starting from the Purcell family’s previous territory.

If it was before, then there would be some difficulties. But now that the Purcell Family had joined, it doesn’t matter. The family was very familiar with the Duchy, and along with the managers of the Markey Family, the Buda Clan can definitely build  a distribution center in the Duchy, seizing the entire grain market.

Zhao Hai contacted Bell again through the Calci Family, having him come back to Iksa Domain and establish another distribution center there. This center would be a collaboration between the Buda Clan and the Calci Family, so the latter didn’t oppose.

By having these two sales networks, Zhao Hai’s sales would definitely increase in the future. This was very important to the Buda Clan.

The reason why Zhao Hai didn’t go to the Prairie after the war was because he knew that the Beastmen were busy as well.

The Beastmen had snatched a lot of things from the humans, and those items needed to be distributed. And because of these things, the Beastmen shouldn’t need anything at this time. So Zhao Hai decided to postpone his trip to the Prairie to the future.

At the same time, the situation of the Continent was a good opportunity for the Buda Clan. The Continent was now suppressing the Radiant Church, which was also the biggest enemy of Zhao Hai. In the past, the Radiant Church had suppressed them before, but now the situations had been reversed. The Radiant Church was now being suppressed, and the Buda Clan can’t just let this opportunity go.

Although the Buda Clan was still lacking in people, but with the Purcell Family, Markey Family, and Iksa Family joining them, the Buda Clan’s management was now enough. Although some of these people cannot be trusted with the Black Wasteland, managing the Clan’s businesses wouldn’t be an issue.

Zhao Hai was planning to show his business to the Continent in the following days. It was important to know that the if the Buda Clan’s business were to be expanded, it would immediately take a superior position. A reason for this was the Haven products, these products’ quality were already quite well-known in the continent. Moreover, one shouldn’t forget that Zhao Hai still had seafood and Prairie products in his hands.

Products from the Prairie cannot possibly be unique to Zhao Hai. This was because a lot of Human Merchants were also doing business with the Beastmen. Therefore, there were a lot of places in the continent that sold these items.

However, marine products were incredibly rare in the continent. Because of this, these items were in high demand. As long as nobody suppresses them, the Buda Clan would surely be able to quickly expand on the Continent.

Moreover, Zhao Hai wasn’t planning on doing this business alone. He was prepared to cooperate with the Calci Family, Crook Family, Charlie, Rosen Empire, and the Shelley Family.

Working with these people would not only make the Buda Clan’s products spread in the continent at the shortest time, the Buda Clan can also draw its relationship closer with these people.

With this plan in mind, Zhao Hai immediately returned to Wild Dragon Castle outside Carson City after he handled the matters with the Iksa and Purcell Families. Then he prepared himself to fetch Lizzy from the Imperial Palace.

Although Lizzy had been spending the majority of her time inside the Space, if Zhao Hai didn’t meet Lizzy officially, the Emperor might suspect something. Therefore, Zhao Hai must show his face from time to time.

When Zhao Hai returned to Wild Dragon Castle, a servant informed him that Jason had visited several times. Moreover, he had left word that if Zhao Hai comes back, he must immediately go to the Crook Family’s castle.

Zhao Hai stared for a moment before he nodded. Then he immediately rode his carriage and headed towards the Crook Family. It wasn’t the first time that the Crook Family’s servants had seen Zhao Hai, so they immediately removed the road block and had Zhao Hai directly enter the mountain.

Outside the castle, Jason was already waiting for him. When Zhao Hai got down from his carriage, he went towards Jason and laughed, “Brother Jason, I heard that you had come over for a few times. What made you so anxious? But this is also good, even if you didn’t go and find me, I’ll still come and look for you.”

Jason walked forward and then hugged Zhao Hai, “Brother, what took you so long? Come quickly, Grandfather is waiting for you.”

Then the two entered the castle using a carriage. And then they quickly went towards Jesse’s study. Seeing Zhao Hai arrive, Jesse smiled and said, “Kid, it’s been a long time before you’ve come to see this old man. What are you afraid of? You’re a Patriarch of a Great Family, you should have some subordinates to keep your schedule free.”

Zhao Hai couldn’t help but smile helplessly and said, “Grandfather, you really are living comfortably. How can our Buda Clan compare with your Crook Family? If our Buda Clan had a few tricks of yours, then I would be able to sleep at home all the time.”

Jesse laughed and then said, “Sleeping all the time? Kid, you’re going to turn into a pig. Come sit down, I have a matter to speak with you.”

Zhao Hai nodded, then he and Jason sat down. After a servant sent some drinks in, Jesse looked at Zhao Hai and said, “Little Hai, your current spotlight was not small. I really didn’t expect the Rosen Empire to make you into a bargaining chip. But that’s good, the Aksu Empire yielded because you you.”

Zhao Hai forced a smile, “What’s good about that, I didn’t gain anything. Right, Grandfather, why did you ask me to come immediately? Is something wrong?”

Then Jesse smiled and said, “You had been busy since after God’s Grace day, so I didn’t have any opportunity to ask you to come. I just wanted to ask you if you have any business that you wanted to do with us?”

When Zhao Hai heard Jesse, he couldn’t help but smile, he also came today because of this matter. Zhao Hai immediately nodded and said, “You don’t need to look for me, I’m actually planning to come here soon. I have some business that i’d like your help with. Now that the Radiant Church has been suppressed, there’s nobody blocking us from expanding anymore. Therefore, I wan you and father-in-law to cooperate and sell our products in your stores. But I want the prices of our Buda Clan’s products to be uniform in all the stores.”

Jesse stared, then his eyes turned bright. He knew that Zhao Hai has a lot of good things in his hand. If he works with them, then it would be greatly benefiting the Crook Family .

He immediately nodded and said, “Alright, this is not a problem. As for the price? You go can just go and tell us.”

Zhao Hai nodded, then he expressed that their cooperation would include Haven products as well as some Prairie products. He didn’t have a lot of seafood right now, so they had to mainly sell the other two.

But even so, Jesse was still very happy. Haven products and Prairie products were very popular in the continent. Especially the Haven products since they were almost considered to be a unique business. Although they had similar products in the continent, the Buda Clan’s Haven products were the best in terms of quality and price.

Chapter 549: Hundred Thousand Slaves

After Zhao talked with Jesse about their cooperation, they ate a meal together then Zhao Hai returned to Wild Dragon Castle to rest. The next day, he went to Dark Soldier Fort and talked to Randolph about the partnership. Naturally, Randolph also agreed, since the Radiant Church has been suppressed, the Calci Family was also preparing to go all out.

After taking care of everything back at Dark Soldier Fort, Zhao Hai returned to his castle. Laura and the others didn’t follow Zhao Hai, they were inside the Space and handling the matters of the Markey Family and the Buda Clan.

Zhao Hai had always been disinterested in dealing with those things, and his wives had enough strength to handle them, therefore Zhao Hai simply placed those things to be taken care of by them.

The second day after he returned from Dark Soldier Fort, Zhao Hai rode his carriage and headed towards the Imperial Palace. He needed to see the Emperor in order to fetch Lizzy and at the same time, discuss the matter of cooperation.

The Imperial clan also had their own businesses. If Zhao Hai was able to cooperate with them,  he could achieve a lot of things in exchange for a low amount of effort. Zhao Hai now had a high place inside the Rosen Emperor’s heart so when the palace guard saw that Zhao Hai had come, he didn’t dare to neglect him. He immediately arranged a room for Zhao Hai to rest in before he went to report to the King.

The Emperor didn’t make Zhao Hai wait for too long, he immediately invited Zhao Hai to his study room. When Zhao Hai sat down, the Emperor looked at him and said, “The Radiant Church had been dealt with this time thanks to you. But the Radiant Church has been repelled for a few days now, how come you’ve only come this time?”

Zhao Hai quickly responded, “I went back to the Purcell Duchy and established a network of shops there. This time, I came to pick up Lizzy. Another thing was to discuss a partnership with father-in-law.”

The Emperor looked at Zhao Hai and said, “You mean a partnership with those products that you have?”

Zhao Hai nodded and said, “I currently have a lot of those in hand. In the past, because of the Radiant Church’s suppression, nobody would buy these things. But now, I can definitely turn this into money.”

The Emperor nodded and said, “Right, it’s no use if those aren’t made into profits. You don’t need to discuss with me about this matter. You go to Charlie and discuss the particulars with him.”

Zhao Hai stared, then his two eyes lit up as he lowered his head to nod. At this time, Lizzy also arrived at the study. Lizzy and the Emperor exchanged some few words for a while before Lizzy left.

When they were at the carriage heading to Wild Dragon Fort, Zhao Hai turned to Lizzy and said, “It looks like father-in-law is already planning to hand the throne over to Third Brother.”

Lizzy stared, she didn’t hear about Zhao Hai and the Emperor’s exchange. Therefore, when she heard Zhao Hai, she became confused so she asked, “Why? Did father tell you that?”

Zhao Hai smiled and said, “He didn’t explicitly tell me. But when I told him that I would like to cooperate with the Imperial Clan, father-in-law passed the responsibility over to Third Brother. If father-in-law didn’t plan to hand the throne over to third brother, then why would he let him handle this business?”

Lizzy’s eyes were shining as she replied, “If father really said so, then that can prove that he indeed wanted to give the throne over to Third Brother. Hehe. It seems like Third Brother needed to thank Brother Hai.”

Zhao Hai smiled faintly and said, “I really don’t need him to thank me. As long as he sits on the throne, our Buda Clan can certainly obtain a lot of benefits. How about we go to Third Brother tomorrow and discuss this matter of cooperation with him. But let’s not tell him about the matters related to the throne. Then the day after tomorrow, we’ll go to the Slave Market to see Lin and ask him if he has our slaves already prepared.”

Lizzy smiled and said, “We don’t really need to state it clearly, if Third Brother hears that we’ll have a partnership with him, he should already know what is going on. But Big Brother Hai, isn’t it too soon for us to get the slaves? The Black Wasteland still isn’t prepared.”

Zhao Hai shook his head and said, “It’s not too soon, planting season will come along with spring. Before that time arrives, we should already have the slaves prepared to cultivate the lands. If we miss this season, then it would be too late for planting.

Lizzy nodded and didn’t say anything more. She was not very knowledgeable regarding the matters of farming. It was much different than managing stores, of which she understood much of. There was really no way for a Princess to touch the topics related to farming, therefore, Lizzy didn’t have much to say.

The next day, Lizzy and Zhao Hai went to see Charlie. Charlie was still very low-key in doing his business, but ever since he cooperated with Zhao Hai, his income had already increased by a lot. It can be said that there aren’t any other Prince that can compare to his income. It was precisely because of this that Charlie had placed great importance on Zhao Hai.

When Zhao Hai came to him to discuss the matter of cooperation, Charlie couldn’t help but get excited. He already knew about Zhao Hai’s intention of cooperating with the Crook Family, Calci Family, and the Imperial Clan. Charlie understood the implications of this partnership, so it couldn’t be helped that he became elated. He even wanted to invite Zhao Hai for a drink. However, Zhao Hai had to decline. He still needed to visit the Shelley Hotel in the afternoon and talk about his partnership with the Shelley Family.

The last time Zhao Hai went to Marriott was to ask the Shelley Family for help. Spreading the news about the Iksa Family’s demise was perfectly executed by the Hotel. Therefore, Zhao Hai wanted to further improve his cooperation with the Shelley Family.

In addition to the Haven products, fire fish and seafood, he also cooperated with the Shelley Hotel by providing Milk Wine. But this time, Zhao Hai was planning to have them sell Rice Wine and Beer as well.

Currently, the Black Wasteland can now make Rice Wine as well as Beer. However, ways of mass producing these items were still under development.

The Ark Continent was still very backwards in their winemaking. If one wanted to mass produce these two products for the continent, one doesn’t only need 1,800 people to work on it, those people needed to be skilled as well.

However, Zhao Hai was planning to offer these two wines as samplers first, like what he did with the Milk Wine in the past. He’ll put them in the Shelley Hotel for a trial run and when the people of the continent becomes used to the two liquors, then the factories would be built. Then the mass production would begin.

The cooperation with the Shelley Family came very smoothly. At this point, the Shelley Family almost has a blind faith in Zhao Hai. They think that as long as they cooperate with Zhao Hai, they can make a lot of money. This preconception was backed with their one year of experience. From the very first day that they partnered with Zhao Hai, they had been making more and more money.

This result satisfied Zhao Hai. After him and the Shelley Family had reached an agreement, he immediately returned to Wild Dragon Fort. Then he prepared for his trip to the Slave Market the next day.

After going to the Slave Market and bringing those slaves to the Black Wasteland, Zhao Hai would then head to the Beastman Prairie. It was already a month after the Beastmen had retreated, going to the Praire should be alright now.

The next day, Zhao Hai and Lizzy headed to the Slave Market and went to see Lin. Lin told Zhao Hai that the slaves were ready for quite some time. But because of the war that was going on, they decided to refrain sending them to Golden Island. If Zhao Hai wanted, he can take those slaves right now.

Zhao Hai immediately paid the price of those slaves, and then had them transported to Golden Island at the shortest time possible. Then, Zhao Hai left with Lizzy. After returning to Wild Dragon Fort, Zhao Hai immediately rode a Blood Hawk and then flew towards Golden Island.

The third day after Zhao Hai arrived at the island, dozens of huge slave transport ships arrived. Zhao Hai had them dock at the naval base and had the slaves kept there.

Golden Island naval base was very big. In addition to the fact that most of the Undead in the base were out patrolling around the island, it wouldn’t be a problem having 100 thousand people there.

What made Zhao Hai happy was that Lin actually had those 100 thousand slaves be families. All in all, there were about 20 thousand households that were sent over. This completely fulfilled Zhao Hai’s requests.

Zhao Hai immediately took advantage of the dark evening to send the slaves over to the Black Wasteland. It was now spring and the weather outside wasn’t that cold. Although there weren’t enough houses in the Wasteland, they can just construct it themselves, and the materials were already prepared by Zhao Hai.

After the slaves arrived at the Black Wasteland, Zhao Hai then had people give them some living necessities. He told the slaves that these living materials are their private property, so they must cherish it.

Many of these slaves were generational slaves, very similar to the original slaves of Iron Mountain Fort. Some of them might even be inferior than those slaves. So when they held their first pieces of property, all of them couldn’t help but get very excited.

The next day, Zhao Hai organized some slaves who had become commoners and divided them into villages. In fact, these villages were already planned by Zhao Hai. The only thing that was needed to be done was built it.

The building materials were already prepared, and at the same time, Zhao Hai also released some Undead to help them build. He already mapped the location of each village and the overall layout of the structure. Therefore, building them shouldn’t be very troublesome.

Zhao Hai wanted to build a village for every one thousand household. And no matter how many members ta household had, the lands would be divided accordingly to their structure. An old man would have 5 mu of land, mature men and women would both have 10 mu of land, and each child would merit 5 mu of land. Every family would be provided by either a bull or a scaled horse. Farm supplies and daily necessities were going to be provided as well.

As for the water supply of the villages, Zhao Hai had already prepared them long ago. The channels for water to flow through were made using Earth magic. What kind of plant to cultivate and where to cultivate it was already planned. There were lands made to specifically grow Bamboo Rice and there were also some lands to be used to grow wheat.

The remaining lands were left for the Beastmen slaves. Zhao Hai planned to have the Beastmen slaves herd here first and then train them to farm bit by bit.

The lands of these slaves weren’t given by Zhao Hai. The slaves would cultivate this land and by the end of the year, Zhao Hai would collect 40% of their harvest as tax. The remaining 60% would be left to the hands of the slaves.

Although this tax was very high, it was already a heavenly provision for the slaves. They didn’t expect that when they arrive at this place, they would be given land, their own property. One must know that this condition was only enjoyed by special commoners back in the continent.

But what made these slaves most excited was the fact that they have the opportunity to turn into a commoner in this place. They saw people who had similar slave imprints like them working in the fort and was eating meat everyday. At the same time, their children were given the opportunity to learn how to read as well as to play. This made the new slaves quite envious of them.

Zhao Hai didn’t immediately enact his plan of universal education. He must regard this matter as a reward. He wanted to reward those who do good. And those good slaves would not only become commoners, their children would be able to go to school as well. It was even possible for them to become Nobles.

Those slaves thought that it was too good to be true. But when they saw the slaves who became civilians, they couldn’t help but believe in Zhao Hai’s words and become motivated.

Zhao Hai also distributed some seeds to them as well as some rations and farming tools. He only managed to do all of these in seven days because of the his Undead. Otherwise, it would be impossible for this matter to be completed in a short period of time.

After all of the things were distributed, Zhao Hai also told them that they could practice other crafts after their work. As long as they learn well, they can become civilians immediately. And if they have some special talents, they can just go to the fort and have it tested. If it was satisfactory, they would be turned into civilians as well.

It took half a month before all of these things had been taken care of. This speed was also because Green and the others already did a lot of work ahead of time. Each step in the process were carefully planned by them, otherwise it wouldn’t have been this smooth.

Also, if Zhao Hai did this with commoners, it wouldn’t have been completed this flawlessly. Slaves were already trained and were very obedient. Whatever you wanted them to do, they would do it without much fuss. So it only took half a month for these 100 thousand slaves to be settled. At this time, the slaves have already begun to cultivate the land.

Sustaining 100 thousand lives requires a lot of things. This made Zhao Hai’s Space unable to be idle. Zhao Hai was even afraid of becoming poor in managing these people. However, he thought that as long as he provided these people with food and firewood right now, they would become self-sufficient come this fall harvest.

The Black Wasteland had been improved to become fertile lands. As long as these slaves word hard in cultivating the land, their future days would surely be good. The 40% tax that Zhao Hai enacted was fixed. If one got 100 jin of grain, Zhao Hai would take 40 jin. If you have 200 jin, then 80 jin would be taken away. The remaining 120 jin would be up to the slaves to use. After the slaves knew about this setup, they immediately became happy. And adding on to the fact that it was possible for them to become commoners, they immediately became hard working people.

Chapter 550: Trivial Matters

With the addition of the 100 thousand slaves, the Black Wasteland had finally gained some human atmosphere. Although 20 villages were still too few for the Black Wasteland, it was still much more vigorous compared to before.

These villages weren’t very far from Iron Mountain Fort. After all, the fort was the Buda Clan’s administrative center. The villages that had been constructed cannot be too far from the fort.

After the slaves settled down, they immediately started to work. Because they now have farming tools as well as work animals, a family can easily plant in their respective fields.

The majority of these slaves had family backgrounds as farmers. Therefore, taking care of a farm wasn’t very foreign to them, on the other hand, they were actually very adept in the practice.

But before, the farms that they worked on were owned by their masters. Even if they cannot slack off, it was impossible for them to give their all towards the job. But now was different, the land was now bestowed to them and the only thing that they needed to do was hand over 40% of their harvests, while the rest were their own. This way, the higher their harvest, the more food they have.

However, farming was a seasonal activity, one doesn’t need to be busy in the field all year round. There are only two seasons where the farmers would get busy, it was the spring for sowing seeds and autumn for the harvest. Other than these two seasons, farmers didn’t have much to do, so Zhao Hai instructed them to learn another craft.

At the same time, Zhao Hai also had Green prepare the wineries while the slaves were planting in their land. After the wineries are built, the slaves should be finished in their busy schedule at spring. Therefore, the slaves can go to the wineries and work. Naturally, their efforts would be reciprocated with pay.

Settling the slaves still wasn’t completely finished, after all, the wineries would still take a lot of time.

However, Zhao Hai can just hand these matters over to Green, he doesn’t need to monitor all of it himself. The stones that were needed for the wineries as well as other particulars can be found in Golden Island. If Iron Mountain Fort needs anything he can just get it there.

A lot of Great Nobles have businesses in Golden Island, and their goods and services have a huge range. They can provide anything that one wants in the continent. If Zhao Hai wanted something special, he can contact them in order to get it.

Zhao Hai didn’t need to worry too much about building the structures. He has a 2 million undead army, building should be alright for them to do, the only thing they need is to have an artisan providing them guidance at the side.

While the factory was being built, Zhao Hao also gave his product orders to the Great Nobles who manufacture them. After that, he didn’t think to much about it. He still has something else to do, and that was going to the Beastman Prairie.

It was now two months after the Beastmen had returned to the Prairie, so Zhao Hai wanted to see them and take a look at their situation. Two months was enough for them to divide their spoils of war. Now they should be needing something again.

Besides, he still needed to deliver new goods to Ah Tai. Zhao Hai plans to contact a lot of Beastmen when he goes to the Prairie this time. He also wanted to get in touch with the Beast King and try if he can have a business cooperation with him. As long as he has a business with the Beast King, the Buda Clan would certainly gain huge profits.

Zhao Hai wanted to gain several large clients in the Prairie and form a large network of business there. This was also part of his plan to expand the businesses of the Buda Clan.

After all, the Buda Clan’s roots have been placed in the Black Wasteland. If all of the lands in the wasteland were to be developed and used for farming, how much food would they be able to produce? The amount would surely pose a huge threat to the food market of the Human Race,

At the same time, the Humans had already signed a fair price agreement with the Beastmen. And with this agreement, the Merchants would have to fork out the expense of transport. Merchants weren’t like ZHao Hai, who can just carry his goods through the Space.

Therefore, the prices of food on the Prairie would still be high, but much lower compared to before. However, this would mean that Merchants wouldn’t be able to earn as much, aside from the large Merchants. Those small Merchants wouldn’t be able to do business in the Prairie anymore since the profits wouldn’t be enough anymore.

But as the matter stands, the Beastmen cannot have another food shortage anymore. If it happens again, another war between the two races would surely happen. Therefore, what Zhao Hai meant to do was to sell the grain from the Black Wasteland to the Beastman Prairie. This way, not only would the Beastmen’s food problem be solved, it would also stabilize the food market in the Prairie.

Zhao Hai also discovered that the Beastmen weren’t like those ancient Prairie dwellers back on Earth. For generations, the people living on the Earth’s Prairie has always been very eager to conquer the land of the Han people. They were bent on being the rulers of that land. Therefore, they were waiting for the Hans to grew weak, and then they would invade China.

On the other hand, these Beastmen had their own civilization. Moreover, their society wasn’t any worse than the Humans. This stopped them from having thoughts of going to the Human domain. In this world that depends heavily on strength, the ones who advocates this rule the most were the Beastmen Race, this made them dislike the Humans. In their opinion, Humans were too starved, which explains their weak and thin appearance, so their lands shouldn’t be that good. Because of this, the Beastmen didn’t covet the Human lands. At the same time, the Beastman Prairie was already too big for the Beastman Race to thrive in.

Since the Beastmen didn’t have much thoughts towards the Human lands, it wasn’t common for them to wage war. The only reason for them to wage war was in the situation where their survival was threatened.

A Beastman’s aggression was deeply connected to their straightforward temper. In their eyes, black is black, white is white. Not unlike other people where grey was in between black and white. The Beastmen simply didn’t have this view.

It was because of these violent tendencies of the Beastmen that they would go into a fight over the smallest details. It gave people the impression that they were warfreaks. But in truth, the Beastmen disliked war as well.

Even if the Beastmen looked down on Humans, they actually depend on human grain to survive. At the same time, the Humans also need Beastmen beast skins, wool, and beast meat. Therefore, it was possible for both sides to depend on each other.

The Beastmen had a straightforward attitude, very much unlike the Human Merchants who were very greedy for benefit. There were several times where Humans and the Beastman went to war because of their greed. They priced their goods too high, negatively affecting the survival of the Beastman race. So in order to survive, the Beastmen would have no choice but to take up their weapons and pillage the Human lands.

Zhao Hai sending his grain to the Prairie would definitely solve this situation. If he becomes the top grain merchant in the Prairie, the Beastmen wouldn’t be able to worry about grain anymore. In this case, it would be impossible for the Humans and Beastmen to wage war with each other anymore.

And if that happens one day, what benefits would the Buda Clan gain? It was even possible for them to be the ones who would have the most profits in the entire Human race.

To be honest, Zhao Hai had thought about the time when the Rosen Empire negotiated for him to have the Purcell Duchy. If he gains control of that territory, it would be equivalent to adding the Purcell Duchy to the Black Wasteland. When that happens, he wouldn’t even need the Space to transport the food to the Prairie using the Space. He could just directly transport the food using normal means. However, it was a pity that it didn’t succeed.

However, Zhao Hai didn’t become anxious about this. As long as there is time, avenues of progress would be found. Later, he would slowly make his own grain route, this was because he didn’t know for how long he’ll live. If he dies, the Space would cease to exist. And when that happens, the Buda Clan would be able to use that route for their business.

Walk one step, look forward three steps, this was Zhao Hai’s attitude. He knew that the Space wouldn’t disappear with no reason, but he was afraid that it would be gone once he dies. Nobody was immortal, even 9th ranks were the same. Therefore, Zhao Hai considered the Buda Clan heavily in his decisions.

It was because of this that Zhao Hai invested his time on the Prairie. As long as he gains big clients in the Prairie, the Buda Clan’s future development wouldn’t be very difficult.

After handling the matters of the Black Wasteland, Zhao Hai went back to the Rosen Empire. Even if he had established his cooperation with the Calci Family and the others, the details would still be needed to discussed well. At the same time, the logistics of the business needed to be considered, otherwise their costs would increase by a lot.

It was important for a store to have a stable transport network so that it could sell and restock its items on time. Because of this, logistics was one of the most important aspects of a business.

There were only two forms of transporting goods in the Ark Continent. One was through the water, with the use of ships, while the other was through land, by having beast-pulled carriages.

Comparing these two, using the waters was much convenient. It was quicker, and it costs was much lower as well. Carriages might cost less in short distance transport, but ships were the most suited for long-distance shipment.

Even if it was good that Zhao Hai had established some good partners, the logistics wasn’t a well oiled machine. Those families have their own transport networks. Zhao Hai’s supplies cannot be just placed at one location, that would be very inconvenient.

In the end, Zhao Hai decided that with the current numbers of the Buda Clan, even with the addition of the Markey Family, it would be impossible for them to have a lot of shops. Therefore he settled for the second choice, establish some supply locations at some major cities. This would save a lot on transportation towards the nearest cities as he handed the goods over to the other families.

The Calci Family and the others naturally agreed to this. They were afraid that the Buda Clan would establish their own sales network since that would mean that they would have a new competitor. But even so, the Calci Family and the others didn’t extend their hands too far. Ruyen was currently managing a Buda Clan business in Purcell Duchy. This was the sole place in the entire continent where the Buda Clan directly sells Haven products.

Chapter 551: Marriage

Nobody expected Ruyen to return to the Purcell Duchy. Right now, she has been changed, she was very much like another person. Zhao Hai sent her to the Duchy because of her familiarity with the place, not because of the Purcell Family’s reputation.

Now, the Purcell Duchy was not named Purcell Duchy anymore. It was renamed to the Northern Border. There is only an ordinary Noble here, not a Grand Duke.

However, this Noble was Boris’ trusted aide. This made Boris relieved in in placing him in the territory. Boris was now one of the people who hated the Radiant Church the most. Because of the Radiant Church’s machinations, he fell into his current situation. Although he had earned the Aksu Empire’s throne, he was actually in very deep debt. His current mood was not very good.

It was not only because of this, because of his error, the Aksu Empire had suffered a huge loss. This made his reputation among the Empire’s nobles  come crashing down. At present, there were a lot of Nobles who didn’t obey him.

The only reason why he was still on the throne was because the Aksu Imperial Family still held a huge influence inside the Empire. And even if the members of the Imperial Family were unhappy with Boris, they knew that if he were to be dethroned, nobody was qualified to please the public. Failure to control the populace would lead to the Nobles gaining more control. So for the sake of the Aksu Imperial Family, the members had no other choice than to support Boris.

Boris also knew about his current situation, therefore he exerted extra effort in arranging his trusted men to hold important positions. So when time comes where the others would want to deal with him, it wouldn’t be very easy.

The Aksu Empire’s current situation was actually fragile. If a powerful force gently nudged the Empire, then the Aksu Empire would have to change its name.

But no matter what, the Aksu Empire’s dilemma was caused by the Beastmen. Anyone who wanted to touch them right now would be despised, therefore nobody took the risk.

When talking about the matter of who would take over the Aksu Empire, unless they were the Rosen Empire, no large influence would be able to face such a mess.

Naturally, Zhao Hai wasn’t thinking about any of these. And even if Zhao Hai appears in the Aksu Empire, Boris would not dare to have some disrespect towards him. All the hatred between the two of them were all Boris’ fault. And now, Zhao Hai’s status was no longer much lower than him, who was an emperor. At this point, Boris can only choose to do good for Zhao Hai.

Zhao Hai didn’t care about this, he just wanted to hand the Purcell Duchy’s affairs over to Ruyen. He also did this under the consent of Green and Merine.

Green and Merine agreed to it after talking it over with Evan. After Green agreed, Zhao Hai knew that his relationship with Ruyen had already been decided. Ruyen might marry him in the near future.

But compared to Laura and the others, Ruyen’s current status surely has a gap for Zhao Hai. If she wanted to marry Zhao Hai, she would need to make some achievements. This management of the shops in Purcell Duchy, now called Northern Border, was Green’s way of testing her.

If Ruyen does well, then she would probably be married to Zhao Hai. If she doesn’t, then it would be difficult to be Zhao Hai’s wife.

Zhao Hai thought that Ruyen’s arrogance would have her disagree with this condition. But Zhao Hai didn’t expect her to accept it without any hesitation. Zhao Hai knew that Ruyen might have some feelings for him, but not as deep as what Laura and the others had. The reason why she agreed was most likely because of the future of the Purcell Duchy.

The Purcell Family must rely on the Buda Clan to survive as well as to progress. For the Purcell Family, Ruyen agreed to be married to Zhao Hai.

After Zhao Hai heard about this result, he sighed. He didn’t object to it. He knew that such an agreement would come. But he wasn’t expecting it to happen with Ruyen.

In fact, even if Ruyen didn’t make any achievements, Zhao Hai would still be married to her later on. This marriage had a lot of advantages, one could even call it a political marriage. If Ruyen gets married to Zhao Hai, then the Purcell Family would be sheltered by the Buda Clan. On the other hand, if Zhao Hai gets married to Ruyen, the Purcell Family would be willing to follow the Buda Clan.

Although Zhao Hai’s wives aren’t any lower than one another, but one must say that the most helpful to Zhao Hai right now was Laura. Although Laura’s status can’t compare to either Megan and Lizzy, but one shouldn’t forget that the Markey Family was now almost merged with the Buda Clan. This gave the Buda Clan a lot of talented people to use. Although Megan and Lizzy’s statuses were high, they couldn’t achieve something like Laura. Their families were just too formidable, and all of them were centered on their own family’s benefit. It wouldn’t be possible for them to help the Buda Clan while sacrificing their own benefits. Therefore, even if they publicly supported Zhao Hai, it wasn’t something hugely significant.

However, Laura’s support was very solid. With the Buda Clan’s present strength, they didn’t need public support, they need support like Laura’s. This was something that Lizzy and Megan can’t compete with.

Zhao Hai was aware of this, so he was also inclined to marry Ruyen so that he could get the full support of the Purcell Family. Even if the Purcell Family was now in a low point, they still had a lot of personal connections that the Buda Clan can make use of.

Establishing a Clan was much more difficult than what others imagine. Money, personal connections, strength, territory were all indispensable. Although the Buda Clan was doing very well, aside from strength, they were weak in all other aspects. Therefore, Zhao Hai wanted to fulfill those deficiencies in order to grow the Buda Clan further.

One has to recognize that Zhao Hai was a person who has a good sense of crisis, it was because of this that he was very careful in his every action. But he didn’t oppose to this marriage. He also believed that Laura and the others wouldn’t object to it. These women had given their hearts to Zhao Hai and the Buda Clan. They wouldn’t oppose to anything that can benefit the Buda Clan.

The more he thought about this, the more Zhao Hai felt that he owed the ladies a lot. Zhao Hai hoped that they get pregnant as soon as possible. But it was a pity that even if he has tried so hard these past few month, Laura and the others still weren’t pregnant.

And when the Space checked, he doesn’t have any issues, the same was true for Laura and the others as well. It seems like they were only having bad luck.

Upon looking at the situation at the Northern Border, Zhao Hai felt relief. Then he prepared to set off for the Prairie. The first place that he would visit would be the Cows. Although it was proper for him to go to Beast God City first, he opted to visit the Herculean Bulls. After all, this was his tribe, and he was their Prince.

Zhao Hai didn’t ride Alien after he went out of the Space. Instead, he released a Blood Hawk and then sat in it as it went out from the Space. This time, the people who accompanied him were only Shun and Shue since both of them didn’t have much to do. Laura and the others were left behind since they had some other matters to attend to. If they also came out with Zhao Hai, things would be much more inconvenient.

Seeing three Blood Hawks coming from the skies didn’t make the Cows panic. The Herculean Bulls already knew that the Blood Hawks were Zhao Hai’s mounts.

After Zhao Hai landed, he was immediately welcomed by the Herculean Bulls. Zhao Hai was also glad to see them as he returned the gesture. He talked with them for quite some time and gave them his Milk Wine.

Zhao Hai’s Milk Wine output was now very high. And to guarantee its price, Zhao Hai didn’t sell a huge bulk of them to the continent. Therefore, he saved a lot of these Milk Wine inside the Space. And since the Beastmen loved liquor, it was a good idea to gift them some.

These Beastmen liked Zhao Hai very much, he seemed more like a Beastman unlike the other humans they had met before. And everytime they greet him, he has some small gifts that he’d give them, this made the Beastmen very glad.

At this time, Mendez’s voice was heard, “You bastards, get out of the way.” When the people heard Mendez, they grunted a bit before they all ran away.

Mendez used this opportunity to approach Zhao Hai. Then he looked at Zhao Hai while shaking his head and smiling bitterly, “Little Hai, you can’t make those guys get used to receiving your gifts every time you meet.”

Zhao Hai laughed and said, “It’s fine, those are little gifts, not really worth much money. It’s good that it makes them happy. Right, let’s go in.” Then he walked to the main tent along with Mendez.

Wales, Yale, and Kony were already inside the tent. When Zhao Hai came in, Wales couldn’t help but laugh, “Little Hai, why did you only come this time? Our attack with the Humans was already finished for quite some time.”

Zhao Hai smiled and said, “I only found time recently. You made the Aksu Empire very miserable. I sold some grain over there and made quite a small wealth.”

Wales quickly replied, “What did you sell to the Aksu Empire? Bread Fruits?”

Zhao Hai shook his head and said, “No, I sold them Bamboo Rice. What happened? You didn’t get a lot of food this time?”

Without even waiting for Wales to speak, Kony laughed and said, “You can’t be anymore wrong this time, Little Hai. We got a lot of good things this time. And it is because of you.”

Zhao Hai became confused as the looked at Wales and the others. Wales couldn’t help but smile and said, “Because of the information that you provided, we managed to defeat the Aksu Empire and the Radiant Church. And since you’re a Foreign Prince of our Herculean Bull Tribe, the Beast King decided to give your credit to our tribe. Therefore, we managed to get a lot of things this time.”

When Zhao Hai heard Wales, he smiled and said, “Well, that means the tribe wouldn’t need to buy food for a long time. Right, I brought over some daily necessities. I don’t know if you still need it.”

Chapter 552: Anticipation

Wales smiled and said, “Oh, you really didn’t have to. You might now know, but we got much more than food this time. We also managed to get some daily necessities.”

Zhao Hai smiled and said, “I heard that you came to the Purcell and Iksa territories, but I thought you didn’t get much. But if you need some in the future, don’t hesitate to tell me. Right, I’ll be leaving fifty Blood Hawks here. These things can be used more as scouts. But it’s a real pity that your bodies are too big. You won’t be able to use them as mounts.”

When Wales heard Zhao Hai, his face turned happy as he said, “Fantastic, I have a lot of uses for them right now. Then I’ll be impolite and accept them.”

Zhao Hai smiled, “No need to be polite with me. Right, do you have any food? I’m quite hungry. I have to go to Beast God City tomorrow. It’s been a long time since I went there, do you know the situation there right now?”

Wales asked, “You directly went here from the Human lands? I thought you went to Beast God City first.”

Zhao Hai smiled faintly and said, “I’m not too anxious about going to Beast God City, I don’t have a lot of things to do there right now. Because of the things that you’ve brought back, I think doing business there wouldn’t be a good idea at this time. Therefore, I decided to come here first.”

Wales felt moved as he looked at Zhao Hai and said, “Brother, your sentiment really leaves me speechless. Right no need to talk anymore, come with me for a drink. If I don’t have you fall face down today, then I would be very unfair to you.”

Zhao Hai laughed and said, “I’m not afraid. Did you think that my alcohol tolerance stayed the same as before? Let’s see who’ll end up face down.” Then the group laughed as they walked out of the tent.

Now, when Zhao Hai comes to the Herculean Bull tribe, Wales doesn’t even need to have someone prepare the feast. The Herculean Bulls would already prepare the food as soon as they see him. These people usually receive Zhao Hai’s liquor, and they didn’t want to just be on the receiving end all the time. So everytime Zhao Hai came, they would prepare some good food from their households. And if they don’t have any food, they can just kill some Argali to welcome Zhao Hai.

When the group arrived outside, the Argali and the bulls were already being roasted. What surprised Zhao Hai was that there were two things that were like mouse on the fire. This made Zhao Hai feel strange.

But when Wales saw those two mice, his eyes couldn’t’ help but turn bright as he said, “Grass Marten? Who brought these things?”

A large Herculean Bull came with a grin on his face. He also had one of those creatures tied up in his hands, then he placed it in front of Zhao Hai and said, “Young Master Hai, when I went out today, I managed to spot these three things. I originally wanted to eat them myself, but since you came, I decided to contribute them and have one given to you since I know you like these peculiar things.”

Zhao Hai looked at the Green Marten curiously. This thing looked just like a big mouse but its skin was green and its eyes were bright black. It looked very cute.

Wales looked at Zhao Hai’s expression and smiled, “This Grass Marten is one of the Prairie’s unique Magic Beasts. Its level isn’t high, only about 3rd rank. But it’s very fast, it can hide in the grass effectively as well. And most importantly, this thing is a rare delicacy. Remember, if you eat this thing, just eat it as is, no need to add anything other than salt. Its innate flavor is the best.”

Then Wales turned his head to the large Herculean Bull and said, “Daws, you really are something. You should make sure to manage your fat. If you get any bigger, people might mistake you to be from the Pig-headed Race. Right, are there a lot of Grass Martens in the Prairie right now? How did you manage to get three?”

Daws didn’t mind Wales’ words, he only grinned as he answered, “Patriarch, I also came here to tell you about this matter. I recently discovered that there are a lot of Grass Martens around recently. Do you have any solutions for this?”

Wales knit the eyebrows on his head, he knew that even if these Grass Martens taste good, they were one of the pests that can destroy pastures. If the surrounding Grass Martens get to a large number, they would start to hunt and kill, affecting the herds of the Beastmen.

Zhao Hai didn’t frown upon hearing this, he just turned and smiled to Wales, “Brother, you don’t need to worry too much about this. Don’t you have a lot of Blood Hawks? The Blood Hawks are adept in hunting these things. In any case, you still need to feed the hawks, so might as well have them look for their own food, making them hunt these Grass Martens.”

Wales stared for a moment before he nods, “That’s right, hawks are the natural predators of the Grass Martens. Good, let’s do that. Daws it seems like you don’t only know how to eat. Right, I need to reward you. Little Hai, come give this guy something.”

Zhao Hai smiled bitterly and said, “Brother, but you said that you’re going to reward him. How did the price become my responsibility?” Although he said so, he still took out a big bag of Milk Wine and handed it to Daws. Upon receiving the bag, Daws’ happiness can be evidently seen on his face.

At this time, the table was already prepared. Then Zhao Hai and Wales sat down before they happily chatted and drank. The group didn’t stop until all of them had gotten drunk.

The next morning, after Zhao Hai left the fifty Blood Hawks behind, he left the Herculean Bull Camp and then flew towards Beast God City.

He hasn’t gone to the neither the Mastiffs nor the Black Bears. Although he has good relationships with them, they still came lower compared to the Herculean Bulls. Therefore, Zhao Hai passed by them and directly went to Beast God City.

Beast God City was much more prosperous than before. However, even if there were a lot of Beastmen, Zhao Hai didn’t see a lot of Humans. Another strange thing to Zhao Hai was because these Beastmen were also sitting down and doing business.

After finding a place outside Beast God City, Zhao Hai left the Space. Then the three walked towards Beast God City. When they arrived, they can see a lot of Beastmen looking at them with hostile eyes.

Zhao Hai didn’t care about those gazes. He understood the minds of those Beastmen. They had just fought with Humans and there were no Human Merchants who came here yet. Therefore, Zhao Hai’s appearance this time was very eye-catching.

But Zhao Hai believed that those Beastmen wouldn’t do anything to him. They only looked at him this way because he didn’t have his carriage nor his friendship flags.

Also, when Zhao Hai arrived at the city, a carriage immediately came over to fetch him, it’s driver was Ah Tai.

When the Beastmen saw Ah Tai, they looked at each other and then smiled. Those who did business with Ah Tai greeted him, even the hostile eyes towards Zhao Hai disappeared.

All the Beastmen knew that the Magic Lily Shop has the friendship flags of the Dog-headed race as well as the Black Bears. But these friendships flags weren’t earned by Ah Tai, instead it was obtained by his boss. At the same time, Ah Tai’s boss not only gained the friendship flags of those two races, he was also the Foreign Prince of the Herculean Bull Tribe.

When Ah Tai went and greeted Zhao Hai personally, their status became clear. Therefore, the looks of these Beastmen towards Zhao Hai changed.

Ah Tai drove the carriage up to Zhao hai and then jumped down. After that, he bowed to Zhao Hai and said, “Young Master, I hope that you didn’t wait for me for a long time.”

Zhao Hai smiled and said, “It’s fine, I’m enjoying the walk. I didn’t think that the Beastmen would do business here. I thought that they only trade with the Humans.”

Ah Tai smiled and said, “Young master might not know, but Beastmen trade as well. Not trading for their entire lives might be possible, but there were rare times when they would, like this time. I heard that they were trading for their spoils of war. They might have things that they deemed useless but can be used by other tribes. Therefore, they might as well exchange some items with each other.

Zhao Hai nodded, then he looked at the transactions of the Beastmen and saw that it was just like what Ah Tai said. There were indeed some things that are useless for the Beastmen, this was because those things are specially made for Human use. For the Beastmen, these items belonged to the weak, but they decided to trade them for something since it was a pity to just throw them out.

When Zhao Hai went got on the carriage, Ah Tai immediately drove the vehicle to enter the city and headed to Magic Lily Shop. Ah Tai’s two children as well as Sister-in-law was already waiting for Zhao Hai at the store.

After Zhao Hai got out, Ah Tai’s whole family immediately came to welcome him. After they sat down on the backyard, Ah Tai looked at Zhao Hai and said, “Young Master, the business in our shop hasn’t been doing good these days. The Beastmen had gotten a lot of good things from the recent war. In the present time, the Beastmen didn’t lack in both items and food. Because of this, they didn’t come and trade with us.”

Ah Tai’s expression was somewhat guilty, he thinks that this situation was his mistake. But Zhao Hai didn’t care, he just waved his hand and said, “No need to be worried, I already thought about this point. Since the Beastmen already had what they need, then naturally they don’t need to buy anything more. But you’re not being smart enough, you should’ve been looking at things that the Humans might use. Since those things are useless to the Beastmen, you can trade them for a low price. When I go back to the Human lands, I can just go and sell them. Even they are sold cheap, wouldn’t we still be gaining profits?”

Ah Tai stared, then as if he was enlightened, he tapped his head and said, “Why haven’t I thought of that? Fortunately, the Young Master reminded me.”

Ah Tai’s wife then said, “I’ve also thought about what Young Master suggested, but most of the things that the Beastmen brought were old. Even if we bring them to the mainland, I’m afraid nobody would buy them even at a low price.”

Zhao Hai nodded, it seems like Sister-in-law was more wise than Ah Tai, she had already considered a lot of things. Zhao Hai smiled and said, “Sister-in-law, those things are indeed unsellable to the Humans, but these things aren’t that bad. Our Buda Clan can still make use of those. Our Clan now has 100 thousand slaves, and the clan still needs to supply them with various things. If we compare buying those things in the mainland with buying them from the Beastmen, we can certainly get much cheaper rates here with the Beastmen.

As soon as Sister-in-law heard Zhao Hai, her eyes couldn’t help but light up. “Right, right, I forgot about this. Now that the Beastmen has a lot of these things, we can certainly save some money if we buy it from them.”

Zhao Hai nodded, “Therefore, from now on, you need to think about this matter. Not only could we get items cheaply, we can also make a good impression towards the Beastmen.”

Ah Tai and Sister-in-law nodded, then Sister-in-law said, “Young Master, after the Beastmen returned to Beast God City, the Beast King left behind a message stating that once you return to the city, you should go and visit him at least once.”

Zhao Hai nodded, he believed that the Beast King would certainly do this. He had given the Beastmen a huge help, so the Beast King would definitely not ignore it. Zhao Hai just didn’t expect the Beast King to leave a message this soon.

Zhao Hai thought for a moment before he said, “Since I’ve just arrived, I’ll go see the Beast King tomorrow. Right, you don’t need to take care of me, I’ll be resting.” Ah Tai and his wife nodded and left, leaving only Zhao Hai, Shue and Shun in the tent.

Zhao Hai turned his head to Shue and Shun and said, “Looks like things are going smooth this time. As long as we take care of our matters here, well go back to the mainland. Then we’ll go explore the other nations, like Lyon Empire, Buddha Empire and the Ocean Waves Dynasty. It would be very regrettable if we don’t go there.”

Shun smiled and said, “The map of the southern part still wasn’t registered in the Space, so we can use this opportunity to place them into the map. Young Master, can we also go and see the Dwarves? From what I heard, they love drinking. Perhaps we can gain good things if we go and see them.”

Zhao Hai nodded, “ We should go and see them. If we want to get some iron in the mainland, it would be very difficult. But if we approach the Dwarves, we might get the opportunity to trade with them. That would be very advantageous for us”

Shue nodded and said, “Dwarf Iron Mountain is in Buddha Empire. Because of that, the Buddha Empire’s Heavy Armor Cavalry was able to move around unhindered. But I heard that the Dwarf Race also have some special plants and animals. If we get those things for the Space, perhaps Young Master can upgrade it. There’s nothing more important than increasing the Space’s levels right now.”

Zhao Hai and Shun nodded. It was true that the most important thing for them right now was to upgrade the Space. Once the Space levels up, it would be able to produce a lot of high level plants. And if they compound those, they might be able to make 8th to 9th level potions. At the very very best, they can make anyone enter 9th rank. Then in the future, they would be able to walk sideways in the continent.

And most importantly, one of the reasons that Zhao Hai was looking forward to the Space reaching level fifty was the ability to use multiple backgrounds.

Chapter 553: Seeing the Beast King

Shun knew that what Shue said was right, but he still frowned and said, “Young Master, I think there is a much more suitable place to make the Space Level Up.”

Zhao Hai nodded and said, “I know that you mean the Elven Forest. I also heard that there were a lot of stranger plants there. It certainly is the place most suitable to upgrade the Space. But you should know about the temperament of the Elves. They absolutely hate Humans. If we just rashly enter their forest, they might see it as aggression. Therefore, I’d rather see the Dwarves first. I heard that the Dwarves have some contact with the Elves sometimes. I want to see if we can learn something about the Elves from the Dwarves.”

Shun nodded and said, “So that’s the case. But is it true? I heard that the Dwarves are hot tempered, with attitudes no worse than the Beastmen. They like to play with iron, drinking liquor, and are generally rude Artisans. One the other hand, the Elves are elegant, seemingly looking like art, and has a huge affection towards music. Would such people have a friendly relationship with the Dwarven Race?”

Zhao Hai shook his head and said, “Who knows, I only read it in a passing note. I don’t know if its true or not. But elves disliking the Humans is something everyone on the mainland knows. Therefore, it would be much better for is to head to Dwarf Iron Mountain first.”

Shun nodded, then Shue looked at Zhao Hai and asked, “Young Master, what do you think the Beast King wants to talk to you about?”

Shun smiled and said, “It should be something good. The Young Master has helped them quite a lot. With the attitude of the Beastmen, they would definitely give benefits to the Young Master.”

Shue actually shook his head and said, “Not necessarily. The Beast King is astute, him looking for Young Master might not be a good thing. Young Master, don’t think that things would be like the Herculean Bulls where the conclusion came in smoothly. For a person of the Beast King’s level, they will definitely think much deeper into this matter. He would surely not completely believe in you even if you helped them this time. Therefore, it would be a good thing if we get careful in interacting with them in the future.”

Zhao Hai nodded, “What Shue said is reasonable. Although the Beast King is a Beastman, he is also a King, and had been for several years. His position being stable meant that he is strong both physically and mentally. We do indeed need to be more careful with him in the future.”

Then the three people chatted for a while before Ah Tai came and offered Zhao Hai a meal. After eating their meal, Ah Tai started to get busy in preparing to trade goods with the Beastmen. But even so, Zhao Hai didn’t actually make an appearance.

The next morning, after Zhao Hai ate his breakfast, he sat in a carriage and headed towards the Beast King’s place. There might only be few structures in the city, but the most famous of them was definitely the Beast King’s palace.

Although the Beast King Palace had palace in its name, its structure wasn’t really that big. It couldn’t even compare to a small Human castle. There was no way for the Beastmen to construct such a large building. If a Beastman wanted to build a house, they would have to kill some Magic Beasts. And one should know that Magic Beasts were extremely valuable assets for the Beastmen. They simply cannot bear to kill a lot of them.

Because of this, although the walls of the city wasn’t bad, the buildings inside were mainly tents. The few buildings that were inside Beast God City were small buildings of about three stories at most that had their own fences surrounding them. The city’s walls can be said to be the most extravagant structure that the Beastmen had made.

There was no fixed master of the Beast King Palace. When the Beastmen changes their King, the new Beast King would relocate to the Beast King Palace. When a King is replaced, then they would naturally need to move out.

It can be said that the Beast King Palace was a holy place in the hearts of all the Beastmen. Therefore, it was understandable for their guards to be very strict. When Zhao Hai arrived outside the Palace, he immediately got out of his carriage and examined the Beast King Palace. The palace walls weren’t very high, only about ten meters in height. Above the main entrance, three characters were engraved that spelled Beast King Palace. And at the walls, the flag of the Tiger Race has been placed on a pole and then hoisted up.

Guarding the entrance were four Tiger Beastmen. On their hands were long steel spears. On their waists were leather whips. At the same time, they were also wearing great leather armor. When Zhao Hai stepped forward, he was met with cold looks from these Tiger Beastmen.

Zhao Hai reorganized his clothes and then arrived in front of a guard and gave a salute, “Beastman Brother, hello. I’ll have to ask you to inform the Beast King that Zhao Hai has come to answer his summons.”

Zhao Hai specifically picked his words, he told the guards that he only came here because he was ordered by the Beast King to do so. This way, the Beastmen guards wouldn’t be suspicious of him and might even allow him to go in.

Sure enough, when the guard heard Zhao Hai say his name, his expression immediately lightened up by a few levels. But he still didn’t make a move, he just gestured to a big tent beside the palace as he said, “You go to that tent over there. Someone would help you once you enter.” After Zhao Hai expressed his gratitude, he immediately headed towards the tent.

The decorations inside the tent were quite simple. There were several small tables inside where a few people were sitting in. Some of these people were Tiger Beastmen while some are from the Fox Tribe.

Zhao Hai didn’t dare to ignore them, so he immediately approached a table with a Tiger Beastman and said, “Brother, hello, I’m here in the orders of the Beast King. I’ll have to ask brother to send word for me.”

The Tiger wasn’t as strong as the others. Although his figure was still very tall, he looked a little thin compared to the other people in his race. But if he were compared to Zhao Hai, he would look like a big man.

The Beastman looked at Zhao Hai and faintly smiled, “So it’s Mister Zhao Hai. His Majesty did give the word for your visit. Please wait for a while, I’ll have someone come and escort you.”

After the person left, the five remaining people looked at Zhao Hai curiously. Zhao Hai gave a salute to these people and said, “Everyone, this is our first meeting. I really haven’t prepared any good gifts. I hope these bottles of liquor would suffice.” Then he gave each of them one bag of his Milk Wine.

The people inside the tent smiled. It was common courtesy to provide gifts when one meets a Beastman for the first time. Since Zhao Hai gave them something, these people immediately felt closer to him.

One of the Fox Beastman, who looked like young man, smiled at Zhao Hai and said, “We’ve already heard of Mister Zhao Hai’s name. For mister to be the Foreign Prince of the Herculean Bull Tribe as well as obtain the friendship flags of the Dog-headed Race and the Black Bear Tribe, this meant that Mister is a true friend to the Beastman. I must invite Mister to visit our Fox Tribe in the future. We have some businesses to discuss with Mister.”

The Fox-headed Race was generally considered to be the most wily among the Beastmen. They were notoriously shrewd, and many Merchants were very reluctant in doing business with them. This was because the Foxes were too smart, and there were times where the Merchant’s tricks failed because of the shrewdness of these Foxes.

Zhao Hai didn’t care about that as he smiled faintly and said, “I’d be happy to do business with the Fox Beastmen. Rest assured, I will certainly give you a visit.”

The Fox Beastman smiled and said, “Alright, we shall certainly kill some Argali to welcome you.”

At this time, sounds of footsteps could be heard. And before long, the previous Beastman came in from outside. He gave Zhao Hai a small bow and said, “I’m inviting Mister Zhao Hai. His Majesty is already waiting for you.”

Zhao Hai smiled faintly and then placed a bag of Milk Wine on the Beastman’s table and said, “Thank you, brother. Please receive this small gift from me.”

The Tiger Beastman didn’t decline. Based on Beastman tradition, if others gave you a gift and you didn’t accept it, then it meant that you didn’t regard the other party as a friend. This was very different from the Human race. Back in the Human lands, if one gives you a gift, it was proper practice to decline it for one or two times before receiving it.

Then the two went out of the tent and headed towards the Beast King palace. This time, the guards didn’t stop them, the two were immediately allowed inside without any obstructions.

Once inside the Palace, Zhao Hai couldn’t stop himself from staring. Inside, he actually cannot see a single Tiger Beastman guard. Most of the people inside were from the Fox Race and the rest were half-Beastmen slaves. All of the people inside were very busy carrying and shuffling Sheepskin scrolls.

The Beast King Palace wasn’t a large place, but the entire place looks like a machine in high performance. People were processing documents, filing them, delivering them to another person and then repeat.

Seeing this scene Zhao Hai couldn’t help but sigh. Compared to the Beast King Palace, the Rosen Empire’s palace, although very stylish, was very short of this kind of vigorous vitaliy. It was certainly a pity.

Under the leadership of the Tiger Beastman, Zhao Hai quickly navigated through the Palace. And in the middle of it was a small building. In front of this building were a couple of Tiger Beastman guards. They wore leather armor while having two steel whips placed on the back.

Zhao Hai and the Tiger Beastman arrived in front of the guards and said, “This is Mister Zhao Hai, allow him to come in.”

The guard nodded, then he waved his hand. The Tiger Beastman nodded and then left.

The guard looked at Zhao Hai and gave him a salute, “Mister, come with me. The Majesty is inside.” Zhao Hai returned the courtesy and then followed the guard to enter the building.

Zhao Hai stared as he went in the building. He expected that there would be a living room and some other rooms inside. But in truth, this place was unexpectedly the Beast King’s study. Inside, there were several large bookcases. Above the building was a sheepskin curtain, a thick wool carpet was spread on the floor. In the middle of the room was a huge brazier, with flames constantly flashing inside. Not far away behind the brazier was a large table. Behind that table was a chair, of which the Beast King was sitting at, with a lowered head as he wrote. There were several Fox Beastmen nearby as well, silently writing on some documents.

The guard bowed towards the Beast King and said, “Your Majesty, Mister Zhao Hai is here.”

The Beast King looked up. Zhao Hai held a chest salute and said, “Zhao Hai has come under the Beast King’s summons. I ask his Majesty’s forgiveness for me being late.”

The Beast King looked at Zhao Hai and laughed, “Good, good. Alright, come and have a seat.” The he stood up and walked towards the brazier. Right beside the brazier was a circular table with stools on it side.

Zhao Hai sat alongside the Beast King near the Brazier. The guard immediately heated some Milk Wine on the brazier before serving it to both Zhao Hai and the Beast King before he retreated.

The Beast King held his glass up and hinted towards Zhao Hai before the two of them drank the wine.

Chapter 554: Cooperation

When Zhao Hai saw the Beast King’s gesture, he didn’t dare to ignore it. Thus, he also drank from his cup.

These days, he has rarely drunk this kind of pure, undistilled Milk Wine. Although the smell of this wine is heavier, he has to recognize that its fragrance made the wine’s flavor quite different.

The Beast King smiled when he saw Zhao Hai drink the Milk Wine without his brows wrinkling. He knew that only a few Humans can stomach Milk Wine. There were Human Merchants who had been trading in the Prairie for a long time but still couldn’t drink Milk Wine. Zhao Hai wasn’t like any of them, he even seems like he loved drinking it.

The Beast King placed his glass down and had the guard serve him another glass. Then the Beast King looked at Zhao Hai and said, “I want to thank you for last time. If it weren’t for your help, our Beastman Race would have experienced huge losses.”

Zhao Hai also placed his glass down, allowing the guard to fill it back up. He smiled towards the Beast King and said, “Your Majesty is too polite. I treat the Beastmen as my friends, and the Radiant Church as my enemies. There is no reason for me to not help my friends and instead aid my foe.”

The Beast King smiled, then he said, “I made someone inquire, and I  discovered that the grain that you sell to the Beastmen was priced much lower than other Human Merchants. Why is that?”

Zhao Hai replied, “This isn’t something strange. The other Merchants needed to recoup their transportation expenses, but on the other hand, I have my Spatial Bags. Since I use Spatial Equipment in transporting grain to the Prairie, then naturally my prices would be much smaller.”

The Beast King nodded, and then he laughed and said, “I’m afraid this method is very difficult for the others to learn. Nobody would use their Spatial Equipment just to transport grain. Hahaha.”

Zhao Hai smiled faintly. He knew that what the Beast King said was right. But the actual reason why Zhao Hai’s method cannot be copied by the other merchants was because they didn’t have Zhao Hai’s Space.

The Beast King looked at Zhao Hai and then said, “There aren’t any Human Merchants that would dare come to the Prairie at this time. I estimate that this situation would go on for several months. Although we had managed to snatch a lot of things, I’m sure those would run out in a few short months. At the same time, small Merchants would refrain from doing business in the Prairie anymore because of the fair price agreement. In the future, I fear that the food shortage would be even bigger than this time. And when that time comes, we could only get grain at a high price. Do you have any solutions to this?”

Zhao Hai smiled to the Beast King and replied, “Your Majesty, you don’t need to worry about this. As long as the Beastmen need food, I can sell it. This is not a problem.”

The Beast King stared, then his two eyes turned bright as he looked straight into Zhao Hai’s eyes and said, “You mean you have a lot of grain? Are they Bread Fruits?”

Zhao Hai smiled faintly and said, “I have plenty of Bread Fruits, plenty of Bamboo Rice as well. Therefore, Your Majesty don’t need to worry about the Prairie’s food in the future.”

The Beast King looked at Zhao Hai, he seems to think that he had misunderstood what Zhao Hai just said. The reason why he invited Zhao Hai over was to gauge if Zhao Hai is truly a friend to the Beastmen. If Zhao Hai passes his evaluation, then he would give him satisfactory benefits. If he fails, then he even if he wouldn’t chase Zhao Hai out, he would still be on guard against him.

But he didn’t think that Zhao Hai’s reply would be this. He was very clear about the amount of food that the entire Beastman Race needed. It was an astronomical amount.

When Zhao Hai saw the Beast King’s expression, he knew what was on the Beast King’s mind. Zhao Hai smiled faintly and said, “Your Majesty, you don’t really have to worry. My territory doesn’t only produce Bamboo Rice and Bread Fruit, I also have other things cultivated there. To be honest, if I don’t sell my food over to the Beastmen and instead dump them to the Human markets, then I’m afraid the price of food would immediately plummet. And I don’t want it to be like that. Therefore, I want to bring them over to the Prairie and sell it here. Not only is the purchase price high in the Prairie, the demand is also very large. And if I sell my products to the Beastmen, I won’t be affecting the Human markets, and I won’t be destabilizing the economy.”

The Beast King nodded, although he was a Beastman, after all these years of being a Beast King he has managed to have some understanding about Human matters. He knew that among the merchants who came to the Prairie, only those big Merchants were able to make a fortune, small Merchants wouldn’t be able to earn a lot.

He knew the price of grain on Human lands, but he also knew how much it costs for the humans to transport grain to the Prairie. Aside from artificial reasons, this overhead cost was the reason why prices of grain in the Prairie was very high.

Because of this, the fair price agreement between the Empires and the Beastmen didn’t include having the same price as in the Human domain. This was because it would be an unrealistic scenario, and there would be no merchants that would sell food to the Beastmen anymore if that happens.

Moreover, the Beast King also knew that in the Human lands, the influence of each Great Noble Family was very formidable. And with how their grain business is closely tied with their military, these Great Nobles would do their best in order to keep the price constant. Any fluctuation to the market would have huge impact to these Great Nobles.

As for the Buda Clan, the Beast King was aware of it as well. The rise of this clan can only be described as absurd. In a very short year, forget about being a Middle-ranked clan, they immediately became one of the most powerful Clans in the Human continent. This kind of development can only be read in legends.

These information were acquired by the Beast King from the Nobles that they had fought. In truth, he had expected Zhao Hai to be someone who didn’t have much reputation among the Humans. But after his inquiries, he managed to find out how big Zhao Hai’s fame was.

With Zhao Hai’s recent response, the Beast King finally believed that Zhao Hai did really have a huge hatred towards the Radiant Church. But if he adds the Great Nobles to his list of enemies, he wouldn’t be able to thrive among his race. Affecting the grain market of the Human Race wasn’t something that the Buda Clan can afford to handle.

Seeing the Beast King starting to believe him, Zhao Hai then said, “I really do see the Beastmen as friends. To tell you the truth, I really don’t like to interact with other Humans, it’s too tiring. Haha.”

The Beast King stared at Zhao Hai before he chuckled and then it turned into a laugh. A laugh so thick that it penetrated deep into one’s soul.

After some time, the Beast King stopped and then with a deep voice he said to Zhao Hai, “Good, good. Starting today, you’re also going be my friend. As well as my Tiger Tribe’s friend.”

The Beast King wasn’t only the alliance leader of the Beastman Race. At the same time, he was also the Patriarch of the the Giant Tiger Tribe. His influence in his tribe was so big that he can claim to say these words.

When Zhao Hai heard the Beast King, his heart couldn’t help but beat in glee. He knew how heavy the words of the Beast King were. With those words, he would be able to walk in the Prairie much more freely. Even the famous Tribes of the Prairie would have to give him face.

Zhao Hai immediately stood up and gave a salute, “Zhao Hai is very thankful to His Majesty.”

The Beast King waved his hand and had Zhao Hai sit down, then he said, “Our Beastman Race’s food problem would be handed over to you. I don’t know if you knew, but why do you think our Beastmen race is always fighting? It’s to survive. If the Big Tribes wanted to survive, they would have to snatch from the small tribes. And in turn, those small tribes would snatch from the smaller tribes. In between these battles, a lot of lives would be lost. All because there is no food. As a Beastman myself, thinking about this is very painful!”

Zhao Hai couldn’t think of any response as he listened to the Beast King. What the Beast King said was true. Do the Beastmen really want to fight? Of course not. No race was born to kill and die, all of them were only compelled to do so in order to survive.

The Beast King sighed and then turned his head to Zhao Hai and said, “These years, we had always wanted to establish a good relationship with the Humans. But the Human race simply didn’t pay any attention to our Beastman Race. They regard us as barbarians, some even look at us as if we are Wild Beasts. The only thing they want from us is more profit. With such people, who in their right minds would want to cooperate with them? Zhao Hai, those few words you spoke back then outside Iron Wall Fortress moved me. You said that in your eyes, Beastmen and Humans are the same intelligent beings. That made me thing, if there was one Human that we Beastman can comfortably cooperate with, it would only be you.”

Zhao Hai stared at the Beast King, he didn’t say anything. He knew that these words of the Beast King were spoken with true sincerity, this was what was truly inside the Beast King’s heart.

After a moment, Zhao Hai opened his mouth and said, “Your Majesty, I’ll stand behind the words that I’ve said. I treat the Beastmen as my equal. Your Majesty doesn’t need to worry about anything if you cooperate with me.”

The Beast King nodded and then patted Zhao Hai’s shoulder, “Alright, I’ll believe you. I hope you can do it.”

Zhao Hai smiled and said, “I won’t disappoint you, Your Majesty. Right, I’ll have to offer Your Majesty a cup.” Then he turned his hand and took out a bottle of Milk Wine.

The Beast King looked the bottle that Zhao Hai just took out, he had seen this liquor before. The Herculean Bulls and the Black Bears have gifted him some of these. To be honest, he really loved this liquor. This liquor was obviously Milk Wine, but it was much different than what he had drank before.

The Beast King didn’t decline and then finished his Milk Wine first before handing his cup over to Zhao Hai. After he took a sip of Zhao Hai’s milk wine, he nodded. This was indeed the same wine that the Black Bear Tribe has sent.

After looking at the Beast King, Zhao Hai smiled faintly and said, “Your Majesty, perhaps we can cooperate and produce this liquor. What do you think?”

The Beast King couldn’t help but stare at Zhao Hai in confusion. He knew what this liquor represented, it represented huge profits, incomparably huge profits.

When he went to the Human lands, he also inquired about this liquor. This Milk Wine was very popular among the Humans as well. Moreover, it’s sold at a very high price. If Zhao Hai cooperates with the Beastmen, then it would absolutely bring them huge benefits.

Chapter 555: Cooperation(2)

The Beast King stared at Zhao Hai, he really cannot believe what he just heard. He knew that Zhao Hai was the sole producer of this Milk WIne in the Human domain. But if Zhao Hai can tell the Beastmen the method, then the Beastmen would be gaining very good benefits.

Zhao Hai looked at the Beast King’s expression and smiled, “I think that the Milk Wine the Beastmen produce actually tastes very good, but it cannot be stored for too long. I can process your Milk Wine and make them into this. What I’m thinking about was for the Beastmen to ferment the Wine and then sell them to me. After that I’ll be selling the processed wine to the mainland. What do you think?”

The Beast King knitted his brows, to be honest, he didn’t like this approach. This was because the Beastmen wouldn’t gain a lot of benefits. But except for this method, Zhao Hai might not accept any other way.

However, after thinking about it, the Beast King still felt relief. This method of turning normal Milk Wine to high quality Milk Wine was something that only Zhao Hai possessed. If Zhao Hai taught them for no reason, then that would be very suspicious.

But even if Zhao Hai didn’t teach them the method, it doesn’t really matter. After all, Zhao Hai buying their Milk Wine would provide an income to a lot of Beastman households.

The Beastmen herd Argali. And like any other beast, the Argali would eventually give birth. And along with that, they would produce milk. However, all of these milk couldn’t be entirely drank by the Beastmen. Therefore, they would transform the milk into other products such as Milk Wine, cheese, milk skin, and so on.

But these products were still hard to preserve, especially in the Prairie. The Prairie’s environment can cause food to quickly spoil.

Sometimes, Beastmen would just drink the milk as though they were water, which was really a waste. If Zhao Hai bought the milk, then it would certainly be beneficial to ordinary Beastmen.

The Beast King nodded and said, “This is a good thing, but how do you plan to collect these Milk Wines? If they were left for a long time, then their taste would change. Once it changed flavor, do you still want to make them into your Milk Wine?”

Zhao Hai smiled, “This is something that I’d like to ask Your Majesty for help. I want to cooperate with some Beastmen, preferably the Big Tribes. I’ll ask them to collect those Milk Wines and then I’ll take them once every few days. What do you think about this?”

The Beast King thought for a moment and nodded, “This is not an issue, it helps the Beastmen as well. But the Beastman Prairie is too large. Even if the tribes are willing to cooperate with you, are you able to pick them all up?”

Zhao Hai smiled faintly and said, “Your Majesty, did you forget? I have my Blood Hawks. I can use them as transport, greatly reducing travel time. I’ll take care of everything else as long as you can make those tribes work with me.”

The Beast King nodded and said, “Alright, then it’s settled. I’ll help you and write an letter to those big tribes. When you have time, you can go to them and discuss your terms.”

Zhao hai nodded, “Thanks a lot, Your Majesty. I’ll go visit them them as soon as possible.”

The Beast King smiled and said, “You don’t need to be polite. This is also a good thing to us Beastmen. Moreover, I’m not afraid of you deceiving me. In fact even if you did, we wouldn’t be losing a lot. These things would sometimes just turn to waste. With your business, we would be able to turn these excess things into money. It’s definitely worth it.”

When Zhao Hai heard the Beast King, he couldn’t help but smile and said, “It would indeed be better if the Beastmen would gain some income, their lives would be a bit better. RIght, I can pay the Beastmen in three ways, first method is paying them with food and daily necessities. Another way is to pay them with gold and silver, they can use it to trade with other Human Merchants. The third is Magic Beasts, such as Argali. Naturally, I won’t be buying them in high price. I also ask His Majesty to explain it to them, I’m afraid that they won’t believe me.”

The Beast King looked at ZHao Hai and forced a smile, “Not only them, even I might not believe it. If you tell me that you’d buy them in gold and silver, then I might believe you. But trading Milk Wine with Argali? I’m afraid that’s too good to be true. You must know that compared to Humans, we Beastmen regard Argali as much more valuable than grain.”

Zhao Hai smiled faintly and said, “I know, but Your Majesty can rest assured, I meant what I just said.”

The Beast King nodded and then he smiled to Zhao Hai and said, “Alright, I’ll believe you. I’ll release word to the Prairie about this. You don’t need to worry.”

Zhao Hai nodded, “I’ll work on this as soon as possible.”

The Beast King gave a nod, then he turned to the Tiger Guard and said, “Little Tiger, inform everyone that I’ll be having a meal with Mister Zhao Hai at noon. Make them prepare something delicious.”

Zhao Hai didn’t stop the Beast King. Having a meal with the Beast King can also give him some advantages. He looked at the Beast King and said, “Your Majesty, I’m planning to see the Dwarven Race after a period of time. Therefore, I’ll leave the matters of the Prairie over to Ah Tai. If Your Majesty needs anything, you can just send word to Magic Lily store and inform him. He will then pass the message over to me.”

The Beast King’s eyes shined as he said, “You want to go to the Dwarves? That’s fantastic. I heard that the Dwarves have a lot of similarities with the Beastmen. They also have contact with the Elves, so they shouldn’t be worrying about food. Zhao Hai, I only ask you for one thing. Can you help us get some ironware when you return? Not just weapons, but anything made from Iron would be great. The Beastmen really lacks a lot of iron.”

Zhao Hai nodded and smiled, “The Dwarves make a lot of metallic items. I think that wouldn’t be a problem. Your Majesty can rest assured.”

When the Beast King heard Zhao Hai, his expression immediately turned to happiness as he replied, “That’s great. I must thank you in advance. Alright, let’s leave and go to the dining room.”

Zhao Hai didn’t decline and went to the dining room with the Beast King. And when they arrived Zhao Hai stared, didn’t expect the dining room to be another small building inside the Beast King Palace. This building has three stories, the first and second stories were places for the staff to eat while the topmost floor was dedicated for the Beast King.

This made Zhao Hai feel new and strange. The Beast King was really very different compared to the Human monarchs. For example, when the Rosen Emperor eats a meal, he would do it in special place, it was impossible for other people to eat there.  The only exception was when the Emperor allowed that person to dine there. But in the Beast King Palace, the Beast King actually dines in the same place as the others.

When they arrived at the dining room, some Fox Beastmen immediately served them several milk products. Naturally, all of these are just side dishes. The main dish was of course the meat.

While Zhao Hai and the Beast King were eating, they discussed the details of the Milk Wine transaction. The discussion was even carried over after their meal. It was evident that the Beast King was very enthusiastic about this cooperation.

After leaving the Beast King Palace, Zhao Hai immediately returned to Magic Lily Shop. But after arriving in front of the shop, Zhao Hai couldn’t help but stare. The state of the shop was much more different compared to yesterday’s desolate atmosphere. Currently, the shop was very lively, a lot of Beastmen were encircling the shop and being noisy.

After listening for a while, Zhao Hai understood what was going on. Ah Tai must have already spread their intent to buy those things that were useless to the Beastmen. The Beastmen were now discussing with Ah Tai about the price of their trade.

These people weren’t representing themselves, but instead their own tribes. Therefore, they didn’t bring anything along with them, but it was certain that the volume wouldn’t be very small.

Zhao Hai didn’t mind it, Ah Tai can deal with this situation by himself. Therefore, he returned to his tent at the back along with Shue and Shun. After entering the tent, Zhao Hai immediately went to the Space and discussed his Milk Wine cooperation with the Beastmen to Laura and the others.

When Laura heard Zhao Hai, she couldn’t help but knit her brows and said, “Brother Hai, this is indeed a great idea. But with this, our prices in the hotel would be lowered. Also, our wineries aren’t fully built as well. I’m afraid we won’t be able to get any profits in the short-term.”

Zhao Hai smiled faintly and said, “I know. But in fact, it’s very simple to process Milk Wine. As long as we have more apparatus for distillation, everything will be okay. We’ve been doing things wrong since the beginning. We have the Processing Machine, we can just produce some more efficient distillation equipment. Not only could it enhance the flavor, it’s output was much higher as well. And don’t forget, although the Beastmen can produce Milk Wine, a majority of them used Argali milk. Even if Argali milk tastes good, it couldn’t compare to the cow milk that we use. Therefore, our own Milk Wine would still taste much better. When we sell the Beastmen’s milk wine, we can just label it as a common liquor, while we advertise our Milk Wine as high end versions. With this contrast, we can still manage to get substantial income from this business.”

As soon as Laura and the others heard Zhao Hai, their eyes couldn’t help but light up. They had experienced how magical the Processing Machine was. As long as they know what they want, then the Processing Machine can certainly make it. They couldn’t think of anything that the Processing Machine can’t make. Therefore, Zhao Hai’s idea was very reasonable.

At the same time, outsiders aren’t able to observe what happens inside the Black Wasteland. So this method was indeed feasible.

Laura looked at Zhao Hai and said, “Alright, then there’s no problem. Now that we got our  trade network, selling them out wouldn’t be a problem. Brother Hai, we must carry this out as soon as possible. Not only would it make the Beastman comfortable, it can also bring a lot more benefits to our Buda Clan.”

Lizzy nodded and said, “Big Brother Hai, i think that we should also inform Third Brother about this. After all, most of our sales involve wholesale, we need to rely on others with regards to retail business.”

Zhao Hai smiled and said, “We don’t need to worry about this for now. We need to first establish a receiving network inside the Prairie. After that, it wouldn’t be too late to discuss things with Third Brother. Moreover, for the system of receiving goods, I already have someone in mind.”

Lizzy stared in confusion as she asked, “Someone? Who is that? We already have our Blood Hawks, we don’t need to cooperate with another person.”

Zhao Hai smiled and said, “The Beastman Prairie is too big. Moreover, I don’t want to bring attention to the amount of Blood Hawks that I have. Therefore, I wanted to cooperate with the Hawk Beastmen. Although they cannot fly as far, short distances wouldn’t be a problem. They can help us concentrate the supply from some small tribes to the big tribes. It would be much more convenient for us to collect it with that method. And if we cooperate with the Hawk Beastmen, it would be equal to tying them with our business. For us, this is definitely a good choice.”

Laura nodded and said, “I agree with Brother Hai’s words. The Hawk Race is also a big Warring Race. The placement of the tribes is very broad, and their status among the Beastmen is high as well. We must ask for the Beast King’s help in convincing the Hawk Race to help us. At the same time, this cooperation would bring benefits to them as well, so they definitely won’t decline. The Markey Family has some relationship with the Golden Ringed Hawks from before, we can approach them for this matter.”

Zhao Hai nodded, then he smiled faintly and said, “As long as this thing goes through, I think the friendship flags of the Tiger and Hawk Race would be in our hands soon. When that happens, our Buda Clan’s reputation in the Prairie would be increased. This would be very good for our future plans in the Prairie.”

Laura nodded, “Although we have a lot of business there, we don’t have a lot of partnerships with the big Warring Tribes, we only have Dogs and Black Bears. If we want to dominate the entire grain market of the Prairie, gaining a lot of partnerships would be the most important thing for us to do.”

Lizzy looked at Zhao Hai and said, “Big Brother Hai, when do you plan on visiting the Hawk Tribe?”

Zhao Hai smiled and said, “I’ll go visit them two days after the Beast King spreads the word of our Milk Wine cooperation. When that time comes, it wouldn’t be too late for me to visit them.”

Megan looked at Zhao Hai and shifted the topic, “Elder Brother Hai, do you really want the Dwarves to make some weapons for the Beastmen? What if they attack the Humans?”

Zhao Hai sighed, then he replied, “It really depends. If the Beastmen are really willing to attack the Humans, they wouldn’t even need weapons in order to do so. But if they don’t want to attack, even if they have good weapons, they still wouldn’t do so.”

Laura nodded and said, “Things are still arbitrary. After all. we still don’t know the situation with the Dwarves. But if the Beast King says that they have a relationship with the Elves, then it is possibly so. As long as we get in touch with the Elves as well, then the benefits to us would be very big.”

The people present knew what Laura meant. They needed a lot of things to upgrade the Space, and they didn’t have the means to do so right now. Therefore, they can only get the materials from the Elven Forests in order to progress.

The Elven Forest was recognized as the most mystical place that was inhabited by an intelligent race. It’s mysteriousness wasn’t any worse than the Carrion Swamp. And from the previous contacts with the Elves, it was said that the forest contained a lot of strange flowers and plants. And it was precisely those things that managed to get Zhao Hai’s attention.

Chapter 556: Karen Goes Insane

Several days passed as Zhao Hai stayed inside Magic Lily Shop. However, he wasn’t idling inside. Although he has mapped most of the Prairie, there was still quite a large chunk of it that he has not yet saved. If he wanted to do business in the entire Beastman Prairie, then it would be better for him to save the Prairie’s map into the Space’s monitor.

At the same time, Ah Tai has been busy as well. He was working hard at making the transactions with the Beastmen. From being an unknown store, the Magic Lily Shop had already managed to make a reputation among the Beastmen. And it was not only because it was the first shop that had Beastmen Friendship flags in it, but it was also because of the recent matter.

Being reluctant in throwing useless things away was another trait of the Beastmen. Because of this, they would have piles of rotting things in their hands. They couldn’t sell it off as well since it was also useless to the other tribes.

But now that Magic Lily Shop was willing to take those off of their hands, it wasn’t a mystery as to why the Beastmen were ecstatic. It didn’t take long before word spread to the entire Beastman Prairie, giving the Beastmen a favorable impression towards Magic Lily Shop.

Five days after Zhao Hai met with the Beast King, a reaction was finally seen in Beast God City. The Beast King sent forth various scrolls out, these scrolls were like those used in Ancient China. those scrolls were sent to various Patriarchs of the Beastman Race, informing them about Zhao Hai’s Milk Wine partnership.

The excitement that this caused was much greater than the purchasing of useless goods. Many Patriarchs had gone to Beast God City to confirm whether this was true or not. In turn, this made Ah Tai much more busy, he now has to deal with the inquiries of the Patriarchs every day.

Zhao Hai looked at the situation and knew that it was the time to visit the Golden Ringed Hawks. Through the Golden Ringed Hawks, he can reach the Hawk Race’s Royal Tribe. Then he would talk to their Hawk King with regards to his plan of cooperation with the entire Hawk Race.

Three days after the Beast King sent word out, Zhao Hai rode his carriage as it left Beast God City and headed to the Golden Ringed Hawk’s territory.

The Golden Ringed Hawks were also a major force inside the Hawk Race. They were one of the formidable Beastmen in the Prairie. Their builds weren’t tall and big, however their flying mounts were fast. Among the Beastman race, the Golden Ringed Hawks were among the most well known aerial scouts.

In the past, when the Golden Ringed Hawks and the Markey Family were in a partnership, they way that the Markey Family conducted themselves were very overbearing. Therefore, their cooperation with the Golden RInged Hawks wasn’t very big. If one were to describe it, their transactions might be in the low to medium sized.

Zhao Hai’s carriage travelled quickly, he wanted to reach the Hawk Race at the shortest possible time and discuss the cooperation with the other races. This way, the logistics of the Milk Wine business would get established as early as possible.

In the past few days, Zhao Hai had spent a lot of gold coins in the Space to make a lot of advanced level distillation equipment. Once these equipment were installed in Iron Mountain Fort, their Milk Wine output would definitely increase by a large amount.

Naturally these equipment needed power, but Zhao Hai had already thought about it. So he also had the Processing Machine make a set of generators in the Space. This generators were hydropower generators. Although their electric output wasn’t high, it was enough to satiate for the power consumption of the distillation equipment.

And since the process involved electricity, Zhao Hai made sure to have the workers educated in safety and reminded them to work carefully. He didn’t want someone to have an accident.

But while Zhao Hai installed these things, a person immediately came with eyes as bright and shiny as the sun. This person was none other than his father-in-law, Karen.

Karen was infatuated in inventions and novel ideas, and the things that he invented were mostly dealing with Magic Formations that increase comfort of life. So now that he saw the new  things that Zhao Hai brought, he immediately felt very curious.

Therefore, it didn’t take a long time before he planned to allocate all of his time and energy to research this new thing. When Zhao Hai saw his expression, he immediately invited Karen into the Space, letting Karen see the blueprints of these new equipment.

And since Karen was an expert in this field, he immediately discovered how useful these things would be in the Ark Continent. Because of the existence of Magic Crystals, most of the equipment in the continent were exclusively using Magic Crystals as sources of power. The blueprints that Zhao Hai showed Karen made him see another side of the world. It seems like there was a power system that can replace the Magic Crystals.

Zhao Hai didn’t plan to stop Karen upon seeing his excited expression. He allowed Karen to inspect the equipment but he also told Laura to pay attention to Karen and make sure that he gets proper food and rest. Zhao Hai knew that Karen was a research freak. Once Karen discovers something interesting, it wasn’t unlikely for him to study without end.

Five days passed by and Zhao Hai finally arrived at the Golden Ringed Hawk’s domain. In Zhao Hai’s mind, he expected the Golden Ringed Hawks to live in a mountain or maybe in a forest. However, he didn’t think that the Golden Ringed Hawks’ camp would actually be just like the camp of any other Beastman in the Prairie.

On Zhao Hai’s carriage, the friendship flags of the Dog Race and the Black Bear Tribe as well as the Herculean Bull King’s flag was erected. Therefore, one could say that his road was always left unblocked. Every tribe that Zhao Hai met treated him with politeness. And when it was time to rest in the evening, these tribes would be very enthusiastic to have Zhao Hai stay with them.

Naturally, Zhao Hai wouldn’t decline their offers, he also gave these tribes some of his Milk Wine as a gift. The tribes near Beast God City were almost all Big Warring tribes. When they went to war, a lot of their loot came up to be useless. So when Magic Lily shop started to buy these items, these tribes were extremely glad. And since Zhao Hai was the shop’s owner, it was no wonder that they treated Zhao Hai as a valuable guest.

At the same time, the reason why Zhao Hai gave them some Milk Wine was because these Beastmen weren’t lacking in both grain and daily necessities. He also decided to give them his Milk Wine in order to show them the Milk Wine that he’d make from the Milk Wines that these tribes would produce. This way, the doubts in these Beastmen’s minds would eventually fade away.

When Zhao Hai finally arrived at the Golden Ringed Hawk’s Domain, he didn’t even need to head towards their main camp before the tribe sent a party to welcome him.

A team of a thousand Golden Ringed Hawk Knights descended next to Zhao Hai’s carriage. When Zhao Hai gave his name, they immediately flew back up into the sky and lead the way towards their main camp.

Upon arriving at the camp of the Golden Ringed Hawks, Zhao Hai was immediately led to the camp’s golden tent. This golden tent was very similar to other golden tents of the Beastmen. But from what Zhao Hai can see, the living standards of this tribe was very good. Their golden tent looked much better compared to the Black Bears.

When Zhao Hai entered the tent, he saw several Golden Ringed Hawks present inside. On the most honored seat, an old Golden Ringed Hawk can be seen. This old Beastman had a huge Hawk Head, and the feathers on his neck were gold, it looked very beautiful.

Zhao Hai quickly noticed an issue, although the Golden Ringed Hawks had Hawk heads, the shape of their faces were more like a Human. At the very least, their eyes weren’t on the sides of their heads, but were instead at the front like how Humans were. They looked more like a Human with crazy hair compared to a Hawk-headed beastman.

Zhao Hai quickly took a step forward and made a bow and said, “Zhao Hai has seen the Golden Ringed Hawk tribe’s Hawk King. I thank the Hawk King for sparing time to see me.”

The Golden Ringed Hawk King laughed and stood up to help Zhao Hai up, then he said, “Mister Zhao Hai is too polite. Even the Beast King treats you as an honored guest, so how could I dare neglect your presence?” His voice was somewhat hoarse, but his imposing tone was very strong, worthy of someone who held the title of Hawk King.

Zhao Hai hastily straightened his body and then smiled and said, “The Hawk King is also too polite. I only became the Beast King’s guest because of his summons. And then we discussed about a partnership. Therefore, I won’t dare to receive the Hawk King’s favor.”

The Hawk King laughed, “Mister shouldn’t be too polite, for the Beast King to accept Mister’s Milk Wine business meant that the Beast King also held you in high regard. Right, Mister, what’s the reason for you to specially come to my Golden Ringed Hawk tribe?”

Zhao Hai quickly replied and said, “The Hawk King might not know, but the Markey Family who had business with you in the past is somewhat related to me. Therefore, I went here to see you first.”

The Hawk King asked Zhao Hai to sit down first then he offered him Milk Tea and then said, “Oh? I didn’t know about that. What relationship did Mister and the Markey Family have? But I heard that Mister is part of the Buda Clan?”

Zhao Hai smiled and said, “My Buda Clan was once a medium-sized family in the Aksu Empire. But were were later framed and was exiled to the Black Wasteland. Since we can’t develop the land there, I had no choice but do business. And then while doing so, I fell in love with a young lady from the Markey Family named Laura. But the Markey Family didn’t like me, and were very adamant in breaking our relationship so they sent some assassins to deal with me many times. In the end, I had enough of it and decided to eliminated them, making my wife the family’s Patriarch. And after my wife took over, we noticed that the family had some business with the Golden Ringed Hawk Tribe in the past. But when we were about to visit, we didn’t expect that the Radiant Church would cause a food shortage in the Prairie. I only have so much food in my hand that it would only be like throwing a cup of water in a burning carriage if I decided to help. And now that my wife is handling the affairs of the Markey Family after the family’s recent conflict, we had no other choice but to let other business go. It’s truly regrettable.”

Zhao Hai said these to the Hawk King because he wanted to tell the Hawk King that the Markey Family who interacted with you before was not the same as the Markey Family right now.

Zhao Hai knew that they Markey Family didn’t have any good reputation in the Prairie. So he was afraid that the Hawks would misunderstand him. If he doesn’t say those words, then the cooperation with the Hawks might go through a bumpy road.

At the same time, from the Hawk King’s words, Zhao Hai understood that the Golden Ringed Hawks were somewhat aware of the situation on the Human domain. Therefore, Zhao Hai told his matters to the Hawk King straightly, avoiding any misunderstandings in the future.

*note – removed the ‘-headed’ from the race names. It makes me feel giddy and is awkward to type in the keyboard xD*

Chapter 557: Hawk King Mountain

The Hawk King quietly listened to Zhao Hai’s words. To be honest, he already had a bit of understanding about Zhao Hai’s affairs. Back at the war, when Zhao Hai gave the Beastmen information, the Beast King had asked the Hawk King to look into Zhao Hai, so naturally the Hawk King would know.

Since the Hawk King found out before hand, therefore he knew that Zhao Hai’s words were true. In the Human lands, Zhao Hai was like a living legend. Turning a fallen clan into one of the most powerful families in the Continent in just one short year wasn’t something that ordinary people could achieve.

The Hawk King asking Zhao Hai about his relationship with the Markey Family was just a decoy in order to probe Zhao Hai. In the Beastman Prairie, there were a lot of rumors about Zhao Hai. Majority of them were about how Zhao Hai treated the Beastmen with sincerity, something a friend would only do. The Hawk King just wanted to see if the rumors about Zhao Hai were indeed real.

And Zhao Hai’s reply didn’t disappoint him. He looked at Zhao Hai and laughed, “Why would mister regret it, you’re already here in our Golden Ringed Hawk Tribe. To be honest, compared to the Markey Family, I’d much better prefer doing business with mister.”

Zhao Hai smiled and said, “I thank the Hawk King for your uplifting words. Today, I came to the Hawk King’s tribe because I have something to ask for the Hawk King’s help with.”

The Hawk King stared, he was curious, so he looked at Zhao Hai and said, “Mister is the Beastman Race’s friend. Tell me your request, if I can offer help, then I would help.”

Zhao Hai smiled faintly, then he told the Hawk King about his plan off cooperating with the Hawk Race. This cooperation involves him providing the Hawk Race with Space Bags. But these Space Bags are to be used to store Milk Wine. Every five days, the Hawks would go to the various tribes and collect Milk Wine while carrying some money along the way. The Milk Wine can be exchanged with grain, gold, or Argali. If they wanted grain or gold, then they can exchange it on the spot. On the other hand, if they want Argali, they would have to pick them up at Beast God City.

After the Hawk King heard Zhao Hai, he immediately knew that this cooperation would bring huge benefits to the Hawk Race. His eyes couldn’t help but light up as he looked at Zhao Hai and said, “Will Mister really give our Hawk Tribe some Space Bags? Are we going to need a large number of them?”

Zhao Hai smiled and said, “It’s not really a lot, 20 Space Bags should be enough.” The reason why Zhao Hai was so sure of this was because when the Space levels up, the capacity of the Space Bags that it produces would get bigger. Right now, their capacity had already reached about a thousand cubic meters, give or take a few cubic meters.

When the Hawk King heard Zhao Hai, he was finally convinced. Zhao Hai really did want to give the Hawks some Space Bags in order to transport Milk Wine.

The Hawk King stood up and then laughed and said, “Alright, since Mister is confident enough, then I won’t say anything more. Mister can take a rest in the camp in the meantime. Tomorrow, I shall bring Mister to the main camp of the Hawk Race.”

Zhao Hai stood up as well and gave a bow to the Hawk King and said, “I give my thanks to the Hawk King.”

The Hawk King laughed and said, “Mister doesn’t need to thank me. Instead, it should be me who needs to express gratitude. This cooperation would surely bring big benefits to my Hawk Race.”

Zhao Hai didn’t dare accept it, but the Hawk King didn’t care. The Hawk King just laughed again and said, “Right, since Mister has come to visit my tribe, how could I not invite mister over for a drink. Come, come, let’s drink a cup.”

When he knew that Zhao Hai was coming, the Hawk King immediately had people prepare. And now that their discussions were finished, it was time for food and drinks.

The night went by without any disturbances and the next morning, the Hawk King sent someone to look for Zhao Hai. After the Hawk King and Zhao Hai had their breakfast, the Hawk King immediately told Zhao Hai that they’d be heading towards the Hawk Race’s main camp.

Zhao Hai would certainly not decline. But the Hawk King also informed Zhao Hai that in order to go to the Hawk Race’s main camp, riding a Hawk would be a much better option. Therefore, Zhao Hai immediately called over his Blood Hawks.

When the Golden Ringed Hawk King saw how beautiful Zhao Hai’s Blood Haw was, his eyes couldn’t help but express his envy. He had heard that the Humans were now starting to develop their Air Force, moreover, the Magic Beast used for the Air Force was provided by Zhao Hai.

Zhao Hai, Shun, and Shue rode their Blood Hawks and followed behind the Hawk King and his 1000 Golden Ringed Hawk Knights. After they left the Golden Ringed Hawk’s camp, they immediately went straight for the Hawk King Mountain.

This Hawk King Mountain was actually a boundary mountain. The south side of this mountain was the Beastman Prairie while at its north was the Northern Ice Fields. The Northern Ice Fields were also one of the continent’s great regions. There was almost nobody who entered deep into the  Ice Fields who managed to return. Even if it was the Ice Hawks, the Great TIgers, the Polar Bears, and the other Royal Tribes, nobody would dare venture too deep into the Ice Field. Otherwise, they would have no other way out.

At the same time, the Hawk King Mountain was also the highest mountain in the Prairie. It was most commonly known to the Beastmen as the Divine Mountain. It was because the mountain’s position allowed it to keep the Northern Winds away. If the Northern Ice Field Winds were to reach the Prairie, then the Prairie would definitely turn into a huge snowy plain.

Zhao Hai and the others flew in the sky for a good three days before they saw a faint image of the Hawk King mountain in the distance. With how high the mountain was, one would even think that it was connected to the sky.

The top of the mountain was azure white, very beautiful. These three days of flight also showed Zhao Hai the tenacity of the Beastmen. The Hawks ate their meals while flying and did so for three days without even going to sleep.

To be honest, flying in the sky wasn’t a very fun activity. Perhaps it might feel good in the beginning, but as time goes by, you would begin to be tired of it. Not only because of the cold air, but the buffeting of the wind was something very uncomfortable as well.

Zhao Hai thought that the Hawks wouldn’t be able to fly long distances like from what he heard. But this flight completely broke his misconception. The Hawks clearly chose to fly short distances and low altitudes in order to fool the Humans.

The Beastmen Race were known to be tough and strong, they can endure even the most rigorous tasks. This time, Zhao Hai was asked to follow the Hawks, so he couldn’t decline. However, when things go bad, he would just go to the Space when nobody’s looking for him.

So in three days, Zhao Hai and the others finally arrived at Hawk King Mountain. When he was close to his destination, Zhao Hai came out of the Space, the Golden Ringed Hawks should be looking for him right now.

After coming out of the Space, Zhao Hai immediately placed some Wind Magic on to his body as well as Shue’s and Shun’s, making it possible for the harsh winds to evade them.

Just after doing that, the Hawk King arrived at Zhao Hai’s side. The Hawks had special leather equipment, a tight leather jacket as well as special gloves on their hands. This way, they wouldn’t be affected by the cold harsh winds.

When the Hawk King saw Zhao Hai, he couldn’t help but feel envious. It was really a pity that the Beastmen were unable to use Magic.

Hawks have the ability to speak in the air, so the Hawk King turned his head to Zhao Hai and said, “Mister Zhao Hai, in a while, a guard of the Ice Hawk King would be coming to meet use. Don’t go anywhere they else until they arrive.”

Zhao Hai nodded and said, “Alright, the Hawk King can rest assured, I definitely won’t make any careless actions.” The Hawk King nodded, and then before long,  a shadow came from the mountain and slowly flew towards them.

It didn’t take a long time before the shadow appeared in front of Zhao Hai. The mounts that these people were riding on were bluish hawks. They were much slimmer than the Blood Hawks, but they appeared much more alive. The Beastmen that were riding on them looked just like the Golden Ringed Hawks but their head feathers were blue in color.

These blue Hawks surrounded the Golden Ringed Hawks and escorted them into the Hawk King Mountain.

They didn’t go to the mountain’s summit, it was too high and too cold. Their destination was instead somewhere along the middle of the Hawk King Mountain. The mountain’s halfway point had big trees growing in them. The trees were so tall it seemed like they were piercing the skies, like swords stabbed on the ground. Most importantly, these trees were very thick, with most of them having a diameter of over 20 meters.

Some houses can be seen on these trees. The houses were constructed in a hole carved into the tree. Zhao Hai can even see a couple of Ice Hawks moving in and out of these houses.

After flying over the trees, Zhao Hai can see a large canyon. The canyon was very wide and it seems like it’s ground was covered in grass. On the walls of the canyon, caves were carved out. The people who lived here were Ice Hawks as well.

However this canyon wasn’t Zhao Hai’s destination. After flying over the canyon, Zhao Hai can spot a very enormous cavern halfway up the mountain. It’s entrance was similarly large, about a hundred meters tall and 60 meters wide. The Hawks then flew towards this cavern along with Zhao Hai and the others.

Zhao Hai discovered that although there were Hawks flying in and out of the entrance, their flight was also very orderly. The left side of the entrance was for entering while the right side was for leaving. This arrangement made the entrance quite organized.

As the group entered the cavern, Zhao Hai came to understand how large this hole in the mountain was. And even if it was 10 degrees inside, there weren’t any winds at all.

Inside the cavern were smaller caves where the Ice Hawk King’s family lived in. In the middle of the cavern, there was a square, and in the middle of the square there was actually a very big pool.

The group slowly descended to that square along with Zhao Hai’s group. When Zhao Hai came down from his Blood Hawk, he pretended to move his hands an feet as he carefully looked around the cavern.

The hole in the cavern was very much like the underground city that the Dwarves had built under Iron Mountain. But compared to Iron Mountain, this cavern was much bigger. Moreover, there weren’t any stairs that can be seen. Anyone who wanted to move anywhere needed to ride a hawk, it was a very unusual sight.

After Zhao Hai got down, the Golden Ringed Hawk King welcomed him to the place as he smiled and said, “Mister Zhao Hai had to endure the hardship. This matter is really too important for our race, I ask Mister for his forgiveness.”

Chapter 558: Price

Zhao Hai smiled faintly and said, “Hawk King is too polite. In fact, I want to thank you. I really am quite anxious about this matter. Haha.”

The Hawk King smiled and said, “This is the Ice Hawk King’s place, this is where he lives and does his work. I don’t know if Mister Zhao Hai has noticed, but the royal tribes of the Beastman Warring Races are all situated in the vicinity of the Northern Ice Fields. Legend has told us that the Northern Ice Fields contain formidable Magic Beasts that can cause a calamity to the Prairie. This was the reason why the Royal Tribes decided to move here, it was in order to protect the entire Beastman Race.”

Zhao Hai nodded, he had developed a habit to not disregard the legends of the Ark Continent. It was because these legends have high probabilities of being true, quite unlike the legends back on Earth.

At this time, an Ice Hawk arrived in front of them. The Ice Hawk issued a salute and then said, “Golden Ringed Hawk King, Mister Zhao Hai, the Hawk King invites you in.”

Zhao Hai and the Golden Ringed Hawk King immediately complied, they rode their mounts and then followed behind the Ice Hawk. The space inside was truly high, even if they had already flown 500 meters, they were still heading up.

In the uppermost lever, Zhao Hai and the others stopped in front of the sole cave entrance present. The cave’s entrance was about 10 meters high, and had a platform protruding out from it. The platform was about 30 square meters. Zhao Hai and the others landed their mounts on this platform.

This time, only three people had come here. When the three of them came down from their mounts, the hawk mounts immediately left. Then the Ice Hawk escorted Zhao Hai and the Golden Ringed Hawk King inside the cave.

After entering the cave, Zhao Hai couldn’t help but stare at the scene. Inside the cave were a lot of ignited braziers, completely illuminating the entire cave.

In this cave, an Ice Hawk can be seen sitting on the innermost part, reading a sheepskin scroll among the numerous scrolls around him.

However, this Ice Hawk didn’t actually process these documents, he was just simply looking through them. This Ice Hawk didn’t have much of a difference compared to the others of his race. He even looked thin, thinner than the common Ice Hawk. He had a golden crown on his head, sitting there as he turned his pair of cold hawk eyes towards Zhao Hai and the others. His mere gaze made Zhao Hai feel like the surrounding air just dropped a couple of degrees.

Zhao Hai didn’t know, but this was actually an innate ability of the Ice Hawk Tribe. Once this ability was in full use, it would send forth a beam that can freeze anything in its way. It’s intensity was just like an attack from a 5th rank mage, and it was quite difficult to deal with.

The Golden Ringed Hawk King immediately issued a salute and said, “Golden Ringed Hawk King has see the Ice Hawk King. This is Mister Zhao Hai, mister wants to cooperate with our Hawk Race regarding his Milk Wine business. Therefore, I led him here to see you.”

The Ice Hawk King nodded and said, “Right, I have heard about Mister Zhao Hai but this is my first time meeting mister, please have a seat.” Although his gaze was very cold, his expression was actually quite temperate.

Zhao Hai immediately responded courteously, “I thank the Hawk King.” Then he sat on a chair after the Golden Ringed Hawk King.

After sitting down, the Ice Hawk King looked at Zhao Hai and said, “The Beast King has sent word out about mister’s Milk Wine business. Before everything, this King here wants mister to accept my gratitude in behalf of the entire Beastman Race.”

Zhao Hai replied, “I don’t dare. This business also makes me money. Haha. This time, I wanted to see the Hawk King because I need help from the Hawk Race.”

The Hawk King looked at Zhao Hai and smiled faintly, “Mister can say it freely. As long as we can be of help, then I wouldn’t decline immediately. For the sake of the Beastman Race, I shall provide mister with a helping hand.”

Zhao Hai smiled faintly and said, “I’ll thank the Hawk King in advance.” Then he told the Ice Hawk King about the details of his intended cooperation with the Hawk Race.

The Ice Hawk King silently listened to Zhao Hai’s words. After Zhao Hai spoke, the Hawk King nodded and then smiled towards Zhao Hai and said, “Mister, this is basically giving money to my Hawk Race. So how can we just push this opportunity away? Rest assured, with how broad our tribes are placed in the Prairie, information about mister’s Milk Wine business would be delivered much more quickly. Mister cooperating with us is indeed something good. I agree, tomorrow I’ll write a letter informing all of the Hawk Tribes, mister can rest assured.”

Zhao Hai didn’t expect the discussion would go this smoothly. He stared for a moment before he hastily stood up and bowed to the Hawk King and said, “This Zhao Hai thanks the Hawk King. But does the Hawk King also want to help me collect the Milk Wine?”

Zhao Hai knew how arrogant Royals were, so he was afraid that it would be impossible for them to help him collect Milk Wine. If the Hawk King was not willing to cooperate, then the Milk Wine business would have problems.

The Hawk King looked at Zhao Hai and smiled, “Of course, mister doesn’t even need to ask.”

Zhao Hai became happy, then he immediately said, “That’s great. I’ll have to ask the Hawk Race to receive the Milk Wine in a radius of three thousand li in a single Space Bag. For the price, one jin of Milk Wine would be traded with five jin of grain. What does the Hawk King think about this price?”

The Hawk King thought for a moment and then nodded, “This price is quite high.”

Zhao Hai faintly smiled and said, “The Hawk King can receive the Milk Wine from the other races with the previously stated price. And once the Hawk Race delivers the Milk Wine to Beast God City, I would exchange them for five and a fifth of a jin of grain for each jin of Milk Wine. These extra fifth of a jin can be said to be the transportation costs for the Hawk Race. What does the Hawk King think about this?”[1]

The Hawk King stared before his two eyes lit up. He knew that this 22 liang cannot be underestimated. Once added up, this amount was very big. Keep in mind, those small Beastman tribe can also produce a lot of milk wine annually. A single Beastman household would be able to provide 100 jin of Milk Wine monthly. And when those 100 jin of Milk Wine were traded for 500 jin of grain, the Hawk Clan would get a commission of 20 jins. Now how many Beastmen household are there? And in the end, how much grain can the Hawk Clan gain? With this arrangement, the Hawk Clan wouldn’t even need to buy food for themselves in the future.

After thinking about it, the Hawk King still didn’t immediately agree, he knit his brows and said, “Mister, in truth, this price is too high. It might be disadvantageous to Mister. If mister owes us, then it wouldn’t be good for the entire Beastman Race. From what I can see, Mister can set the price at one jin of Milk Wine per three jins of grain. And then our Hawk Clan would get about a tenth or so jin of grain as commission.”

Zhao Hai was shocked, he didn’t see someone like this before, lowering his benefits in order to decrease pressure. However, once he thought about the Hawk King’s words, Zhao Hai understood what he meant. The Hawk King was afraid of Zhao Hai owing the Beastmen and making him stop his Milk Wine business, causing the Beastmen to lose out on the long run. Also, the price that the Hawk King quoted was somewhat of a fair price for the Beastmen.

Zhao Hai knit his brows and then said, “Lower the price? How much jin of Milk Wine can the Beastman Race produce every month?”

The Hawk King smiled faintly and said, “Mister doesn’t need to worry. The average Beastman household would be able to produce not less than 50 jin of Milk Wine every month. This is already quite a large number.”

Zhao Hai nodded, he already expected these numbers. He had lived with the Beastmen before, so he knew that they cannot go without Milk Wine. But even if they produce more than 50 jin each month, they would also need to leave something behind for them to drink. They would only sell their excess off. If a household can sell 20 jin of Milk Wine each month, it would produce about one or two jins of Milk Wine after distillation. This is already acceptable.

Zhao Hai nodded and said, “Alright, then we’ll go with the Hawk King’s suggestion. I’ll have to trouble the Hawk King to spread the word tomorrow.”

The Hawk King smiled and said, “It’s not too much trouble, this is something good for the Beastmen. But mister, I’ll have to inform you that it would be impossible for the households to sell 50 jins of Milk Wine. Even if we Beastmen can stand not being able to eat, we cannot survive if we don’t drink. So the only wine we would sell to Mister would be the excess. I hope mister has prepared his mind for this. Along with the news, I’ll also have the Hawks do some statistics in each tribe, getting data on how much Milk Wine each one can produce so that Mister can have a figure in mind. Is Mister alright with this?”

Zhao Hai smiled and gave the Hawk King a bow and said, “Zhao Hai thanks the Hawk King. This matter is truly very important for me.”

The Hawk King chuckled, then he helped Zhao Hai up and said, “Mister doesn’t need to be so polite. We’re now in a partnership, so we would do our best to help Mister. The higher income Mister gets, the higher cut we receive.” Zhao Hai smiled at the Hawk King’s words.

After a day of rest, the Beast King spread word to the Hawk Tribes in the Prairie. At the same time, he also divided the Prairie into 20 different regions. A Hawk Tribe would be responsible for receiving the Milk Wine in each region.

Upon completing all of these, Zhao Hai returned to Beast God City and waited for the news from the Hawk Race. It shouldn’t take too long for the Hawks to tell him how much Milk Wine the Beastman Prairie would produce each month.

And five days after Zhao Hai arrived at Beast God City, the Hawk King sent him the numbers. For the entire Beastman Race, they would be able to sell about 10 million jin. This number was much smaller than what Zhao Hai expected. But in the end, he understood. The Beastmen also had a lot of uses for their milk, aside from making Milk Wine. At the same time, they would also leave behind some milk wine for themselves, which explains the small amount they could sell each month.

Although the Beastmen lacked grain, because of their living environment, they became able to consume milk products while eating their food. After all, they cannot just use up all of their grain before the winter, or else, they wouldn’t be able to survive until spring.

But because of this, the Beastmen were very grateful towards Zhao Hai. They weren’t looking at Milk Wine as a main source of income, they just use the liquor as some sort of pocket money. It was like those people in the rural areas back on earth. If they have excess eggs from their chickens, then they would sell if off as extra change, if they don’t have a lot, then they would keep it for themselves to consume.

Even if it was pocket change, it still helped them out a lot. Plenty of Beastmen decided to not trade their Milk WIne with grain, but in daily necessities instead.

After knowing about this situation, Zhao Hai didn’t care. He wasn’t afraid of spending 30 million jin of grain. And he was also not worried about not selling the 1 million jin of milk wine to the Human lands.

After taking care about the initial steps, Zhao Hai handed the matter over to Ah Tai. Ah Tai was just responsible for collecting the Milk Wine as well as giving out the payments. He didn’t have to do anything else, it was this simple.

When he saw that things had already been taken care of, Zhao Hai returned to Iron Mountain Fort. The winery in the Fort was already finished. The winery was divided into four districts; one was for Fruit Wine, one was for Rice Wine, one was for Beer, and the last one was for Milk Wine.

The machines for these districts were already installed as well. Some of them might be modern equipment, but the workers were already adept in using it.

Now, the Beastmen appeared to be understaffed. The earliest of Zhao Hai’s slaves were already sent out to manage the villages. Therefore, the ones left to man the brewery were only the Beastmen. Because of this, Zhao Hai asked the original slaves to help with the situation. And since the new slaves were already settled down and were working on their own fields, there happened to be some surplus manpower in the villages. Therefore, Zhao Hai had those people go to the winery and help, this would also aid the slave families earn a bit more income.

After this was taken care of, Zhao Hai also asked Green to start making the school for the children in the Black Wasteland. There were plenty of idle children right now, so Zhao Hai wanted all of them to be educated at school. Naturally, this was in the premise that they would be diligent in their studies.

When the matters in the Black Wasteland were done, Zhao Hai then returned to the Rosen Empire. He still needed to approach, Randolph, Charlie, Jesse, and the Shelley Family. He wanted them to prepare for the Milk Wine business.

The Milk Wine that Zhao Hai wanted to sell this time was the distilled Milk Wine of the Beastmen. Although it wasn’t as good as his Milk Wine, it’s flavor was still very tasty. Moreover, it also developed some kind of acidic taste to it. This acidic Milk Wine and Zhao Hai’s Milk Wine was different, one could definitely tell just from one sip. But it still gave a very unusual flavor, so Zhao Hai continued on to make this wine.

He also had Randolph and the others taste this new type of wine, and they agreed to sell it. Zhao Hai’s new wines weren’t priced very high, general commoners would be able to afford it. Therefore, their attraction towards Randolph and the others was quite big.

The grain in the continent was just sufficient for them to eat, moreover, they also needed to supply the Beastmen. Therefore, nobody was thinking about making wine out of grain. What people usually drank was Fruit Wine, but not all fruits can be made into liquor. This made wines quite rare in the Human lands, especially to the cash strapped commoners. If Zhao Hai’s cheap wine gets sold to these commoners, how much daily sales could Randolph and the others get? It would surely be an astronomical number.

* * *

1 jin is 16 liang

Chapter 559: Business Nuances

Some small merchants in the mainland always think that only expensive things can make the most money. But they didn’t know that, in fact, the most profitable things weren’t those expensive products, it was sometimes those things that people use in their livelihood. Those things were where true money can be found.

Although Zhao Hai’s liquor made from Beastmen Milk Wine tasted average, it wins in being cheap. And since its degree was very high, ordinary civilians would be afraid of it being consumed quickly when they take it back home. And since it was priced low, it would certainly be popular among the commoners.

Randolph and the others had their own business outlets, and these outlets mostly deal with people’s day to day lives. If the liquors were launched, then their business would surely get better.

The most profitable businesses always involved unique products. Although the Milk WIne wasn’t unique, it’s definitely so to the commoners.

Average civilians would also pick their own fruits and make it into wine. But the wine that they make had very low degrees and weren’t tasty at all. And most importantly, the commoners didn’t have the time to improve upon this craft.

Commoners were generally busying themselves in order to survive. If they go out of town and get some fruit, it would take them at least a day to do so. They would rather use this one day to make money. And if they were to get some fruits, they can just sell them immediately. Therefore, for the civilians, making Fruit Wine just wasn’t worth it.

Randolph and the others were much more experienced than Zhao Hai. When Zhao Hai wanted to cooperate with the Beastmen about their Milk Wine, they had him temporarily stall it. After all, they still needed to do market research and determine whether the Milk Wine would sell well on the Human markets.

And after undergoing strict calculations, they decided that Milk Wine did have a place in the market. Therefore, they immediately agreed to Zhao Hai’s proposal.

At this time, the first batch of Milk Wine was being received in the Prairie. The Milk Wine were then sent to Iron Mountain Fort for processing. At the same time, the Hawk Race also brought forth news that for the Milk Wine, the Beastmen opted to not choose grain since they didn’t lack any of it. Instead, they wanted to be compensated with living necessities.

Zhao Hai understood their decision, and he had already expected this outcome. Although he can’t make living necessities, Randolph and the others can. Zhao Hai would sell the Milk Wine to Randolph and the others while having some of the payment exchanged for cheap living necessities. Then, he would trade those daily necessities to the Beastmen for cheap Milk Wine. Zhao Hai didn’t do anything else other than be the middleman. But even so, he had gained huge profits in doing so.

With the advent of Zhao Hai’s Milk Wine business, the human continent immediately went into a stir. A cheap but still tasty liquor was something inconceivable. Although the commoners thought that the Milk Wine tasted weird, they still found it quite fragrant. Not only did it have the taste of wine, it also had a hint of milk in it. Even if people cannot drink much of it in the beginning, they began to get used to it afterwards.

At first, Zhao Hai placed a hundred thousand jin of this Milk Wine into the market. But it didn’t even take a single day for all of these to be sold out, the market’s reception of the product was very good. This fact made the confidence of Randolph and the others increase.

And at the same time, when Zhao Hai used daily necessities to trade with the Milk WIne, the entire Prairie immediately seethed in excitement. These things might not be precious, but for the Beastmen, their pocket change can finally be traded for something of value.

Brewing Milk Wine was too simple for the Beastmen, almost each household would even do it. But since these Milk Wine cannot be stored for a long time, a lot of them were thrown out every year. But now, the Beastmen didn’t need to worry about this anymore. As long as they sell these Milk Wine to Zhao Hai, their problem of excess would be solved. Not only would they stop wasting things, they could also trade for something that was very useful.

After this success, Zhao Hai’s Milk Wine production line, logistics network, as well as sales had finally been established and was operated very well.

It wasn’t only Zhao Hai who was happy, Randolph and the others were elated as well. After their shops sold the Milk Wine, it became evident that the performance of their shops had become much better than their competitors. For them, this was absolutely good news.

Zhao Hai’s clan was very happy as well. The biggest earners in this Milk Wine business was them. Not only because they were the processors, but also because of having the advantage of price differences.

Although the Beastmen and the Human had signed the fair price agreement, the price disparity between them was still very large. Zhao Hai would buy the daily necessities in factory prices and exchange them for cheap Milk Wine with the Beastmen. But since these daily necessities were bought at a higher price in the Prairie, the amount of money that Zhao Hai can gain along the way was very big.

Except for the losses during the distillation process, Zhao Hai was gaining profits everywhere else. At the same time, Zhao Hai also didn’t need to worry about transportation. Although he had the Hawks working with him, the Hawks were just treating it as a sideline job.

After the initial success, Zhao Hai went to the Herculean Bull Tribe and met with Wales. After all, when this matter gets done, he would be leaving for a faraway place.

When Zhao Hai came back from the Prairie, he didn’t immediately go to the Rosen Empire. Instead he went to the Purcell Duchy to see how Ruyen was doing. And she was doing very good. The shop that she opened in the Duchy was now expanding outwards. At the same time, Ruyen didn’t look at Zhao Hai in discomfort anymore, and was now smiling in front of him. It seems like she had found her own calling.

When Zhao Hai saw Ruyen’s state, he also felt relief. Ruyen already  knew about the things discussed at Iron Mountain Fort. And since she now has an inseparable relationship with him, Zhao Hai slowly accepted Ruyen into his heart.

Zhao Hai wasn’t a person from the Ark Continent. People in the Ark Continent with statuses like Zhao Hai’s still held a woman’s chastity very seriously. But for an Earthling like Zhao Hai, he knew that the chances of finding a chaste woman at his age back on Earth was akin to the chance of winning the lottery.

Because of this, Zhao Hai really didn’t care about a woman’s past. Therefore, he wasn’t very concerned about Ruyen’s previous life. After all, past is past, everybody needs to move on.

Zhao Hai stayed with Ruyen for a day in the Purcell Duchy and learned about the business matters there. He also ate a meal with Ruyen, cultivating their relationship and then he told her that he was going to a far away place. After that, Zhao Hai returned to the Space.

Laura and the others didn’t mind Zhao Hai’s actions. Zhao Hai being with Ruyen was very different from Zhao Hai being with them. Laura and the others felt this difference, therefore they weren’t jealous.

After Zhao Hai returned to the Space, he took an evening rest before he returned to Iron Mountain Fort. The situation at the fort was very good. The slave villages were stable, and the slaves were enthusiastic about work. In order to make the slaves working at the wineries more comfortable, Zhao Hai set them up with an undead carriage for them to use to commute to work.

For the slaves living in the villages, their current lives in the Black Wasteland was like a paradise compared to the places that they used to live in the past.

Everything in Iron Mountain Fort was working properly. The new machines for the wineries have been  figured out. And the slaves weren’t stupid, it didn’t take a long time for them to get started.

The machines that Zhao Hai took out this time should be very simple to operate. It was because the machines were relatively advanced. The more advanced a machine was, the easier it would be to operate. Most of the machines in the wineries only needed someone to turn them on, everything else would be processed accordingly.

What small physical work that the slaves did wasn’t tiresome as well. It wasn’t a difficult task for them to take barrels from one place to another.

Zhao Hai also knew that the slaves were relatively uneducated. If he were to make them carry out complicated work, they would certainly be incompetent in it.

Now that the Milk Wine business has been stabilized, Zhao Hai had Ah Tai build a tent specifically for the storage of the Space Bags. That way, Cai’er could regularly take those Space Bags and send them to Iron Mountain Fort. And then have the processed Milk Wines transported to each supply points.

Naturally, the entirety of this process, the shipping and receiving, wasn’t solely done by Cai’er. Cai’er would release Blood Hawks outside Beast God City and had them go to Ah Tai and take the Space Bags. Then the Hawks would re-enter the Space when they were out of sight. Iron Mountain Fort doesnt need to be that troublesome, the bags can just be left inside s specific storehouse. But from Iron Mountain Fort towards the supply points, the Blood Hawks were needed again. All of these were deliberately done in order to mask the Space’s existence as much as possible.

This kind of method wasn’t something that people can easily predict. At most, people would find out that Zhao Hai had several Space Equipment in his hands. With Zhao Hai’s strength, there were only a few people who would dare snatch his Bags right now. After all, Zhao Hai had already turned his Clan into something that rivalled the influence of a millennium-old family. At his current state, nobody wanted to annoy him.

The reason Great Nobles were great was their businesses, thus it was an unspoken rule that nobody would use overly shady things in order to affect a family’s business. If one wanted to do shady things, then the affected Family would no doubt do their best to eliminate the person. This was the aggressiveness of Great Clans, and this was the aggressiveness of the Buda Clan as well.

After the the completing his tasks at Iron Mountain Fort, Zhao Hai returned to Golden Island. The island was now developing very well as more pirates traded here. However, don’t think that the existence of Golden Island made the seas more peaceful. Instead, the island actually made the surrounding waters quite chaotic.

It was publicly know that Golden Island was somewhere that people can dump their items in, whether they be fairly acquired or not. And for the pirates, this was good news. Because of this, pirates had become much more rampant in the seas near Golden Island.

However, these pirates didn’t dare cause any troubles inside the waters of the island. First, it was because the Buda Clan had already showed them what they could do. And second, it was because they didn’t want to destroy their relationship with the only place that they can do business safely.

Although some of these pirates had Great Clans at their back, but as they stay on sea for a long time, they would need money to sustain and entertain themselves. In the past, they didn’t have any opportunity to achieve this. But now that Golden Island appeared, it was natural that these pirates would want to behave in the island’s territory as much as possible.

Chapter 560: Meeting Pirates

Zhao Hai was currently sitting inside his ship, the Haven. The sea breeze and the sight of birds on the horizon made him feel very good. Although the environment of the Space was much better compared to outside, Zhao Hai still felt that the outside world had a type of realistic feeling in it.

Laura and the others were also standing by Zhao Hai’s side. They were currently leaving Golden Island and was heading towards the Buddha Empire. Although the Lyon Empire was much closer to Rosen Empire than the Buddha Empire, Zhao Hai sill wanted to go to the Buddha Empire. Going to the Dwarf Mountains was much more important than visiting the Lyon Empire.

Actually, because of the enormity of the Dwarf Mountains, it wasn’t entirely located in the Buddha Empire, a small part of it was also in the Lyon Empire. However, the Dwarves had a much better relationship with the Buddha Empire. And with the strength of the Dwarves managing to rival the Beastmen, the Lyon Empire wouldn’t dare to attack them even if their empire was the second strongest nation in the continent.

But although the Lyon Empire wasn’t quite close with the Dwarves. They still had something that they can count on, the Accra Mountain!

The Accra Mountain was famous in the continent. The main reason of the Mountain’s fame was because it was one of the five forbidden areas of the Continent.

The Five Forbidden Lands in the continent were namely the Carrion Swamp, Accra Mountain, North Polar Icefield, Inferno Island, and the Demonic Abyss! These five places had their own special characteristics. For example, the Carrion Swamp was well known for its poisonous mist as well as its Undead creatures. It was a place that nobody can leave once they enter.

The characteristic of the North Polar Icefield was its freezing cold atmosphere. When one goes then, their metal weapons would be frozen until it gets brittle like glass. Even the strong Beastmen only dared to explore it’s vicinity.

Inferno Island is the exact opposite of the North Polar Icefield. It was a world of fire. Fire spirits and beasts of Fire attributes prevailed there. Only a few would want to think about going to that island.

The Demonic Abyss was the most mysterious place in the continent. Legend says that it was the gateway to the Demon Realm. In the past, Zhao Hai didn’t believe it, but after seeing Cai’er strength, he was finally convinced that Cai’er came from the Demon Realm.

But Accra Mountain was very different from the other four, it was actually the most favorite place of adventurers. It was because the Mountain is a kingdom of Magic Beasts. There were a large number of Magic Beasts living inside the Mountain and people can catch some of them in order to make money. However, they cannot go deep. Accra Mountain was, after all, still one of the forbidden lands, once one goes very deep, they wouldn’t be able to come out. This rule didn’t exempt 9th rank experts.

Accra Mountain was the natural border between the Rosen Empire and the Lyon Empire. But the majority of the mountain was inside the Lyon Empire, only a small part belonged to the Rosen Empire.

Because of this, the Lyon Empire held the most elite Magic Beast cavalry. This cavalry was all made up of Magic Beasts obtained in Accra Mountain. Although they had been trained by the Humans, they still had the wildness in them, making their attacks very strong. This made the empire’s cavalry quite fearsome in the continent.

But Zhao Hai didn’t want to go to the Magic Beast Kingdom right now. Although there were a lot of Magic Beasts there, it was just too dangerous. And even if he wasn’t afraid of danger, business was much more important to him right now. He wants the Buda Clan to be stronger as soon as possible, so he didn’t want to upgrade the Space yet. But with that said, although one can easily catch Magic Beasts in Accra Mountain, the high-level ones were still quite rare. So in the end, Zhao Hao chose to go to Dwarf Mountain first.

And if he went to the Dwarf Mountain, there would be a chance for him to visit the Elven Forest. Although it feels like going to the Magic Beast kingdom was a much better idea, but don’t forget that Zhao Hai would meet two intelligent races instead of none. If he wanted to expand the Buda Clan’s business, this was definitely a good idea.

After Zhao Hai thought about these matters for quite some time, Laura suddenly said, “Brother Hai, do you expect our visit to the Dwarves to be smooth?”

Zhao Hai smiled and said, “It should be smooth. After all, the Dwarves and the Humans had more contact compared to the beastmen. Moreover, conflicts rarely happen between the two, so there shouldn’t be any big problems.”

Laura nodded and said, “The Dwarves are famous metalworkers in the continent. If we can get some of their products and trade it with the Beastmen, we would certainly be able to get some good things. The Beastmen crave iron the most.”

Zhao Hai nodded and said, “I also heard that the temper of the Dwarves are much worse than the Beastmen. And they also love to drink. I think our wine would be able to impress them.”

Laura nodded and said, “I hope so. I also think that we would have problems this time. At our current strength, there would be nobody who would pose a danger to us. Even the pirates wouldn’t offend us.”

Zhao Hai smiled and said, “Pirates wouldn’t even think about robbing us when they see a Buda Clan ship. And with the addition of the Markey Family, even the Aksu Empire wouldn’t be able to move against us. And as for the Radiant Church, they are now too busy protecting themselves, so they wouldn’t have any time to think about us. I think that besides the mysterious Engraved Ark, nobody can deal with us.”

Megan smiled and said, “That would be best. I just want to play well. To be honest, the Space is good, but after a long time, it becomes stale. It’s good to relax outside from time to time.”

Laura said, “But there isn’t a lot to look at in the sea. It wouldn’t be a long time before you get bored of it. The scenery just remains unchanged.”

Zhao Hai smiled, “But you can see other people here, other ships. In the Space, there are no other people besides us. And also maybe some flocks of animals.”

After he said that, the sounds of Magic Cannons being fired was suddenly heard. Zhao Hai and the others gawked, they knew that there was fight nearby. Zhao Hai immediately opened the monitor to see what was going on. What he saw was a pirate ship and another ship, naturally a robbery was going on. But it was not Zhao Hai’s ship that was being robbed, but a five-masted ship instead.

Zhao Hai looked at the ship’s flag and wasn’t able to recognize it. So he turned his head to Laura and said, “Do you know who that flag belongs to?”

Laura stared at it for a moment before she nodded and said, “I do, it belongs to the Buddha Empire’s Hurricane Family. That Family’s status in the Buddha Empire is very high. In the past, they were also being suppressed by the Radiant Church because they weren’t firm believers in the religion. The family had a peculiar characteristic, it doesn’t matter if they were man or woman, as long as one had any blood relation to the family, they would have a huge probability to have the affinity to the Wind Element. No matter it be Battle Qi or Magic, their attributes would be Wind. They are very famous in the continent because of this affinity. And because of this characteristic, they only worship the WInd God. In the Buddha Empire, they are also classified to be a millennium-old Family, quite similar to the status of Megan’s family. But why did the pirates dare attack them?”

Zhao Hai looked at the ships and smiled faintly, “I have to say, these pirates are indeed rich. Who would’ve thought that five-masted ships would be part of a pirate fleet. This is the really the first time that I’ve seen such a thing. If all the Pirates had these kinds of ships, then I’m afraid that our Buda Clan’s restriction would be put to trash.”

Laura and the others also noticed what Zhao Hai was referring to. The ships of the pirates that were attacking the Hurricane Family turned out to be Advanced ships of the continent. Not to mention pirates, but even Great Nobles cannot just casually have those kinds of ships.

Lizzy’s eyes turned sharp, “Is someone trying to kill them? Big Sister, who are the enemies of the Hurricane Family?”

The Big Sister that Lizzy meant was Laura. Although Meg was the one who spent the longest time with Zhao Hai, it was Laura who had helped him the most. And adding on to the fact that Laura was the oldest one of them, it was acceptable for the women to call her Big Sister.

Laura shook her head and said, “Although the Hurricane Family has formidable strength, their temper is very good, and they don’t like to offend people. Most importantly, they really don’t strive for power and money. In addition to them being very loyal to their faith, the family members are very good-hearted people. So how could these possibly offend someone? Besides the Radiant Church, the Hurricane Family is friends with everyone. When the Radiant Church suppressed them, a lot of people went out of their way just to provide help. I can dare to say that the most friendly people in the continent would be their family.”

While Zhao Hai was listening to Laura, he had felt confused, “Laura, how did you get this information? Why was it so detailed?”

Laura smiled and said, “Brother Hai, you don’t know? Our Markey Family has collected information regarding the various families in the continent. The history and emblems of the families were written in great detail. At the same time, we also have the Robert Family’s archives that had more or less the same content.”

Zhao Hai smiled bitterly and said, “I really didn’t know which family was who, their emblems and so on. Remembering these things gives me headache. It’s nice that you remembered them. Right, do we have a good relationship with the Hurricane Family?”

Laura shook her head and said, “Most likely not. The Hurricane Family rarely does business. They basically get what they need from their territory. Because of this, business with them was very rare, so we don’t have much contact with them.”

Zhao Hai smiled faintly and said, “Then this is the right time, let’s go draw them in to be our friends. Right, Laura, can you recognize where the ships came from?” Naturally Zhao Hai wasn’t referring to the Hurricane Family’s ships, but instead to the Pirate ships.

Although the ships in the continent looked very much the same, a fairly discerning person would be able to see some slight differences on these ships. Each country had their own flair when it came to their shipbuilding that experienced people could distinguish.

Laura carefully looked at the several Pirate ships, and after some time she opened her mouth and said, “From the shape of the ship, it’s probably from the Buddha Empire. But its color very much belongs to the Ocean Waves Dynasty. I really cannot be sure.”

Zhao Hai’s eyes flashed, “Ocean Waves Dynasty? Them again?”

Chapter 561: Kristen?

Laura asked, “Brother Hai? When did the Ocean Waves Dynasty offend us? How come I can’t remember?”

Zhao Hai coldly snorted and said, “Did you forget? When we chased Grand Duke Lionheart, wasn’t the ship that was supposed to save him came from the Ocean Waves Dynasty? The ship may have been snatched by the Church or maybe borrowed. But still, the matter wasn’t that simple.”

When Lizzy heard Zhao Hai, her face sank down as she said, “So it’s the Radiant Church. Is there a collusion between the Church and Ocean Waves Dynasty?”

Zhao Hai sneered and said, “That is not impossible. The Radiant Church had just suffered a huge loss and had to let go of their grasp of the Aksu Empire. And naturally, they wouldn’t show all of the cards that they had. I think that the Ocean Waves Empire have already been colluding with them from the start. If the Radiant Church’s plan in the Aksu Empire succeeded, then the church would be controlling the northernmost and southernmost nations in the Human domain. If they gain enough strength, they would launch a war against all of the nations in the middle, attacking them from two fronts. With that method, it would be possible for them to unity the entire Human territory.”

Lizzy and the others couldn’t help but stare in confusion, Laura looked at Zhao Hai and said, “How could they have such a huge courage? And how could that be possible? Not to say the Rosen Empire, but the Buddha Empire and the Lyon Empire aren’t very easy to deal with either.”

Upon hearing this, Zhao Hai couldn’t help but sneer, “Not easy to deal with? Remember, where was the first place that I had an initial clash with Lionheart? It was in the boundary between the Rosen Empire and Aksu Empire. The garrison guarding the fort there are all people of Grand Duke Lionheart. If all of their plans went by smoothly, when the Aksu Empire launches its attack, those defenders would not only refrain from fighting, they might even surrender at the very first sight of the enemy. This would make the Rosen Empire’s strongest barrier vanish. I think that the Radiant Church also had the same arrangement in Lyon Empire and the Buddha Empire. The ambition of those people are too big.”

Laura and the others thought about it and couldn’t help but get what Zhao Hai was saying. If what Zhao Hai said was true, then the ambition of the Radiant Church was truly too great.

Laura looked at Zhao Hai, puzzled, and then asked, “Brother Hai, how did you think of these?”

Zhao Hai chuckled and said, “I just thought about this since I’ve always felt that the Radiant Church aren’t careless people. But their recent approach in Aksu Empire was simply too simple and crude. But now that I had seen these ships, everything connected in my mind.”

Laura then turned his gaze towards the monitor and said, “Then why are they dealing with the Hurricane Family? Isn’t this act too unreasonable?”

Zhao Hai laughed out loud, “Why? The Radiant Church is now being suppressed by everyone. But if they already have some relationship with the Ocean Waves Dynasty, then they can utilize that nation’s strength. Moreover, they are now working in the dark, making it much more difficult to deal with them. And it seems like they had changed their approach. Instead of enticing Nobles into their religion, they were now going after the Nobles that were in opposition to their belief, Nobles who they have enmity with. Now think about this, compared to the Buda Clan and the Calci Family, isn’t the Hurricane Family much easier to eliminate?”

Laura and the others nodded to Zhao Hai’s words. They think that what Zhao Hai said was right. Although the Hurricane Family was also a millennium-old clan, their reputation wasn’t very widespread because of the temperament. If one based it on influence, they can’t compare to the Buda Clan and the Calci Family.

Moreover, the Calci Family and the Buda Clan’s fighting with the Radiant Church was already quite known to the Continent. If the Radiant Church deals with either the Buda Clan or the Calci Family at this time, then the people of the continent would surely know that it was the church who had done it.

But if they deal with the Hurricane Family, nobody would be certain that it was them. The fight between the Radiant Church and the Hurricane Family was very muted to the other people in the continent. Therefore, if the Radiant Church were to move against the Hurricane Family, it wouldn’t bring too much attention to the continent. And since the Church would make sure that nobody survives, nobody would know that it was done by them. These must be the thoughts of the people in the Church.

Naturally, all of these were just Zhao Hai’s guesses, they still needed to be confirmed. Therefore, Zhao Hai had the Haven approach the battlefield as soon as possible. They must save the people of the Hurricane Family. At the same time, they would deal with the attackers from the Ocean Waves Dynasty and turn them into undead, haring the truth from their very mouths.

The Haven has now been very well modified, it’s speed has become quicker while its defensive strength had increased. After all, this was Zhao Hai’s flagship, and he was the Buda Clan’s patriarch, his status was much more different from before. So if he uses any ordinary battleship, he would become a laughing stock among the people.

In a few short minutes, Zhao Hai was finally close to the battle. There were a total of seven ships present. Six five-master battleships and one ironclad freighter. For six battleships to attack a single freighter, it seems like they aren’t giving the freighter any chance to survive.

The six battleships were surrounding the freighter and was blasting if continuously with Magic Cannons. There seems to be Mages on the ships, and from time to time, they would send some spells towards the other ship. The colorful magical attacks made the scene look like a huge fireworks event, very beautiful. However, this beauty represented death! The seven ships weren’t close to each other. It seems like the six assailants weren’t willing confront the freighter in close combat. They wanted to use magic to completely destroy the ship. This tactic was also the best way to eliminate a target at sea.

Zhao Hai didn’t think about it too much as he made the Haven go straight to the battleships. When the six battlefields became aware of Zhao Hai’s presence, two of them detached from the group and approached him.

The three ships were quickly getting close with each other. And when they were near, a voice was suddenly heard, “The ship over there, listen. We are the Hurricane Family’s pirate group. If you don’t go the other way, then we would be forced to be impolite.”

Upon hearing this statement, Zhao Hai couldn’t help but laugh and said, “Funny, this is too funny. It’s the first time I’ve heard such a joke. For a Hurricane Family pirate group to attack a Hurricane family freighter, Hahahaha, this must be the most hilarious thing that has happened in the continent. Listen, know your limitations and get the hell out of this place. Otherwise, I would be the one who will be impolite.”

The other party wasn’t expecting Zhao Hai to be aware of the Hurricane Family’s identity. They were now in a disadvantage, keeping up this facade had now become much more difficult.

While the two people exchanged words, their ships were still getting closer with each other. And as Zhao Hai’s ship was about to be attacked by the other ships’ cannons, Zhao Hai immediately released a lot of undead on board those ships.

The people on the battleships didn’t expect Zhao Hai to be able to release undead at such a distance, and they were completely caught unprepared. Additionally, Zhao Hai’s undead were very strong. Because of this, what happened in the battleships after can only be described as a massacre. Before the people on the two ships were able to react, they were already slain by the undead.

The people on the other four battleships weren’t aware of this. In their minds, although the three ships were not far from each other, close combat would still be impossible. At this distance, the only suitable way for engagement would be long distance attacks.

After eliminating the people from the two ships, Zhao Hai immediately turned them into undead. After that, the immediately had the two ships open fire towards the Haven.

Naturally, this attack was under the control of Zhao Hai. He wanted to have the others think that they were still fighting. This would deceive the other four battleships into thinking that the two ships were still on their side, naively allowing Zhao Hai’s new feet to enter their encirclement

As the three ships slowly approached the battlefield, the other four battleships didn’t feel anything wrong. And after Zhao Hai entered their circle, he immediately released massive amounts of undead onboard the other four battleships.

The fate of the four ships couldn’t compare to the first two ships. They didn’t even expect Zhao Hai’s attacks. A lot of them wasn’t even aware that they were already dead.

Immediately, the four ships stopped firing. This made the people on the Hurricane Family freighter feel somewhat strange. And while they were confused, they suddenly heard a voice from the ship that just arrived, “Friends from the Hurricane Family, hello. No need to fear, I’ve already taken care of the enemy. May I come on board?”

The people of the Hurricane Family stared, although they didn’t know the other party, they were still confident about their combat effectiveness. Therefore, their leader said, “i don’t know who friend is, but we shall welcome you to our ship.”

Zhao Hai smiled faintly and then had the Haven slowly approach. Then he had a springboard extended to reach the Hurricane Family’s ship. After that, Zhao Hai led Laura and the others to board the ship.

The Hurricane Family’s ship was very damaged. There were also a lot of injured crew onboard, waiting to be treated. Zhao Hai smiled and then waved his hand as a bunch of Light Magic flew out and landed on the wounded, effectively curing their wounds at an observable rate.

At this time, the party that was preparing to welcome him stopped. Their face turned ugly as they looked at Zhao Hai and said, “I Mister from the Radiant Church?”

Zhao Hai turned his head to the one who spoke, this person was quite beautiful, she had brown hair and light green eyes, a fairly sharp face and snow white teeth. Although she might not be very beautiful, one could feel a very attracting aura while looking at her.

But when Zhao Hai looked closely at this person, he couldn’t help but be surprised. He was very familiar with this face, this face belonged to none other than Kristen Stewart, an actress quite known for her role in a movie called “Twilight”.[1]

One must say, that among the actresses, Kristen wasn’t the most beautiful one. She just has a very attractive aura in her. Quiet? Smart? Elegant? These words might not fit someone like her.

Because Zhao Hai quite liked the movie, he was able to recognize her face at a single glance. This girl looked very much like Kirsten.

Zhao Hai couldn’t help but deeply sigh, his luck was truly fantastic. First was Taylor, then Megan, then Keeley, and now there was Kristen. The heavens were really looking after him. Being able to meet these people back on earth wasn’t an easy thing.

However, Zhao Hai had detected some vigilance in the woman’s expression, so he immediately answered, “Sister might have misunderstood, but I’m not a person from the Radiant Church. Hasn’t sister seen my ship’s flag?”

The she heard Zhao Hai, she couldn’t help but turn her head towards the Haven’s main mast and seeing the Wild Dragon Flag fluttering freely above the blood soaked sea.

When she noticed the flag, she couldn’t help but gawk. Her brain seemed to stop for a short moment. She seem to have seen this flag before, but she just couldn’t remember when, or even where.

At this time, she overheard a person’s voice exclaiming, “Heavens, is that the Buda Clan’s WIld Dragon Flag? Are you from the Buda Clan?”

Upon hearing the person, the girl couldn’t help but look at Zhao Hai in confusion as she asked, “You’re from the Buda Clan? But how can you use Light Magic?”

Zhao Hai smiled faintly and said, “Who says my Buda Clan can’t use Light Magic? Let me introduce myself, my name is Zhao Hai Buda, the current Patriarch of the Buda Clan.”

The girl stared at Zhao Hai, seemingly forgetting her courtesy. This wasn’t surprising since Zhao Hai was a well-know Dark Mage in the continent. Seeing a Dark Mage using Light Magic was even more surprising than seeing a tree planting itself.

Zhao Hai didn’t comment of the girl’s expression, instead, he beckoned towards Laura and the others and said, “These are my wives, Laura, Meg, Megan, Lizzy, and Ni’er.”

Seeing Laura and the others giving her a salute, the girl finally responded, with her face red in embarrassment she performed her own salute and said, “Kristen Hurricane has seen Patriarch Zhao Hai as well as the madames.”

After both sides exchanged greetings, Kristen then turned his head to Zhao Hai and said, “Patriarch Zhao Hai, I must express my greatest gratitude to you. If not for you, then we might have fallen to the other party’s attack. These pirates are really too hateful.”

Zhao Hai smiled faintly and said, “Sister Kristen doesn’t need to mind it too much. I just gave a small helping hand. Now that those battleships are under my control, Sister doesn’t need to worry about it anymore.”

Although Kristen didn’t know how Zhao Hai was able to control those battleships, she didn’t dare to ask him how. She knew that if Zhao Hai wanted it to be known, then he would tell her eventually.

Kristen then gave Zhao Hai a salute and said, “No matter what, I’d like to thank Mister. Mister, please come sit with me in the cabin.” She said that as she gestured her arm as an invitation.

Zhao Hai didn’t become polite, he accepted the invitation and led Laura and the others to walk with Kristen towards the cabin.

The ship’s cabin wasn’t very big, only about the size of a normal living room. After the group had sat, the room immediately became quite crowded.

* * *

Here we goooo hahaha

Chapter 562: Confirmation

A servant came in and served them something to drink. Because the battle didn’t take too long, and since the other party were using long-ranged weapons, the damage on the Hurricane Family’s freighter wasn’t very serious.

The group sat down as Kristen dictated the events before the attack. Although the Hurricane Family was constantly low-key and rarely did business, it was inevitable that they would have to trade some goods with the others. However, their trades weren’t on the scale as large as that of the other Great Clans.

For Great Clans to maintain their strength, they needed to have some form of sustaining that strength. Even if the Hurricane Family didn’t like to do business, it was unavoidable if they wanted to have their territory run normally. But because their family weren’t very good in it, they would just trade the minimum amount to maintain the normal operation of their territory.

This time, Kristen’s mission was to trade in Rosen Empire and then go back home. In Rosen Empire, they didn’t trade in Golden Island, but preferred Rising Water City instead. Their previous transactions were always done in Rising Water City. Even if Golden Island was on the Rise, the Hurricane Family didn’t seem to get attracted to it. They still continued their trade with Rising Water City all the same.

But when they were heading back, six five-masted battleships bearing pirate flags suddenly surrounded them. Although they had the means to fight back, their firepower just cannot compare to the other party. And adding on to the fact the the enemies had battleships while they only had a freighter, if Zhao Hai didn’t come, then they would surely be finished.

After Kristen finished talking, Zhao Hai smiled faintly and said, “We wanted to go visit the Buddha Empire, but we didn’t expect to encounter such a thing. But does sister Kristen feel strange? How could pirates get their hands on six five-masted battleships?”

Kristen’s personality was the same as that of the Hurricane Family, as long as you don’t offend her, then she would treat you kindly. But this didn’t mean that the Hurricane Family were fools, on the contrary, they were quite smart people. They just placed this intellect in improving their magic and other things, but not for ambition. This was the general impression of the Continent towards the Hurricane Family.

When Kristen heard what Zhao Hai said, her eyes turned sharp for a moment before she looked at Zhao Hai and said, “What does mister want to say? Please speak.”

Zhao Hai smiled faintly and said, “I suspect that the assailants weren’t pirates. Sister Kristen should know, most pirate groups in the seas have Great Clans supporting them. But with the Hurricane Family’s background, I believe that no pirate would want to attack you, moreover, pirates with great strength, am I right?”

Kristen nodded and said ,”That’s right. It’s just like mister said, our Hurricane Family has a lot of friends in the continent, and very few enemies.”

Zhao Hai smiled faintly and said ,”What sister said is true. But even if you say there are few, that means that the Hurricane Family still had enemies. And did sister forget that you have one big enemy?’

Kristen stared, then she looked at Zhao Hai and said, “Is mister thinking about the Radiant Church?”

Zhao Hai smiled and said, “That’s very possible. How about this, I’ll go call some of those undead on the battleships and ask them. What do you think?”

Kristen seemed to not understand, then she looked at Zhao Hai and said, “You mean, you have turned everyone on those ships into undead? Patriarch Zhao Hai, isn’t that bad?”

Zhao Hai smiled faintly and said, “Why would it be bad? I’ve turned hundreds of thousands of people in the Aksu Empire into undead. Why would I care about these few people?” He then stood up and walked outside.

Kristen looked at Zhao Hai’s back with eyes that showed loathing. The Hurricane Family were famously good-hearted people, therefore, they aren’t used to seeing Zhao Hai’s vicious and merciless actions.

However, she still followed Zhao Hai out of the cabin. This matter can affect the Hurricane Family’s future, she couldn’t just ignore it.

Zhao Hai didn’t care about it too much, he didn’t want to get in Kristen’s good graces anyway. The reason why he helped the Hurricane Family was because he wants the Radiant Church to have a harder time.

Outside the ship, Zhao Hai recited a few incantations before he waved his staff. Black gas started to appear from the staff and surrounded one battleship. When the gas disappeared, Kristen discovered that there were people standing on top of the ship’s deck.

Zhao Hai repeated the pattern and turned the people on the other battleships into Undead. Then he had the battleships approach the Hurricane Family’s freighter. Then some of the undead boarded the Hurricane Family’s ship.

Kristen had recognized some of these people from the time of the battle. Therefore, she didn’t suspect that Zhao Hai sent his undead to pretend.

After the undead boarded the ship, Zhao Hai immediately had them report who they were. The assailants weren’t pirates, but instead the navy of the Ocean Waves Dynasty. Ocean Waves Dynasty was the country most developed in the research of the Water element. Because of this, they had the most powerful Navy in continent.

However, even if these people were from the navy, they had nothing to do with the Radiant Church. They only thing that they knew was that they were ordered to attack, nothing more.

But Zhao Hai wasn’t worried, he asked these undead about which one of them was the commander of the six battleships. Zhao Hai was already used to the Radiant Church’s style, it was impossible for the church to not send someone over to monitor the operation.

It didn’t take too long before these people named someone. So Zhao Hai immediately called the person over and interrogated him. Sure enough, he identified himself to be part of the Radiant Church. Moreover, his level wasn’t low, he was a Priest. This time, he was ordered by the Radiant Church to deal with the Hurricane Family, however, he didn’t know of anything else.

But this information was enough. At the very least, Zhao Hai wanted to let Kristen know that the ones who wanted to deal with the Hurricane Family were indeed the Radiant Church.

Zhao Hai had also confirmed his suspicions. The Radiant Church truly had control over the Ocean Waves Dynasty. Moreover, they had changed their methods into moving in secret.

After the interrogation, Zhao Hai made the undead return to the ships and had them leave. Then he returned to the cabin along with Kristen.

Kristen was frowning, she felt that this matter has gotten quite thorny. Although the Radiant Church has been suppressed, their foundation was still intact. Even if their presence has been reduced, there were still people who worshipped their faith. The monarch of the other countries didn’t really see them as a threat. Aside from the Rosen and Aksu Empires, nobody really went full on in eliminating the church. Some Churches were even still present, with Priests preaching in them albeit the much lesser numbers.

Therefore, even if the Radiant Church was now behaving, they were still very strong. Kristen wasn’t a fool, she had deduced from the testimonies of the undead that the Ocean Waves Dynasty and the Radiant Church certainly didn’t have a simple relationship. It seems to be like what Zhao Hai thought, the Radiant Church had become much more formidable now that they were in the shadows.

Zhao Hai looked at Kristen and smiled faintly, “Sister Kristen, I just want to take this matter to heart. And since the matter is finished, then we would be taking our leave. We still have an urgent matter to take care of in the Buddha Empire.”

Kristen gawked and immediately responded. She was lowering her head in deep thought that she wasn’t able to talk to Zhao Hai, which was something very disrespectful. When she thought about this, Kristen’s face couldn’t help but turn red. She hastily stood up and gave a bow to Zhao Hai and said, “I’ve been unfair to mister. I was suddenly too absorbed in my own thoughts, so I neglected you. I ask for mister’s forgiveness. But why would mister leave immediately? Mister had done a great deal of help to us, please stay behind and let us express our gratitude.”

Zhao Hai smiled faintly and said, “Sister is too polite. There’s no need to do that, to me, this is but a small effort. Moreover, I also obtained six battleships, this can be said to be my reward. I really do have something to do in Buddha Empire, so sister shouldn’t feel bad.”

Kristen quickly replied, “What does mister need in the Buddha Empire? My Hurricane Family has some sort of influence there, maybe we can help mister.”

Zhao Hai smiled faintly and said, “i’m travelling to Buddha Empire because I want to go to the Dwarf Mountain and see if I can do business with the Dwarven Race.”

Kristen couldn’t help but frown when she heard Zhao hai. The Dwarf Mountain held a special status in the Buddha Empire. The Empire needed heavy armors and weapons from the Dwarves. However, they also didn’t want the Dwarves to be too strong. So just like the Beastmen, the Humans controlled the amount of trades that would be sent to the Mountain. However, the Dwarves weren’t fools, as long as they notice that they had been deceived, they would surely declare war against the Buddha Empire.

So because of this, the Buddha Empire merchants didn’t dare to trick the Dwarves. However, the Empire still thought of a method. They wouldn’t let the merchants of other countries to contact the Dwarves, ensuring that they would have full monopoly of the Dwarven market.

Since the Empire was restricting trade, only a few merchants were able to make trade with the Dwarves for long term. Even Great Nobles didn’t have the opportunity to dictate themselves. Therefore, it was natural for Kristen’s expression to turn ugly upon hearing Zhao Hai’s words.

When Zhao Hai saw Kristen’s expression, he asked, “Sister Kristen? Is there something wrong?”

Kristen didn’t hide the truth from Zhao Hai. In fact, this matter was already known by the top level powers in the continent, so there was no reason to keep it a secret.

After listening to Kristen, Zhao Hai couldn’t help but smile faintly and said, “It doesn’t matter. If I can’t do it, then I don’t really care.”

Chapter 563: Dwarven Ironware

Kristen frowned, and finally made up her mind, “Mister shouldn’t rush to leave. I ask you to go with me to our Hurricane Family. Maybe we can help you with your trade with the Dwarves.”

Zhao Hai looked at Kristen and smiled, “Alright, then I’ll have to bother sister. Right, my ship is very spacious, does sister want to get on board?”

Kristen shook her head and said, “I’ll have to decline mister’s invitation. We just passed through a big fight. I still have a lot of matter to take care of.” Zhao Hai nodded, and then returned with Laura and the others to their own ship.

After arriving at his ship, Zhao Hai ordered the six battleships to head towards Golden Island. At the same time, he also informed Kun about their arrival so that he can take them in.

After completing these, Zhao Hai and the others entered the Space. When they had settled down, Zhao Hai looked at Laura and said, “It seems like going through the trouble of lending a hand was worth it. If the Hurricane Family would really help us in our matter with the Dwarves, then our travel would be much easier.”

Laura nodded and said, “That’s true, Buddha Empire is very strict regarding Dwarf Mountain. If someone of our status gets in touch with the dwarves, then it would definitely get their attention. Those Buddha Empire fellows seem to think that the Dwarves are their personal blacksmiths. If we directly go to the Dwarves, we might get into huge trouble.”

Zhao Hai frowned, “Do the Great Nobles of the continent really don’t have anything to say about this? How can they just let the Buddha Empire monopolize the Dwarf Race’s business?”

Laura smiled and said, “How could they not have an opinion? It’s just that even if the Dwarf business is very profitable, those families don’t want to offend the Buddha Empire. The Buddha Empire also has methods to deal with those who wanted to come in contact with the Dwarves. In fact, it is very simple, they would just suppress that family’s business in the Buddha Empire, causing that family huge losses.”

Zhao Hai stared, he didn’t think that the Buddha Empire would do this. However, he has to recognize that with how much importance the Buddha Empire has placed on the Dwarf goods, there would be no way for the other Nobles to get their hands on it. Exchanging their existing business in the Buddha Empire for a one-time transaction with the Dwarves is not worth it.

Lizzy smiled and said, “Not only that, the Buddha Empire might have also been talking to the Dwarves about how malicious the merchants of the other nations were. At this point, the Dwarves would have already been convinced that aside from the Buddha Empire, the others were simply swindlers. Therefore, making it much more difficult for the other empires to trade with them.”

Zhao Hai smiled and said, “This will make the travel to Buddha Empire much more interesting. It seems like Dwarven Ironware is really fantastic, otherwise the Empire wouldn’t be this critical about controlling it.”

Laura nodded and said, “It really is. With the same type of weapon and the same iron, Human blacksmiths just couldn’t compare to the Dwarves. Human swords might break after one war while the Dwarven swords can last five, not to mention how much sharper the Dwarven swords were. By relying on Dwarf made goods, the Buddha Empire has managed to reach its current status.”

Megan nodded as well, “I used to see a Dwarven made steel dagger in my father’s study in the past. The dagger wasn’t very gorgeous, nor was it eye catching, but it was very sharp, better than those made by a senior Human blacksmith. If you take a Human-made dagger and sliced it with a Dwarven-made one, the Human dagger would surely break into two.”

Zhao Hai nodded, “So that’s how good Dwarven daggers are. But I want to know how it would compare to something that the Processing Machine makes.”

Laura shook her head and said, “I’m afraid Dwarven daggers are stronger. They are handcrafted, repeatedly tempered, so they should be special.”

Zhao Hai agreed, then he looked at Laura and said, “I’ll go write a letter to Grandpa Kun later. Telling him all about what just happened. I think it would be best for father-in-law and the others to know about this, so that they can make proper preparations.”

Meggan nodded, “Right, but wouldn’t the Church be evading the Rosen Empire by now? They would be courting death if they do. The hatred for the Church has now reached its peak. Even the commoners were in opposition to them. It would be very difficult for the church to return to the Empire.”

Zhao Hai smiled and said, “No matter what, being prepared is always good. At the same time, I also want to see how the Hurricane Family reacts to this incident. If the Hurricane Family doesn’t spread this out, then we would be the ones doing it. We’ll drag the Ocean Waves Dynasty along as well. Let those people from the Radiant Church withdraw even more.”

Laura nodded and said, “That’s also good. The Radiant Church had always been up to no good, it’s too annoying. Even if they are strong, we should just rid of them.”

Zhao Hai shook his head and said, “That won’t be a good idea. If we remove the Church, the targets of the continent would be switched to us. That would make things much more troublesome. The strength that we have been showing is just the same as Great Nobles, which is still acceptable for them. But if we show strength beyond their expectations, then I’m afraid they would unite and deal with us.”

Lizzy sighed, “That’s true. I don’t understand how the people of the continent think, but for me, our current situation is quite good. At least nobody comes to bully us.”

Zhao Hai smiled faintly and said, “What I’d like is to upgrade the Space even sooner so that we won’t be afraid of anyone. Moreover, we can also use a lot of backgrounds, when we get bored, we can just explore a new background. That would be very good.”

One could clearly see the look of anticipation on the faces of Lizzy and the others. Zhao Hai had shown them the different backgrounds  in the Space’s shop, and those backgrounds were indeed very beautiful.

The group continued to chat in the Space for while before they left  Cai’er to pay attention to the situation outside. If Kristen were to go see them, Cai’er would immediately send word. But for now, they secretly returned to Iron Mountain Fort.

When Zhao Hai went to the Prairie before, he was actually also planning to get his 100 thousand slaves. However, he didn’t expect how much damage the Herculean Bulls had suffered. Now that they needed to recover their strength, having those slaves were indispensable. Therefore, Zhao Hai chose to just leave them there for the time being. After all, he still had his 100 thousand slaves, so it wasn’t really a big deal. Moreover, he also decided to get another 100 thousand slaves from Lin, Zhao Hai believed that those would be delivered soon.

The situation in Iron Mountain Fort was very normal. Although it was impossible for the slaves to have a commoner culture, but one day they will, so they were very obedient. If these 100 thousand slaves were to disobey, Zhao Hai’s management would have so much problems. But fortunately, the slaves behaved themselves.

Karen was still buzzing around the machines everyday, to the point where Laura was now complaining about it to Zhao Hai.

This time, Zhao Hai went to see how the slaves were doing, and they were doing very good. Majority of the allocated lands were already planted. But Zhao Hai told them that this will be the only year where he would provide seeds to plant. The next year, they would be free to plant whatever they want. Zhao Hai was also planning on buying some seeds in the Space and selling them over to the slaves, using grain as trade.

They stayed for one day in Iron Mountain Fort. The next morning, Kristen sent someone to notify Zhao Hai. After some simple repairs, their ship was now ready to go.

Their travel then on was very smooth. They didn’t run into any enemies along the way. The merchants that they passed all shouted in greetings.

One has to recognize how well received the people from the Hurricane Family were. There were several instances where ships from other Families discovered how battered the Hurricane Family ship was and thought that it was attacked. So they stopped by and visited Kristen, they wanted to know who attacked the Hurricane Family.

At the same time, these people were also very enthusiastic regarding Zhao Hai. Zhao Hai wasn’t expecting them to be this accommodating, but after thinking about it for a while, he finally understood. All these people were kind to him because of Golden Island.

Golden Island was now the continent’s most famous trade harbor. People who go there because of the safety of their transactions, the low taxes, as well as the cheap goods in comparison to other places.

Most importantly, there were a lot of Merchants who were chased by pirates and went to Golden Island to hide, but those pirates didn’t dare to move against them. This made the Merchants prefer to involve themselves with the Buda Clan.

Zhao Hai naturally returned the enthusiasm of these people. He exchanged gifts with them and chatted with them for a bit, giving Zhao Hai some special understanding about these nobles from other countries.

Zhao Hai was now in the Lyon Empire’s seas. Merchants coming and going here were mostly from the Ocean Waves Dynasty and Buddha Empire, Aksu Empire ships were rarely spotted, the same was true for Rosen Empire ships.

This was normal. Now that the Aksu Empire was still under recovery, there were few Merchants who travelled from there. On the other hand, the relationship between the Rosen Empire and the Lyon Empire wasn’t very good. Therefore, it was normal for Rosen Empire ships to avoid this region of the sea.

But Zhao Hai still didn’t meet any obstructions in the Lyon Empire. Whether it be the Hurricane Family or the Buda Clan, both of them were powerful families in the continent. Even if the relationship between the Rosen Empire and the Lyon Empire wasn’t good, the Lyon Empire’s relationship with Zhao Hai was still normal. At the same time, nobody wanted to needlessly offend both the Buda Clan and the Hurricane Family.

After about a month of navigation, Zhao Hai and the others finally entered the Buddha Empire’s seas. But they were still very far from the Hurricane Family’s territory, they would still need to sail for five days before they arrive.

Chapter 564: Strange Hurricane Family

Inside the Buddha Empire’s sea region, the travel with the Hurricane Family people came smoothly as well. In the Buddha Empire, there was almost no reason to offend the Hurricane Family.

The people of the Hurricane Family were not interested in influence. The people from the Buddha Empire were very friendly with them because they weren’t striving for power nor profit. The Royal Family also liked to intermarry to their family, which made the other nobles treat them very well. One could say that the Hurricane Family was the most accepted people in the entire Buddha Empire.

However, Kristen wasn’t in the mood to think about all of this right now. The group was currently entering the Buddha Empire’s largest river, Iron Warhorse River.

According to legend, the founding Emperor of the Buddha Empire has managed to obtain the approval of a unique Magic Beast, an Iron Warhorse, in this river. With the horse as his mount, he managed to make a lot of achievements and finally established the Buddha Empire. After taking his seat as Emperor, he immediately changed the name of the River into Iron Warhorse River.

The territory of the Hurricane Family was along a branch of this river, inside a mountainous area. The mountain didn’t have any ores, and its land wasn’t fertile. It can be said that this territory was the worst in the Buddha Empire.

However, even after holding this territory for millennia, the Hurricane Family didn’t even attempt to expand it one step, nor did they seek help from others. The Family only relied on their family members to excavate the mountainous area and make terraced fields of which Bamboo Rice, oil trees, and green vegetables were planted. They were living in something like a mundane paradise.

In the eyes of other Nobles, this might be an example of not making progress. However, the Hurricane Family seems to like living like this. They were selling a lot of Bamboo Rice, oil products as well as vegetables, but not Magic Vegetables. This made their yearly profits much lesser than the other nobles, but this could still satisfy the family.

But as many years passed by, the Hurricane Family were still a Great Clan. Other clans rose to the top, others fell into depravity, but the Hurricane Family still stayed the same. They just lived their day-to-day lives peacefully, as they did from the very beginning. This made people quite speechless when discussing them.

However, if you think that the Hurricane family was weak, then you couldn’t be any more wrong. Because of their innate Wind attribute, the Family had a lot of experts within their members.

The other families might have 7th or 8th rank experts as their Foreign elders, eliciting respect and resources in order to make their strength grow. But it was different with the Hurricane Family. One might see a farmer on the fields, tending to his crops, only to know that the person was an 8th rank expert. You might even see someone peacefully chopping wood, but actually had the strength of 7th rank. There were no other family in the Buddha Empire that was just like the Hurricane Family.

The Hurricane Family’s core values is based on being good to others. They had helped a lot of families in the Buddha Empire before, making the entire Buddha Empire nobility grateful to them. One could say that in the Buddha Empire, the Hurricane Family was the most detached family in terms of political agenda.

When the Radiant Church was at its strongest, they wanted to suppress the Hurricane Family because of its non-compliance. But when they came to doing it, they found out that they weren’t able to do anything. The Hurricane Family didn’t have any businesses aside from their rice, oil, and vegetables. And these things were daily supplies, so they really cannot be suppressed. And when the Radiant Church wanted to use other avenues to deal with them, the Nobles of the Buddha Empire disagreed. In the end, the Radiant Church can only take a step back.

Although Zhao Hai had some understanding of the Hurricane Family, in the end, he was not a person of the Buddha Empire. His understanding of the Hurricane Family was only based on some writings on paper. As to the actual prestige of the Hurricane Family, Zhao Hai has close to no clue.

After travelling for three days in Iron Warhorse River, they finally sailed on a branching body of water known as Blooming Flower River and stopped at a place called the Blooming Flower Lake.

On the east of Blooming Flower Lake, a stone pier can be seen. This pier was Hurricane Family’s personal pier. At the same time, this Blooming Flower Lake was also part of the Hurricane Family’s territory.

After the two ships stopped on the pier. Zhao Hai discovered that there were a lot of people present. The one leading them was an old man wearing an azure Robe. This old man’s robes was neither magnificent nor luxurious. The robe looked just like the robes that low-level Mages used to wear. It didn’t have any special qualities in it.

The hair of the old person was white, he had a wrinkled face that made him look like an old Mage that had zero accomplishments in his life. However, Zhao Hai didn’t dare look down on this person. Although the old man looked weak, Zhao Hai’s intuition was telling him that he was an expert.

After lowering the springboard, Zhao Hai, along with Laura and the others, walked down from their ship. Kristen also disembarked from her own ship. Naturally, Kristen had already sent a message towards the old man, informing him about what happened as well as Zhao Hai’s presence.

Kristen went to the old man and gave him a salute. The old man smiled kindly towards her and said, “Good. It’s nice that you’ve come back safely. I told you to not go, but you insisted to. Right, let’s not neglect the guests.”

Then the old man turned to look at Zhao Hai. Zhao Hai didn’t neglect his manners as he bowed and said, “Buda Clan’s Patriarch, Zhao Hai, has seen the Elder.”

The old man smiled faintly and returned the bow before saying, “Juno Hurricane has met Patriarch Zhao Hai.”

Zhao Hai quickly replied and said, “Elder shouldn’t be too polite. You’re old enough to be my grandfather. No need to give me a bow, I don’t deserve it.”

Old Juno looked at Zhao Hai and smiled faintly, “Patriarch Zhao Hai has rescued my granddaughter. That’s a great service to my Hurricane Family, that’s enough to merit a bow.”

Zhao Hai smiled, “Elder is too polite. I just did it because of the coincidence, so I helped a little. Not really a big deal.”

Juno smiled a little, he didn’t want to dwell too much on this topic. So he said, “Since mister has come to my Hurricane Family, then we would of course show you our hospitality.” Juno changed how he addressed Zhao Hai from Patriarch to mister. It seems like their relationship has gone one step closer.

Zhao Hai also noted the change to how he was addressed. He smiled and said, “I’ll have to trouble the elder.” Then the group went to leave the pier and approached some carriages. The carriages were very ordinary, something even merchants wouldn’t ride on. But from the looks of the Hurricane Family members, it seems like they were already used to it.

Zhao Hai was now very curious about the people of the Hurricane Family. He wasn’t expecting that there would a millennium-old family like this to exist. It made Zhao Hai think about how great it would be if he were to be born into such a family. However, his fate was on the opposite direction.

After the group rode the carriage, it immediately headed towards the depths of the Hurricane Family’s territory. This showed Zhao Hai that the Hurricane Family’s territory was a mountainous region, no flat lands can be seen. The road that they were going through were all mountain paths paved with stones.

Zhao Hai looked at the lush, Bamboo Rice and oil trees in the mountains. Then he turned to Laura and said, “This place is really good. It’s much better than our Black Wasteland.”

Laura smiled and said, “Their lifestyle is really astonishing. I didn’t think that there would be a millennium-old clan that is like this. I used to hear how the Hurricane Family lived, but I really didn’t expect it to be like this.”

After crossing two mountains, their carriage stopped. Zhao Hai didn’t immediately get down from the carriage, he was busy gawking at the scene.

This village wasn’t different than the villages that they had seen in the past two mountains. Stone houses with a stone walled courtyards, of which several fruit trees were grown. Dogs can be seen running around the vegetation and pigs’ squeals can be heard. It’s a typical mountain village that one can see everywhere.

However, this typical mountain village was actually the Patriarch’s residence of one of the most famous Great Families in the continent. This scene made Zhao Hai stare blankly.

At this time, people can be heard walking towards the carriage. This made Zhao Hai recover as he led Laura and the others down. Juno had also reached Zhao Hai’s carriage as he smiled, “Mister Zhao Hai, this is where I live. It’s quite crude, I hope you don’t get offended.”

Zhao Hai quickly replied, “This is actually a very good place. I like it very much. I’d have to trouble the Elder to take care of me.” Juno smiled faintly and led Zhao Hai to enter the courtyard. Kristen was also following them from behind, while the others went back to their own households.

Upon entering the courtyard, Zhao Hai can see another old person there as well as two children running around like crazy.

Kristen entered the courtyard and immediately ran towards the old person as she held her up, “Grandma, I’ve missed you.” The old woman looked at Zhao Hai and then back to Kristen as she said, “Good girl. Right, go invite the guests over inside.”

Zhao Hai looked at this old woman and immediately knew that she was an expert as well, at least 7th rank. Zhao Hai hadn’t seen an 7th rank Mage like this old woman before. Moreover, she was a millennium-old Patriarch’s wife.

At this time, Zhao Hai also entered the room with Juno. The living room was quite big, when he entered, he can see wooden chairs and tables inside, looking like they were already antiques. The items inside gave off a serene and deep aura.

After the group sat down, Kristen got them something to drink. Then Juno looked at Zhao Hai and smiled, “Is Patriarch Zhao Hai not too familiar with a crude place such as this?”

Zhao Hai shook his head and said, “Not at all, I’m quite used to it. A year ago, I lived in a similar condition. It’s even much worse than here. Hahaha. Even the place that I’m living in right now is not much better than this.”

Juno smiled and said, “Our Hurricane Family had been living like this for as long as I can remember, so we’re already quite used to it. Right, I heard that Patriarch Zhao Hai’s purpose this time was to contact the dwarves, am I correct?”

Zhao Hai nodded and said, “I did come to do some trades with the Dwarves. But I’m quite unfamiliar with the place as well as the people here. I’ll have to ask the Elder for help.”

Juno smiled and said, “Patriarch doesn’t need to be polite. You’ve rescued Kristen, such great kindness needed to be repaid. If I can help you even for a little bit, then I would be very happy.”

Zhao Hai smiled and said, “Elder is really too polite. I feel quite uncomfortable receiving such remarks from a respectable person like you.”

Juno just smiled and said, “Alright, no need to talk about this. I’ll have to ask Patriarch Zhao Hai to stay here for a few days since I’ll need to arrange this matter. After I take care of it, I will personally accompany you to Dwarf Mountain. I believe that those old Dwarves would still give me some face.”

Zhao Hai stared blankly before he immediately said, “I’ve dared to cause the Patriarch too much trouble, I’ll have to deeply apologize.”

The Old man waved his hand and said, “It isn’t a big deal. I happen to have several good friends among the Dwarves. Patriarch Zhao Hai doesn’t need to be too polite. Right, I’ll have to ask Patriarch Zhao Hai to rest in his room first. In a while, I’ll be inviting you over for dinner.” Zhao Hai complied, and then he led Laura and the others out.

After walking out of the house, they saw that Kristen was already there waiting for them. However, Kristen was very different compared to the first time that they’ve met. In the past, Kristen was wearing a long skirt, with her hair fairly unkempt. But the present Kristen was now wearing ordinary clothes, she also had her hair into a braid, she looked just like an adorable neighbor.

Kristen gave a small bow and said to Zhao Hai, “Patriarch Zhao Hai, please come with me.” Then she led Zhao Hai towards a nearby building.

After arriving at the building, Kristen turned her head to Zhao Hai and said, “Patriarch, this is the place that Grandfather has arranged for you. It looks quite simple, we hope that Patriarch doesn’t get too offended.”

Zhao Hai entered the room. It wasn’t that big, the inside was divided into two; the living room and the bedroom. If one carefully looked at it, one could see that the room was spotlessly clean.

Zhao Hai turned his head to Kristen and then said, “Sister Kristen is too polite. This place is very good, it’s very much to my liking. Thank you very much.”

Kristen smiled and said, “Patriarch is too polite. Then I’ll leave patriarch here so that you can take a rest. If Patriarch needs anything, don’t hesitate to tell me.”

Zhao Hai nodded, then Kristen turned around and left. Meg and the others also came inside as they evaluated the house.

Laura smiled and turned to Zhao Hai, “Brother Hai, I didn’t think that the Hurricane Family would be living this humbly. It’s really too strange.”

Zhao Hai smiled and said, “I also didn’t think that the famous Hurricane Family would have this kind of lifestyle, it’s completely out of my expectations. With how strong they are, they still chose to live such lives, they have my utmost admiration.”

Laura smiled and said, “They really do make people admire them. But I feel like our situation is quite similar to the Hurricane Family. We have the strength to rule a nation, but we chose to live our current lives. Maybe we are pursuing the same life as them.”